[Music]
thank you
dream shifter day 10 can you believe it
it's incredible you guys survived day
10. this is unbelievable think about it
10 days
of the brain shot therapy the power it
has on the brain the power it has to
heal Miracles are happening people's
lives are changing it is incredible when
you think about it we're day 10.
information from above no one has ever
seen heard or tapped into and we're
using it and lives are changing and
people are healing and that's what it's
about just think about the power in that
empowerment Enlightenment all of it
you're using your free will
to heal yourself ready for this you're
free will where does it come from
it comes from your brain that's where
your free will comes from it comes from
your Noggin right here you're using your
free will
you're becoming an expert
you're taking the knowledge from above
and you're using your brain to heal your
brain you're using your free will to
heal your brain you're using your actual
brain to heal your brain think about how
incredible that is I just want to say go
to Medical medium.com if you're getting
kicked off
any of the platforms any of the apps go
to medicalmedium.com watch me live there
at Medical medium.com by the way you
guys have you checked out Medical
medium.com
you see how we've made it all incredible
with the recipes everything else you see
how it's completely rigged and such an
awesome easy to use way to help people
heal to provide information
medicalmedium.com is a free website what
I mean by free is you're not going to
get pop-ups for subscription fees pay
walls you're not going to have any of
that going on you know there's nobody
being taken advantage of at
medicalmedium.com what you do is you go
there you learn you heal you can watch
all of the the brain shot therapies of
the past on there we can do it all there
it's incredible when they have we're
enhancing that website it's amazing
there's nothing going on on there in the
sense where all that paywall stuff and
subscription fees you guys were day 10
dreams shifter
now this is one of my favorite brain
shot Therapies
one of my favorite it is that incredible
that powerful that mind-blowing
it's it's the one that
and I'll just go into it now a little
bit it's the one that if you want to
grow from your dreams learn from your
dreams alter your dreams
make your life when you're not dreaming
or sleeping better during the daytime
because of it this is an incredible tool
and those are just a couple of reasons
why to use it let's see what it says in
here
let's find out dream shifter you guys
now if you just got on here and you're
new to all of this and you don't know
like what's going on like what is
happening we just did nine days
of the 10-day brand shot therapy
challenge cleanse challenge that's free
now you can go to medicalmedium.com
and you can still download your free pdf
of your grocery shopping list and you
can watch the other videos of the last
nine days and you can do the challenge
over if you want how incredible without
being charged or any fees or taking it
and creating a course out of it and not
letting anybody go near it unless they
actually paid something like a thousand
dollars or something crazy look all of
that and that's what's incredible about
the medical meme information and what
we're doing here
but here is the most incredible piece
the incredible part is that the brain
shot therapy is a miracle
now medical medium info people always
say is a miracle because they've healed
from debilitating diseases conditions
and symptoms
All Through The Years through the eight
medical the other six medical medium
books right
but the brain shot therapies are an
additional tool
from above that's literally creating
Miracles it's unbelievable what's
happening I know you guys are feeling it
MV Doom says it really is a miracle in
Envy Doom if you say that then it really
is true because you don't mess around
because I've watched your comments
before and I've read your comments over
there on YouTube and stuff like that
I've seen and I know that if you say
that then it's it's right on because I
know I know that you totally don't mess
around I've seen that
and the thing is is that like
when I think about someone's
life-changing fast like that
it's just this is mind-blowing it really
is we're in the dream shifters the
dreams shifter
shot
today it's day 10. I saw Dr Fond go up
his comment go up went up
yep incredible so I'm glad we're all
here you guys
all right so let's talk about the dream
shifter for a little bit so let's go
into that for a little bit okay are you
guys ready
this shot can be taken at any time of
day or evening you guys I'm on the brain
saver books I just want to remind you if
you just got here and you're wondering
what's going on brain saver books
rain saber books here we go we're in
brain shot therapy right now we're on
day 10 okay
this shot can be taken at any time of
day or evening now remember that you can
take the shot during the day that's how
powerful it is
and it's still gonna help you when you
go to bed tonight
I'm taking this shot today with you and
I'm doing three of them today one now
one a little later one a little later
this shot can be taken at any time of
the day or evening if you wish to take
it before a nap or before bed
you're welcome to make the shot earlier
in the day and save it in the
refrigerator until you're ready
examples of when to use it include
you want to use your dreams as a gateway
to understand your soul and your Soul's
past
here's the thing with SOC everything SOC
has done and given to me in information
throughout the years has literally been
true
Advanced information the science of
research is stealing and poaching from
the medical medium books that are
published and believe me my Publishers
knows this and sees it
they see the the plagiarizing out there
and the stealing and the thefting right
of the mm books but what's incredible is
Spirit of compassion
has always been right with the
information and people have gotten their
lives back out of wheelchairs they've
gotten rid of the brain fog they've
gotten rid of terrible gut problems
they've gotten rid of so many things
that it's always true so when I read the
miracle brain shot therapy right when I
read about them in here
um the first thing that hits me is like
oh my God you can learn from your Soul's
past
through the dream shifter
think about that for a second
you want to use your dreams as a gateway
to understand your soul and your Soul's
past is that not the most mind-blowing
thing you've ever heard or is it just me
and for some reason I think that way and
I'm like oh that's the most mind-blowing
thing I've ever heard like
and it's just me or do you guys think
that's mind-blowing
corny M.A says the book blows my mind
Hey you made this live just now
incredible usually you're working right
you want to use your dreams as a gateway
to understand your soul and your Soul's
Passover let me tell you right there how
powerful that is because your Soul's
past is before this lifetime so think
about that for a second
the dream shifter helps us to understand
if we want that direction
what information from the Soul's past
is about
that means your soul before this
Lifetime right here
before your soul
ended up
magically appearing in the womb
think about this
okay how about this one now okay you're
having difficulty dreaming and wanted
dreams so many people I know that they
have a difficult time dreaming they want
to dream but they can't
Erica Malik says the dream shifter gave
me such vivid dreams I've always been
really connected to my dreams this shot
amplifies that on a whole other level
that's just incredible
here's one right here too okay Lana says
these shots have already changed my
brain and I can't wait to see where this
journey takes me Lana
these shots absolutely are miraculous
and they have the ability to turn lives
around in such a way but don't stop the
other medical medium tools even though
you can do this tool without doing the
other tools you still you still have to
learn the books and the information
there's so many important tools for
different conditions and symptoms all of
it with these brain shots it's a whole
nother level oh my God especially if
you're doing other medical medium tools
and you bring these in Tamara says I try
dream shifter uh oh really incredible I
slept good loud thought finally faded
and remember my dream with total with
real Clarity or real dream really
clarity I had repeated dream
from the other night but was introduced
with gentleness and not aggression
aggressive peppermint makes drink really
nice too that's incredible I love that
I've been using the dreams shifter
periodically
I already have some really really crazy
dreams and the spirit of compassion
talks to me in my sleep on top of it and
since I was a child I had the ability to
enter someone else's dream
and then do things like that and so the
dream shifter is actually even giving me
more of an ampage with my dream state
I haven't been sleeping that many hours
lately because I'm keeping up with a
billion times work of all this stuff
which I have to tell you this friend of
mine just said why don't you why don't
you be truthful to everybody I'm like
what are you talking about I'm always
truthful every everybody
and a friend of mine was like tell them
about what you do before you go right on
live
and I'm like what what do you mean what
do I do I'm doing everything it's like
tell them tell them about your little
cheat I'm like that's unfair what do you
mean my little cheat it's not a cheat I
said tell them what you take right when
you go on and this is so funny right
before I go live
I take the celery Force
and I take the Gaba
that's what I do right before I go live
every time before I go live these are
the two things I take and that's the
Bemidji I mean I won't take another Gaba
from anywhere else because I don't trust
it and I won't take obviously there is
no such thing as this anywhere else it's
the beverages stuff to sell the reports
I don't know if you guys ever tried it
but see that's the Bemidji stuff you
know V as in Victor i m e r g y.com but
that's what I take right before I go
live after I've already been up since
five in the morning I've already had you
guys like four meetings
and I've been working and then I got to
get ready in here and everything so but
you guys know I've endorsed these guys
because of the four reasons the four
unbelievable reasons son endorse these
guys
um but anyway
and friend my friend wanted me to tell
you he's like why don't you tell them
what you do right before you go live
anyway so okay let's go back to this
dream shifter
your dreams are troubling very stressful
or even frightening
so your dreams are troubling
stressful or frightening that's when you
have to say hey you know what I'm gonna
get into the dream shifter
I'm gonna work on the dream shifter
let's do it let's get it in me
here's one right here you ready you want
to decode the meaning of your dreams and
gain more insight into your dreams
that's a reason all on its own to do the
dream shifter
you want to decode the meaning of your
dreams how incredible is that gain more
insight
into your dreams that alone is really
powerful okay here's another one too
if your dreams are waking you up did you
ever have dreams that wait woke you up
like the dream is waking you up and you
need your sleep but the dream wakes you
up that's another reason why to do this
so Jackie says I take celery for us when
I'm really sleepy and I need to be awake
it's great incredible I'm glad you I'm
glad you use it it's it's I rely on it I
actually rely on it
Marge just says what Gaba and cellular
Force are you what are you doing for you
well it's the Imaging
so
that's the Gaba right there it's V as in
Victor I Amazon Mary e r g y.com
I endorsed them because of the four
reasons so the four reasons are
mind-blowing I don't have time to talk
about it though but there's four
incredible reasons that nobody does
nobody has
Lucas says I know celery force is
amazing it totally is it's actually
probably
when people don't realize like for me in
my personal life some of the things that
I do and and like celery Force I rely on
it's how I survive a day that's how I
feel it's the craziest thing because I
wake up at four or five in the morning I
go all the way till midnight I try to
get three or four hours of sleep but if
it's really heavy duty work time
schedule I'll get two hours of sleep one
hour sometimes when I did the book it
was like barely any Pamela says on
YouTube I've been buying the demorgy and
tossing the other things I'm I'm
streaming and cleansing
my some reason the comments are just all
like
[Music]
streaming and cleansing my kitchen okay
cool
streamlining and cleansing my kitchen
haha sorry sorry I butchered the comment
the crazy stuff with the tech was
happening at the same time pernella says
celery Force really helps my brain to
work better
I rely on it I actually use it as a
crutch I mean I don't have to use it but
I use it as a crutch to push harder
because
um I I can't stop working so what I do
is I wanna see because I burn the candle
four ends so then I do the cheat and I
use the celery Force so I could burn the
candle at five ends because because
that's what I want to do
Jackie says celery Force helps if you
don't get a lot of sleep that's my life
story that's my life story so anyway
that's what it is for you guys know
about that anyway you know about that
it's feas and Victor i m e r g y.com you
guys know about it I do the Gabba right
before I go live by the way ask your
doctor what's right for you I'm just
saying that that's what I do but man do
I do I lean up and the thing is it's the
four things
that no other company I don't care who
what how does you guys have talked about
in the past it's it's mind-blowing this
company that's why I endorsed them all
right dream shifter
just a little window into like what I'm
doing for myself so you guys actually
know what's happening it's a friend of
mine was like why don't you tell them
right before you go on you take it
literally a minute before you go on
every time okay
you're fearful of going to sleep how
many people do you know that were afraid
to go to sleep like you got fear and
anxiety creeps up so like fear and
anxiety creeps up before going to sleep
right Pinellas the cellular Force brings
Clarity to foggy brain
that that's my experience as far as like
anybody I've told it told about doctors
I tell about my experiences I hear the
same thing from different doctors my
patient
you know feels better my face patient
feels better with this but it's it's
incredible
so yeah so you guys anyway
fearfulness of falling asleep what do
you think about that
did you ever experience that in your
life did oh you get that so Robinson
says yes I get so you do get that like a
fearfulness in falling asleep so many
people have this fear that comes over
them right before they fall asleep or as
they fall asleep and that's really
difficult for a lot of people Terry
Appleman says love the energy Southern
Force
I mean I love it I can't live without it
you know and but yeah it's it's happens
to so many people all right
you're trying to reach others through
your dreams
do you ever want to reach anybody
through your dreams
it's an incredible experience
since I was younger that I had that
ability to do that
and but the dream shifter can help other
people and I'm gonna go into like what
it unlocks like how does the dream
shifter even work in here in the Noggin
and so that would be so cool you're
trying to reach others through your
dreams how cool is that
here's one right here
you're trying to enter other people's
dreams you got that one right we talked
about that you're not sleeping enough
this shot can help you heal through your
dream process in the short amount of
sleep you're getting so if you're not
sleeping that much dream shifter's
critical because it can help you heal
and do what you need to do in that short
amount of sleep you get which is the
reason I've been using the dream shifter
for myself personally because I don't
get a lot of sleep because I'm working
too many hours I have so many demands
and responsibilities it's insane
and and because of that you know I get
only this amount of sleep I mean to do
these two massive Bibles
to do these two massive Bibles right
here what it took this would take a
health author like seven years in their
life just to get something like this
done and of course it wouldn't be from
information from above it would just be
whatever gathered information from
whatever but the point is is I've lost a
lot of sleep because of it it's
incredible
Lucy Cohn oh my God incredible you're
here been doing this shot almost every
night for the challenge and it's helped
me fall asleep without needing to be on
my phone something I've struggled with
for decades that's incredible let's see
amazing
my God that's that's incredible
so
here's another one Monica the dream
shifter shot is amazing when done before
bed
better sleep and able to remember my
dreams more vividly love this brain shot
incredible
I mean when I think about what was given
to us right like I'm the messenger and I
want to get this information out when I
think about what was given to me because
I can use these too and that was on
Instagram those comments you guys I can
use this too
like and it's given to all of us when I
think about like how powerful is that
all of it
it just
Karen says Karen Churchill says just SOC
hear us when we thank him in our prayers
yes for sure because you have to know
this that when I'm here
right now when you think about it and
I'm listening to SOC SOC knows you know
knows about you guys like what's
happening and stuff and what you're
doing and all that here's another one
Hill of Sophia says all the brain shots
are mind-blowing calming me every time I
take one incredible
just really is special I mean when I
think about it the brain shot Therapies
one more one more comment Anthony I felt
like a new human since I am using the
brain shots since one week Karina
that is worth everything it just is
your life is changed that's on Instagram
because your life has changed
when you think about that I mean the
power in your healing process like how
it's pushing your healing process along
like that giving you the instant relief
let's go into this a little bit now
the medical medium brain shot therapy I
can't wait to make this one by the way
you guys see I have the
some frozen mango here I have some
frozen cherries here I have some mint I
have some zucchini I have some ginger
no one would know it's this exact
combination in the amounts it is
roughly in the amounts it is
nobody would know on this planet there's
no researcher there's no food Science
Guy there's no lab technician there's
nobody A lab technician could get a
grant for 250 million dollars and still
not know that there's something in a
cherry that actually
systematically works phytochemical
compound wise with mint at the same time
systematically working with zucchini
zucchini of all things systematically
working with ginger and systematically
working with mango that would that would
never be found out anywhere anyhow
it's not possible it comes from above
you don't have to have faith and you
don't have to believe in me and you
don't have to believe in this and you
don't have to believe in the book but
when you do the brain shot therapies
your life will change you can hate me
just like me not way not like the way I
talk or look you cannot believe you can
think I'm talking to a ghost you can
think whatever you want but when you do
the brain shot Therapies
your life is going to change
because it's gonna do profound things
with your health because of what it is
you don't even have to believe that's
the whole point you can walk on the
street with a shot of this in your hand
that was just made and walk up to a
stranger who doesn't believe in anything
and say start sipping this and that
stranger can start sipping it
and they're going to have a profound
effect that day that hour that minute or
later on and that's how incredible the
brain shot therapies are
it's really amazing medical me and brain
shot therapy offers instant relief it
offers
your brain and body have a quick
response to medicinals delivered in
liquid form
but it goes beyond that it's the
combination and what it is that allows
for quick absorption through that liquid
form to go directly into the blood
vessels and find their way to the brain
really fast so with the brain shot
therapy does
is it gets to your brain
really fast now the dream shifter which
we're going to talk about in a little
bit you guys we're gonna get to the
dream shifter the dream shifter gets to
the brain the emotional centers of the
brain
an incredible place to heal so we can
sleep and heal through our dreams
the relation okay you guys these brain
shots are composed of specific
combinations of ingredients that working
together systematically for specific
reasons that only a source above could
ever know no science to research no lab
technician no food science guy no keto
guy no
workout trainer no
uh functional medicine doctor no
naturopath no acupuncturists no massage
therapists not disrespecting anybody
everybody's out there trying their best
and working hard
with with great intentions and
everything but the point is is no one
can figure out
that these brain shots are composed of
specific combinations of ingredients
working together systematically for
specific reasons that only a source
above could know no one would know that
the relationships among these
ingredients are intricate and unknown to
anyone the relationship among these
ingredients are unknown to anyone you
guys
hence why a miracle can happen
that's why a miracle can happen that's
why people's lives are changed and
miracles are happening with this you
don't have to believe me you could come
on here and be like who is this medical
medium guy I always hear about
and then
literally though if you're struggling if
you got a problem if you got a health
issue and you Embark into this your life
can change and well the relationships
among these ingredients are unknown to
anyone until now the knowledge from
above has remained untapped it has been
remained it has been remained untapped
if that makes any sense
so
the whole point you guys is it hasn't
been tapped
so look let's go into it a little bit
let's talk about dreams
a couple different areas to go with this
so here's an incredible section right
here
if you guys just came on this is the
10th day
incredible
amen actually it's the 10th day of a 10
day brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
and
my life has changed from these 10 that
were chosen
from above now you could choose any 10
you'd like out of the 30 brain shot
therapies and your life will change
but it's an incredible moment to be here
right now on our 10th day
and if you guys just one last mention
before I go into the information inside
the brand saver books
medicalmedium.com if you're having
problems watching me on social media go
to medicalmedium.com if you missed a
challenge you can watch the replays at
medicalbeam.com
check out the menu
hit the brain shot therapy section on
the menu and you can replay the videos
so you can get the replays
so I'm in the I'm in the book right now
I'm on page 93 I want to read a little
bit to you guys
everyday toxins and poisons
inside the brain or a large part of the
brain limitations we experience
we have brain limitations because our
brain
gets filled with all the poisons and the
junk and all the garbage
Brenda said so true what you're saying
aw we've enjoyed watching how they
affect my husband
amazing because your husband probably
doesn't believe right and but but yet
you give it to your husband and it's
like there's a profound effect
Sarah Anthony these are literally the
best books of all time
dreamed I had five copies of each that's
incredible that's actually the best
dream
thank you for recognizing they're the
best best books of all time
they're the greatest books in history
and health
Evan says is there a dosage or ounces of
the shots that can be given to kids
check out the books and look into it and
you can look into it I honestly
and Christian says the brain shots are
going to bring them bring the
non-believers to mm info because the
results yes that's the whole point
we want everybody to heal even somebody
that doesn't believe in it you still
want them to heal you still want them to
find the information and get better
that's what we want
everyday toxins and poisons inside the
brain are a large part of the brain
limitations we have
including emotional limitations
including emotional emotional
limitations
because of poisons and toxins clouding
up our brain
you guys see where I'm going the dream
shifter I think some of you guys can
guess the dream shifter
can reroute reset and rewire the brain
because the brain's filled with so many
different toxins and poisons that it
clouds up everything we're on page 93 of
brain saver
there
if an area of the brain is clouded up
with an abundant level of poisons and
toxins ranging from toxic heavy metals
to solvents to Plastics you guys are
like I don't got any of that in my head
some of you oh no yeah you do
and other petroleum petrochemicals to
Pharmaceuticals a lot of people got
Pharmaceuticals in their brain they just
do they got a lot of pharmaceuticals in
their brain
to air fresheners
to fragrances the scented candles and
Beyond
and that's just theming a few of the
toxins and poisons that area of the
brain
okay
that area of the brain that's clouded
with these poisons and toxins the brain
betrayers I call them can almost go into
a sleep mode
but you're not sleeping this doesn't
mean we'll be sleeping
it means an area of our brain is not
functioning optimally so that's the
whole thing so we walk around
where
an area of our brain is not functioning
great
so a area may not be functioning right
another area may not be functioning
right different areas in the brain
because we have so much stuff in there
this is why the dream shifter is
actually really important
this is also why
the rest of the medical beam information
is also really important too to get rid
of a lot of these poisons and toxins
including Metals out of our brain
so this doesn't mean we'll be sleeping
it means an area of our brain is not
functioning great so we'll rely more on
other parts of our brain that are less
clouded and clogged up with toxins it
also means we'll be limited in brain
function here's how it works
foreign
if we have poisons and toxins in an area
in our brain
our brain has to rely on another area to
function
certain areas in our brain
go into sleep mode
because there's too many poisons and
toxins in certain areas
so that little bit of tissue in the
brain
where all those neurons are in glial
cells
dumb down
and go into kind of like a non-active
mode
then our brain
has to rely on the areas that actually
work
and so a switch happens inside our brain
for survival
we have to rely on the good parts of our
brain meaning the parts that are not all
clouded up and filled with garbage and
junk and poisons
in order to survive function and fight
our way through every day it's why
people are on caffeine
parts of their brain aren't quite
working so great
so they have to do caffeine
to try to push their way through it they
have to drug their brain
when emotional centers of the brain
become filled up and clouded with toxins
and poisons we become more reliant on
other parts of our brain as a result we
can become limited in our emotional
understandings of others so what happens
is
the more we get filled up with junk and
garbage and toxins and poisons inside
our brain tissue
the more we lose that understanding
of like what's going on around us so
much
we don't pick up unsubtleties
we end up going into some depression
some anxiety some depersonalization
we have a hard time reading things
not words but just reading the
environment
reading others around us
we can become Limited in getting in
touch with our own emotional state we
can actually have limitations on our own
emotional state understanding our own
emotional state like why am I doing that
how come I'm like this how come I'm
getting this diagnosis
how come I feel like I have brain fog
and brain problems how come I don't
understand what that person's saying how
come I'm angry all the time how come I'm
so moody and Confused
Jenny Jenn says it's scary to think
about how these chemicals and toxins
have changed their personalities and
made us less than what we were meant to
be
it really is
we can become Limited in feeling and
expressing emotions too too many toxins
and poisons in our brain makes it so we
have a hard time expressing ourselves
that makes it hard have you ever had
that happen in your life where it's a
hard time to express yourself and then
the other person you're expressing
yourself to
misunderstands you
so you're misunderstood
and that's a whole nother thing that
could happen
we can become Limited in feeling
expressing our emotions Limited in
harnessing emotions too like harnessing
the emotion like not reacting when we
get taken over by the emotion you know
when you're just like what did that
person do what did that person say to me
I've been hurt and it's hard to wrap our
heads around it and kind of control that
right but yours says oh my God not even
any doctor can explain the way you are
doing aw
thank you so much for these books
I think SOC
I mean yeah I had to be the implement
soc's tool and Implement in messenger
Brenda says is this the reason for
narcissism
well yeah our brain can get completely
filled up with metals and everything
else absolutely and we can do that but
you know we also have a soul in there
too keep that in mind we have a soul
and we have a Consciousness and
subconsciousness and physical brain we
have all four of those things and
anything go wrong I talk about that in
the books and we also have a free will
and a free will can also be involved
there too but yes clouded up with all
the poisons junk and garbage definitely
can send us into a lane that could even
be narcissistic
toxins and poisons clogging the
emotional centers of our brain
can also mean
that we become extremely emotional
without understanding why why am I so
emotional
why
am I so darn emotional
I get triggered so easy
I got a triggers list up to here
and every time someone triggers that or
something triggers that I'm set off
I'm crying I'm upset I'm sad I'm
depressed anxiety gets up
I'm hurt
but I don't know why
I just don't know why
dreams can become very intense it's
another comment here Carrie Miller mm
these shots have changed my life yay
I can't tell you I want to jump up and
scream actually because knowing your
life was changed is everything that's
the whole point I'm 37 years old and I
have chronic fatigue syndrome since I
was 16. the energy shot shifter is
bringing back energy and vitality it's
feeling like you got stability
whoa
when I think about that and I think
about how incredible that is
dreams can become very intense
extremely emotionally challenging where
constant dream After Dream After Dream
evokes emotions because the body is
trying to heal I want to talk about that
I'm reading on brain saver 40 off
amazon.com us please I beg of you to get
a book so your life can change it's two
books you see the protocols up here too
you guys can see it over there in our G2
get them free at the library if you need
to if you don't have the it's a 40 off
amazon.com us if you don't have the 26
dollars
go to the library and get it for free
I don't care
it doesn't matter to me if everybody
went to the library and got it for free
I still don't care
if I have to live under a bridge
in a cardboard box because everybody
goes to the library I still don't care
I'll actually be happy in my little
cardboard box okay
because I know that everybody is healing
and their lives are being saved these
books hands down are so mind-blowing and
life-changing
dreams the only problem about the
cardboard box thing I wouldn't be able
to reach all you guys if I know ways to
get you guys more information and all
this free info and everything else so
that would not be a good idea but still
go to the library get it for free no
matter what Amazon has a sale on these
two books insane too
so here's the thing with dreams why do
we have emotionally challenging dreams
do you guys have I want to ask you guys
a question can I ask you guys a question
do you have bad dreams
or an uncomfortable dream you guys got
any answers for that bad dreams or
uncomfortable dreams
do you ever get nightmares
do you have difficult dreams marja says
yes
they have dreams that Jenny Jenn says oh
my God this just scared me torturous
streams that's terrible my God and Lisa
says a lot
Tyler says not often
after Julie says absolutely yes yes me
too 787 Hey on YouTube good to see you
YouTube I don't see your comments
anymore YouTube 787 used to leave
comments on YouTube
I read all the comments you guys
so you guys are getting bad dreams so
you have intense dreams right where it's
stressful
you ever have dreams where you're
running from somebody
how about that
do you have dreams where you're running
from somebody someone's chasing you
you dream every night
yes it comes back over and over again
always I see that power of compassion
always dreams of people chasing you
dreams where you're like running from
somebody that you feel like they're
gonna hurt you
dreams that they're just bad dreams or
nightmares
okay your daughter does
so
what I'm reading right here
these books are so incredible
I'm
you can go anywhere in these books and
find pieces of information that are just
mind-blowing and every page every
sentence
dreams can become very intense extremely
emotionally challenging where constant
dream After Dream After Dream evokes
emotions because get ready for this
because your body is trying to heal the
emotional centers of the brain
foreign
the reason why you're running from
somebody in your dream the reason why
you're tortured in your dream and your
torture stream the reason why you have a
bad dream the reason why you have a
struggle in your dream the reason why
you have an uncomfortable dream the
reason why you have a sad dream the
reason why you have a dream that's
confusing or perplexing the reason why
you have these dreams
is because
we're healing
that's why
your
body your soul your brain your
Consciousness and subconsciousness is
trying to heal from something in the
past
or something in the present
because the body is trying to heal the
emotional centers of the brain where
you've been hurt somewhere along the way
may not even remember or even know
someone I just saw someone ask about
seizures
oh my God
the seizures chapter
is unbelievable in the brain saver books
they can't get the book at amazon.com us
for 40 off the books go to the library
for free if you need to there's a
protocol section in here bring it to
your doctor see if it's right for you
bring the protocol sections to the
doctor
these are medical textbooks
that also
has spiritual information too
we do a lot of emotional healing through
our dreams you guys we actually do
emotional healing through the dreams
because the brain and the Free Will and
your soul and your Consciousness and
subconsciousness you guys are trying to
heal the damage done trying to heal the
imprint within the cells trying to heal
the brain tissue itself from any kind of
thing that happened in your life that
was emotionally difficult
healing is happening
hence
the dream shifter
we need help with that healing
if you have any kind of emotionally
struggling or any kind of emotional
struggle or something to happen in your
life a loss or something difficult or a
hardship or anything in your life
betrayal broken trust or just anything
and for some reason the emotional
centers of the brain is still injured in
there
and it hasn't healed and you're having
difficult dreams struggles in your
dreams problems with your dreams
torturous dreams whatever it is going on
it's you your body your Consciousness
your subconscious your soul trying to
heal but we need extra help so what SOC
did what Spirit of compassion did from
above
Spirit of compassion just told me just
now somebody just glazed their eyes over
when they heard that someone who's here
doesn't believe I'm talking to anyone
and just thinks I'm a really smart guy
and I was able to somehow comprise these
books with information
that's okay I still want you to be here
you don't have to believe I'm just a
messenger you can believe I'm a genius
trust me I'm not a genius
and even a genius wouldn't have this
wouldn't know what even a genius
couldn't breathe this this this line of
books here
that the prophecies in these books don't
even it's not even possible a genius
couldn't do it but thank you for
thinking I'm a smart guy I'm honored but
yes it came from above all right let's
move on past that when I get information
from SOC while we're doing this
sometimes I can't help but to put my two
cents in
Okay so
what's happening is is we need that
extra help so that's why I got the
information from it but was given to me
because so many people struggle with
their dreams from emotional wounds and
need the extra push they need the extra
help in rewiring and resetting
how incredible is that
it's not my first walk in the park
I've been discriminated against because
of hearing a voice
I've been whatever I'm not treated
kindly because of it I got a kick me
sign on my back it's not my first walk
in the park so not my first rodeo with
it so it's okay if you don't believe any
of it but I want you to stay here
because I want you oh half time because
I want you to heal
half time break it up you guys you want
to do a robot maybe you got a better
dance than the robot I like the robot
protein robot protein robot remember
protein robot protein robot protein
protein protein this isn't about protein
[Music]
thank you
foreign
I don't know what I'm saying all right
you guys incredible
those are halftime
all right let's let's move through this
people who have more toxins in their
emotional centers of the brain tend to
dream about drowning okay I want to ask
you this question
did you ever have a dream where you were
underwater or drowning
let's see what it says in brain saver
okay
they almost just rock the bot
see Henderson my mind is blown after
reading most of brain saver you read
most of it
how did you get through it so many never
before heard insights I try to tell
everyone to read them
the heavy metal detox movie is critical
for anything mental health or
neurological Henderson spot on I'm
honored here thank you for for reading
through almost all the way through the
book
I just have one request from you
Henderson
you're gonna have to read the book all
over again when you're done because
you're gonna there's things that you
won't believe you read but you don't
know because that's how it has I have to
do that I have to read it over and over
and over again just because I got the
information from him up because I'm like
wait a minute what where how it's
incredible there's that much information
in there Brad
the things I'm experiencing on these
shots are so profound
the clarity is unreal especially with
the mold exposure the mold exposure shot
the mold exposure and nerve shifter
shots so grateful SOC and aw ungrateful
you're actually brave enough to do the
mold exposure shot every time I do the
mold exposure shot
I got this other friend that has a moldy
house right
and you can smell it whenever time
you're in there you smell mildew
so whenever I'm in there I spell mildew
and his friend came over to visit me
and
I was just like bold exposure shot
I was just doing them all day and then
you know it was really torturous because
it's not a great tasting shop but it's
powerful whoa all right
let's talk about this I want to ask you
guys this did you ever have a dream
where you were underwater
drowning
or swimming and you were
in trouble
or you were a boat was sinking and you
were on the boat
people who have more toxins in the
emotional centers of the brain tend to
dream about drowning being in water
playing in water oh my God you ever
dreamed playing in the water and you're
not drowning I just want to ask you guys
do you ever ever have a dream of being
trapped in water or playing in water
where you're having fun and you're not
trapped or you're drowning or you have a
dream of just being in water how many of
you guys have that you got a shark one
that's water I saw water many times when
I had dreams but not underwater but you
saw water that's another one too
also lots of Ocean Dreams okay
yeah I see it so a lot of you guys have
that
yeah so I see you guys lots of your
comments coming up talking about that
okay
that means you have a lot of toxins
closer and in the emotional centers of
the brain that's where the toxins are
a lot of the toxins if you have the
water dreams
just letting you guys know
is this epic information because my mind
keeps on getting blown over and over
again
foreign
have you guys tried this brain shot what
did you feel what results have you
experienced please share a story a post
a real
if you can tag at Medical medium hashtag
medical medium
that would be incredible so I could
repost Katie says one time I drowned in
a dream
okay ready
okay
I want to just read this part because
this is just blowing my mind so I have
to repeat the first line are you guys
okay with that I can't help it
I mean it is scripture from above it's
worth repeating
people who have more toxins in the
emotional centers of the brain tend to
dream about drowning being in water
playing in water or being trapped in
water whether ocean
weather Ocean
Pool lake or river
because their emotional state is in a
way underwater with toxins Who would
know that anywhere no scientists nothing
it's that's from above it blows my mind
foreign
the one cool thing about suffering
through the the taking the every word
for word from above and doing these
books and the amount of hours and the
sacrifices like I made I made
unbelievable sacrifices that someday I
may talk about it
um but unbelievable unbelievable
sacrifices I get emotional choked up
about it
to do this and but at least I get my
mind blown all the time by the
information I mean that's cool and of
course the most important part I see you
guys healing through the medical medium
books all eight of them that right there
is is that's worth pain and suffering uh
for me in my life okay you ready
they can also have dreams of running
from people like we talked about not
being able to get away when someone's
trying to kill or harm them
while these dreams can have other
meanings many times they occur because
toxins are in emotional centers of the
brain we have poisons in the area of the
brain where emotions are harbored inside
the neurons and so that's why this
happens
May that hopefully that happens someday
may I saw your comment
so
basically what I'm trying to say I will
put this in the nutshell I will put this
in a half egg shell no let's not get it
in an eggshell
all right we'll put this
straight
the dream shifter
is there
quickly
shoot a bolt of Medicine
into the emotional center of the brain
to help
relocate toxins appropriately
because what it does is it goes right to
the emotional center of the brain
fast
and starts to move toxins out of the way
along with rewiring and resetting
that area of the brain
if you are having trouble with uh
announcement announcement if you're
having trouble viewing this live on
social media go to medicalmedium.com
please Medical medium.com
check out brain shot therapy in the menu
hit it and watch the replays we can do
that too put some live at
medicalmedium.com as of right now which
is incredible
it's a great escape from the chains of
social media problems
keep an eye on medical media medium calm
please you guys I want you guys to go
there tell people about
medicalmedium.com the reason why is
because I'm doing all this stuff in the
website to make it even more easy to use
friendly information free everything you
name it like we've always done I'm
updating and adding free resources so
you guys can have that information
santara's healing I read your I read
your review again
on Amazon and blown away and haven't
forgotten that you burned out your
highlighter in the Box
if you guys want to leave reviews at
amazon.com that would be incredible or
wherever you got the books that would be
amazing so other people can find their
way because that is very helpful so
other people can find their way
but santar seriously that review to know
what you went through in your life the
struggles how hard you had it the
powerful words that you put in there and
the empowerment that was in there too
like all of it it was it was I know you
worked hard on just expressing yourself
getting all that in there and I actually
don't take it for granted
I don't that was uh an amazing review
from the heart
um God bless you so
you guys any and look anybody if you
leave a review because you like the book
you could just say great book
that's all
you'll be like
you know
it's the greatest book
Okay so
you guys let's make
the dream shifter
all right
let's go day 10 we're in dream shifter
is what we're making very excited about
this
getting the mm-1500 over here
if you're interested in a juicer I call
this a medicine maker
cold pressed masticating juicer it
doesn't burn the juice like the other
juicers do
and I will say one more thing about it
it saves you money because it squeezes
everything out that we need squeezed out
it's powerful it's an incredible juicer
let's get this going and it's 20 off
right now
and you guys know I work with these guys
endorse them Marina you said the shots
move the toxins but they don't remove
them
it's not a detox shot it's a rewire
and reset shot but it allows the toxins
to be removed easier through other
medical medium tools like your celery
juice your straight 32 ounces of celery
juice like you're like your heavy metal
detox cleanse like it actually helps
with other with other tools that's
what's even incredible but it's a what
it is it's a shifter remember that
that's one of its miracles
it's actually one of the shifters so
it's a shifter shot and that's what's
incredible about it so you Quicken your
healing so you move forward and heal
a lot of these shots
definitely detox get poisons out cleanse
they do all that a lot of these shots
are incredible exposure shots remember
there's 10 exposure shots there's 10
stabilizers and 10 shifters this one's
part of the miraculous shifter family
which is amazing
it really is when I think about it
it's mind-blowing just talking about it
well that's a thing you know
like really
it's mind blown just talking about it
she conscious says I thought the shots
gave me celery juice and extra hit power
you gave your you gave your celery juice
an extra hit of power absolutely
just don't put them together don't take
the shot and mix it in your celery juice
wait 15 to 30 minutes before you do the
one or the other
all right half piece of Ginger there
half inch
get that in there
boom
Carrie Pearson says my new omega mm-1500
arrived last night lucky you ordered it
on the third day of the challenge so
excited to use it Carrie
um
it it's it's an incredible juicer what
you'll notice is the pulp comes out dry
like very dry it's squeezing harder
there's compression making sure that as
much juice can come out the other
juicers don't do that
I know the other juicer companies the
sharks that got into the community they
think everybody's rich
because they're not squeezing all the
juice out like these are
and so these save money and you actually
pay for the juicer over and over again
like the savings pays for the juicer but
right now the MLM slash affiliate sharks
brought the juicers in the mm community
and everybody's getting tricked by the
by The Flash and the Frills and chills
but don't realize this is a slow
masticating cold pressed juicer that
actually squeezes so hard to get the
juice out and you save money because the
other juicer companies much think it
must think everybody's just Rich the
price of food going up who cares just
buy more produce buy more produce
okay
I mean think about that it's insane and
that's why I've endorsed these guys all
right half cup of fresh or frozen mango
is next
I have my frozen mango right here
boy I'll tell you
this
shifter shot
is just such an incredible shot I don't
even know what to say
it just is
let's move on to the next piece right
here
half cup
Frozen or fresh cherries but I'm gonna
go with
Frozen cherries here
nice they're pitted don't put pit don't
put the pits in here whatever you do
please don't put the pits in here
amazing
incredible
all right so we're moving along
what's the next order of business with
this recipe it's the raw zucchini
I'm gonna peel mine back a little bit if
you guys don't mind
so
half cup of chopped raw zucchini
I'm just gonna peel some of my skin off
you don't have to peel the skin off I
like to peel the skin off
foreign
get some of this in here
we're gonna do about a half cup
a little bit more to go
thing is about the dream shifter
you feel it as the day goes on if you
take it in the morning I get an instant
shot instant hit from it by the second
sip but you really do feel it
nice
[Applause]
so then the last is some a quarter cup
of loosely packed
mint
so peppermint leaves
now
that's the one to use is the peppermint
leaves
[Applause]
so a quarter cup
so I'm going to need some more mint now
the thing is is if you're not a fan of
mint just kind of hold your nose
that's what you can do you can hold your
nose that's pretty much coming around a
quarter about a quarter right there
[Applause]
will be a touch more and we're good when
you tightly pack it
what happens is
it takes a decent amount of mint because
that's what it is it's not Loosely
chopped it says tightly packed so that's
about a quarter there
we go
Marina can a regular mint be used
instead of a peppermint yes indeed
is it a homegrown mint in your backyard
in your garden bed is it a is are you
growing it in your backyard are you
growing it
incredible
this is day 10 the medical medium brain
shot therapy challenge
[Music]
it's an incredible time
I don't even know what to say
it's a very special time
[Applause]
[Music]
okay just need some room here it's day
10. Leslie mm 1500 isn't in stock yes it
is will they honor the sale price when
you are notified
the mm-1500 is in stock
I think they have the blue one in stock
which is it's actually my favorite one
is the blue one I just don't have it
here
[Music]
but they have the blue mm 1500 in stock
I love it it's like this cobalt blue
I love it I think what I'll do is I'll
I'll get one here so I can show you
it's just got such a such a
killer look to it
[Music]
that's the first sip
I'm getting hit on the first sip of the
dream shifter
not even on the second set
Second Step do you feel that
you guys feel that
I'm kidding I'm rushing glucose to the
brain instantaneously
this is incredible
[Music]
that is definitely hands down
medicine from above
the thing is is what you're gonna feel
with this
is you're gonna feel it go to the
emotional centers of the brain you guys
that's what you're gonna feel it do
you're gonna feel go to the emotional
centers of the brain
[Music]
and that's what I'm feeling
I can't wait to see what I'm gonna dream
tonight I'm gonna teach you more of
these because I'm doing three shots a
day you can do one shot a day
[Music]
bartender
bartender give me another
day 10 the medical medium brain shot
therapy challenge cleanse
mediation says Love this life you are
saving my sanity and health I'm honored
you're on YouTube thank you
incredible you guys
I can only just say this that I'm
honored to be a part of it with you guys
I'm honored to be here
Maria mm 1500 or an mm-900 which is best
I love them both I love them both
I mean the ml okay let me just say this
okay quick just so you know the mm1500
can make hummus
like I've never seen anything before it
can make nut Butters it can make nut
Butters without the added oil you guys I
have to tell you this
nut Butters when you buy them in the
store they add oil that wasn't even from
those nuts in there even if it's the
same type of oil they add it
it's a it's a it's a Shifty game you
know they play you can make your own nut
butter with the mm-1500 it's
unbelievable I got some in the fridge
it can make sauces hummus it can make
like so many things it can make sorbet
so it's not just this incredible cold
pressed masticating juicer it is
literally like this incredible Chef out
of a unit like I can't even tell you and
it's mind-blowing so I'm just letting
you know about why I love the 1500 for
those reasons it's incredible
anyway you guys know I've endorsed this
this brand because of this because of
what they do and because it saves you
money and the other juicer companies for
some reason like I said they think
everybody's rich and doesn't have to
worry about everybody's so rich they
don't have to worry about food costs
Rising
so they're they're you know they're
giving everybody Flash and pop with
their juicers the spinning thing and all
that stuff but they don't realize this
is a cold pressed masticating juicer
that actually saves you money because
it's squeezing more juice out because
everybody isn't rich
I mean the audacity and nerve of the
other user companies guys what did you
feel
what was the results you experienced
please share your story at Medical
medium tag at Medical medium medical
medium and remember imposters are out
there and they say they're medical
medium hi I'm medical medium the Anthony
William here's my profile pic it's the
medical medium and I want to offer you a
consultation that's an imposter I don't
do consultations I can't I got to do all
this stuff to make sure you get all this
information free 24 7 so people can heal
I have to make sure you get the brain
shot information that's why it's in the
books I got to make sure that you have
the Bibles to heal that you have the
information right here you can take the
dream shifter at night before bed whoa
read the details about that in the book
books it's one big book how to be
splitting two you guys this was day 10
of the medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge amethyst says I wasn't
having dreams for months and then after
the dream shifter had a great important
dream that night that's exactly why
that's it that's one of the reasons
that's the whole point if you have
problem dreaming problems you can
actually work on getting some healing
done and have the dreams
I don't even know what to say all I can
tell you is that shifter shot the dream
shifter shot is making me feel really
good
it's going along really good with the
Gaba and the celery Force I took before
I went live you guys you know that's the
MRG you guys you know that
right November G
um
and I endorse those guys because of the
four things that blows my mind I love
getting my mind blown life's hard enough
but when you can have your mind blown
with just incredible stuff all of it
you can take it you can take the dream
shifter any time of day at any time you
can take it at night you can take it in
the middle of the night right before bed
or during the day I'm doing three of
them I took one I'm going to take
another and then I'm going to take
another later on closer to bedtime
whoa Renee says yes fueling the shot
whoa absolutely
incredible Madeline says amethystwood
fabulous I did one dream shifter shot
last week as I was falling asleep I had
a few odd scenarios play out I was just
falling asleep but it was noticeable
because that never happens but I didn't
remember any dreams that night I hope I
do dream tonight keep on doing the dream
shifter when you can
absolutely but the thing is I know it's
hard because there's 30 miraculous brain
shot therapies 30 of them which one to
pick the heel which one to pick to help
well that's the thing that's what it's
all about you have it in here you guys
it's incredible
I don't even know what else to say
I might have to do you know
the famous doctor guys
who are you guys
this glass of wine is 52 000 a glass but
I have millions of dollars to choose I
can do this glass of wine every day 52
000. we will do another brain shot
therapy challenge cleanse in the future
keep an eye on the newsletter and the
website to see what's coming next
medicalmedium.com sign up to the
newsletter know what's going on what's
Happening know that it's all about
getting you guys free free free free
free
and we're going to be eventually doing
the light blast which you guys know that
in concert that's what I would do in the
past give everybody the light Blast From
Above which is also life-changing and
eventually we're going to be doing that
too so keep an eye out for the emails
the newsletters you guys know when that
comes up and you don't miss out because
that's no joke what we're going to be
doing
Jennifer says you're amazing thank you
so much Anthony without you I'd still be
on mattress Island you saved my life
God bless you I'm so happy you're off of
mattress island people do not know what
that is unless they've been there you
don't know what that is unless you've
been in that person's shoes where they
can't they can't live their life they're
too sick and they're struggling too much
neurological problems and everything and
they're basically on mattress Island
which is mattress and couch Island
you guys listen out for my exclusive
telegram audio messages by the way I'm
Jennifer I'm really proud of you because
I know you did the work and you're
becoming an expert with the information
to heal yourself
exclusive telegram audio messages I'm
doing where I grab the book read a
little bit at it it usually catches me
in this one moment at the end of the day
where i'm like coming off of a ride of
work and at the same time I'm coming
down I take a little bit of celery Force
and take some celery Force and you know
and I get ready I grab my book I sit
down and I get the phone out and I try
to figure out how to turn that telegram
thing on and finally I hit the button to
start recording and I grabbed the book
and I start just talking from the heart
and whatever from the book and all of it
and uh so exclusively on Telegram
you guys if you could share
medicalmedium.com with others that would
be amazing please share the website with
others like send a medical medium.com so
they can partake in all that freak um
cool healing stuff and information
recipes incredible recipes on there
right you guys check out medical medium
podcasts at Apple podcast
and check out the light infusion
meditation as well
which is incredible if you missed the
guided live meditation I just did you
watch replay at medicalmedium.com and
you can close your eyes
while it's on
find yourself a nice little spot to lay
down and relax
and listen
and do some soul healing
I am at your service
indeed
I'm at your service
yes
oh AWS Bar and Grill sorry Mrs Ferguson
Mr Ferguson did he get did is he coming
down
this is a hotel you guys there's a hotel
upstairs this is the bar and grill right
here
um Miss Ferguson is coming down for a
moment
he's still stuck upstairs Mr Ferguson
he's on the toilet
constipated again
tell him we got the brain shot therapies
ready for him and we can give them one
right when he gets downstairs Mrs
Ferguson
hey you guys
God bless you I probably just lost a
couple of people because they're like
don't like his humor I don't know what
to do
I'm just doing the best I can I'm only
human
[Music]
Spirit of compassion said we had to give
you the gift to hear
because you can handle it
choked me up a little bit
can I I'll try my best
this is the end of the first medical
medium brain shot therapy period therapy
challenge
when you get choked up you stumble on
some words this is the end of the first
medical medium brain shot therapy
challenge cleanse and we're gonna do
more
we're not messing around
it's about getting you better
no time to waste who has 10 years to go
to doctor to doctor doctor still wants
to see your doctors but who has 10 years
to waste this specialist this guy this
functional person this lady this person
this man
and then you're still sick we need
answers we need them now
we got them let's do some healing bring
the books to the doctors like they've
been doing people been doing for years
10 years now almost you can keep going
with the brain saver books and the Brain
shots on your own pace please share your
experiences and your stories reels posts
tag at Medical medium hashtag medical
medium
[Music]
guys
someone said they unsubscribed because I
did the robot someone actually left me a
comment on YouTube and said because I
did the robot they unsubscribed and then
they went by
I'm like okay
sorry sorry
I love you guys
see you guys soon look out we're gonna
do