hi everyone I'm Danielle delate back
here for night two with the
collaboration of medical medium and Cafe
Gratitude we are so excited we hope you
had a great night last night cuz we had
so much fun here and we can't wait to do
it all again tonight we're going to kick
things off with our first guest from the
medical medium Community how are you hi
what's your name my name is darit so
nice to meet you where did you travel
from to be here this evening oh I'm a
local live I live very very close by you
are so lucky to have this collaboration
in your home Town isn't this awesome oh
I'm so happy and I'm a regular I come
here all the time to eat so I'm looking
forward to this awesome what was it
about this event that made you want to
come I really want to support this
community and I feel so a part of this
community by following social media and
being a part of the medical medium
Instagram group and seeing everybody
post their videos and their stories it's
just so inspiring and you're just not
alone in this world with changing your
habits of eating and the food and the
drinks and everything so I'm so grateful
for this community and I just wanted to
come and see everybody tonight did you
come with anyone did you bring a friend
I did I came with one of my friends
she's the one that introduced me to the
medical medium in the books oh wow so
why did she introduce you to it were you
dealing with some health issues at the
time she was she was telling me about
her friend and then she was telling me
about certain things that her friends
were going through and I'm like well you
know what I got to look into this I
ordered the book off Amazon I started to
follow the medical medium on Instagram
and and I'll tell you within a week I
saw the difference of the celery juice
and the heavy detox
metal smoothie that like I make and then
they started having it at Air1 it was
like wow this is fabulous I'm just I'm
so grateful I am so grateful cuz I've
seen changes in my life would you like
to talk about some of those changes
maybe some of the symptoms and
conditions that you've healed so far
well I used to break out with acne with
blemishes and I was living with that for
the past 15 years
and I couldn't get rid of it I thought
it was the coffee I thought it was the
foods I was eating and the celery juice
within a week I'm not kidding people
were looking at me your face is all
glowing and I wasn't even and I wasn't
even wearing makeup walking into the
office and people would be like what do
you you people thought I was a lot
younger than my age so I'm so grateful
because I did see the change in my skin
and I felt healthier and on top of that
no more coffee and when you drink coffee
if you don't take coffee for a day or
two you start to feel the headaches no
more headaches and I don't even crave it
anymore I don't even want to go to the I
don't even want to mention the name the
s store anymore but it really I don't
even crave the coffee anymore and also I
noticed that when I started to drink the
heavy detox smoothie my fatigue was gone
and it was something that I was living
with for the past couple of years now
and it got worse in the middle of the
day I would be sleepy and I took the
detox smooth and I started to really see
the changes I'm not fatigued anymore I
have so much energy and I there are
times it's like 1:00 in the morning I am
I don't even want to go to bed because
of all of the drinks that I've changed
the foods that I have started to eat
that I've changed has really helped my
energy level wow that's incredible do
you think having these mail options on
the menu at Cafe Gratitude will help
your healing Journey will make it easier
and more enjoyable definitely cuz I come
here all the time and I especially on my
birthday cuz they send me my birthday
gift card so so uh yeah I've I've been
coming here since the past I want to say
15 14 15 years I've been a regular
customer here CU I live in the
neighborhood and I'm looking forward to
the sushi I'm looking forward to the
different options that they're going to
start having because they do have um
seasonal menu which is great the food
here is fantastic you know you get some
of the winter produce and you get the
summer produce but this seems to be like
it's going to be more like an annual you
know set menu so I'm grateful for that
and I looked at the smoothie I can't
wait to try it speaking of the smoothie
I had one just before the live stream
and I feel amazing it's the I am
precious smoothie you are going to love
it it's divine I cannot wait thank you
so much thank you so much it was lovely
talking to you enjoy your evening nice
to meet you thank you so much we have
our next guest here hi I love your dress
by the way thank you you look gorgeous
too oh thank you what's your name for
everyone watching hi my name is Lauren
so nice to meet you where did you travel
from to be here I came from Connecticut
actually oh wow yeah you flew quite away
yes I definitely wanted to be here I've
been doing medical medum for almost 10
years now so um it saved my life so yeah
in what ways did it save your life what
health issues were you dealing with
prior to using the medical medium
information I had Crohn's disease
neurological Lyme disease um was really
honestly at a really dark point in my
life and had gone to so many different
medical colleges and Clinics and
everything was in conclusive I was a
writer I come from a family of writers I
started to lose the ability to write I
had severe brain fog fatigue twitching
just every symptom and it just kept
getting worse and I found his book four
or five years in and started the
protocols got my life back and have a
full-time job now I'm engaged so
congratulations by the way so much all
these dreams that I had for myself are
now happening because of medical medium
so I had to come and say thank you wow
uh you're engaged so does your partner
do the protocol as well do you get him
in on it he does he he like does the 369
cleanses with me and then the next day
he'll eat pizza and I'm like all right
but he does what he can and I appreciate
that yeah I I think it's beautiful that
you guys do it together I think that's
really a nice way to connect what was it
about this collaboration that you are so
excited for the food is amazing I just
made an Instagram about it because to
come out here and to not have to cook
and many of us even for me for work I
have to go meet clients sometimes and
not eat because I know there's going to
be something hidden in the food I'll
have intestinal upset from it or
whatever it may be to come here and not
have to cook a meal when usually you're
cooking three meals for yourself a day
is just amazing and then to be around
such beautiful souls I saw one of your
interviews yesterday with the gorgeous
couple that was so sweet and touching
and it's like people don't always get
we're different you know we have to eat
differently our lifestyles are different
to be around people who understand that
is just so nice yeah it's so beautiful
the medical medium Community is so great
did you come with anyone this evening or
did you travel alone no last time I went
to the book signing my I dragged my twin
and my mom along but this time I came
alone but I don't know it's very special
to me because I probably never could
have done something like this alone in
the past and so to do it on my own is
kind of celebration of me so you're
healthy enough to travel to be here with
everyone and I feel like you're not
alone this evening cuz there's such an
amazing community and I feel like people
make friends in the line as they wait so
that's what's like brilliant about this
community is just it's such a friendly
warm uh uplifting Community absolutely
it really is yeah everyone's so sweet
you I mean everyone here it's been a
blast so thank you so much well thank
you so much for talking to us have a
beautiful night so nice to meet you too
yes thank you you too okay we're going
to talk to our next guest if you would
like to come over and stand here
hello you look familiar from the Air1
Calabasas if you'd like to stand here
yes yeah nice to see you I'm Danielle
again for everyone watching again Toby
hello Toby hi I'm Sky hi Sky well so
lovely to see you again uh what was it
about about this event that made you
want to come tonight well I think it was
a really great opportunity to get to
meet Anthony on a more personal level
and just really sit down and enjoy a
meal and have like community in a
different way and what other time do we
get to dress up and come to a red carpet
event so oh yes of course and have a
full course meal that is all full of
goodness and healing it's beautiful
right yeah exactly I'm looking forward
where did you travel from to be here
today so um yeah I I was coming from
normally from Switzerland but this time
I was coming Switzerland uh Munich
Germany and then all the way to
Charlotte I think Charlotte andot yeah
and then Los Angeles yeah and then
yesterday I arrived so I'm here right
now it's uh it feels like a dream but
it's real right I think so yeah yeah
you're here yes yes and it's really cool
to see also like uh like likewise people
here and um that's cool like you you do
you know any uh of the community that is
coming this evening do you have any
friends that you're mating up with mhm
yeah I mean Tobias meets a lot of people
I'm a little bit more reserved but I'm
sure that I'll get to know some more
people today as we sit down and get a
chance to mingle and Converse it's like
a 2hour long event so I'm really excited
for it awesome what is it about this
event that you are most excited for you
know to have the opport Unity to come to
a place where we're able to have food
and not worry about what is in the
ingredients and just feel really calm
and at peace and you know cuz usually if
I'm going out I'm like what's in this
and what's in this and I can't have it
and then it it can get a little bit
overwhelming and so to be here and just
enjoy it and I'm I'm sure that it's
going to be delicious I actually already
tried one of the dishes oh which one do
you tell the sushi is amazing I love
that one and I'm looking forward to
trying the other ones and what are you
most excited for this evening so um I
I'm excited of of course because the
likewise people are here I'm excited to
see anony to say hello the people also
like behind the scenes and to try the
nice food and I think I'm also excited
because everyone it's here right now
they they come maybe from a point that
was not able a couple of months or year
ago or two years years ago to to be here
right and I say it's like maybe our time
to shine now so to to be back on track
and enjoy uh food and uh like so
socializing uh together like yeah and
this is this is a really good thing when
when we think about it because sometimes
we forget when we get out of this um uh
crazy um chronical disease or something
like this and then we forget oh where we
was coming from but when you think about
it it's like a miracle no nowh here like
looking fancy and uh are here with you
in front of the camera it's like a
celebration of Health it's a celebration
of Health yeah this this a good thing
yeah yeah I love it it's really
beautiful well enjoy the evening tonight
was so nice talking to you and maybe
we'll talk to you after the after the
meal and see what you think yes thank
you so much thank you thank you oh oh
thank you you two look beautiful
absolutely study yes come through hi oh
you're all dressed up you look you look
perfect for the red carpet your red
carpet ready I haven't dressed up since
prom so this is my special day to feel
beautiful yes well enjoy that moment
feel beautiful on here enjoy the lights
camera
action yeah what was it about this event
that made you want to come meeting up
with everybody and the people but just
having a chance to meet Anthony I went
to the other two events um but I wanted
that more personal one-on-one moment
hopefully I'll get with him tonight just
to say thank you above all things and um
just sharing with everybody my healing
Journey it's been a a couple years and a
really hard couple years but um I know
know a couple years ago I wouldn't been
able to even fly to get here so this is
a blessing in itself and where did you
fly from again to get PA here in
Sacramento so not too far but yes still
it's still a jetty and you have to be
well enough to to Trel you got to pack
all your adrenal snacks and you still
have to drink your water and you still
have to do everything you do when you're
at home yes yes what are you most
excited about with this event tonight
the food meeting Anthony and talking
with everybody else it's super hard to
find um restaurants that we can just sit
down and just eat and not worry about
what we're eating and knowing that it's
all safe we don't have a lot of that
especially up in my
area and with Cafe Gratitude medical
medium do you think that having these
menus on the meal for people to on the
menu for people to enjoy will make their
healing Journey easier and more
enjoyable absolutely a lot of us cannot
go out to eat at all so we're making all
of our meals we're prepping and as
everyone knows it's like sometimes hours
and days of prepping um and so just it's
a sense of freedom yeah is what it is
you know when you get sick and you're
trying to heal you don't go out to
restaurants and some of this is kind of
just a way to feel free for the night
and not worry knowing that it's safe
right because Anthony's made this all
possible so yeah which is incredible
it's so exciting so exciting like so
exciting so exciting could you talk a
little bit about your healing journey
and how the medical medium information
has helped you absolutely so in 2021 I
got super sick dropped 40 lbs in 30 days
had a adrenals fight or flight um
doctors kept telling me it was anxiety
and depression it was not anxiety kept
giving me medications um I kept seeing
Anthony on Facebook um books U my cousin
actually healed um colon cancer from his
protocols so he wow colon cancer huge
mass gone um and so he kind of was like
it's okay to try these things so I tried
it and didn't tell any of my friends or
family CU I didn't want to hear anything
negative and they just saw me getting
better and better and better um so I
have healed from breast impant illness I
had breast implants got strong enough
with medical medium protocols got those
um explanted last September and since
then I've been able to do two 369
whereas before I was not be able to do
any 369 um and hormonal IM balances have
been regulated and um I'm really working
on my medals getting my medals out rain
fog that's that's my part of my journey
that I'm on right now wow incredible
thank you so much did we talk at the
Air1 Calabasas we did for a couple
minutes yes yes a couple minutes you
look so familiar to me I'm glad that I
asked you that because yes so it's
lovely to see you again yes like friends
seeing friends again yeah part of this
community that's what I love about this
community it's just so beautiful that's
why I'm saying like you come for the
community you come from the community
cuz sometimes a lot of us we don't have
support at home you know and um there
seems to be a lot of like community in
LA but not so much where I live but
there is a group that we meet up once a
month and have and we have a little
potluck which is amazing and safe too
because you know you can eat whatever is
there too yeah so but yeah I think the
community is a huge part why keep coming
to the events MH yes that's beautiful
maybe more communities can you know or
people can connect with each other
through this live stream if they can
share where they're at and people can
connect with each other you know
absolutely thank you so much thank you
so nice to see you again enjoy the
evening we might see you later in the
night thank you who do we have next oh
hello hello Sara yes so nice to see
you how was your trip it was actually
better than last time okay yeah it's a
long it is a long trip but we're here we
made it everyone watching at home
centara flew all the way from Australia
to be here this evening yeah that's
incredible especially you opened up
about your healing Journey with
everything that you've gone through and
now to be able to travel to the United
States it's incredible I've actually
been reflecting on that a little bit
like on the flight over here it would
have been impossible if you would asked
me years ago and even just growing up
and going through all that I went
through with my health being completely
bedbound and having to turn down just
the simplest of plans like literally
just going out with friends I'd have to
turn down plans I'd feel guilty I'd feel
shame i' just all of this stuff growing
up and to actually be flying here now
and not turning that down being able to
jump on a plane and get here and feel
amazing and feel healthy and feel
vibrant and have energy not be crashing
in the middle of the day not have brain
fog not have aches and pains and tingles
and numbness and all the rest of it
crazy gut issues which that
like information has really just changed
my life in such a pivotal way the
bloating the cramping the the gastric
pains and everything is gone wow it's
just incredible I was following your
Instagram by the way and I saw that you
had some tips for traveling and I think
it might be nice to share some of those
tips on how you stay on the protocol
whilst you're traveling cuz it seems it
seems kind of hard and overwhelming at
times I think especially with a longer
flight it's so important for me to get
lemon water in so I will be at the
airport and I've made so many friends
this way because people will ask what
are you doing you're like squeezing
lemons over there I will go through
customs and get like some spring water
I'll have my lemons already cut up ready
to go right cuz I'll bring good tip
that's a pro tip Pro tip cut your lemons
up have them ready to go in a little
sandwich bag and then I just squeeze
them when I get through customs sit at a
little cafe you know get the lemon water
into the spring water and so I have that
ready to go for my flight um and I do
love bringing like things like bananas
onto the flight they're just really
simple and easy um and then on my flight
which was really lucky they do serve
fruit platters so I really love that
option as well but those are just some
incredible tips to keep hydrated if
they've got coconut water at the airport
I will grab one of those as well just
anything to keep the hydration up when
you're on that plane yes wow that's uh
such amazing tips and I feel like
tonight we're celebrating uh you know
people that are coming like such as
yourself your health for being able to
travel to be feel good to be here this
evening it's like a bit of a celebration
of Health that you are able to be here
and to enjoy this and connect with
Community yeah it's honestly mindblowing
to me to be here and to come have come
this far over the years I don't really
have words to describe it it honestly
feels like a distant memory or a dream
it doesn't even feel real to think of
what I went through and but at the same
time when I think back it's like like
what Anthony that's that Soul's gold
that you collect along the way and that
wisdom that you collect it it means a
lot as you go through that struggle of
chronic illness it's not all for nothing
when you get to the other side yeah it's
like it never happened in a way it's
like you can't even connect with it on
the way as if you were experiencing like
that but the wisdom and everything the
knowledge and the experience you gain is
more than words can describe do you feel
like when you're on the other side you
have a appreciation in a different way
for all the things that you were now
able to do yeah and more of an
understanding and compassion as well I
mean people it's really unfortunate to
see the state of the world kind of
getting sicker and sicker I'm seeing
family and friends and people around me
start to come down with their first
symptoms and go on the doctor shopping
journey and going doctor to doctor and
you know I'm speaking with them and
because of what I've been through I can
really connect to what they're
struggling with and it doesn't seem like
like they know that people out there
have been through what they've been
through like I went through it so young
and so I know I know the feeling and I
can really relate to them and their
experiences and be that kind of
compassionate shoulder for them um but
the gratitude that I feel being on the
other side of the chronic illness that
I've experienced throughout my life and
just the emotional battles and the
everything that I've been through the
trauma everything that the medical
medium information has really helped me
heal from and just move
past no words no words and speaking of
gratitude we're here at Cafe Gratitude
for the medical medium Cafe Gratitude
collaboration what was it that made you
want to get on a plane and come here you
know this is a once in a-lifetime sort
of opportunity and to be here with this
community is unreal it's honestly at
this point it's just like catching up
with old friends again just with this
whole year with all the other events as
well um it's incredible just to connect
with everyone again it's really my soul
family and what are you most looking
forward to with this evening's events
well I am really looking forward to
trying the food I haven't tried it
yet I know I'm really looking forward to
it I've been eyeing off a few of the
dishes have you tried them yet I've
tried them yes it's so good and I just
before we started the live stream I had
the IR am precious smoothie oh
refreshing oh refreshing slightly
indulgent tasting but like you know it's
good for you it's so good I'm I'm really
looking forward to just feeling really
light afterwards cuz there's no oil in
there and because the ingredients are so
clean and it's like who else does this
out there no it's so hard to find on
Friday night I was very excited for this
event so on Friday night went to Cafe
Gratitude in Venice tried the I am
trustworthy the fajitas with the Millet
tortilla they look oh my God and
afterwards just felt so light yeah like
you're saying like this incredible dish
and it's like wow there's no oil there's
nothing nasty in there you can just rest
assured everything has been taken care
of and you can eat and enjoy it and not
be worried about your health or your
healing going backwards it's supportive
for all of that exactly do you think
that Cafe Gratitude having these uh menu
options from medical medium on their
menu continuing forward will help other
people with their healing Journey make
it kind of easier and more enjoyable for
them I think so I think so it's really
convenient to have a place to go and
pick up meals ready to go and have it
made for you I know a lot of people can
relate on the healing Journey having to
really make all of the things yourself
and so coming here and just enjoying
this every once in a while and you know
it being oil free as well is really
supportive for people with really severe
chronic health problems that are trying
to avoid that higher sort of fat load um
I think it's really supportive and
really incredible and it's awesome to
see how the medical medium information
is really getting out there in this way
it's it's like it's welld deserved and
it's about time but at the same time
it's like it feels like the perfect time
for all of this to be getting out there
in the way it is first with you know aan
this year and now with Cafe Gratitude
and just seeing the incredible
collaborations coming to play it's
beautiful oh it's great and I feel like
people are wanting this you know there's
a huge Community out there that really
wanting these options to have for the
healing Journey yeah thank you so much
for chatting to us enjoy the evening oh
so good to see you too see later yeah
see you later for sure thank you who do
we have for our next guest here
would you like to be on our live stream
Hi how are you I'm Danielle fine how are
hi nice to meet you where did you travel
from to be here from Germany it's from
Black Forest oh in the south from
Germany yeah wow and you flew in just
for this event only and is the only
reason why we come it's the third time
to La third time yes wow it's the first
time uh in in the LA in June and um
Anthony says come and event and we go my
English is not so good sorry no you were
doing so well if I had to speak in in
German I would not be doing very well at
all thank you yeah but anony is the only
reason then we can yeah yes it's great
and what are you most excited for this
evening what are you most looking
forward to um it's the energy from
Anthony the directly energy is um the
most important thing for us and for me
and um I um enjoy the food I think so uh
it's um it's awesome to go out and eat
mhm uh and since my wife and I we um
live this information since 5 years and
um it's one of the first time we go out
and eat and uh come together with
another uh uh guys um who live this life
and it's great it's uh it's great isn't
that so exciting can you talk a a little
bit about your healing journey and how
the medical medium information helped
your health yeah um my wife
chulia oh she's not here tonight she is
she is in LA but um in in the Airbnb
um is fragrences too strong and she lied
in the bed and had um um much pain in in
the legs and in the whole body and um so
he can can just can come see she's
crying um but it's it's not can we send
her some love send some
love and um so my journey was um a long
time my stomach I I hope it's right my
stomach was um was the wall open reflux
um ref reflux yeah and um nothing helps
School medicine over many years um kind
and then my wife is nature doctor um and
so it was a little bit better but um not
to the end MH and um only by my wife too
and for 5 years we we found the first
book from Anthony and it was awesome we
we search so long time we look for and
we
we of TM um we all uh and um and uh now
we we read the book and yes that's it it
and and uh I I think so um from Anthony
is um not uh um the um the food the yeah
so all the soul the heart yeah and
everything everything and everything
it's all connected right yeah absolutely
it's all and you you read the books and
it it's all all in it's all in you you
need no another book no no yeah no it's
incredible do you have a message you
would like to share with the community
that's watching uh encouraging message
to help them with their healing Journey
so for me um or for us the most
important um words from Anthony you did
not create your
illness it's it's uh so um uh um
important these words for all chronical
ill people um and um yes and um never
give up and keep a light heart it's um
our journey um each day oh three steps
for yeah and two steps back and now by
my wife two steps back and um yeah and
then but we'll get through it again
three steps forwards next yeah
absolutely absolutely that's the most
important words for me from Anthony you
did not create your illness yeah yeah
yeah have you connected with the
community during these events absolutely
it's great um in in our hometown we live
in a in a town with uh 20 houses and and
42 peoples and see she look at you and
think so wow crazy no meat no coffee no
beer um and and she she don't know what
us to do yeah yeah and and we are
together and and uh and uh and and we
enjoy together these things um and it's
it's amazing to um other people to meet
with the same idea with the same heart
with the same Journey um through for to
sits back and so on it's um it's good
it's uh yeah yeah it is beautiful uh
beautiful Community to connect to and
just uh that people have that
understanding and compassion as well
kindness this is the right way um these
people um also compassion and um we the
other people I we think um very
compassion yeah we we we uh yeah yes
yeah sometimes it's hard to understand
if they haven't been through it
themselves but that's what's this makes
this community so amazing absolutely yes
well I'm so glad that you're moving
forward with your healing Journey that
you're able to be here with us tonight
we're celebrating at Cafe Gratitude
medical medium with the whole Community
thank you so much for your time really
appreciate it thank you thank you uh do
we have any more people to interview uh
we might take a break short L but what
an amazing evening so many incredible
stories that people are opening up and
sharing with everyone at home we hope
you at home are having fun watching this
live stream we're having just another
magical night in true medical medium
fashion and we'll be back shortly after
this short
break
e
e e
and we are back here at the live stream
with two beautiful souls here standing
next to me uh can you for everyone who's
watching at home introduce your names
absolutely my name is GES my name is
Rico uh so nice of you to be joining us
this evening where did you come from for
this event so I came from Houston Texas
here in the United States I came from
Toronto Canada across the border
beautiful and this is not your first
medical medium event you at
Calabasas where were you you at the
Calabasas one as well or is this your
first I can actually tell the whole
story we met at the very first event we
were standing in line and actually it
was really nice to go back to this event
the exact same spot where we met each
other and we hit it off so well that we
decided to not only go to the second one
but also come tonight to the dinner
that's what's so amazing about these
events is that connecting with uh other
individuals that have also been through
these Journeys that are also doing the
medical medium protocol it's so exciting
it's very uplifting as well absolutely
it it encourages me at least to keep
going with these uh medical Medan
protocols and um it's just awesome to
have somebody who's also you know
involved and a part of the community to
be in touch with uh with people it's
amazing so it was you know it was
awesome to meet him at the first event
and to to see him back to back at the
next uh the next the following uh uh two
events including today was just it's a
blessing it's it's amazing it's amazing
here's to more events let's put that out
there
yes absolutely absolutely yes so what
was it about this one uh that made you
want to come to Cafe Gratitude what are
you excited for with this collaboration
I think I was kind of we were both
excited about the smaller amount of
people coming so it was going to be a
more intimate sort of evening have more
time to talk to people even though I
think it'd be very difficult I think we
would both agree to top the Canyon from
last time of 10 hours of sitting and
talking with people with amazing food
but I think tonight will be just as
awesome yeah and uh I I I think uh extra
few seconds with Anthony would be um you
know amazing and it's what I'm looking
forward to that was one thing that you
know came to mind when I signed up for
this event and just to be around you
know medical medum people was you know
it's awesome like I said the other two
events I was at and I thought you know
why not go to a third if um if able to
and here I am before because of how sick
I was I was unable to to travel for a
long time Pro probably about a decade
without being able to go anywhere and uh
and now thanks to Medical medium
information I'm able to to finally
travel again so I thought why not you
know commemorate by coming to his events
three times in the same year um yeah
it's uh I wasn't last time I went on a
vacation was in
2011 in the summer so it's it's been a
while and like I said thanks to Medical
medium information I'm able to to do it
again and thanks to that I'm here today
yeah wow wow thank you this is like a
milestone year for you absolutely
absolutely it's I'm celebrating multiple
ways today yes can you talk about some
of the symptoms or conditions you've
helded with medical medium information
start with you uh yeah I was I was a
total mess to start with um I mean it
all began with uh I was symptomatic with
regards to uh sinus sinuses issues uh I
had um you know science infections
periodically throughout the years up
until 2011 when it it really got it got
really you know worse and um I was on a
psycho biotics I I then decided to I I
suffered some side effects from that I
decided to to play soccer just uh you
know just I guess men's you know uh
local soccer division around town and uh
I sustained a concussion from that so I
was a total mess from that I was on a
chair daily for about 9 years easily 9
years not able to do much so my biggest
symptoms I would say are neurological uh
issues um all kinds of other stuff like
I said sinuses they they persisted and
uh and most of that has has healed for
the most part the B of is behind me but
um there's still some work to do so I'm
just excited about that finish line I
could see it now that I you know
surpassed so much and uh I've been
through you know very very bad place to
say the least and I'm just grateful to
be be to be here on the light side of
things we're grateful that you're here
with us and that you've come so far on
your journey and I am getting the signal
that I do have to wrap it up or we can
do one more I I before we quickly do one
more we didn't get to hear your healing
Journey so we just wanted to heal if if
you would like to share with us just
very quickly sure so thankfully I'm
somebody who's been you know one of the
people who are hasn't had too many
ailments but I've healed things like
excessive dandruff and really high blood
pressure um I would say a little bit of
depression and depersonalization and
anxiety as well and one of the most
healing things aside from being on
celery juice the heavy metal detox
smoothie and you know staying away from
no Foods has been coming to these events
it's been kind of like a soul healing
experience to see that there are so many
of us that we're not alone you know it's
one thing to look online on you know
Anthony's millions of followers it's a
whole another thing to actually come
here and be able to talk to people in
person that's so beautiful there
something about that connecting in
person and maybe that will give some
people hope as well watching the live
stream who maybe couldn't be able to AR
able to travel yet because they're on
their healing Journey as well absolutely
absolutely for a long time I was in
those shoes of not being able to go
anywhere so I I I I I kind of got a
little bit of a sense of what you're
going through but uh I'm I'm sure if you
continue to uh you know be on these Pro
these medical medium protocols you'll
get to where you want to be and U you
know in the future probably near future
you'll be in one of these events
yourself so keep going keep f it keep
that medical medium LIF style yeah keep
that hope alive as well yeah yes so
thank you so much for talking to us
really appreciate your time thank you
lovely to see you again yes we've got
one more story here hi hi I'm Danielle
hi Danielle I'm here hi nice to meet you
if you come and stand on this cross here
so nice to meet you what made you want
to come to this event this evening um
it's been a n-year
um something I look forward to meeting
Anthony for like N9 years so U it was an
opportunity to meet him and also to meet
people in the community MH have you
enjoyed that waiting in line and meeting
all these beautiful souls oh yes um I've
met so many wonderful people and we were
at irwan today also I just happened to
by chance be there having lunch and I
got to meet some wonderful people there
as well so that was a lot of fun that's
so great did you travel to be here this
this evening I did um I came from uh
Southern Ohio oh wow and what is it that
you're most looking forward to with this
event tonight uh meeting
[Laughter]
Anthony and this Community is awesome
we've also got a Comm the community
watching online do you have a word of um
encouraging words that you would like to
share with the community watching online
uh this gets me a little emotional so um
anybody that's um struggling with um
chronic
illness um the medical medium
information has answers and people can
heal and you can do it pretty easily um
maybe some people more easily than
others but I had profound um effects
even within the first week of
implementing um celery juice and amongst
a couple of other things so it's just
it's profound um I would encourage
anyone that has anyone in their family
or themselves that are struggling with
chronic illness or symptoms um that's
making their life difficult to check
this information out that's incredible
thank you for sharing that I know I know
it can be quite emotional would you mind
sharing some of the symptoms and
conditions that you hailed from using
medical medium information if you feel
comfortable absolutely um thank you and
so I had a very long list of just small
nagging symptoms so some of maybe not
not so small as others but one of them
was um I was having terrible indigestion
and bloating and um difficulty even
though I was eating um pretty healthy
food and I was living a fairly healthy
lifestyle I was still I was just never
able to get over these um digestion
issues and uh I know this sounds
miraculous than it was I was able to
heal uh make significant um progress
with my digestion just within a week of
celery juice and then making a couple
changes to my diet it was profound and
fast and it was like just I mean if I
probably sat down and looked at every
you know researched every little nagging
symptom I had I I I had probably over 50
and maybe maybe more might have been 75
and um many of them are gone or um but
if I get get too far off track some of
them start coming back and then right
back I go to the information and uh I'm
doing fabulous I sleep really well and
um I'm I'm happy and uh so it's
wonderful and I just encourage anyone
that has any um anything to to check it
out cu it's really profound in what ways
was your life limited by some of those
Health struggles struggles that you had
prior to the medical medium information
so it was really um you know I struggled
I'm I'm a mom my my kids ever since they
were teenagers i' and they're in their
30s now um I really struggled with my
health so it was difficult to be a good
positive wonderful mom that I wanted to
be so um I got that back and um uh being
just a good a fun friend and a a fun
person to go out and do things like I
was really limited what I could do and
um how much I could
um uh enjoy my life I just really wasn't
enjoying my life and it was just really
hard on me and to not be able to go to
social events and go to things and
people just didn't understand and um so
I've gotten all of that back and more
that I wanted to enjoy my life and to do
what I want to do and it's it's
fantastic and profound yeah and now
you're here let's celebrate for a moment
that you're here in Los Angeles at this
medical medium event with Cafe Gratitude
you're about to have dinner a dinner
that you can enjoy without feeling heavy
and Bloated afterwards is that a is that
super exciting for you because that I
feel like this is a moment oh yeah and
to have a restaurant like Cafe Gratitude
offering something like this this is
unheard of U in most restaurants and and
it's available here and it's such a
smashing success that hopefully other
restaurants will see uh and people chefs
and things like that will see the
benefit of offering something like this
and and the demand for it and hopefully
it'll be available not only at Cafe
Gratitude but hopefully it'll be
available at other places as well maybe
start something here yeah oh I I asked
Cafe Gratitude um if they would be
willing to sell franchises
yeah that's not a bad
idea do you think that Cafe Gratitude
including the medical medium menu
options uh for future uh will help
people that are having the healing
journey to be more enjoyable and easier
for them to be able to come here for
sure and people maybe they're looking
for somewhere to travel to or to enjoy
for a vacation and people will ask like
wonder wonder what I can eat and then we
be wondering what what can I eat like
maybe they would choose to come to this
part of the country because there's
somewhere that they can a restaurant
that they can dine out at and enjoy
amazing
food now there is going to be a light
blast tonight are you excited for that
oh have you seen any of them on live
stream I have yeah so that that's very
exciting as well um to be in the
presence of one of those oh yes yes and
with this whole Community that's been
amazing there's been a queue out there
you've been waiting in line did you
connect with some beautiful people there
oh yeah I've met wonderful people from
all over the world in this line and
learned a lot about um different
people's Journeys and things and some
really inspiring stories as well you've
got one of those inspiring stories by
the way it really is truly incredible
I'm so glad that you are healthy enough
to fly here this evening to be here to
enjoy this four course dinner at Cafe
Gratitude be on the red carpet here as
well yeah it's it's an honor in so many
ways and um I'm I'm so happy to be here
and
grateful do you have one piece of
medical medium information that you felt
really just changed everything for you
that you'd like to share with everyone
watching uh definitely celery juice and
then the vgy supplements they're so pure
and um I really saw the needle move when
vgy started started um offering their
supplements things the needle moved
really fast so celer juice and then
yes vimer I just had I put an order in
for some vimergy as well the barley
grass juice uh extract powder yeah I
hope I got that right but I add it in
for the heavy metal detox smoothie oh my
God I have so much energy with the heavy
metal detox smoothie well yeah it's the
the spirina and The Barley well it's a
combination of everything but spirulina
and a barley grass juice powder are
fantastic and be prepared for your skin
to look even more amazing than it
already
does oh I'm all about that one yes you
talk about your you have your family as
well have you shared with them some of
the medical medum protocols that you do
have they joined you on any of the
cleansers so they're not really excited
about um the this the details matter as
Anthony says they're not really excited
about the details they're happy to eat
the food and drink the um take the
supplements and but they're not really
none of them are sick so they're not
really interested in the backstory of
why we're take why we're having this for
dinner or the potatoes or the celery
juice or the different juices that
so not yet but they they've tried it and
they're enjoying it oh yeah and they
what they really love is the benefits of
they feel better and um uh I my
significant other is 56 years old and he
has so much energy and just works 12
hours a day and he is doing fantastic so
um on the medical medium because he's he
doesn't have health issues so add in
medical medium on someone that doesn't
have health issues like they just have
so much energy yeah that's the thing
like even if you are healthy adding in
these Protocols are just like they take
it to the next level it's incredible
thank you so much for sharing your
journey with us you have an amazing
Health story really appreciate you
opening up and sharing that with
everyone watching at home we're going to
let you go in line to meet aw very
exciting now yes yes so enjoy
that oh we're wrapping up here for now
but we're going to cross over to aw and
check out the meet and
greet
e
e e
I come here all the time I get my
birthday gift card from the oh my God
this is the best place I can't wait I
can't wait to see your collaboration did
you did you try it yet the food yet not
yet tonight oh man it's really good
thank you so much for coming out and
doing this and thank you all you've been
doing mm stuff you been when you can
you've been doing all the time oh my God
no blemishes no acne my fatigue is gone
with a detox smoothie so I wanted to
thank you for that I went to the doctor
the last three years no do anything oh
my God no blemishes and everybody thinks
I'm 10 years younger so thank you for
the celery ju next is the liver cleanse
that I'm going to be doing well you know
you'll get there don't worry you're
doing a lot okay you're already doing it
thank you you're healing that's
incredible okay fatigue I know that's a
big deal that's a big deal yeah you had
it where it was weighing you down you
just felt like it was dragging you down
no more going to that place called s
anymore for coffee that's with and it's
fabulous amazing the celery just just
gives me the energy I'm in the office at
seven I have celery juice I'm proud of
you people laugh at me cuz I'm at the
market with eight Stacks the whole week
thank you I'm proud of you I appreciate
it seriously do you want to get a pck
yeah let's do
it here we
go perfect thank you thank you enjoy
yourself I'll see you later hey what's
going on nice thank you so much for
everything you actually saved my friend
really one of my best friends she cured
her lung disease in 20 years and she
learned about the Lyme disease how it
works she read the book she read the I
read the book and I screenshotted it and
sent it to her really thank you that's
incredible no I love knowing that
anybody I help with Lyme disease that's
a big deal it was a huge like a 20 year
thing for her yeah yeah she's been
through uh hell and back with the lime
dises I'm sure well thank you for thank
you for all your gifts you know I celery
juice even my boyfriend you got your
boyfriend on it yeah a real skeptic too
but you know Heep told him at the
dentist he didn't bleed yeah so from the
oh well there you go because you know
and then he'll he'll be like wait a
minute so well let's going a pick Let's
get a pick wonderful right here come
right up here
great amazing enjoy yeah go ahead real
quick I'll be really quick well he can
he can grab it right there can you take
one my phone thank you I don't want to
hold the line
coming this way thank
you there you go thank you so much enjoy
have a good night I'll see you thank you
thank you guys no no thank you for doing
this okay yeah I got to stand by the
ACT thank you I appreciate we're
together thank you oh awesome I'm going
to constantly be putting you back okay
okay thank
you boots miy you're
Lauren of course so nice to meet you
good to see you here over thank you for
saving my life I'm I don't want to get
too emotional but I'm so grateful to you
and for a while I couldn't write and my
passion was writing you couldn't even
write it was just the brain fog wasn't
coming to me the way I thought it would
so um I wrote you something you're a
writer you're a of course you're a
writer write again and I just wanted to
thank you for that so I this is for me
you wrote something yeah it's just a
little thank you a little thank you not
this is amazing what do you mean
hopefully you'd read my handwriting but
I will okay Lauren I will thank you okay
seriously tell you that in my dreams I
always thought oh my gosh I'll meet you
and you can do a reading and tell me
what I need to do and you know I always
realize that you've given me all the
tools and I know what I need to do I
just oh thank you for thank you are
doing it and thank you for doing it
seriously you're working with everything
you're doing good stuff you're healing
you're already moving forward okay and
and and I'm I'm seeing you out there I
know I know and okay yeah thank you for
just so you know that you're so sweet
thank you let's get a pick yes okay
we'll sit right here or stand right
here amazing amaz I'm so excited thank
you for coming did you try it yet have
you been here for a little I've been
here way too much I you're here for once
now you got to have it again for dinner
thank you so much thanks laen you're the
best hello hello what's going on here
this is special year Hi how are you how
are you nice to see you nice to see you
I love the mask yeah yeah I do yeah be
safe it's good be safe exactly lots of
stuff going around I just want to say
thank you that my for everything you
and and and you're so you're doing all
the different stuff are you feeling
better much better amazing yeah that's a
big deal were you sick for a while M my
my daughter my daughter my daughter was
the one
so so I want to say thank you
to awesome awesome getting better and
better that's very special that's
wonderful I love hearing that you're
healing your family your healing thank
you for coming where did you come from
oh my God right here nothing better you
can come here you can eat the food it's
safe to
eat okay thank you very much well let's
get a picture let's get a picture right
here incredible well I'll see you
okay hey Mike wants me behind the ex
little
Shadow Hi how are you oh my god ni to
see nice to me nice to see you again I
want to just thank you for doing God's
work and I know that you are touching
the lives of so many people and youve
touched my life and I had so many
moments where I cried and I prayed God
to give me healing and I found your
information and it's been incredible
I've been doing mm since 2001 oh my God
no I I've been I've been out I've been
doing the work yeah before 2001 so I'm
thinking maybe that's you come across my
path yeah but you've been doing it since
20 um 21 really oh that's that's amazing
been really amazing so I just want to
thank you from my bottom of my heart and
I know you're doing great and yeah
you're doing God's work too okay yeah
well yeah it's going to be pretty
intense when when when it gets out there
um I just want to say I appreciate you
coming seriously and and being here and
working on yourself and healing your
body okay I'm very very proud of you
that's a big deal means the world to me
and uh 2021 you've been in it a while
you're seasoned and that's a lot do you
want to get a pick we get a pick
together okay okay a little bit
more amazing I hope you enjoy the food
thank you for saying saying
H
okay hey what's up Christ nice to meet
you hey nice to meet you I've been doing
medical medium for 3 years since 2021
and I've healed so much tremendously and
I have to tell you both my parents they
passed away at a very young age due to
chronic illness my mom was 49 my dad 52
yes2 I was headed down the same path I
had ALS and and it was awful did you
turn it around yes you turn that ALS
around completely healed that's the way
to do it yes and so I just have to tell
you it was you know because I found the
truth you know the medical medium
information that helped me do that and
I'm so grateful and I have to tell you
now I'm actually helping other people
heal so I'm able to wake up every day
and know that I'm working for God and
helping others well you have a you have
a big story I mean ALS
um that's a big deal and you yeah and
you conquered that and you're here
you're
talking that's that's beautiful that's
just really special well I have to say
thank you and thank you to Spirit of
compassion and you know I'm helping
others not only through your books but
through the angels as well and I'm so so
grateful good using that information is
really powerful yes it is and thank you
for tonight because that's a lot of work
right to cook this every day at home I'm
the only one in my family that does
medium so to sit down and have a
wonderful dinner at a restaurant I hope
you enjoy it too it's really amazing I
can't wait let's get a pick excited
thank you so much come right up here
let's amazing thank you come on inside
get a
seat hey how are you thanks for coming
you I appreciate it I appreciate you
just a
little I appreciate you you're my
favorite
well thank you you're my hero too cuz
you're doing the stuff you are you doing
any of the metal smoothie are you doing
the celery juice at all are you doing
stuff I've had the heavy metal smoothing
for every day for probably six years now
six years now yeah so juice to that's
incredible past two years I've been
cleansing every month so hopefully I
just keep improving keep improving
that's so incredible that's so amazing
I'm really really really proud of you
it's not easy to do but you're doing it
you know you made a commitment you you
said I'm going to heal I'm going to work
on this and you stuck with it sir it's
worth it and listening to your podcast
all the time you like the podcast should
I still do the podcast I still I listen
to I'm driving in the car and I hear
your voice and it's just really
motivating I'll keep them coming I'll
keep them coming let's get a pick
okay amazing thanks so much I hope you
enjoy the food tonight
[Laughter]
Tobias what's happening hi hey Anthony
nice to see you again good to see you
again truly you know how how are you
doing good doing good I'm happy I'm here
to see you see everybody there's nothing
better than that no I would there's
nothing I'd rather do so I'm honored
you're here truly thank you so much I
can can be here was uh did you take a
long trip to get here yeah it was a
longer trip to get here yeah it was I'm
I'm happy to to be here and I was
thinking what I can ask you and so many
things but probably a billion questions
you know a billion question but I think
they'll hit you tonight yes you'll think
about them tonight and be like I should
have asked them this it's true yeah I I
think the most important thing is um I
get uh most healed and now I'm ready to
rumble to um try to help also others and
to inspire them it's going to come yeah
it's going to come it's going to
basically fall out of the ether and land
in your hands and you'll get inspired so
let's get a pick Let's Take a picture
we've had them before let's get it yeah
okay let's it's okay when I yeah sure
that's fine it's okay when I when I put
the head here like yeah that's cool so
cool thank you so much I enjoy the food
man thank you so much for everything
I'll be here what's going Michelle from
Michelle yeah Michelle I know you I know
you thank you so much for my great
lifestyle I love the healing lifestyle
well thank you for the support okay you
have been supporting medical medium
information you've been supporting me I
know and I'm honored I want you to know
that okay you're so comp I know it
hasn't been easy for you so we really
appreciate you thank you I appreciate
you okay I want I was happy you came
tonight all right I was happy you
came and um yeah and all the work that
you do and fact that you care I know
that you care about people in the
community I know that I know that it's a
big part of like your life about wanting
other people to heal and and spread the
word and everything and I I you have to
understand that I really deeply
appreciate it okay I do thank you and
I'm making I'm so glad I got a chance to
talk to you oh my god oh oh no way so
we'll take a picture with that okay okay
I love
that thank you anony appreciate you
thanks Michelle Michelle is this yours
yes thank you
hey what's going on how are you I'm nice
to see
you I appreciate you coming did you try
the food yet have you been here yet I um
I did Uber eat the other day really
yesterday I was fantastic oh my God
thanks for getting all this going of
course options of course have you been
doing celery juice at all have you been
doing some stuff um I try to I haven't
been doing so good lately um that's all
right that's that's okay this is this
this is exciting okay we got a chance to
talk and you'll pick back up on it on
some celeries you and that's great um
and uh trying to to uh get all that
going back in my life and Things One Day
at a Time one day at a time there's a
lot going on in everybody's life you
know it's not easy and I know that I
know that you know you don't have it
easy and I know that I'm I'm honored
just I'm honored okay truly let's get a
pick let's go let's go here right here
sit stand next to the sa
for amazing I'm so excited well come on
in thank you
Anthony here he is all the way from
Germany thank you I'm so credit you to
be here good to see you are we going to
get another pick together or what let's
go let's go let's get one my wife is is
sick my wife is Julia we had a strong
fragrance in the Airbnb okay okay pain
in and body can't come best wish from
okay tell where tell where I send my
blessings okay get okay thanks a lot oh
I
have thank you for coming okay it's for
me okay thank you enjoy
enjoy you got a book for me hi an hey
such an honor to meet you um thank you
so much for everything I'm in this world
because of you but I'm still having a
really hard time surviving like with all
my brain
problems I don't are you doing oh are
you doing some of the medical medium
stuff do everything doing everything
that's good that's good but it takes
time you know how I say that all the
time you know how I talk about that how
long how how long youve been doing stuff
been trying for 5 years I've had really
bad food addiction so for one year
probably one and a half or 2 years been
doing really good now I understand food
food again
I totally understand thanks to you I
healed but now um so 2 years has been
properly doing everything and I I just
it's amazing my brain like getting worse
in a sense you know it it it it takes
time when it's nervous system okay it's
just the
PTSD let's get a photo let's do
that well listen listen
I know and the PTSD could be really
difficult but but you're you're you're
doing stuff that you wondering if
there's some advice you can give me
you're listen just stay diligent stay
strong okay and and keep keep forging
head okay I see it in you okay I see
didn't good stuff thank you for
everything I can't thank
you hey hey I like the mask thank you
are you guys together uh yes uhhuh you
guys want to come up here let's get a p
picture together yeah nice me nice
meeting you amazing um yeah step right
up here I've been following you since I
don't know I think
2015 2015 yeah 16 15 15 oh my God yeah
that's a long time what about this guy
you got this guy hooked on
somewhat the theal you're doing the
lemon water you're doing the metal detox
yes all right right it's putting a smile
on your face look at you right
now for sure I app appreciate it good
good apprciate youo well I'm proud of
you guys okay just know that that's a
long time 2015 keep up all the good work
I'm proud of you she's doing a lot of
work she's she's got all your books she
has all the stuff out it's all on the
counter you got the books she's telling
me all about it you're making the
recipes you're doing you're doing all of
it right can you believe you're eating
out right you're did she say she she
can't eat out at places cuz it's got
this in it and that in it all this
poisonous stuff exactly and you don't
have to worry and you can come in here
tonight and this is so great yeah and
she just finished a 39 369 369 so now
she can you're brave you got some balls
you're bra you're brave okay well I'm
proud of you guys come on in and and try
to get you know relax and thank you okay
I'm proud of
you hey what's happening what's going on
let's let's get a pick together right
here
wow amazing thanks for coming yeah it's
good here where'd you come from from
Germany really you made the trip man we
made the trip third time third time I
thought it was two times but was the
third time my my grandmother asked me
why are you going another one jly and
I'm glad you did man I can't thank you
enough seriously and I'm proud of you
you know that right I do appreciate it
and you come in all that way and trust
me it's in my heart okay cuz uh that
means means a lot to me all right I'm
proud of you you have you been here
already in the last couple days have you
been here yet one time last one time
okay okay well I can't wait can't wait
to see you later okay amazing did we get
a pick did we get a
pick Papa what's going
on what's Happening my brother man how
are you good to see you look great you
look great you want to get a pick yeah
let's get coming up here close no
against the rules yeah yeah yeah no it's
all right
no no no good good good you look good
man you got some you're in the
gym you say that one's life I remember
that last story you were talking about I
remember it was I think one of the one
of the things that I'll never forget is
that video you posted of laying on that
table and then getting your chest pushed
on and getting your your your abdomen
pushed on I never forgot that video all
adrenaline yeah all adrenaline man
adrenaline emotional release I know I
remember that you were like I tried this
I tried that I tried this and then you
post and then you had that in the video
there that's some mindblowing man you
know you hear it all the time but you
are an amazing human being top tier top
I'm I'm honored man I'm honored
seriously means the world okay and your
support means the world right forever my
brother for this guy all right all
right hey what do you it's not a it's
not a chocolate cake is it it's not it's
not it actually holds a letter which
should be good no no it holds a letter
from my cousin that you help to he colon
cancer from oh my God so he can never
attend to any of your events but but I
just want this is incredible there's
there's a letter in here there's a
there's a gift from me and a letter from
him okay I well this is incredible want
to get a pick together right here
absolutely thank you there's the
[Music]
camer amazing thank you what do you do
with someone like me that's struggling
to um pray to the angels and ask for
help don't try so
hard just know they're
there just know they're there and do a
little bit at a time meaning like you
know they're there you're taking a walk
say hi don't even don't don't over don't
over
trry okay and don't don't use your brain
so hard trying to that's you go to bed
at night and just say good night to them
baby step
yeah it's powerful it's all you need to
do sometimes so so yeah can I give you a
thank soce you thank you I'll see you
later for this
event
hey how are you it's so nice nice to
meet you and oh my God meeting you like
in the flesh oh amazing I'm honored okay
I'm honored and you got here even with
the crutches you got here not easy it's
not easy at all super hard but you're
doing it I am doing I'm proud of you my
eyes and my hearing and my shoulders and
my gums all healed my God that's a big
deal cuz people say you can't heal gums
you can't heal this and then you see the
craziest stuff out there trying to heal
those things but it isn't the things
that do it you know you probably tried
so many things I didn't even know I
wasn't even trying to heal those I was
trying to heal this and it and then it
and and then it healed it it heal I was
shocking and it was something it was
measured by doctors so they could they
could see you know that is incredible
and then there's so much more to go like
this is so bad but I guess I'm just
trying to keep the faith right you got
to keep the faith okay and just know
that your body's healing do you want to
try to get a pick I know you to go this
is I know if you wanted me to talk so uh
what do you mean I do I
do okay
I also wanted to get a pick with you
well well come on in and and and try to
get comfortable I will I will thank
you hey what's going on I'm just so
happy to be here and I appreciate so
much everything that you've done thank
you I appreciate you appreciating it
okay that means the world seriously any
support I can get is a blessing and I
don't take it for granted okay I know
that I know that I I appreciate that you
keep putting the truth out there for all
of us who need I'll keep on I'll keep on
doing it I will I will thank you for
your support you want to get a picture I
should
do incredible I really appreciate it
have you tried the food yet not yet I
can't wait tonight's T
night oh my God how are you how are you
to thank you for coming um I just go to
the calabases yes calab okay okay okay
that's what I thought um but I didn't
get to tell you last time that I'm so
impressed and you're such an inspiration
you know healing the world fighting the
bad putting these events on like I I
want to be like you just having that
energy having that stamina someday well
look you're you're you're working on it
you're in your healing process right how
long you been doing stuff 4 years 4
years amazing okay it's keeping you
going little things are heal at a time
okay and and you know the information's
there you can dig deeper when you need
to right you can you it's there but know
that I'm proud of you it's not easy it's
not an easy process what you doing how
do you keep all the wrinkles off me I
don't do anything for for my face so
thank you thank you for anyway
it's this it's all the good stuff from s
so okay good well you put lemon no no no
I don't I don't you don't do any okay I
don't bless your heart I hope you have a
good time tonight I'll see you
in hey how are you the honor is mine
it's it's it's the other way around it's
the other way around absolutely am over
here Fant I got to say that your ability
and stamina to get every get up every
day and fight the battle that you're
fighting it's absolutely inspiring cing
on my heart
strings it's an easy work no it's it's
it's not it's not but you know what I'm
here I'm here because I need to help I
want people better and uh I keep on
fighting for it and just like look
you're doing this stuff you're working
hard and I'm proud of you don't forget
it I appreciate that yeah it's it it
works both ways okay I will work hard I
know you're working hard
that's what counts I appreciate you very
much thank you so much do you want to
get a little photo here
absolutely amazing well come on in relax
thank you for being here it's an honor
what's going
on I I I have no words I'm so thrilled
to meet you well I'm thank you for
giving your life to all of us
Hest well thank you for being here
making the trip coming here have you
tried the dishes yet at all but okay
tonight's a night okay good that's
that's good then you'll know you'll know
tonight you'll know if you like them
want to get a picture here
yes amazing thank you so much is there
any any Spirit compassion has any words
you're very giv
person okay thank you and you know that
you know that that's
right you
are fre time this year what a
treat Jo how amazing it was last time
the music what a treat oh God thank you
a little nervous to see you I wanted to
thank you for creating this opportunity
for us and celebrating healing together
and mm Ando so so grateful it's an honor
okay it truly is and thank you for
coming again you know because uh you've
already gone and seen the music and seen
what we did and now you're you know
you're here and it means something to me
okay it means something to me I'm in my
eth year in the mm lifestyle and it
changed my life that's a decade okay
that's a decade yeah you have a message
from you know um s so says that
you have been hard on yourself
throughout the years but less hard less
hard now and that's good keep up keep up
the good stuff let's get a picture here
a picture thank
you bless your
heart well get in there get comfortable
thank you
what oh my God Hi how are you how you
been good how are you good good thank
you thank you for coming a letter no way
really oh my God oh my God this is a big
letter oh my God that is unbelievable oh
my
God this is amazing thank you thank you
how are things going you doing okay want
to come over here for a picture yes okay
you're not crying I'm not you're not
that's good okay that's
[Music]
good you been working hard absolutely
you've always been a hard worker though
yeah okay going all the way back I know
I know that I know that and you're tough
you're very strong I know I think I was
in the military I know you were I
know I know I know and the thing is you
know and I know that though and I'm
proud of you I am I am so it's a big
deal you know it's a big deal to me all
right
to thank you appreciate you one in and
I'll see you I love you too okay thanks
Kelly hey hey thanks for everything
you've done to me I appreciate it you
know I appreciate you being here I was
really messed and I'm I'm you know
grateful to to I haven't traveled since
2011 up until that June event 2011 and
and then you tell me the June 15th event
right you came to cover
City so yeah I was so messed and you got
me out of the ashes so thank
hey I'm honored man I don't if's telling
you anything about me but I'm be curious
to know I'm proud of you man I'm proud
of you okay cuz I know how hard you work
and I know I know how you care you care
a lot you do okay and I know that you
care about the people around you and you
want the message to to to to get to
other people absolutely I I know that
about what I can I even been at work I I
eat so they ask and they ask you and
they're like what are you doing and
you're like I do this I got Bo
I'm proud of you let's get a photo here
okay amazing we'll try to enjoy yourself
tonight okay and I'll see
Youk hey what you again thanks for all
that you do I know what else to say you
know one thing is of course that you
know from your information it's nice to
know how not only scary the world is
that you tell us right how to protect
ourselves but also how beautiful it is
right almost like with angels it is it's
true I mean you're you're right I mean
that's what it is there's a bunch of
stuff you got to protect yourself with
and then how to protect yourself and
then and then the beautiful things that
are here okay something maybe in the
future like podcast or something you
could do um some information about how
to distinguish between like Soul injury
and heavy metals that's like a podcast
about what in heavy metals a soul injury
oh okay so oh yeah I would love to I'll
do that okay absolutely absolutely
this is amazing thank you okay are you
going to enjoy yourself tonight
absolutely what's going on I a really
powerful story that I wrote an around an
Angel and the light okay I'm a
nutritionist okay PR it to and I know I
have the time to do that here but it's a
real an angel real real powerful story
and the I don't all right so so so it's
in here though right okay but I'm okay
but did you write it in here
okay no no no it's good to know though
that you're telling me like this in
person and then I can read this too okay
really appreciate it and I was um
classmat with sneak Ray she was going to
introduce us but then I get a photo okay
okay let's get a photo right here sorry
thank you I appreciate it
amazing listen thank you all right and
enjoy yourself
tonight Hi how are you
hey good to see you guys good to see you
too we're here this is Kim you friend my
long lost friend of course I know
Kim good to see you guys seriously you
want to get a pick together in the
middle all right we got to be up here by
the X okay we get in the middle all
right you got it you got
it hey Jay I don't want to lose this
it's very special
okay
incredible thank you you guys strong all
right all right he you got it you got it
love you guys enjoy the food I'll see
you I'll try to do a good speech tonight
you always
hey hi how are you than nice to see you
thank you um Dre medical media
instructor for two years who two years
is a lot you know um if you're in it for
just a couple of months it's it's a lot
and you're doing two years and but but
strict means you found you found the way
you need to take care of yourself right
in the books and the information you
found your path
yeah and then you're doing it right to
what it is okay you're you're a warrior
okay you're a warrior let's get a
picture
here oh
sorry you're a
warrior Hi how are you thanks for coming
you're welcome it's E from Austin I know
I know but I can't
yeah no I know no I know and um You Came
again but this time you're not waiting
from 7 in the morning till 1:30 how
about that do you want to get a picture
together I would love to it'd be a great
honor oh my God this um this is amazing
did we did we know ahead of time you
didn't let us know you're coming I I did
I texted you okay good good but it was
kind of late it wasur oh I might not it
might it might I might have missed how
busy you are it might have okay that's
great I I'm so glad how's your son doing
yeah he's doing great okay good and your
daughter-in-law yes they're all fine
they'll probably be in touch
maybe okay well thank you for coming
we'll talk on the phone we'll talk okay
come this way this way awesome okay
thank you thank you thank you
eile hey hey the half oh my God oh my
God she needed her time okay so she made
you stand in line for 8 hours that day H
in
June that's what I do so you you know
that well see you're a good manth gwenth
introduced her to you did she tell you
that yeah yeah no I know it was gwenth
right yeah yeah great I know I know yeah
so good I ran it to you really quick
during cover and uh you know the
blizz gave you my card was for state
shield I don't know if you remember that
I'll get your card again okay yeah yeah
but I'm working with on the who issue
what it's doing to our healthare system
I want I want to hear about it I don't
know if you know about that but if
you're happy to are no I I want it
you're you you you're probably you're
the expert okay yeah okay buddy thanks
let's get a pH come on come on come on
what's the post right here
yeah amazing okay thank you you know I
love you all right all right you better
go find her this
way hey how are you oh my God
I know I look different no no no I'm a
little um what do you call it the snow
blindness yeah yeah yeah you know hey
nice to see you thank you listen I have
a message for you from people who are
they love you and they're so glad you're
doing this and they feel the energy even
though they're not here all right well
tell tell them I'm blessed to know that
they care and they're they're sending
their energy okay yes it means the world
to me all right yeah it does thank you
thank you all right let's get a photo
together it's our second wait no third
third photo right yeah oh which which
camera am I looking at
okay is it our third photo now or second
okay second from Italy walked up to me
and she goes I don't know you but I want
you to know that Anthony loves you oh my
God I was like okay that's amazing I
love you I love you too okay
yeah hey how are you I'm speak
speechless but I'm I'm good I'm
speechless too okay I am too I'm so
grateful for your you and spirit of
compassion your information
and the my commitment to doing this has
given me so much more strength than I
even knew and it's just to me it's
changed my life completely it means the
world to me okay it does it does it
means everything that's why I get up in
the morning and it's why when I go to
bed at night I say that's that's what I
want to do I want to help you and get
you out of bed get you going through
your day okay it's good reason to heal
and that's what you're doing thank you
let's get a picture come on this would
be amazing this the camera Straight
Ahead a lot of cameras here I
see thank you Inc thank you so much
you're welcome thank you for everything
you've done for us I hope you enjoy the
food
will what is going on there's a little
baby here iess that brought my baby yeah
you brought your baby I brought a baby
book too really check that out do you
want me to sign it if you don't mind um
it's a celery juice baby book that I got
oh my God that's crazy that's
crazy thank you so much thank you so
much for all the working it's changed my
life I'm honored seriously
okay I really appreciate you thank you
for coming and thank you for bringing
your
baby if there's anything you need us to
help with or anything since you have
your little baby please let us know and
we'll find we'll find somebody if you
need any support tonight handshake are
you kidding a handshake I would love
that my hands are so let's get a picture
shake your hand thank you so much let's
get a picture together
here for about
that thank
youate see you around hopefully
okay what's going on my favorite
person I I was the girl that e was
talking about oh my God yes she was just
telling me well thank you for coming
thank Youk thank you how are you good
good have you tried the foods yet not
yet is this how long you been here in
the area um the food what do you mean
have you tried the food in here yet the
food yeah yesterday oh yesterday you
tried it didn't you remember oh yes yes
yes yes of course my God you came again
of course I'm sorry you might be a bit
like snow snow blindness
no no it's okay this is incredible the
gift did open it oh yeah yeah yes yes
yes I'm opening it in probably tomorrow
or the next day okay I am I am we went
to do a beverage with my mom a drink
that is inspired by you restaurants went
to put it on the already and we wanted
to ask you do you think fresh is the
best or
HB I know HB is not the best well
well do you think it it depends well
let's get a picture so I don't forget
here is this for okay right
here I have to think about it and and
talk more about it okay and then we'll
see but that's what you're doing yeah
yeah my mom wants to do it she wants to
do it she's so smart she I want to help
kids oh that's amazing it's me tell her
I'm proud of her I will okay she needs
to definitely do what she has to do for
sure cuz that would be exciting oh yeah
thank
you you know what I'm GNA ask what what
I want to
which uh where should I look how do I
get those bugs out how do
I you know what I'm saying well no no no
I mean you were telling me about you got
some things in the works how do I get
the look where where should I be looking
it's going to come naturally you you you
you have the inspiration you have the
passion you're extremely passion it came
up from came from there so came in the
shower I said not not me no no I know I
know but it's going to be okay all right
you're working hard everything's going
to happen the way it needs to happen for
you okay you know that you know that all
right I love you thank
you all right I'm proud of you okay
thank you thank you for coming again
I'll be here tomorrow the next day good
good
hey proper meeing this time yes do you
know who I am yes I
do do you know what I'm up against
listen you got to know that I'm really
proud of you though okay I know you're
always up against stuff lately but you
got to know that I care what the hell I
know you shouldn't be I know what the
heck is it though can you tell me look
look you know when you're when you are
somebody that has a very bright light
you know this you know how it works a
very bright light right there going to
be more challenges okay there just is
okay do I have like big things coming
coming for sure okay you do and I need
to know how old is my soul it's really
old really it is like can you tell me a
number or no is that against the r you
got to use you got to you got to think
you know how old it is you got to go
back the years you got to say is it a
th000 is it 2,000 is it 3,000 and then
you're it's going to hit it's going to
hit you're going to know is it you got
to go far back okay I'll give you that
and then what's wrong with my Nails why
are they like
that we get a PO photo this time I'm not
crying you got a good photo this time
cuz you're not yes you're not crank but
the last one was great but you have to
yeah you have to know that you have
everything it takes just keep on moving
forward and yes you're a very old
soul hey how are you I love the glasses
here come over here you like avocados
yes and I love avocad
was too much my sister Lea Leela how are
you so lovely to meet you how are you
good to see you good to see you good
good thank you for coming you guys let's
get a picture together okay
great y amazing you guys thank you for
coming I'm so proud of you are are you
you guys doing medical medium for like
how long now she's been you've been
doing a long time yeah maybe like four
or five years or something four five
years yeah it's just four or five years
that's it know I guess only only four or
five years no biggy but you know how you
kind of like I don't know you you like
it'll be few weeks on you know like it's
it's to be that consistent is well I'm
proud of you thank you for coming you
guys and thank you for coming
okay
wait Candace Candace are you K it's
Anthony hey so good to see you you know
I wouldn't even be here 4 years ago if
it wasn't for you I couldn't get out of
my house with my anxiety I remember yeah
I remember when it started with you I
remember you know when you first started
posting I remember all of that you do
yes okay I do I know I don't want you to
think that I haven't seen your work on
yourself and your work and life and all
the good things you're doing okay yeah
and I'm proud of you and I'm honored you
came
thank you and I and I know you came to
calab basses yes I know you came there
and I know you couldn't make it to the
June I was almost I almost almost almost
went let's get a picture again okay
awesome thank
you I'm proud of you kiddo okay I want
you to know your character your fight
your drive is what keeps me going I'm
going to keep on fighting okay and I
know you're doing it with me all right I
will yes hey St here I wrote know what I
want to say cuz I didn't want to fub it
still working on my okay I'm all ears
I'm all ears go ahead working on my
healing but I just want to say that your
graciousness towards everyone is
inspiring to me and I'm humbled to be in
your presence right now and thank you
and God bless you God bless you too okay
I I I really appreciate those words they
mean a lot to me you wrote them you took
the intention and wrote it down and uh
and you're reading them to me and that
means the world to me okay it does okay
it means the world to me let's get
picture yes seriously that's very
special your heart okay it's going to be
okay we're going to sit down we're going
to have some good food okay lots of
love what's going on how are you how you
been I don't want to make you laugh this
time I wanted to have a conversation no
it's you you make me laugh no away you
can tell I was like let me look in your
eyes I'm always so hyper but today I'm
like really nervous have you
been okay there's a lot of stuff
happening you know I'm always so proud
of you thank you all right I was going
to ask you did you get my drawings did
my did you get my card and my drawings
from last time yes you did yes okay
don't you worry I did I did keep that in
mind all right and uh I love all the
work you're doing okay I look forward to
seeing your post I look forward yeah of
course are you kidding you what
celery celery
what
lupus who is come on come on come on
let's get I just smacked her back let's
oh sorry sorry but okay wait I can I
wipe my tears
off thank you Anthony I love you so much
you changed my
[Music]
life of course I know who you are in and
and I'll see you okay I'll be in there
talking thank you so much God bless you
bless you God bless you and thank you
for the support means the
world hi what's going on here come over
here oh my
gosh oh my gosh sorry I always spaz out
every time I meet you and I just want to
say thank you cuz I have not got the
chance to say just thank you so so much
to you andc for just bringing my health
back and also bringing purpose into my
life just thank you so much thank you
for being here okay I appreciate it yeah
yeah I
doct it's okay because I want to keep it
lighthearted and I don't want no no you
are you are keeping it lightharted you
are yeah you are for sure know a lot for
you because everybody's got their story
we'll get a quick yeah no I know I
know yeah okay you're the best thank you
for coming okay
brother what's happening my brother can
you give me ey What's going on huh how
you
doing
hey hug yes thank
you you got the Hat on yes good to see
you of course we made it to the beach
you made it good good good good good I'm
proud of you guys okay you did how how
long did you
travel 5 hours okay good good you made
it safe you're here 10 hours okay let's
get a photo here you guys
guys here come on comeing up a little
closer thank
you
amazing okay enjoy the night you guys
okay you guys know I care being the me
I'm honored I'm
honored hey what's going on nice to meet
you have you been I'm I'm good and
better things too well I'm honored
you're here okay how long you been
working on the medical medium stuff now
you know what's crazy I got your book in
2016 but you didn't dig into it yet I
didn't dig into it and then that's what
happened yep yep and it came it kind of
hit later it hit later it was last year
so it's been about a year and you know
once I started diving in it made so much
sense every something clicked cuz I was
so low carb and low sugar before but no
energy and my adrenals were you know and
then you knew you were like okay this is
working for me and it clicked incredible
so thank you
amazing well thank you for coming okay
hope you enjoy yourself tonight
glutenfree bread with you I can't wait I
can't
wait what's going on what's Happening
enjoying the moment right now hey thanks
for coming my friend okay you know I
appreciate it okay let's get a pick
[Music]
I always keep an eye on your stuff on
social you
know thanks Gabe all right thank
youo hey what's happening what do you
got you got you really
yeah this is all you dude that's crazy
did you try you picked this yeah came
off this is insane that's amazing try it
last time yeah I did of course it did
but that's off a tree yeah I mean your
tree you picked it I been with the trees
for 10 years it's my client's trees but
I taken care of that's insane this is
all you D that's insane it's
[Laughter]
amazing I'm honored much love brother
I'm honored it means the world to me
that you you had the intention to pick
the fruit yourself and and give it to me
okay I love you for it
hello hey what's going on my name is lra
hey nice to meet you IED something for
you whoa this is really good
work wa this is
incredible and I I see there's a I think
there's a tortoise or a turtle yes okay
that's amazing and I see um geese did
you know geese are my favorite
oh geese and hummingbirds are my
favorite geese I love ducks this is this
is amazing okay do you want to get a
picture
yes okay sorry oh right here s it's okay
it's
okay this is incredible thank you okay
thank you I'm proud of you I wanted to
ask the spirit of compassion has a
message for me maybe just listen you a
lot of times you don't think you're
doing the right things in life okay and
you're and you're very difficult on
yourself just know that you are doing
good things okay keep on remember that
is that good are you going to take take
take this it's
mine
hey how are
you thank you for
coming did you travel far from yeah I
travel from Germany Germany but I came
from that's a long trip I have to get to
Germany see I I owe the favor I owe the
favor back and I need to go to Germany
well we want to invite you to the
compassionate Souls Festival next year
you never know next year you never know
you never know I mean I never thought
I'd be doing this right now okay let's
get a picture right
[Music]
here amazing thank you for coming coming
in there I hope you enjoy the food
okay hey what's going on
so good to meet you good to meet you too
um my daughter was so so sick and she
was in bed in mattress Island for years
and she's now getting better thanks to
your information I'm just like no words
can even explain I'm just so honored to
be able to meet you and to be here in
the Community Mat silent is is it's very
difficult to be be on and my heart pours
out to her okay because I know that and
people don't understand that they don't
know what it's like until they've
experienced it and I know that okay and
the whole world is going going and it's
very difficult and no no send my love
please I will tell her that I'm proud
I'm proud of her okay let's get right
there straight ahead
okay amazing thank you for coming okay I
hope you Eno oh you're
welcome what's going on how are you
thank you been the other two you the
other two yeah I recognize you do yeah
yeah thank you for coming my name is R I
thought I should thank you thank you for
everything you do I know what to say I
feel the same way for your support okay
I I I appreciate it any support that s
so and I get is is everything so and you
came here tonight did you how far did
you travel I'm from Germany oh my God
it's so worth it I would do it every
time that means the world to me it does
Straight
Ahead third photo is that our third
yeah
amazing what's going on hi I'm Tracy
nice dress nice dress thank you thank
you so much it's such an honor to meet
you has been life changing so I really
you've been doing the medical medium
stuff yes I've been drinking celery
juice for three or so years now 1 can't
drink it for a week it's a lot of water
some people can't drink it for a week
they can't they do it for a week and
then they stop and you're doing it for 3
years you have something inside of you
that says this is working this is it
feels amazing this is what I need yeah
yeah it's important I'm proud of you I'm
thank you I appreciate your work thank
[Music]
you could we take a
selfie oh okay we we'll do it this way
yeah he'll he'll get
okay thank you so much thank you Anthony
well enjoy yourself
tonight hey what's going on come over
here Michelle Michelle oh my God nice to
meet you nice L whoa pure fuel wion pure
maple
syrup can I answer some question sure
sure so what is your favorite color my
favorite color I don't have one favorite
color that's the problem what about I
have like three you know I like Maroon I
like that color right you know and so
yeah there's the other there's it it all
depends you know I like different I like
blue green you know there's different
colors I like but what's your favorite
color I like green you like Green do you
like Green like plants yeah that's
amazing let's get a pho all right
amazing thank you for coming I love all
animals oh my God and dogs I love I love
we love
them hey thanks for coming thank you
appreciate it thank you thank just
really want to I just want two things I
really want to say to you one is I just
really want to thank you for the hours
and hours and hours are you going to get
me to cry yeah the hours I've been doing
good tonight that you have sent and have
received this information and just like
in the books it all comes from all comes
from Spirit of compassion I write it
down and uh it's not easy I just want to
say thank you for all the hours that you
have sat there and received that
information for all of us and the and
that just means the word to me it's
received it's received and I want to
also say thank you so so much for all
the times that you have wanted to walk
away and all all the times that you have
wanted to say not no more but you have
hung in there and stay there so I'm I'm
super grateful for
[Music]
that and it means the world to me okay
please know that it does what is going
on what are you
doing are you having a good time yeah
okay is it okay
you give me a hug oh my
God thank you for coming you're welcome
I really appreciate it are you guys
having fun we are okay okay good good
thank you for everything but you got to
do some Acappella on the Fly tonight uh
I I music heals the soul I know I know
maybe we will be doing that soon then
okay want to get a photo you look
straight ahead here right okay you
guys all right here
one more
more amazing amazing oh wait do you want
to thank you for coming I hope you like
the food top of my heart than you for
you know that I hope you like the food
okay good
good oh
no what are you doing you know I love
your support okay you know that right
yeah I love all the information
I was oh this is for he was here
yesterday yeah I know of I you this
really yeah okay good good can I can I
hand it to Joel over
[Laughter]
[Music]
here well listen listen you know you can
just when you look at the books right
and you look at the adrenal information
you just you just have to say what is
what is right for me you can find it in
there it's there yeah you know right
yeah n you know
that all right let's get a pick right
here let's get a pick here he can grab
it and he's going take a little p
picture which can make it even better
he'll get a good one
[Laughter]
right
right you know I appreciate you right as
long as you know that for real I'm
supporting you I'm trying to get other
people him out of that won't that
weren't ever won't ever be believer
unless I like show that and I know that
you're like a fighter for me I swear to
God I'm a fighter for everyone did you
get tell me how to work I know you just
press that that's it once so just press
it yeah
ready
cheese that's better than a selfie one
all right you're the best thank you for
being here thank you thank you thank you
I'll take the water I'll drink it later
all
right hey good to see you good to to see
you thanks so much good to see you thank
you man love the earrings oh thank
you y yeah those are cool how are you
doing awesome thanks for coming you guys
you got did you travel far or not too
Faro an hour just an hour oh my God
doesn't get that around here I I do I do
I do yeah I live in a couple different
places but I spend a lot of time out
here I do I love it and I love it here
so you know if you guys come here ever
you might see me in here okay oh that's
cool what's your favorite snack favorite
snack hanging out at home yeah what are
you snacking on it all depends you know
got a lot of good
snacks I'm getting too many
[Music]
snacks amazing I love papaya I find that
as like a if I can get a good papaya
everything changes if I can get a good
one did you ever get a one that's not
good yeah yeah when I get a good papaya
that's a snack for me like nobody's
nobody's business thank you okay thank
you good to see you
okay hey what's going
on yeah yeah how are you how are you God
which year do I talk to talk to this
year here because so is talking to this
year and there's a lot going on and I'm
hearing a lot of information how are you
um I'm getting along but I wanted to ask
you um do I need like can I cure my skin
Cancers and my cataract do I need
cataract surgery well you know outside
of working with your doctors you add you
add the things that hit that that hit
you you add the things that you know
that that speak to you in the books okay
just just you know like what can I do
here and you look for that there's
information for that kind of thing in
there you have to find it I found and
then and then that along with the work
with doctors you're doing it you take
one day at a time okay let's get a
picture
do you remember Ela do you remember
Elisa my daughter yes really is that say
you remember yes
yes thank you so
[Music]
much and I love you for all your support
okay all right all right thank
you what's going on thank you for coming
thank you thank you for the work that
you do and uh really appreciate it I was
diagnosed 10 years ago I still have
never had it in Mission and I've can so
if you have anything you can share with
me that comes to
your you know you know the informations
in the books it's there right
um there there
are there when you when you look at it
does it come to you when you read the
books do you get the connection do you
get the information mean like does it
does it sing to you at all yeah of
course okay good good good there there
it's in there okay you're after tonight
you're going to you're going to find
that path okay you are I can tell cuz I
know just being here just us talking and
everything thank you so much I really
appreciate
[Music]
it I don't know where to
look yeah definitely okay we're going to
do light blast later I think so all that
will help thank
you okay he's with
you
Sor here got to come over here oh wait
it all depends
sorry thank you so much thank you thank
you thank
you hey what's going on
are nice to meet you okay good to see
you man look at you thank you for coming
you guys to come far I know it's we're
local we're so lucky that Los Angeles
all the events do you guys eat here at
all yes really this will be our third
time this will be your third time okay
good good wonderful well thanks for
coming let's get a picture together you
guys yeah wonderful come up here yeah oh
which this no no right here Straight
Ahead straight ahead you know you know
[Music]
[Applause]
amazing thanks guys get get yourself
comfortable okay enjoy
yourself
hey come over here oh my God how are you
how you been I've been good getting some
healing more nice nice you're working
hard I'm trying and it all counts it all
counts okay I just
need well can you just tell me something
just tell me something good today no I
mean of course you listen you have a lot
of purpose you know that
right cuz you doubt it a
lot don't make me you doubt it you got a
lot of purpose okay let's get a pick
Let's get a pick before I
forget right here
stra I'm proud of you listen you know
that all right so I want you to keep on
building up your your faith okay this
way hey what's going on it's been a year
oh my God thank you for coming
okay how things going
okay hair is falling out I'm still
trying to K my reproductive system it's
been 3 years what Isen any Improvement
not yet not yet you're working with all
your doctors too and no just just you
doing the medical medium stuff okay yes
well you take one day at a time right
and then you know and and the
information's there you know that yeah
so you have to customize it right right
there's a way to do it okay okay to get
the results you need yeah if you need to
ask your doctor to look at the books or
uh somebody to look at the books with
you and the strangest things happen
information seems to come down and and
there it is right in the book where
there uh energy and light comes down and
the books are there the information is
there yeah let's get a quick
one and you know I'm proud of you okay
this way thank
you what's going on how are you how are
you how are you doing so much better
each trip amazing I can't believe it and
you're here now oh my god let's get a
picture together okay here we'll come up
here a little bit
okay amazing did you try the food yet no
no this the first time you saf me thank
you you're going to get me choked
up oh okay that's good I like
that that's amazing I love the hat okay
thank you I love wearing it actually
well every day every night it's a great
honor all right you want to get a
picture so it's a good be here again no
thank you amazing came for the third
time already
go I was going to say it's it been three
times yeah it has do you remember well
yeah of course really but it was
Calabasas right but you were the June
15th too cuz that's where you got the
house yeah yeah thank you for coming and
thank you for your support okay thanks
so much for doing that for us it means a
lot to me means the world I hope you
enjoy the food thank you
what's going on huh what you going on
good to see you I'm proud of you you
know that
right always proud of you yeah right you
look good so you you know so how long
youve been in town now uh here I just
got here yesterday just got here
yesterday thank you for coming you know
course and you keep on working on your
healing process I know you're very you
know diligent and you're
committed you know I got the wisdom you
got a strong Soul a very strong Soul
what is my purpose what is your purpose
you have your purpose I have my purpose
get a quick phot here let's get a
listen spirit Spirit compassion tells me
if you don't have just one
purpose Spirit tells me that you have
more than one purpose
okay yeah you have more than one okay
you have multiple and that's how you
have to think don't think about just
your purpose you have to have the
realization that it's a lot more it's
you have many you have multiple purpose
and that and that's very very that's
very powerful okay
okay you know I love
you thank you for coming this time you
it was those light cards it was the
cards it was the cards you know I love
you I love you too
what's going on still thank you for
everything thank you for being here
changing my life and I know you will
continue to be so well you're doing the
work though remember you're doing the
work I can only do so much okay so
you're my hero you're doing the work and
that matters to me greatly right you
are thank you for being so
courageous for doing everything that
you've done for all of us well keep keep
up everything that you're doing keep
onun moving forward okay keep a light
heart okay well come over
here right straight ahead
okay amazing thank you so much enjoy
tonight okay I'll see you thank you
what's going
on strong
handshake he how are you doing good
thank you guys for coming your skin is
so pretty your skin is so
pretty it's all the exfoliations I don't
do I know I talk about that it's funny I
thought it would make you laugh I ask
you one question tell me what's going on
um I just okay it's for Spirit can I ask
it shoot okay we only got a second
though um
um all right
here let's get you're going to make me
laugh okay okay she wants to know how to
Spirit know
what two more how's Spirit know what
food tastes
like is that the question oh my God
you're the first that's ever asked how
does he know if he's not like how does
he
know I've asked as SOC thousands upon
thousands of questions okay and um he
knows
okay okay okay I'll talk about it you
know what I'll do I'll talk about it
soon
okay hey what's going on come on over
here I don't know what to say to you hi
thank you so much for everything um
you're welcome you're welcome changed my
life you know I I but I know that I can
only do so much I was saying that
earlier and if I'm changing your life
that means you're doing the other half
I'm trying to get the info to you and
you're doing it so think about that how
powerful that is that you're you're
using your free will to do the healing
okay that's tough I I I can't take the
credit I can't you're doing you're doing
too much you're doing all the work okay
thank you
I would like to take the
credit but between so and the work
you're doing that's that's
incredible what's going
on are nice to see you good to see you
you're working hard on your healing I am
you are I guess I mean I'm not 100% all
the time it's hard to do that it's not
easy to be 100% it's not easy you know
you can only you know every day life
brings us things and then we just try to
push through and it's hard to take care
of ourselves at the same time okay but
but I know that you're trying and you're
working on it you are actually Spirit of
compassion tell me you're working on
[Music]
it amazing so proud of you okay you know
that
right so good to see you where's your
guy could but he wants me to tell you
that he loves you and that he really
hates tell him I love him okay and I'm
proud of him he knows that though yeah
he knows that okay when I told him it
completely melted his car it was like
wonderful to watch you Tak oh you got
out of the house and you got here you're
on the red
carpet it's amazing okay did I wanted I
didn't get to tell you last time but I
just wanted to quickly tell you that
every effort that I make and that I've
ever made to be here with you
thank you for taking the trip
[Music]
seriously rata I hope you enjoy the food
have you tried it yet okay okay I hope
you like it
okay what's going on to see you again
great to see you too apping your info
for eight years and I'm seven years in
the clear Earth cancer so and now I help
other
people and they are very lucky they're
very lucky that you are helping them
that you are using all your knowledge
your experience thank you and you're you
know like gracious and generous by
helping others okay and just know I
appreciate it thank right I appreciate
you helping others and I appreciate the
experience you have and what you've been
through and all of it and and and you
got this incredible credible work that
you're doing okay I love you for it I
love you for thank you so much it really
means the
world thank you so much for everything
very proud thank
you hey what's going on you got a book
yes you're amazing you're an amazing
human being you're an amazing person
thank you for all you do I wish I was
amazing but you're more amazing for
getting here getting here working on
your healing and wait a minute and
reading this yeah it's it's a big one
people don't know how bad you read all
this it's a Bible my husband it's it is
a Bible it's a health Bible can you put
it to Ben can you just put Ben yes and
David that'd be
awesome and David and Aaron and Aaron
yes and r i n they they think that you
should call it cleanse in order to heal
so we call it C I will I take that
seriously a way life and I cannot thank
you enough bless your heart okay you
thank you send my love to them okay I
will
[Music]
will amazing and right there
okay you got it cannot thank you enough
cannot thank you enough love you much
you're awesome I love you you're you're
amazing thank
you what's going on how are you thanks
for coming this is my third time over
the last three years it's the third I've
been to the last three you been the last
oh my God that's incredible okay I
wasn't sure if it was all of them but I
cuz I recognize you thank you for coming
again okay mean means a lot to me I I
seriously because you know you could
have just gone to one but you're here
thank you thank you thank you oh my gosh
how are you doing me yes I I am doing I
am doing amazing great because I'm
around people that care I'm around
people that have
compassion um around people that
understand you know so much season they
know how the world of Health Works and
I'm not in it alone okay so I'm very
blessed very blessed here let's take a
picture
okay amazing thank you I hope you enjoy
the food come this way is this your guy
yes
here's the pen that they want oh okay
okay oh we got a we got a pen yeah
that's yeah do you like this book this
is a good one that was the first one
that my wife and I read to each other
really it was celery juice book amazing
just written it was like 5 and a half
years ago started it's been a while it's
been a long time yeah I'm proud of you
let's get a picture together
sure amazing thanks for coming and I
hope you enjoy yourself
tonight what's going on hey how are you
doing great thank you so much for
everything you do oh bless your heart
seriously thank you for the support
thank you for the support and everything
okay oh thank you thank you let's get a
picture I love the
hat right here
amazing have you tried the food yet not
yet no okay well tonight tonight is
going to be so
[Music]
good what's going on look at you events
if you recognize me I oh you do thank
you for coming again seriously course um
thank you so much I've healed from so
many things TMJ pain all that stuff
still trying to heal a spine injury but
I am a nurse coach and I now use your
information to heal others that's a
great honor okay you're a nurse coach
you're using the
information you know for others to heal
I I nothing there nothing more important
than that okay so I I treasure that
thank you okay thank you that's amazing
well let's get a photo together
awesome
okay I know it's getting towards the end
thank you so much for talking to us all
you look familiar I'm Kelly Jo Kelly Joe
Kelly
Joe how's your family doing okay are
they doing okay do you want me to sign
this for you yes please I have a couple
random questions for you do you have a
favorite meal a favorite meal yeah like
when you're at your birthday or whatever
yeah that's a really good point let me
see if I can think of it usually because
things have been so crazy for so long
I'm basically standing in the kitchen
just eating a potato yeah you I don't
think I've sat down to eat in in 3
years okay my other question is do Quil
eggs feed
viruses like chicken
eggs quail eggs yeah they don't but it
doesn't mean they don't as much they
don't as much oh but they do a little
all depends on where they came from what
they were like what they were fed like
all these
things it's not a straight answer like
black and
[Music]
white remember I mentioned it remember I
mentioned the quail eggs no well
somebody told me they were safety and I
was like I've never heard him say that
they're safer if you're going to have if
you want an egg
okay pleasure to meet you hey pleasure
to meet you too amazing thank you for
coming thank you oh you got a book for
me I do thank thank
you oh
wonderful awesome thank you thank you
appreciate it I appreciate want to get a
picture I definitely do where am I going
[Music]
you amazing thanks for coming I hope you
enjoy yourself
tonight what's going on you got a 3M is
that an n95 I do I do
sorry no no don't be that's great I just
was in the hospital a week and a half
ago oh yeah no thank you no no but thank
you because you put out a post about Lo
sodium that's why I oh my God the low
sodium post literally the day got oh my
God thank you so much oh bless your
heart do you want to get a
picture thank you for coming I hope you
enjoy yourself I really do some good
food coming yes absolutely
nice to see you again good to see you
again okay you know I'm you know like I
can't believe this is happening I am
Star Struck okay I am you have to
understand something I don't take this
lightly I'm uh a very shy person
sometimes all right so this is a big
deal for me all right twins we even got
the same
man that's why I'm going it out you know
I like the North Face stuff okay you
know that you're me I'm trying to be
like
[Music]
you trying to you trying to grow your
hair long in the back you're trying to
get a man bun there yeah you inspire me
North Face the everything you know you
know I love you man love you to what's
going on to meet you meet you I just
want to say you have helped so many
people you have helped my mother um
overcome so much and it's just I'm so
grateful for you and for your brain and
your knowledge so thank you uh can you
tell where I said hi yes I will thank
you okay many blessings thank you I will
all right amazing do you want to take a
picture together please if we
could incredible are you going to enjoy
the food tonight awesome
awesome what is going on I told I one
day asked me a question but I didn't
want the cameras to hear oh well no well
we're you know we're miked up
here I don't know if I have an
answer come
on okay if I'm if I'm meant to be then
you have to introduce us okay
[Music]
okay you're amazing have you been here
in this in this place before Cafe
Gratitude it's an incredible Place
incredible food how long you been doing
mm since 2016 dabbling oh my God I'm
going to give you a double shake okay
2016 thank you all right thank you for
everything your you're amazing thank
you hell again again my girlfriend had
an extra ticket she couldn't make thank
you for coming how's the music going
music's going awesome you remember
what's your favorite instrument guitar
probably that's amazing any any messages
from Spirit of compassion from me always
proud of you okay you need to know that
because sometimes you get an insecurity
in the
past spirit says and you don't know but
you're doing good stuff all the time all
right light
heart cuz you believe believe in
everything you do but then sometimes you
lose a little confidence no no no no
you're the best at what you do okay
right this way man' this
way hey I love the hair man incredible
thanks for coming I appreciate you man
about 10 years been watching stuff
posting on Facebook just helping me
learn about fruits and vegetables all
the healing qualities so thank you so
much hey that's music to my ears I mean
that's a decade and and you've been
doing the stuff and you've been looking
into it that's incredible oh yeah
healing a lot so I'm proud of you man
I'm proud of you let's get a pick all
right amazing you're going to have good
food tonight with us absolutely all
right thank you brother have a good
night you
too what's happening so much for
everything that you've done for me hey
man I'm honored you know that right I am
thank you for coming tonight okay it's a
big deal to me well it's a big deal to
me too likewise you help me through all
the you know
homelessness um you know serious skin
conditions and just the worst insomnia
F say I love you for that man I love you
for doing the work okay okay cuz it
takes two takes me takes you takes
really Spirit I'm just a messenger but
then it takes you okay you're doing the
work don't underestimate that you're
you're strong man you're strong so how
do I help others you're doing it
okay amazing you know I love you brother
this way sir love you too
anony what's going
on look at you time see good to see you
let's get a pick Let's get a pick
[Applause]
[Music]
amazing took a nice long trip here you
made it things are going good thank you
for coming seriously thank you thank you
I'm going
to thank you for everything seriously
I'm honored okay and honored for all
that you're doing know I'm proud of you
all right keep up all the good work all
right all
right you're the best you're the best
I'll see you I'll see you yeah he needs
one more photo oh come on got
this got I got my ex that's what it is
you're going to be over
here thank you yeah I'm instructed I
have to be on that a yeah you got to
stay
there amazing amazing very well very
very well here we go oh you
got C
thank you so much for coming out this
evening we kindly ask that you take a
seat because the first course is just
about to be served so if you kindly take
a seat we can get started this is very
exciting the first course looks
delicious and it's on its way out right
now everyone that it is serve family
style just so that they're aware okay
okay great and I'd like to quickly
remind everyone that this dinner will be
served family style so please please
enjoy have a seat and we'll get ready to
bring you that family style dinner
[Applause]
[Music]
I e
[Applause]
know
don't
[Music]
[Applause]
I'll you
us
[Applause]
don't
spe
[Music]
so e
that's
just don't
[Music]
my my
you
[Applause]
I
[Music]
okay
this
time
[Applause]
around e
how long do you
[Music]
sushi
rolls sush
rolls how's everybody doing over here
you guys are
okay
really
incredible it's a it's this is a
legendary
restaurant okay it's a legendary
restaurant and they have medical medium
dishes think about
that I mean right it's
historic it
is what's going on you
guys this is the Rowdy Bunch right here
this is the oh my
God
unbelievable you guys I appreciate
everything seriously thank you for being
here and the food's good right okay all
right that matters that matters
incredible you guys that's the Rowdy
gang in there man don't go in there
don't go in there what's going on guys
how's everything over here Christian how
you doing great oh good my brother good
my brother you know I love you how's it
going over here you guys all
right amazing amazing amazing you guys
oh my God Lauren Scott CHS Kim Chels
amazing these guys are family these are
family of mine right here they've
they've had my back for many years and
and they're here
tonight
um are you guys getting stuffed yet or
no because there's more food coming
there there's more food all right so
just pace yourself how about that that's
what I do all right but you guys know I
eat a little fast I'm always working and
I just shove it down which is bad I know
that's bad bad way to do but not tonight
tonight we relax and we take our time
right and we're we're with people oldest
Souls out there I'm telling you the
medical medum community the oldest Souls
they really are so you guys are here you
guys are anyway enjoy yourself okay this
is amazing amazing a lot of you guys
came from far away I know and I just
want to just say thank you and if you
came an hour away incredible okay
incredible but um I know people traveled
all over the world Germany there's a lot
of there's a lot of people from Germany
in here here right
now it's it's amazing when I think about
that that's amazing well you guys enjoy
keep you know keep on eating right and
I'll be back and um I'll do a little
talk all right a little
talk we'll see we'll see what comes from
Spirit of compassion
tonight I never prepare it's just
whatever whatever happens God God help
us anyway I love you guys all right
all right you guys doing good all
right amazing
amazing incredible
hey love you guys
to
wasn't
until I started to
[Music]
you time
spe
very
[Applause]
[Music]
I for
don't
[Applause]
every
can
you
been for
now
come
hope e
[Music]
NE
you
[Applause]
tell
don't
[Music]
you e
to yeah I
[Applause]
don't e
you're
[Music]
you
[Applause]
to
for
[Music]
[Applause]
e
for for
[Music]
you
actually
tell you
[Music]
and
the
to
[Applause]
think
[Music]
[Applause]
why
my
[Music]
for for
[Applause]
[Music]
the carpet here it's now Night 2 how do
you feel everything's going for this
incredible popup dinner event
it's going amazing you know I I was
wondering what would night two be like
and it's just it's incredible it's
unbelievable it's um you know you can
feel the energy you can feel the light
you can feel the love it's all there so
it just doesn't get any better than this
it doesn't no it's incredible the energy
here tonight has been unbelievable what
is it that makes medical medium food
different you know it's it's missing
something that's what makes it different
it's missing something it's missing a
lot of things and I know there's a lot
of talk out there about food and
chemicals and things and you know and
and pesticides and but people don't
realize in the health movement yet
they're they're not there as advanced
the medical medium information is so
Advanced they don't know about the
citric acid they don't know about the
natural flavor so much you know mm info
broke that information out years and
years and years ago and um and and so
what medical medium food is missing is
all those things it's missing the corn
it's
missing it's missing too many nuts and
that's the thing like yeah nuts are good
for us in different ways but too many
nuts you know it's just nuts everybody's
on all these so it's missing the soy
which I've talked about all this time
everybody said hey soy's you know you
got to look out for GMO soy it's like no
you got to look out for all of it you
know you have to look out for all of it
and the dishes here and this is what's
incredible about Cafe grish at itude is
that they've taken the medical medium
dishes and recipes and they've elevated
it and they it's unbelievable how pure
how clean how you don't have to worry
you don't have to say what's in here you
don't have to say wait what is this or
what is that it's that it's that
wonderful it really is oh it it really
is and I've heard you talk about how the
chronically ill are not respected can
you talk a little bit more about that I
mean the chronically ill have been swept
under the carpet for ages it they just
have been um they've been ignored
they've been told they're lazy they've
been told that they're they're not
really sick and even though the industry
is changing in the health world where
they're recognizing um conditions and
they're recognizing symptoms more and
you know there's some good people good
professionals working in the health
field it's still not enough The Chronic
chronically ill are still disrespected
they're still not listened to enough
they're still not understood they're
seen as a bank roll too uh that's
another thing in the health industry now
so you know it's it's it's all about you
know likes and clicks and everything and
I understand that's how the industry
works but the chronically ill you know
you have to look out for them you have
to care about them and that's not there
you know it's like yeah people are sick
they're suffering and struggling sure
right but we need to care and we need to
look out for them and really focus on
like what's best for them and that's
been my entire Mission it's about what's
best for the chronically ill what do
they really need what can really protect
them and and keep them safe with all the
different obstacles and the pitfalls out
there and the snares and the tiger traps
they're there and they're there for
people who are healthy enough now but
everybody's getting sick everybody and
when people think they're not going to
get sick how do you think we end up
leaving this planet we get sick
somewhere somehow down the line and so
yeah it may be a little later for
someone it may be a little later for
this person but everybody becomes
chronically ill at some point eventually
so we should respect a chronically ill
when we're not sick because we need to
understand what they're what what
they're doing to heal what they're doing
to move forward because that's precious
information that other people can use
that aren't sick now but then they run
across somebody in their family or a
friend that gets sick and they can have
this powerful information and and
actually you know spread this
information with the chronic ill for
years been called like liars and and
they're lazy and they're you know
they're not really sick and they're
making it up it's all in their head or
they're just bored or something or
they're just neurotic or have some kind
of phobia when really they got sick they
got real reasons There's real reasons
underneath there inside their body
that's why they're struggling and
anything like OCD or PTSD that comes
later for a lot of people who are sick
it's from being sick too long it's not
respected it's not people are not
appreciated they're um and that should
change and I think medical medium
information and the mission is to help
The Chronic leel and to change that to
change that narrative out there that's
out you know that's happening to the
sick people who are struggling and we
need to do something about it and this
is an incredible step right here we're
at Cafe GR they have the the best meals
they're using the medical medium
information they're putting the meals
together in a way that's never been done
before so it doesn't get any better yeah
it's incredible you're talking about the
medical medium information so why is it
that so many people are healing I've
talked to them tonight and I do have to
thank you as well because that kindness
and compassion that you have for them
it's just I I feel that when I talk to
them so thank you for that and why are
they hearing from this information you
know I've been a messenger this whole
time and I get my information from above
I hear a voice perfectly clear and that
voice has provided Advanced Medical
information that are in the medical
medium book series and I know that P
everybody thinks they're a genius in the
health movement right now okay and
they're all working with biohacks and
everything but when you put those
biohacks to the test with somebody who's
chronically ill and been down and out on
mattress Island it only makes them worse
this information's different it gets
people from mattress Island where
they're spending 20 hours 22 hours
sometimes 24 hours a day where they're
stuck on mattress Island they're stuck
in bed at home or on couch Island on the
couch and the mm information they can
take somebody for Mattress Island take
them out of a wheelchair and move them
forward last night we had like a half a
dozen people minimum like half a dozen
people that got out of wheelchairs they
were walking they walked here last night
right down this red carpet into the
restaurant and they couldn't do it any
other way it it's this information that
I'm messaging and that's what you know
sets it apart yeah it's incredible there
stories from people being in wheelchairs
now being able to fly here enjoy this
dinner meet you in person and say thank
you it's just incredible yeah that's a
big deal it really is and when you can't
get out of the house and you've been
sick a long time and then you finally
heal and now you're flying on a plane
and now you're here forget meeting me
just taking the trip is the is huge huge
so big and and people are doing it and
they're healing and moving forward so
just nothing better really it's so
amazing it's such a celebration here
tonight night two we're going to head
back inside and check out this amazing
four course medical medium a medical
medium dinner oh amazing I'm I'm so
hungry looking at all that food I'm
hungry too yeah amazing thank
[Applause]
you for
[Music]
girl
he
need
[Music]
look
spe
never
a
think
people
[Music]
know
[Applause]
can you hear us audio when we talk oh
there is okay
[Music]
[Applause]
I never really met
someone it was
always you know it's healing you you
know it's moving
it still holds it still holds a mon ago
two months
ago your body knows this and and it
holds it's okay okay I'm proud of you I
am your body's healing and you take one
day at a
time e
[Music]
on yourself and have
compassion all right are you enjoying
your
meal you had
it I
of
[Music]
m
I know well yeah
[Music]
want
she
[Applause]
prob
we are back inside Cafe Gratitude we're
going to check out this four course
medical medium dinner and we've got some
guests here are you enjoying this
food what a treat I mean how lucky we
are this is re I can't say that word
revolutionary to have mm dishes at Cafe
Gratitude we're so grateful for this
collaboration it's amazing yeah the
dishes are so amazing so good we really
enjoying you know having the freedom to
sit down at a restaurant and and have no
worri so it's it's a real triat we're
going to have to come to La more
often I think you should can you show us
a little bit of the food that you are
eating here what dishes do we have out
the
front go ahead right now we have we have
here the portabella pajitas with uh bell
peppers and red onions and then they
made a m tortilla so you can make tacos
and it came with guacamole and it came
with h p
deallo and uh with uh what else it came
so you could make a whole t
yes amazing Taco there yes but healthy
version healthy healing food at a
restaurant how about that concept right
yeah it's brilliant uh what was your
favorite dish so far that you've tried
on the menu uh the
sushi and this actually the papaya salad
and the
sushi sushi is I mean delicious and the
papaya salad really really refreshing
like the blend of spice was just perfect
you have to come and try it people try
it it's amazing what were your two
favorite or favorite dish or true
favorite well I I honestly I like all of
the food cuz it's very different and the
profile so if you you like more like the
Mexican side you can make tacos and
that's amazing they were really good I'm
from Mexico so I can say they're very
good so yeah no I I like which one are
your favorite I guess the
were was one of my favorite yes what did
you think of the Millet uh tortilla I
was very surprised because M it I
thought the tortillas were going to be
you know they're going to be hard not
not soft to make a real taco and I was
blown away actually would love to you
know know how to make those tortillas
cuz they they're amazing yes really good
have you gotten to the Smoothie yet have
they brought out the IR am precious no
will be there
cherry on top I mean the
dessert are there cherries in that
actually uh no wait wait wait wait yeah
cherries yes so you knew it's a cherry
on top that dessert yes it's a cherry on
top oh wow well thank you so much for
talking to us this looks incredible it's
making me even more hungry okay yes okay
thank you so much thank you we have some
more people to talk to about their
dining experience here hello hi hi I'm
sorry you're still eating we surprise
you there I'm I'm Danielle hi M nice to
meet you so nice to meet you could you
share with us what you are eating at the
moment so I'm having the fajitas with a
millet tortilla and some roasted
potatoes and everything is delicious and
beautiful do you have a favorite dish
that you've tried so far yes I love okay
I love the kelp noodles I was
very did you like the kelp as well it
was really good yeah delicious very
pleasantly surprised had like a nice
citrusy flavor I was kind of like
looking at the menu to see cuz I want to
try to recreate it um but yeah it was
amazing I don't know what Mauna is but I
want to find out it was really good yeah
that's so cool that you want to recreate
this at home oh absolutely yeah I mean I
that's kind of the fun of coming to a
place besides getting to meet Anthony of
course is getting to try dishes that are
medical medium friendly and then you
know recreate it at home and have that
um yeah with your loved ones so yeah now
did you know any of this lovely
Community before you arrived this
evening we just met each other we all
just met each other um I actually was
following her on Instagram natural naen
so yeah it's fun I've been meeting a lot
of seeing a lot of people that I follow
that in the medical medium Community
here so that's been really fun to like
see the faces that you know and love and
follow for advice um so yeah it's been
an amazing experience so far and do you
enjoy connecting with the Community as
well totally yeah absolutely now what
was your favorite dish um I would say it
is the fita with the mushrooms and
peppers this is my 14 a row eating it so
yeah it's good I just I keep talking
about it but I loved the Millet tortilla
I was so it's so good yeah it's
amazing and what about you over here
what was your favorite meal sushi rolls
sushi rolls with the dipping sauce oh
yes no soy sauce no soy sauce and it
tasted amazing everything was amazing
the the kelp noodles burst of
flavors different textures different
flavors amazing all of it's amazing and
for the people eating at home we what do
we have here on the table oh my God
watching at home I said eating at home
but they're watching at home here's the
bejitas the mushroom bejitas with the
onions the milet tortillas which to die
for amazing amazing hold up together
well like they're not soggy they're
great I know I was so surprised when I
was eating those on Friday night I put
one together and I was like this is
great it held up so well yes
absolutely yes yes and what about this
guacamole here guacamole oh my gosh
delicious was that next level yes yes
the guac was Next Level everything yes
um potatoes I think there's like some
cheese on the potatoes some type of
cheese sauce is great and then the beans
that are
spicy we had the IM am Nal earlier this
evening gosh it's really good those
potatoes Next Level yeah all of this
just like next level all this at
home I'm just so excited that
restaurants are adopting medical medium
food and it's becoming slowly more and
more mainstream and like cuz my dream is
that one day I can just leave my house
and buy medical medium prepared food
like wherever I go cuz you know it's it
takes a lot of time and it's a labor of
love but so one day I see a world where
you can get medical medium friendly food
everywhere you go just like fast food
you know so amazing if we had a drive
through medical medium
food yes that but in the maintime you
could just make some trips to Los
Angeles have a bit of a a Weekender here
and come to Cafe Gratitude absolutely
yeah of course yeah well thank you so
much for sharing your experience and
your meals we're going to go around the
table over here oh we got some more
people over here okay we're going to
make our way through the through through
the here
oops over to this over to this table
hello I'm reunited again with you hello
lovely to see you you at the Culver City
oh not Culver City the Calabasas event I
was at both at both yes and I saw you at
Calabasas yes you did yes you did so we
wanted to just find out you know if
you'd like to share with us what you're
eating where are we up to in the in the
dinner menu here of course so we're
eating the the Millet uh Pell tacos I
think that's what it's called Uh the
fajitas incredible Inc just like clean
ingredients I haven't been to a
restaurant in like
years um it's just incredible experience
with Incredible Souls so you haven't
been to a restaurant in years you were
saying and this is your first time out
eating at a restaurant enjoying this
meal what a what a beautiful moment
exactly I mean most of the time I would
bring my own food you know make my own
food and and do it and have my family
like what is that what are you eating
and uh yeah like this is it's clean it's
light you know it I don't I don't feel
bad and uh it's just it's just great
it's it's a blessing to have like man
this this restaurant is incredible and
I'm I'm from Florida so like I've never
been to Cafe Gratitude before and
um just really grateful yeah a lot of
gratitude going around this evening for
sure for sure what was your favorite
dish off the menu Pro probably the the
sushi oh okay the sushi was so good yeah
and what was your favorite dish the
sushi I think if you or papaya salad if
you ask anybody here I think the the
sushi was I I don't want to talk for
them but yeah for you yes and can you
imagine going out to eat and eating
healing foods
do you feel good right now oh yeah
yeah yeah and what about you over here
we'll move
around a this is this is extra special
for me because I've been doing um no
overt fats for 5 years and so that means
no a avocado no pumpkin no nuts no seeds
um or coconut milk or anything like that
so I got to celebrate tonight and
actually have this meal and it's so
flavorful so
delicious um yeah it's a wonderful
celebration on multiple levels so were
you able to have a little bit of the
guacamole which one did you have a
little bit of the avocado yeah to
celebrate my my 5 years yeah it's
beautiful and what was your your
favorite dish to sa um I actually really
like the green papaya and kelp noodle
salad I thought it was really delicious
I love the like flavor profile of it um
also the sushi is amazing so
yeah beautiful and you're a local so you
can come back to Cafe Gratitude now and
and enjoy this menu I will definitely be
back I'm already planning it yeah thank
you so much for talking to us we have
another table up here we're going to
visit I don't know if you can hear the
background noise but everyone is just
having so much fun talking connecting
this beautiful Community it really is
such a fun night hello hello now what
are you eating here or what are you
finishing up here this was the burrito
bowl and the fajitas wow the spices were
so good so like it was mild and it was
hot it was really very ta very tasty
it's fantastic and the kale was well
done the guacamole I mean he was reeving
about the
guacamole yeah every the guacamole is
almost gone over there yeah
yeah it it was really great
presentation great flavor
what a collaboration they had together
it was great do you have a favorite dish
can you pick one from all of those it
would definitely be the burrito bowl it
just was so fa I mean the flavor was
just amazing it was great I it
everything was well done and the sushi
was fabulous in the beginning I mean he
was raving about it too yeah spectacular
every thish was just was awesome and you
know being conscious that it's clean has
that bonus it makes it taste even better
so it's awesome what was your favorite
probably I wasn't expecting but probably
the sushi probably the sushi and the
Burrito Boy Burrito Boy was a close
second though they're both
amazing really good lovely yeah
delicious and we're going to get some
more reactions over here before you take
that bite of beautiful food what did you
think of the meal oh it was delicious
thank you are we getting a bite on
camera there are
you well what was your favorite meal oh
it's hard to
say they're all just so good so tasty
right yeah yeah incredible incredible is
everyone else enjoying the evening are
you enjoying the evening yes it's been
an incredible evening I've been so lucky
to be able to talk to Anthony and have a
good conversation cuz of both both
previous times that I came um I was so
like hyper and so excited that I
wouldn't let him talk I would be like hi
Anthony I love you Anthony thank you
Anthony you changed my life so I
wouldn't stop talking and this time I'm
like Anthony I'm not going to make you
laugh this time I want to have a
conversation he's like you made me laugh
and I said yes last time I was so hyper
he was like oh and so he said a whole
bunch of
really like he knows you you know and um
oh God now I'm going to cry but yeah it
hit me like he said he said like thank
you he said I'm proud of you
it really it really like it just makes
you keep on wanting to go and keep
sharing the information yeah it's
beautiful I feel like it's like he
really sees you he does he sees
everybody he knows everybody and he
knows everything that everybody is going
through and so yeah he even asked me if
I was okay cuz he knew it's like I know
he knew what was happening with
me H yeah anyway I better stop cuz I'll
cry oh it's emotional evening do you
have here a favorite dish we could ask
you about yes the
sushi the sushi was like I cuz I don't
even like sushi but this Sushi was like
incredible so you don't like sushi but
you you love this Sushi this Sushi was
amazing yes amazing like I I could have
just had sushi and I would have been
happy and then I feel like there was so
many other amazing dishes as well they
were all delicious like I can't say that
they were but my favorite was the sushi
yeah a stand out a standout go all the
way from Atlanta to to be here and enjoy
this so I'm I am enjoying every single
one I see you guys are making your way
through it you're doing well doing a
great job and then the Smoothie is going
to be coming out soon yes I I have room
for the smoothie I did I kept room for
that I'm going to enjoy it do you feel
good yes after eating it no issues no
bloating no like gassiness like you
don't feel any of this you're just happy
and no indigestion
I mean I don't know have you tried this
food oh yes we ate we ate the I Am Noble
this evening I've tried the I am
trustworthy but I'm yet to try the kelp
noodles the I amys I need to try that
they're very refreshing I feel like if
it was summer I would love them more um
but yeah but still Sushi I also tried
the I am precious so I know that you're
in for a treat with that dessert it is
oh it's so good can't wait I can't wait
thank you thank you so much for chatting
to us we're going to walk this
way do we have another table to talk to
or we wrapping up we're going one
more
okay okay we're going to keep going to
another
table where are we heading soon's going
to be starting oh that's a wrap up okay
actually I thought we were going to
another table but as you can hear it's
craziness in here it is such an amazing
energetic room full of beautiful people
call but Anthony is going to be back
with us soon aw will be uh talking to
everyone with a lecture and a life blast
so make sure you stay tuned for that
[Applause]
this
and
you
[Applause]
think
[Music]
for for
[Applause]
[Music]
I
[Applause]
[Music]
like for
[Applause]
you
w e
[Applause]
you
[Music]
[Applause]
Happ
okay
[Applause]
back
I
[Applause]
[Music]
to
hi baby
[Music]
[Applause]
,000 that's how I roll
told me she
[Applause]
[Music]
you I hope I'm getting the Rea
[Applause]
[Music]
you
[Applause]
you guys ready for a
little there's a lot of energy in here
tonight this
is yeah this is the Rowdy Crow
[Music]
[Applause]
you know I was thinking this morning
when I got up really
early and I was thinking about the earth
going around the
Sun and how you know we're all on the
Earth right now going around the Sun
okay how incredible that
is and then I was thinking
about how is it possible that we're on
the Forefront of time right now right
this is the present moment of time every
second that clicks forward we in it
together think about that a little
bit how many civilizations have come and
gone right why are we here altto
together doing medical medium
information you know healing how are we
all in here in this restaurant this
beautiful incredible restaurant together
right now with all the civilizations
that have come and
gone think about that one billions of
people have come and
gone
billions throughout the
years but we're here on the Forefront of
time right
now and that then leads me to something
Spirit of compassion has always told me
is
we come back if you're okay with that
one I know some people are like no you
don't come back you're just you're here
and then you're gone and that's it I
actually know it's
different I actually know it's
different and the information I get is
we're always on that Forefront of time
so we're back but we're right here
together now is it a coincidence we're
all here together tonight no way no way
it's not possible it's
not and I noticed in the medical medium
community and I've said this before that
there's really old souls here okay
you've heard that before you've heard
that right maybe you saw somebody maybe
you saw an intuitive and they're like
you're an old
soul and people talk about that but the
people in this community really are old
souls there's a lot of reasons there's a
len tested for that there's reasons to
believe that you guys are old souls so
if you ever doubt it you're like I don't
know how old of a soul I really
am but you really are one of those
reasons to believe that you're a really
old soul is that you guys are brave you
found this information and something
spoke to you whether it's Angelic forces
Supernatural forces I hear the book just
landed on somebody's lap one day maybe
it was in a doctor's office on a coffee
table maybe a friend just said try this
maybe it was in a store somewhere but
there's a
supernatural connection to how that book
got to you or that information got to
you it's much different than anything
else out there in the world of Health
you talk to other people out there and
it's like yeah I saw some ad on social
media and I'm trying this bioh hack and
that's what it is but that's not how the
medical medium information works or the
people that Discover it how it works
it's an entirely different situation
when you ask people how did you find out
well I found out through my loved one
how did they find out well you know what
they were in a store and it spoke to
them and they saw it on the shelf and it
spoke to them it fell off the shelf
someone told me years
ago that the medical medium book fell
off the shelf right in front of them in
Barnes & Noble they were just walking
down the aisle they weren't even looking
for a health
book they were sick but they weren't
even in there doing that they were
cutting through the aisle and as they
were cutting through the book just
nudged itself off the shelf they watched
it and it landed on the ground face up
they picked it up and they said what is
this and who is
this they held on to it they read
it and they realized it saved their life
it saved their life and they're an old
soul now a lot of times I've said this
I'm not the oldest soul I was given this
gift yes you guys know about it you guys
know and you probably get a lot of
for it too you listen to the medical
medium you you read his
stuff right I never knew when I was four
years old that it would give a lot of
people but my great grandfather he
knew and my parents they knew they're
still
alive trying to convince my dad to go on
to a podcast someday with me and I
actually think he's going to do
it and and my
mom
but there's something to be said about
that you know it's it's you have to have
a bigger Consciousness to do medical
medium so you have to be an older
Soul right you just
do because the information blows your
mind it's blown my mind right when I
heard the information from above my mind
was blown when I did the last books the
brain saer books it was too much almost
on me because I was like what every
sentence was like what
but I've always said I'm not the oldest
soul I just have something inside of me
the spirit of compassion said you'll do
you'll
do you might you might not be the oldest
Soul the people who will receive this
information are going to be old souls
you might not be the oldest Soul they'll
be thousands of years older than you for
sure but you got something inside of you
and we need that
you got something kind of tough about
you like
really I'm that
tough tough enough to hear the voice and
hang in there stay sane you know and and
through that process you know message
message and message but that's only a
part of it it's nothing without you guys
it's nothing it is I could be in my own
little room somewhere getting the
information from above receiving it
learning about it and in the end what
does that do if I can't get it out to
you guys you know I think what happens
when an author and I forget I'm an
author I actually forget because in the
end I'm not writing the
books it's coming from above it's
prophecies it's Advanced information so
really am I even an author probably not
but on the book it says
so
right but if I didn't have the ability
to get this information out there and I
remember when my
publisher okay they were like yeah we we
want you we we want to help people I
couldn't believe it couldn't believe it
we want to get the message out because
we've never seen anything like this and
I was like oh my God there is a God
there is because I could just be sitting
in my
room right scribbling the information on
papers and piling them up and it never
going
anywhere so I'm only one half of it you
guys are the other half of it the other
half and you guys do the work you guys
do it even if you're dabbling it still
counts I don't want anybody to think oh
I'm dabbling and maybe I'm not that into
no you're into it and it's going to kind
of ebb and flow it might be like now
you're doing one thing and then you look
up in the book or you see something I've
said that's coming from above and you do
another thing and another
thing and I know the road is hard you
guys got a lot of faith you guys got a
lot of faith because the stuff out there
challenges that a lot right and so
you're like what do I do I heard this
thing out here what do I do you know aw
is not a science Professor no not that
the science professors get people
chronically ill better I mean how many
do I don't
know but it's it's easy to be challenged
and then your faith is challenged and
then you're like what do I do and then
you being an old soul you come back to
and say I know what I'm doing I know
what I need to do this is the
information it is working it got people
out of
[Music]
wheelchairs last night last night here
there were people that were walking
about they were here they're eating food
and they were in a
wheelchair they were in a wheelchair in
the past I don't mean a past life I mean
in the past 10 years ago 5 years ago
they found mm info they're out of their
wheelchairs they're living their
lives
now one of the things that leads to you
guys being the oldest Souls correct me
if I'm
wrong no one's getting a big old gold
medal for doing it you got out of your
wheelchair no one's saying here you go
here's your you know $10 million check
in gold medal no one's getting a big old
trophy for when they get out of bed
you're on mattress Island for 2 years 5
years 10 years right no one's saying
good job for getting off a mattress
Island and going back to work and being
productive and living your life here's a
big old
trophy you're your old souls man your
old
souls because you don't need a
trophy you don't need that you don't
need a gold medal you don't you don't
need that at all
okay you guys possess something
different you're not after this shiny
flashy thing just because you get better
you guys got soul you guys have been
around you're seasoned you're seasoned
for lifetimes you know what's going on
and you know that you're going to get
better and then tell that story to
someone and that's the reward is you're
telling somebody else and you're seeing
them turn their lives around right or
you're seeing them contemplate and
possibly sitting on the fence and then
falling off the fence on the right side
and then doing the things they need to
do the reward is bigger than a big old
trophy or somebody saying good job you
got out of bed you worked your ass off
to get here it's more than that you guys
are telling other people you're
messaging that you guys are holding the
light you guys are holding the light the
light that stands in the way of the
darkness that the trophy that's the gold
medal so we're we're on this
rock we're on this
Earth it's going around the
sun right that's what it's
doing the sun is shining a light
energy it's hitting seeds that were
planted in far arms those seeds grew and
I said this last night this part right
here I said last night okay would those
seeds have ever thought if they can
think and they have a Consciousness and
they may have a Consciousness they may
I'll ask Spirit of
compassion be one of the questions that
the next thousand questions I
ask they have a Consciousness and
they're growing is it possible they're
growing for you tonight right now for
this very
dinner they were harvested at a farm
they were grown for you specifically and
then they're here on this plate is that
a
coincidence your body has every right to
heal every god-given right to heal never
forget that I have to say it time and
time again because we can easily believe
that we don't deserve to heal we don't
deserve it because the world beats us
down and it's very hard here on planet
Earth planet stress is what I call it
you guys heard me say that
before but we have the tools to keep our
bodies healthy recover from things that
have happened in the past move our
bodies forward we have the tools we have
the food counts it does it's a big piece
of it I love when people try to you know
call out on medical
medium and they're like he doesn't say
the food does anything he doesn't say
the food heals he's all about
supplements if you read the books and
you learn the information food is a
massive piece of it a massive piece of
it and yeah this world is so difficult
and there's so many exposures that we
need some things added to that yes we
need some additional pieces that are
critical every one of you here has not
like joined a club in which I close the
doors and then I'm teaching you the
information you
guys are some ballsy people that took it
upon yourself and you got into the books
and you saw the
information and you customized it for
yourselves that right there doesn't
happen in the health movement in the
health movement everybody needs to be
kind of like their hands held they need
to sign up to some big course they need
to be right doing some kind of training
to try to show them
way you guys didn't do that here talking
about old souls that's a big one right
now that one right there you guys did it
for yourselves you guys
yeah you guys didn't join the Anthony
William Club somewhere some membership
or something where you know you didn't
do
that you got the book somewhere from the
library you got it from Barnes & Noble
you got it from a bookstore in Europe
you got it somewhere you got it and you
said I'm going to do this intentions
that you you actually did yourself what
is that that's old soul stuff that's
what that
is and the other thing is which is a big
deal you guys are no strangers to the
supernatural
forces you guys believe in angels and if
you don't believe in angels that's fine
do you believe in light maybe you
believe in
light maybe that's what you believe
in I know a lot of you guys access
Angels you talk to angels and that's a
big deal you know I leave telegrams
about the Angels you know I I put
information out there it's in the books
as well I know many of you guys have
learned how to access angels and if you
haven't learned you still have them at
your fingertips very very there for
you all of that takes Faith you guys
have
that old souls equals Faith which is
missing in the Alternative Health
movement right now and you guys have
faith because face it are you going to
the medical medium
book when you get sick no no but you
guys did first thing someone does when
get sick you think they run to a
medium or would others say profit you
think they run there oh I just got sick
I'm going to bypass a 100 nutritionists
I'm going to bypass a 100 chiropractors
I'm going to bypass 100 NDS 100 Do's 100
MDS I'm just going to go straight to
Medical medium information that's what
I'm going to
do no people
don't but they get sick tired they're on
their hands and knees they've been
through hell and back they've seen
everything done everything tried
everything and the last thing I swear if
I hear one more time in the health
movement out there oh yeah you know
people who tried everything come to me
over here and people who tried
everything come to my thing over here no
no no no no no people who try everything
and have tried everything and Been
Everywhere come here they come here
[Applause]
and that's because you guys are old
souls and that's because you guys have
faith you guys have done everything you
tried everything you guys are
seasoned yeah and you guys said you know
what I don't know if I believe in this
guy entirely some of you might be but I
like his stuff and but you get into it
and you're healing and you know what I'm
open-minded more wait what he hears a
voice oh that's a little too hard but
you know what I'm going to do it I'm
going to do the stuff and move forward
through it some of you guys are like I
don't care if he hears the voice I don't
care what he says I don't care if he's
an alien I don't care what he is he
saved my life he saved my sister's life
he saved my father's life saved my
daughter's life and that's all that
matters and his and his information
makes sense it makes it's not common
sense
it's
not almost all of medical medium
information isn't common sense for sure
it's not but it makes sense once you
learn it it makes sense and you move
forward you guys ready for a light blast
are we okay for
that right right ready for a light
Blast how many had it before had the
light blast
before that the light
blast it's pretty intense where do you
want that light to go I have to
ask cuz s so tells me ask that it's
important cuz I'll just forget I'll just
forget like ready for the light blast
where do you want that light do you want
it on your heart do you want it on your
pancreas are you worried about something
you want it on your
spleen are you missing a spleen do you
want it there are you missing your
gallbladder where do you want it do you
want it where your gallbladder used to
be your appendix used to
be where do you want that light right
emotional do you want it in the
emotional center of the brain do you
want it someplace in your brain your
Consciousness do you want it at your
soul which harbers around your brain do
you want it
there and it's okay if for some reason
you walk out of here and you're like I
should have had it hit my heart this
time it's okay it's all right that
light's coming down it's hitting the
crown of your heads it's going right
through you but it's important anyway to
just have a location and if you don't
it's still
good do you want it on your knees your
feet are
sore and do you want it somewhere else
do you want to try to get it to go
somewhere else to somebody you
love or do you want to sustain that
light as much as possible because you
can once it hits and you want to say I
want the light to stay in me so I can go
and Touch Somebody I love later a week
from now two days from now my
grandmother a month from now and I want
to go and I want to hold my
grandmother's hand a month from
now and I want that light to drive out
of me into that person think about that
too that's important all right so I'll
say count of three right I'll say count
of three and take a deep breath and then
release we're going to start with that
real quick we're just going to do this a
couple of times all right you guys ever
look at the stars at
night you do you do see them now close
your eyes it's just first moment and see
them now what do those stars look
like well we're getting this light from
behind those Stars it comes from far
away it's not coming from planet Earth
it's not coming from here that light's
not
coming from anywhere here on Earth it's
coming from above and it's going to come
down real fast and it's coming down from
behind the stars and it's going to hit
the top of our
heads okay counter three deep breath in
then release one two three deep breath
in and then
release we'll do one
more one 2 3 deep breath
in and then
release and this isn't a contest you
don't have to take the Deep biggest
deepest breath can take a gentle one you
can easily take a gentle
one okay so we're going to do the
first shot of light the first light
blast now count of three you're going to
take a deep breath and then you're going
to hold it for a quick
moment one two 3 deep breath in hold it
light light light light light
release you guys are are not that
blocked tonight there's just there's
just uh
20% 25% are are
blocked you guys know who that is you
guys feel
it you're feeling kind of
blocked you are all right it stopped
here let's go we're going to do it again
and the count of three deep breath one 2
3 deep breath in hold it light light
light light light release
that's amazing where is it now it went
everywhere it went right through it's
going to go to the bottom of your feet
and
out we're going to do just a deep breath
and then release we're not going to do a
light blast a second just let's do that
count of three deep breath release one 2
three deep breath
in
release okay now here's the big one
right
here are one of the bigger ones on a
count of three deep breath in we're
going to hold it one two three deep
breath in hold it light light light
light light light
release there's only a few of us left
right here somebody over here up at the
bar somebody up here at this this table
here there's a few there's two in here
and I think one one or two more get
ready it's going to be high powered on
the count of three 1 2 3 deep breath in
hold it light light light light light
light
release we're all clear we're all clear
you guys that's
amazing um that light's going to stay
with you guys it's going to stay with
you for quite a while could stay with
you for months but what's going to
happen is what usually happens is people
get instant
relief as of
tonight instant relief instant symptom
changing symptoms
gone a bunch of you it's going to take a
little time and you'll see things
change some of you will be like now I
know what my purpose is now I know what
my true purpose is Right which leads me
to say one thing that's really important
about the medical medium Community is
about you guys
here right here is that you guys have
purpose but you guys have what purpose
plus sounds a little corny I always
thought that when I heard that from SSC
I'm like what do you mean what's purpose
plus like what is
that purpose plus is having more than
one purpose everybody's caught up in
their mind and they think it's one
purpose and that's their purpose they
feel lost and they don't even think they
have a purpose because it's this one
purpose they're looking
for you guys have multiple purposes you
have lots of purpose purpose plus
everything you went through being so
seasoned your struggles getting here
today some of you can't even believe
you're taking a trip for the first time
or this is your second trip in many
years right you're here you're healing
you got purpose
you have that but you have more than
just purpose don't forget it never doubt
your purpose what am I going to do now
what's going on in my life now I don't
know if I have a purpose actually no way
you got more than one you're already
probably doing three or four and you
don't even
know but you guys you come a long way
you're going to get a lot of healing
from that light blast tonight I could
feel it and you guys know I love you
guys
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm choked
up maybe next time I'll get the guitar
out God
willing you guys you guys keep a light
your heart you guys know I love you you
guys love you truly all
right lad down on this on some of the
masterful work that you've done with the
medical medium dishes I know they're no
oil no nuts which is incredible all on
its own gluten-free soy free soy free
and easy on the salt exactly so tell me
a little bit about how like working with
those parameters and everything well I
mean it was like I said it was a great
opportunity to look at cooking in a new
way so it was and and to look for
alternatives to the traditional flavor
builders that we usually use in food um
as you know part of the collaboration
that we have here is that we assign
affirmation names to all of our food
which actually helps the healing process
in our opinion um and mine too yeah
right it is a good thing so here we have
imys which is our green papaya and kelp
noodle salad um with a coconut based
dressing and lots of TI spices and herbs
here we've got the I Am Noble for the
noble potato cuz it's the spicy potato
burrito bowl with your cheese sauce and
the potato is Noble for sure exactly and
a healing food a lot of people don't
know that so that's really powerful the
name goes perfect with it right there
and we've got a black beam Pico that
goes with that and then some water
sauteed kale and some great Pico deallo
well you got the kale that's incredible
to got some greens in there to sort of
lighten it up a bit and so this is I am
trustworthy which is your uh original
portabello and uh pepper fajita dish
we've dressed it up with a little bit of
lemon marinated red onions some
guacamole and some Pico de Gaya with a
squeeze of lime as well and we serve it
with the Millet tortillas which are I
think you're sort of famous for those
right and you can see it's the Perfect
Blend and you got the Millet tortilla
you can put a little bit of guacamole in
there you can put a little bit of the
onion in there you can make it the way
you want it that's incredible and then
it becomes like finger food then you
have in your hands you can enjoy it then
you could add a little bit more want
those little tortillas in my hand and I
want to put a little that because I've
tried guacamole in different places and
Cafe Gratitude guacamole is another
level it actually has flavor and that's
the key well in part of the affirmation
healing you can trust that everything in
this plate is going to be good for the
body right so that's why we're calling
it
trustworthy and the last one that we're
having as part of the menu here is the I
am insightful which is a jasmine rice
and organic jasmine rice vegetable Sushi
we serve it with uh pumpkin seed tofu
which is something that I think is a
really great soy alternative another
whole food avocado some vegetables
carrots cabbage and also some cucumber
in there as well you got the zinc and
the Pumpkin Seed so there's just there's
healing there's all kinds of different
aspects of these dishes that are healing
and I want to go to the papaya which is
incredible you're not using the Hawaiian
papaya no that is mindblowing right
there because you know like just if
somebody's going to use papaya it always
seems to be the Hawaiian papaya and I'm
like no this is incredible so you got
the shredded papaya and that's IM am wi
yes we we work with Organics pretty much
exclusively and I believe under the
organic certifications you can't have
the genetically modified papaya so
that's why we don't go with the Hawaiian
one unfortunately but that's just the
reality it's just the reality of it oh
we forgot the precious the uh wild
blueberry and cherry smoothie there it
is right there an mm smoothie okay and
that's the wild blueberry that's the
Cherry people are going to love the
flavor it's juice yeah oh it's so good
and so so rich but yet so light you're
satiated but you won't leave like we're
feeling real heavy and greasy and all
that it's just absolutely not absolutely
not just healing food people can fill up
get satiated and then they can do
whatever they need to do their workouts
they can go to the beach whatever they
got to do live their life but they got
the best food purest forms they don't
have the uh the nuts and the oils and
I'm saying that like nuts are terrible
or anything like that it's just that
these are breaking those rules and it's
like the no oil the no soy the no gluten
the no nuts and then the easy on the
salt I mean it's mind-blowing well the
more the more guidelines that we can
follow here the the more people we can
bring into this way of eating right so
if somebody wants to eat healthier but
can't eat nuts then half of the menu you
know is not going to be available in
this case they can have the whole thing
there's no nothing that they don't have
to uh not have you know I challenge
people to come in and try it I really do
I want to see what their pal how their
palette responds how they feel about the
flavors I want to see them give it a
shot try it see what they like about it
I want them to be honest about how they
feel everything and that's what I'm
excited about is having people come in
and being like hey okay you know what
let me take a look at this let me try
this wow you know what we got something
here and like I said before and this is
a big deal to me you took you took the
the recipes and you said aw let's do
this let's do a little of this let's do
a little of this and that is incredible
I'm so excited about that seriously
that's what chefs do I'm gonna be coming
in that's what chefs do that's what
that's what amazing chefs do and I'm
gonna come in and I'm going to be
ordering it too so and I want people to
know that I'm going to be in here a lot
so it's not just like once in a while
I'm you know if you come in here there's
a chance you're going to see me
somewhere sitting in here I'm going to
be enjoying these dishes and I want
people to know that that I'm making a
home here and I want people to know hey
aw's going to be in here you know catch
them when you can I'm going to be
ordering these dishes is I'm pumped
about it I love it I love it very
exciting thank you so
[Music]
much so everyone just finished that
beautiful four course dinner and I am
here with the gorgeous Greenley hi I'm
Danielle how are you today good how are
you good thank you did you have a fun
night tonight yes I did what did you
enjoy most this
evening I'm going to have to say the
sushi
oh yeah that was your favorite meal yes
yeah and what did you think of how was
your experience meeting aw oh I loved it
I I love meeting
aw and this is your second time or third
time meeting aw yes my third time wow
wow and what was your experience with
the light blast
like I don't know it felt like it's hard
to explain I it's more like your it kind
of feels like you're floating on the
cloud but like I don't know it's like
there's like a spark inside of you or
like it feels like something's buzzing
buzzing in your chest I don't know how
to explain it oh wow that's incredible
yeah now you flew in from Connecticut am
I right to be
here what an adventure it must feel
pretty late for you right now cuz the
time difference right yes yeah and how
did your medical medium journey start I
know we talked a little bit about it at
Calabasas but if you wouldn't mind
sharing that again that would be great
so when I was a
baby I got a um a
shot uh vaccine and I um was in 8 months
of intractable
seizures but now I I'm seven I think and
a half years seizure free
wow that's incredible and what part of
the medical medium protocol do you
follow do you do the celery juice the
heavy metal detox smoothie what do you
do we do all of it wow you say we is
that everyone in your family yeah sorry
I'm used to saying we a lot me my mom my
dad
and sometimes my grandmother because my
grandmother goes to Panama
so I love that you all do it as a family
do you have fun juicing together making
the Smoothie is it kind of fun to
connect and do all that together yeah
but when I get up in the when I get up
early in the morning I'm really tired so
I don't want to do
it sometimes do you like having your
celery juice made for you yes yeah does
Mom do that for you sometimes yeah yeah
that's a nice way to have it in the
morning do you as a family do you feel
like the family is healed together you
know you're all getting healthier yeah
yeah I do
but I feel like it's it's been kind of
hard because my dad now lives in
Florida
so now it's hard because um we're not
together and I miss him a
lot hopefully he's tuning in on the live
stream that'd be beautiful right yeah
yeah you want to send him a little hello
do the live stream hi Dad hi does he do
the celery juice sometimes yeah he does
all of it it's just my grandma he she
doesn't
when she's in Panama she sometimes has
chicken and food like that but but when
she's around you we do all m m and yeah
we that's beautiful what is it that made
you want to come to this event why do
you keep coming to the events out here
in Los Angeles cuz it's a big flight
right yeah
cuz kind of cuz I do love the flight cuz
I get to watch TV
so yeah and I really wanted to see
Anthony and go to my first ever four
course meal that is MM friendly this is
your first four course medical medium
friendly meal in Los Angeles I feel like
you're doing it in style aren't you
you're having fun Los Angeles you're in
the red carpet now yeah yeah yeah well
what a great night I I hope you had so
much fun this evening and you look
gorgeous in your dress those shoes are
beautiful I might have to get a pair
like that for my next red carpet event
too yeah they're gorgeous thank you so
much for talking to us it's so nice to
see you again thank you bye a thank you
can I get a hug a thanks we have someone
else to talk to oh we're back again do
you want to come back together um doing
it solo Oh solo we're doing a solo this
time okay no it's it's all good now we
spoke to you inside you enjoyed all of
the meals you had a great time what was
your favorite part this evening um I got
to say my favorite part was uh meeting
Anthony shaking his hand and just being
able to exchange some words with them
for sure did you like this setup it was
a bit more intimate than the than the
last two events absolutely much more
intimate less people uh more time with
Anthony and and intimate as well with
the other fellow medical me medium
people at the table did you meet new
people that you hadn't met before in the
community I did I absolutely did and uh
it was such an awesome Vibe it felt like
we knew each other for years it was just
amazing yeah do you think you might keep
in touch with those members of the
community we absolutely are we exchanged
the information and we're going to keep
in touch oh for sure that is beautiful
what was your experience if you might
don't mind describing during those light
blasts so I you know being blessed with
receiving life last multiple times this
year having come to the other events I I
just felt I actually I felt a little
different this time refreshed I felt um
I felt like um I felt like it really I
felt it from head to toe it felt
different for sure than the other two
times it was uh yeah it was deep it was
something else yeah like I I think it's
going to I could feel it's going to last
for a while but I definitely felt immed
fact like I I noticed a little bit of
you know L fog year of a of a mind you
know so yeah just to give an example
yeah yeah that's incredible well thank
you so much for checking back in with us
for chatting we're going to chat to your
friend now so thank you so much hope you
had a brilliant
night thank
you hello welcome back again thank you
for having me again so we kind of
visited you at the table can you just
remind me what was your favorite dish
you know I kind of liked everything um
my friend and I we came here yesterday
to kind of test a few things out and I
didn't get the sushi thinking that it
wasn't going to be good or having had
sushi a really long time ago just
conventional and been liking it and
tonight was a really really big surprise
I think it was one of my favorites but
to pick one would be be very very
difficult they were all really amazing
that's so interesting a lot of people
are saying that about the sushi that
they were just so surprised and that a
lot of people are saying it's one of
their favorites absolutely yeah I mean I
guess the the chef that made it really
really worked hard and I wouldn't be
surprised if had some input on how to
put things together really well and it
was just an awesome experience what was
your favorite part of the evening my
favorite part I think uh I came in here
just being really excited to talk to a
lot of people and last time I think it
was really Soul healing for me and the
same thing happened tonight just feel
much much lighter being amongst I think
people who think the same yeah it's
beautiful what was your experience like
with the life loss with the light blast
I think for me it takes a little while
until I feel the effects but immediately
it's kind of like just a feeling of
lightness and more of a presence kind of
like um maybe dis Association and like
brain fog being a little bit better you
know and continuing your medical medium
Journey uh would you like to share with
anyone out there one piece of
information that has really been a game
changer in your healing Journey
absolutely so I know for example you
can't always do something perfectly you
know you might continue eating meat or
you know minimizing how many eggs you
eat but one thing that I was doing which
was holding me back with strap and this
was something that was brought up to me
by a woman that um I talked to in
Calabasas not Calabasas sorry at the
first event in June in Clover City was
that eating rice is not really good for
strep because you might not realize but
it creates an environment in your body
that that really allow strep to prosper
and I hadn't really realized that and
it's interesting it sometimes it can
take a long time for you to either find
the information in a book or from
someone and realize the full scope of it
you might be doing celeres you might be
doing the heavy metal detox but there
might be a few things that you're still
doing wrong that can Propel you further
when you stop doing them I think that
would be a big piece of advice yes
that's so interesting that like you're
saying there's some things that are
maybe like hidden causes or things you
don't think of that are causing your
maybe like setbacks or your healing
journey to progress forward a little bit
more so yeah thank you for sharing that
information I'm going to keep that in
mind as well absolutely yes well I'm so
glad that you came out this evening did
you enjoy meeting all those new people
at the table absolutely and we connected
and hopefully when another event happens
here in California or potentially
somewhere else that will come together
or even you know come together
separately I mean what was really
interesting was it seemed like we were
seated very intentionally that there
were two women at my table who found out
that they live blocks apart you know so
I was telling them it'd be amazing for
them to have a dinner together oh wow so
you're saying they live blocks apart
blocks apart yeah and they connected
this evening not knowing that like their
blocks apart being medical medium
followers and part of the community and
they got to connect here in Los Angeles
absolutely just happened to be sitting
at the same table wow that's incredible
do you think that like Cafe Gratitude
having this uh medical medium menu uh as
part of their own menu will help people
heal and make it a bit easier and more
more enjoyable for people to enjoy
absolutely because you know this is a
huge thing for a restaurant to have such
a clean menu and this might be a way
that somebody might find out about
medical medium information see the menu
begin to heal be a great step into the
whole you know world of medical medium
wow I never thought of it like that but
that's so true they might see it on the
menu be like what is this and another
way of people finding out about how to
heal right yeah and realizing that
Health isn't necessarily pills it's not
necessarily you know hot yoga or
something
it's just simple food fruits and veggies
you know nothing mind-blowing there yeah
that's incredible thank you so much for
your time really appreciate you yes
thank you so much so glad you had a had
a great time this evening thank you so
much we're going to talk to our next
next medical medium guest would you like
to come over yeah we'll find out how you
enjoyed enjoyed the
night it is a little cold right now it
did get chilly the temperature dropped
quite a bit that's why I put a jacket on
but did you enjoy the evening oh it was
it was but words can't even describe it
you know so good oh yeah the smaller the
better the intimacy it was nice yeah
with the food like this it's it's good
what was your favorite part of the
evening tonight oh my conversation with
Anthony he just made me feel like you
know he knew what I was in my mind you
know he spoke to it so wow incredible
and you yeah definitely meeting Anthony
and just everybody together cuz everyone
is sick around the world different
countries states whatever and when it
can be like this it's like Familia it
just feels good yeah now I interviewed
you before but we didn't get a chance to
talk to you before this evening did you
guys travel together did you meet here
this evening how do you yeah were you
seated at the same table how did that
yeah we were yeah we were Yeah we
actually had someone you know cuz they
asked you for if you want to sit
together email or whatever and someone
didn't put all the who we knew together
it was nice yeah and it's nice cuz we're
doing the 369 together so we're both the
oddballs you know not eating the food
but yeah yeah made it easy so what was
your favorite moment of this evening for
you um well besides meeting Anthony just
seeing everybody again um yeah like he
said it's like family um deeper
friendships you know that we all just
understand each other what was your
experience like with the light
blast oh oh gosh I could I could feel
the lights when I shut my eyes I could
just see it every time he said light and
that didn't happen last time um you know
it's different every time I experience
it so and your experience with the light
Blast how was that good peaceful usually
takes a couple days to kick in but it's
always nice and if anything besides
seeing my friends I would pay just to
get that done swear to God yeah just to
get that done like plane ticket hotel
stay I would pay $ th000 just to go
light light light to go through that
process yeah was it different from the
other times you've seen him in person
with the light Blast for me it was um at
the last event I didn't really see any
light except for one moment but this
time it was the entire time I felt it
you know what about
you say that one question is this your
first light blast or have you been
multiple times third so how was this
different from the other light blast
that you've
experienced you just get better at the
process and visualizing it but you set
the
intention God's magic Works wherever it
comes from and you do feel a differ it's
surreal yeah do you feel like you're
leaving this evening making more
connections with this beautiful
Community yes and just getting closer
every time like you just come together
even more and more it really is
beautiful yes it is it's the