what happens in our brain when we get
angry what goes wrong inside of our
brain
when we get mad
we get upset
and we get angry or we even hold that
anger out it's not like we want to hold
that anger out we don't want to be angry
you don't want to be angry do you know
anybody that wants to be angry where you
want to be angry and you want to stay
angry no way right
because people don't want to be
naturally angry on any level do they
we're talking about the anger shifter
this is day five of the medical medium
brain shot therapy cleanse Challenge and
I really like the anger shifter because
if you've been betrayed or Something's
Happened where you've just gotten really
mad maybe you're dealing with
emotions and they come up and they
Bumble up and they they Bubble Up and
you get mad anyway you get upset anyway
and you feel like it's out of your
control the anger shifter is a great
tool so this is a medical medium tool
this is day five of the brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge we're doing
the anger shifter today but I'm going to
read about what happens inside of our
brain when we get angry what happens
inside of our head when we get angry
so it's really important information
critical information to anyone who's
struggling with some kind of mood
disorder too where you're getting pissed
off and angry all the time or frustrated
constantly frustrated or maybe you're
trying to beat out that frustration and
anger and you're moving along okay and
then someone trips you up and you get
triggered that's another thing too
everybody seems to be getting triggered
now
and getting triggered along the way and
that's interfering with them so they're
getting angry because they're triggered
and they get triggered into the anger
then the anger makes them more triggered
then the triggered makes them more angry
and now they're in a vicious cycle and
they can't get out of it and it's like
how do I break this anger how do I break
this anger or what if you got OCD
OCD is a whole other thing if you're
struggling with obsessive thoughts and
you can't break them and it's making you
angrier and more frustrated and more
upset and what happens there right
that's a whole other problem too so many
people have
OCD and it becomes a vicious cycle where
it's like it's over and over again it's
like you got the obsessive thoughts you
can't stop the obsessive thoughts you
know you need to stop them so you can
have some peace in your heart for the
moment peace in your mind and then you
get upset because you can't stop them
and then you're angry and then it's bet
it's like it's getting triggered and
it's Recycling and it's this Catch-22
right so many people struggle with anger
in so many ways and so many different
having different complications with it
too so I'm going to talk about what
happens inside this brain right here
your brain our brain
what happens in the brain when we get
angry I'm going to read about that we're
going to do the anger shifter too so
let's get into it now let's start
reading about it let's roll into it
so I'm going to go to page 30 I think
I am looking for page 30. there we are
page 31 right here brain saver you guys
this is going to be really important
information imperative information for
anybody who's struggling or suffering
with
chronic mystery anger or anger bouts or
frustration bouts or maybe you're
depressed and the anger hits when you've
been depressed for a while
and then you have that burst of anger
and then you cry and then now you're
depressed again
and then you're angry the next day and
it keeps on going so many people have
this issue so many people are struggling
so there's a section in brain saver
called melting down
and it's page 30 right here I really
need the anger shifter today actually I
would love to have the anger shifter
today that'd be fantastic
there's people out there that are
struggling with
Untold unbalanced Untold unknown bouts
of mystery anger at different times of
of the day different times of the week
the month for so many and this is so
helpful let's talk about melting down
what does that mean melting down
it's a meltdown right we're having a
meltdown
when our brains get hot
and there's metal involved I'm talking
about toxic heavy metals a little bit
because this is important
because so many people you can be angry
and frustrated not have toxic heavy
metals inside the brain but so many
people do have toxic heavy metals inside
the brain
they really do this is Advanced
information it's Unique information from
above just so you know it's in the brain
saver books published here first
it's incredible info when our brains get
hot and there's metal involved the toxic
heavy metal particles break down
think about that
how incredible that piece of information
is since research doesn't know that
alternative medicine doesn't know that
when our brains get hot
and there's metal involved the toxic
heavy metal particles
yacto particles
the tiny particles nanoparticles
break down
the metals melt
did you hear that you guys the metals
melt
these tiny nanoparticles septoparticles
the active particles whatever these tiny
particles melt
every time a brain gets hot
the metals melt inside of our brain
toxic heavy metals in the brain get wear
and tear
when electrical currents are entering
them
all the electricity in your brain you
guys has to hit
every bit of metal that's in our brain
Mercury copper lead arsenic
aluminum
cadmium nickel right
we have metal in our brains toxic heavy
metals and electrical currents
entering
arm like our neurons are hitting these
metals and they're giving them wear and
tear
and when that happens
the metals start to change
their shapes change
this is incredible information when I
was writing this information down
through the painstaking process
that I desperately needed anger shifter
the anger shifter at that time right
this information is so incredible
there's a comment on IG
let's see Boheme says my ayurvedic
teacher taught me this I beg to differ
that's for sure
somebody else said oh the same person
said stop claiming you're the first
your ayurvedic practitioner did not
teach you what I'm telling you it was
never published anywhere it's Unique and
original I know
that's hard to take in I'm gonna need
the anger shifter today you know I know
that's really hard to take in and hard
to digest
but the medical medium books are all
from above
my publisher has no requirements for me
to create any citations because it's not
taken from any sources here in the
Alternative Health World on any level
so your ayurvedic doctor
does not know that electricity melts
yacto particles of metals in your brain
nobody did
your ayurvedic practitioner didn't know
about toxic heavy metals I spent 35
years teaching about it and how they
work in the brain and how to get them
out of the brain and body that
information is unknown to research in
science so unless you're ayurvedic
medicine doctor is making it up
there's no study that shows it or
anything of the sort in their teachings
or any other teachings
I'm not dissing alternative medicine
whether you're naturopathic
acupuncturist an ayurvedic doctor or
whoever you are the information is
unique and original
and that's just a fact
anyway I appreciate though you're saying
that
because it actually at least gives me a
chance to talk about how incredible this
information is how it's original how
it's Unique and how amazing that is
a publisher
would never let this out
if it wasn't original and unique
that's how it works
it would all have to be cited to all its
sources to all the different sources out
there if it wasn't original and unique
enough with the fun let's get into let's
talk about the powerful bits of
information on here
pieces of information Phyllis is
absolutely fascinating when peeps claim
they've heard it before just fascinating
I know there's a reason for that there's
a bunch of reasons for that I can go
into all that someday but some do it on
purpose because they heard Metals before
from somebody so they think everybody
knows about it
does not know a lot and they have a lot
of misinformation I agree with you same
with TCM in fact they say the opposite I
agree 100 that's accurate that's really
accurate
all right
and maybe somebody's ayurvedic
practitioner purchased the medical
medium books maybe they purchased
medical media maybe they purchased
cleans a heel maybe they purchased Liver
Rescue maybe they purchased
life-changing foods and they learned
about something from their
and incorporated or maybe a patient came
into the ayurvedic doctor's office with
a book or just with the information and
just started talking about metals and
metals in the brain mm info and that's
how they heard it
but it's all original and unique
the metals
change shape when electricity is hitting
them and then corrosion can can occur
first of all there's no signs of
research or anything
anywhere that talks about the metals the
active part-sized metals particles in
the brain corroding
no one knew anywhere on this planet on
this Earth
that corrosion occurs to nanoparticle
sized Metals in the brain
nobody knew that corrosion occurred to
them this is just one out of whatever
it's in here
I need the anger shifter shot today they
don't want me to be able to claim my own
information
isn't that hilarious they don't want me
to claim my own information from above
they want me to be silenced they want to
make it like they can that I can't stick
up for myself or stick up for the
information that's so powerful
they they want to take the information
though from me and then
and then just basically tell me that I
don't know what I'm talking about and
it's already out there
and it keeps people from coming to it
right that's the reason they do it it
stops people
from coming to this information
it's amazing
the smaller of the particles the more
easily they melt under the heat of the
brain
so metal changes shape in the brain and
the tinier the particles the easier they
melt inside the brain
they transform into a liquid gas
chemical composition I'm sorry but that
information is not out there
that is the metals change from a solid
to a liquid gas and can spread and cover
more ground inside the brain more easily
because I have a real publisher behind
me right it's not independently
published I can't just put any old
in here
cite the source
I have a real publisher
I can't just put information in here if
I took it somewhere else
I would have to cite it
your serious responsibilities
that go along with all of this right
here
in these books
if I was independently published and I
wanted to put out anything and
everything and steal whatever I want to
steal that's one thing
but I can't do that this is all unique
and original
you guys have we even started yet
when toxic heavy metals reside inside
the brain and they melt you guys heavy
metals that reside in the brain they can
transform into a liquid gas chemical
composition the metals in your brain can
literally turn into liquid gas
Hannity I think uh Dr Nesbit showing up
today later
Metals change from a solid to a liquid
Madeline Scott if the info wasn't true
why would they say it's already out
there
both can't be true thank you for sharing
the truth with this aw
it's a powerful comment
you know what I love about the medical
meaning community
you guys actually understand you're
smart you're seasoned
your intelligence level is just off the
charts
you guys are smarter than me many of the
people in the community are way smarter
than me I'm a messenger I hear the
information I write it down word for
word but that doesn't make me a really
highly intelligent guy there's some
incredibly smart people in the medical
medium Community it blows my mind
but their games will all make you crazy
out there the games that they play
you know there are no real studies
from any of it but they'll like post
they'll post somebody will put a link to
a blog post of something that mentions
metal
and then all of a sudden there's the
answer but there's no even answer in
there
all right
toxic heavy metals when they get hit
with electricity and your brain heats up
turns from a solid to a liquid gas
science also publishes papers and
theories
they just study they just publish papers
and theories that are written by people
that steal medical medium information by
the way
and they also they also backdate
and change and edit articles they take
medical meme information now did you
know this and they back date
articles articles that we have
screenshot
they came out in like 2019 what they do
is they literally change the date to use
the same article and then take the date
off and make it look like it's older
they do that too
we have so much data from so much of the
trickery and the clinics are taking
medical meme information every day right
now with no studies behind them they're
taking the mm info all the clinics right
now have the medical medium brain saver
books and they have
clinicians reading them extracting from
it
and trying to publish it on their sites
when there's no studies behind it and
never existed before
foreign
but there's no darkness in this world
Metals change from a solid to a liquid
gas and can spread and cover more ground
inside the brain more easily what that
means is when the when the metal heats
up and it turns
from a solid to a liquid it can spread
throughout the brain more
and then you hear all the fork tongue
out there
remember that word for tongue
because
there's a crap ton of it going on now
and then the media is never nice to
Medical medium we know that how many hit
pieces have been out there on me
it's unbelievable
it's unbelievable what's happening out
there
there's a new hit piece on medical
medium
like in the media every month
and the it's just you know and that's
what's crazy media can say whatever they
want it's all false they can say
whatever they want
it's actually sick
hey this is really great because you
know what we're doing the anchor shifter
today so we should talk about all this
crap that's going down that's really
frustrating and then we can do like an
experiment which can get me as
frustrated as possible out on this
information and then I'll I'll send down
the anger shifter it'll be fun
let's see draw says this is my first
time watching in medical medium live
video after just purchasing the celery
juice book are they always like this no
they're not always like this
this is the brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge this is different so if you're
watching this right now on IG that we're
doing a 20-day braid shot therapy
cleanse challenge you're welcome to join
us for free so if you just learned about
medical medium and you say you purchased
a celery juice book know that
everything's for free
and it's powerful healing information
it's healed Millions around the world
saved lives all around the world you can
join this free cleanse challenge right
here we're doing 20 days we're having
some fun
we're talking about some of the stuff
going on and when you read the books
you'll you'll see like the information
is just mind-blowing it's incredible
all right so we all have toxic heavy
metals in our head the particle size the
smaller the particle size is
then the change the composition of that
metal changes so that metal then melts
turns into from a solid to a liquid form
the hotter your brain gets and for
example if you're angry
if you're mad
the matter you get the more Angry you
get or the amount of stress you could be
under the brain heats up when the brain
heats up it then transforms
solid particles of metal like yacto size
septocise Nano size it transforms them
into a liquid gas then that metal
actually travels through neurons and
brain tissue worsening a condition over
time
they move and they slowly travel to
adjacent brain tissue over the years
melting toxic heavy metals in the brain
are one reason why so many conditions
and symptoms like Alzheimer's for
example worsened with time the gas alone
can worsen any mental physical or
emotional condition so someone has any
kind of issue
whether it's brain fog confusion focus
and concentration issues whether it's
Alzheimer's dementia whether it's none
of that then they're just dealing with
some depression right
if the metals are actually moving about
it changes the symptoms too that's why
someone's psychiatrist would be like
well how come you know it's different
than it was a year ago how come it's
different than it was two years ago they
don't know meanwhile metals are melting
transforming and moving around
another reason brain conditions worsen
with time is that more toxic heavy
metals continue to collect in certain
areas of the brain
the brain's electromagnetic field draws
Metals in I'm on page 30 of brain saver
people keep on asking where am I
so toxic heavy metals
get attracted to the electric
electromagnetic field that the brain
causes
that electromagnetic field draws metal
in creating an accumulation effect that
makes large deposits of toxic heavy
metals keep growing so our
electromagnetic field pulls Metals into
the deposits that are happening inside
the brain that are collecting inside the
brain building these deposits bigger and
bigger that's another thing that happens
too
especially if we're angry all the time
and we're melting the particles and the
particles are going from a solid to a
liquid form and then hardening back up
into a solid form they eventually can go
and find other metal deposits like
Mercury
so Mercury can find Mercury this way
as mercury melts
it can transform into a gas and then
move as it's moving and we're angry and
that electricity is going through our
brain an electromagnetic field can draw
the mercury in even more collecting into
a deposit
um creating an accumulation effect that
makes large deposits of toxic heavy
metals keep growing the larger the
deposit the greater its electromagnetic
pool so that's another thing too the
larger the deposit of metal aluminum
Mercury lead arsenic cadmium nickel
building up in the brain the larger the
deposit that's inside our brain
the more electromagnetic pull it has so
that metal deposit inside somebody's
brain whether it's the left hemisphere
the right hemisphere frontal lobe
whatever wherever it's residing the
brain stem
it's going to draw more
metal
to that deposit it's going to be a
stronger electromagnetic field
it will keep attracting toxic heavy
metals into it making the deposit larger
and larger over time because that's what
happens to people if you don't get the
metals out of your brain
the deposits will keep growing and
growing and growing
and that gets us in trouble because if
we're not being at if we're not actively
getting the metals out of our brain and
the metal deposits are growing larger
inside of our brain
then there's more corrosion that current
occurs within that big deposit
and then we end up getting Alzheimer's
down the road
Tamara Jones says
there is high level competition among
scientists to get grants yes and their
careers ride on this yes the lying is
rampant true 100 percent
and they're also hungry for new
information so they take it from the
little medical medium and we know this
if someone's doubting that it's actually
factual we have evidence for instance
the publication of multiple sclerosis
being caused by Epstein-Barr and then
Harvard took that info and published it
eight years later after medical medium
already published it
and I taught about it for years too
so we have
lots of evidence of that
while the brain's electromagnetic field
is drawing toxic heavy metals into other
areas of the brain too the metals tend
to accumulate where the field is
stronger due to these nuggets nuggets
you know about gold nuggets
right gold nuggets everybody wants a
gold nugget
all the miners the gold miners are
looking for gold
always want gold nuggets
well we get in our head instead of gold
nuggets we get Mercury nuggets we get
nickel nuggets we get aluminum nuggets
we get copper nuggets Jackie B good to
see you hey at least if we're pissed
beforehand we'll feel it working laugh
out loud and I can't wait that's exactly
true like I think I'm getting you guys
all riled up by accident or something
because I'm getting riled up
Hannah T been on heavy metal detox
smoothie for three years and now in the
metal exposure shots I'm getting medals
out like crazy my mental state has
improved a thousand fold Hannity there's
a guest coming on later to say hi to you
doctor
when it comes to Mercury deposits
they're not just formed through
electromagnetic Pole
Mercury doesn't need this
electromagnetic field to accumulate in
the brain so Mercury is one of those
rare metals that doesn't need the
electromagnetic electromagnetic field in
our brain to grab onto an additional
metal and bring it in and create that
nugget
Mercury finds Mercury on its own
and
hence it says it right here Mercury
finds Mercury on its own
with Mercury deposits forming in the
brain both from electromagnetic
nature and from Mercury's tendency to
find Mercury Mercury deposits are that
much more of a hindrance so what happens
with people with Alzheimer's dementia
what happens with people
with the personalization with depression
with severe anxiety severe depression
what happens with people with bipolar
and OCD Mercury deposits they're a big
nuisance because Mercury finds Mercury
easily without even our electromagnetic
field doing it so Mercury finds Mercury
easy so Mercury deposits become bigger
in our brains that's why it's critical
to get those Mercury deposits out
because they're really a hindrance
scientists need a hypotheses
to do anything with to even attempt to
do anything
where do where do they get their
hypotheses I'd like to know well from
medical medium all the time
that
when it comes to Mercury deposits
they're not just formed through
electromagnetic fields as I said Mercury
finds itself important thing to remember
if we're experiencing a lot of friction
and stress in our lives
yeah what electricity travels through
our brain at a higher intensity and
velocity
so for under stress electricity travels
through our brain at a higher velocity
a higher intensity
because adrenaline here science and
researchers know this check this out
because adrenaline both increases heart
rate and enters the brain raising the
brain's heat levels
adrenaline raises the brain's heat
levels
I remember when I was writing that down
and I heard that piece of information
from above right from SOC I was just
like Blown Away
so when we're under stress electricity
is running through our brain in that
high velocity and high intensity
and it raises the heat levels but
adrenaline contributes to
because it increases the heart rate and
that adrenaline then enters the brain
the more toxic heavy metals in the brain
the hotter it runs
so here's another problem the more metal
we have in our brains the hotter our
brains run
the more metal particles we have
throughout our brain the hotter our
brain is
and remember this Metals retain heat
metal retains
Heat
that's so important to know it could
become a vicious cycle I don't like this
vicious cycle
for instance someone who's
perpetually angry about anything and
everything we're talking about anger
someone who's always angry about
anything and everything
or who has frequent spells of anger
may have higher levels of toxic heavy
metals in the brain in the first place
and that's aggravating the anger and I
talked about that earlier right the more
metal we have in our brain the more it
makes us frustrated and angry the more
we have bouts of anger
the more bouts of anger we have the more
we're heating up the battles it's this
vicious cycle that keeps on going over
and over again
as he is generated for any reason the
metals change shape and form those anger
spells will then generate more heat as
anger raises the electrical field
creating an electrical storm
what you'll notice when someone's really
angry and they got medals involved an
electrical storm happens inside their
brain grid
which in turn melts more metal so that
it spreads and has the potential to
interfere with even more electrical
signals in the brain that's the Vicious
Cycle about it that's why it's critical
to
be on anchor shifter if you're angry all
the time the other thing is it's
critical to know this so you can get the
metals out
which in turn melts more metal so that
it spreads and the potential to
interfere with more electrical signals
in the brain those melting toxic heavy
metal spreading through spreading their
liquid gas can hinder bodily functions
and communication I see so many people
out there suffering so bad
suffering emotionally suffering mentally
suffering physically just
just plain out suffering and they're
stuck in these Vicious Cycles of
depression and frustration and anger
then depression and sadness to
frustration and anger then then OCD then
bipolar frustration Mania then anger
than just all of it like they're stuck
in it and no one's telling them no one's
teaching them the cause of this is toxic
heavy metals you have mercury you have
aluminum you have copper you have nickel
you have lead in the brain and it's not
findable unless someone cuts open your
brain and puts it under a microscope and
they're not going to do that because
they don't want to find metal in the
brain
if the industry finds metal inside our
brains the industry would be blamed for
it because those Metals will go back the
forensics will show where those Metals
go back to in a lot of its
Pharmaceuticals
because Pharmaceuticals use a branding
type of metal an industrial metal that's
different than other metals and if that
was ever distinguished it would show
pharmaceutical Metals inside of our
brains
so so the science of research doesn't
want to know metals are inside our
brains they just let people stay sick
and sick and sick till down the road
they end up dying down the road or
something for some reason they're never
going to cut open their brain and look
and say oh whoa what's all this metal
doing here in the brain tissue hmm why
is the brain stem filled with metal hmm
what kind of metal is this well it looks
like an industrial variety of metal
that's used in Pharmaceuticals
foreign
on YouTube thanks let's see what does
this comment say from Omar this is
actually very fascinating honored thank
you for being here
if you're new here you guys anybody new
here
you're wondering if this is a normal
medical medium
this is a normal medical medium live
we're live right now by the way
this isn't pre-recorded
if this is normal I don't know if this
is normal
but check out medical meme podcasts at
Apple podcast when you get a chance and
listen to all my podcast episodes if
you're brand new to Medical beam
information
all right let's keep on going just
looking into the info here
people know stress and anger as bad for
our brain and body and health we do know
that too much stress not good give you a
headache
those in the health world don't know why
they're bad for our health
foreign
it is innately known out there that too
much anger and too much stress isn't
good for our body that's known out there
but those in the health world don't know
why we're talking about why
that's all about the mm info it's why
how where what
they don't know what systematically is
at the root of it they don't know about
the process occurring inside of our
brain the health world has no idea how
anger affects the brain in this way they
don't know why even with the best
Neuroscience techniques meditations and
thought pattern construction which is
all great and all mastering the mind is
a struggle for so many wise strategies
for managing stress and anger patterns
can fail and why people fall back to Old
patterns we don't know why
why
this is why
people struggle because of the toxic
heavy metals Underneath It All
trying to hack or rewire our minds leads
us back to the same old patterns if
toxic heavy metals are not being
addressed at the same time
there are people in the medical medium
community over the years
that have healed
their emotional
struggles through just ridding Metals
out of their brain
allowing them to play in meditation land
again allowing them to play in the
spiritual world again allowing them to
do these things because
they were healed the medals got out of
their brain and the natural process that
followed was beautiful The Details
Matter
with all of this
if you don't get the medals out of your
brain
you can be
seeking help
for your emotional torment forever
a whole lifetime of doing it 30 40 50
years
Hennis says no other modality worked
when I was dying with botox poisoning
people don't talk about Botox Botox
poisoning enough out there
I just don't
only medical medium info works if you
are too sick and that the details matter
right there if you are too sick
Hannah thank you for writing this
comment
I am forever grateful to have found UAW
thank you so much aw and SOC
people don't talk about Botox poisoning
enough how bad it really is meaning how
many people have suffered from Botox
poisoning
holy cow and the needle doesn't always
land right
when they when they apply Botox
it's like sure you know
okay I'm ready I'm in the chair it's
like
oh
okay it's in there pull it out
and
right
but anyway
sure you know it's like botulism variety
of pharmaceuticals right
cosmetic botulism use people don't talk
about cosmetic botulism use
all right
let's move on a little bit
yeah
thank you for dealing with me
reading through all of this I really
appreciate you guys your patience too
Iona says McLeod says I healed extreme
OCD whoa just knowing that you went
through extreme OCD it's just terrible
which used to take up hours of my day I
understand why is social anxiety
stuttering taking longer to heal okay so
first of all if your OCB is healed
extreme OCD
that's incredible because OCD metal
deposits
we're stopping electrical impulses from
going through and they were bouncing I
talk about in the Brain book They're
bouncing off that metal deposit then
ricocheting up then ricocheting up
if you have other things you're working
on healing if you had severe OCD to
begin with
then
there was a lot of metal there
we we have to do a lot of work take the
books to your doctor ask your doctor
what's right for you
but when I talk to doctors about OCB I
notice that there are patients have a
tremendous amount of metal inside their
brains
and
so severe OCD means there's more Metals
inside the brain with so many doctors
I've talked to with their patients that
have helped with that I helped the
doctors figure out what's wrong with
their patients
if he says only after doing medical
medium protocols did I realize all
non-physical techniques like meditation
therapy counseling psychedelics Etc just
try to compensate for physical defects
in the body but don't heal they're just
Band-Aids they're just Band-Aids
I don't like the Psychedelic Band-Aid
but meditation Band-Aids cool there's
there's that mean I'm totally I'm
totally into meditations Spirit of
compassion has given me so many
meditations to help to help um everybody
and they're in the books there's so many
meditations in these books now there's
medically there's meditations in Liver
Rescue there's meditations in medical
medium book one there's meditations in
brain saver there's there
right and they're really powerful and
they help really shift and rewire but I
notice out there like psychedelics and I
always tell people go to your therapist
go to your accounts counselor go to your
therapist go to your counselor do your
meditations but I never tell them do
your psychedelics
I'm always pro-counselors Pro therapy
whatever Pro meditation anybody wants to
do any meditations out there in the
world
but I'm not pro psychedelics
I'm sorry but I'm not and I never will
be Pro psychedelic
I'm I'm pro- why someone is trying to
use a psychedelic because I feel for
them and I'm not judging them I know
they're using a psychedelic because
they're not well they're sick and no one
understands them and what's wrong so
they're trying a psychedelic because
they really don't know what else to do
so I'm Pro that person not judging them
or shaming them I'm not pro-sychedelic
use read the chapter on microdosing
inside brain saver here the micro dosing
chapter it's insane I can't wait to read
it someday to you guys too
trying to hack or rewire our minds leads
us back to the same old patterns of
toxic heavy if toxic heavy metals are
still stuck in the brain and not leaving
the brain
all right
I want to find another little spot to
read if you guys got a moment
if that's okay
it's chronic anger disorder section
I don't know if you guys want to do uh
an intermission at all do you want to do
a half time maybe break it up before
we'll do that a little later all right
let's keep on going
chronic anger disorder on page 340 in
brain saver
if post-traumatic stress disorder
has been ruled out
which is to say if it's been determined
that Trauma from past abuse or suffering
is not the cause of someone's chronic
anger
and rather it's unexplained chronic
unexplained chronic anger
then toxic heavy metals saturating
emotional areas of the brain
and a stagnant sluggish liver are the
underlying causes
keep in mind
you can also have a mix of all three
trauma
metals
and an overloaded overworked stagnant
sluggish overburdened liver
all terms from original medical medium
info
if I don't shout out for my self then
what am I going to do
if someone had a sluggish liver and went
through mental abuse and toxic heavy
metal exposure at roughly the same time
The Chronic anger will often be
expressed more aggressively and more
frequently so many people have had toxic
heavy metal exposure during some trauma
at the same moment
I can tell you one area where that has
happened recently with millions of
people
not just millions of people in this
country of the United States but
millions of people all around the world
in other countries
there was a lot of trauma that occurred
the last two and a half years a couple
years whatever it's been now a little
bit more and a lot of mercury entered a
lot of people's bodies at the same time
they were emotionally
trauma traumatized and tortured
and it's heartbreaking
I'm not just talking about 10 people I'm
talking about Millions
tens and tens and tens and millions
were tortured emotionally recently and
Mercury entered their bodies
their brains
someone had a sluggish liver and went
through mental abuse of toxic heavy
metal exposure roughly the same time
that's what I'm talking about that's
just one example chronic anger will
often be expressed more aggressively and
more frequently for example if someone
went and got their Mercury Dental
filling so it wasn't talking about
Mercury Dental fillings but I'm just
saying I'm talking about it now
this is just I think one example if
someone went and got their Mercury
Dental fillings removed
which destabilizes the metal and also
got the worst news that day or week so
the day they had their Mercury amalgam
removed they also was they also got a
bunch of bad news
keep this in mind how it works this is
incredible information
simultaneously if someone had a Mercury
filling removed at the same time they
had a breakup in a relationship or some
other type of trauma or some kind of
emotional hardship or stress
the emotional impact of
of the difficult development plus the
Mercury exposure can lead to more
symptoms of frustration and anger if the
Mercury saturates the brain's emotional
centers
it's really Advanced information
go back and read the medical mean and
book series all the time people think I
should know every single word that's
been put in these eight volumes these
eight volumes here in books
but between hearing Spirit of compassion
all the time in my ear giving me
additional information non-stop every
day including what SSC already put in
all these books it's it's almost like an
impossibility to just keep it all
together
see Vex lens on IG said yep therapy is a
coping mechanism to help you
love with symptoms but it does not get
rid of symptoms since it does not
address the cause
that's really that's really so true
it's a really amazing comment
foreign
saturating other areas of the brain can
lead to other neurological symptoms such
as fatigue
nobody knew that
mm info
just saying
most often chronic anger stems from
toxic heavy metal exposures long ago in
childhood happens a lot too
here with Mariana says I healed an
addiction
that's incredible
so most often chronic anger stems from
toxic heavy metal exposures long ago in
childhood
can you think of any
toxic heavy metal exposures in childhood
oh I can think of plenty
as someone gets older the metals age and
oxidize causing chronic anger to worsen
through later years
anger can worsen as you get older
because the metals are oxidizing that
happens to so many people anger worsens
as the years go on
cold white spring says I could think of
some kind as the years go on Tara
Appleman mind-blowing information no one
could come up with this if they tried I
agree it can only be from above
so complex but clear exactly and Tara I
am not a smart guy
there's a doctor like pretty recently
called me a genius
because he doesn't believe it comes from
above so he thinks I'm a genius
I was like I don't know what to tell you
but it came from above and it didn't
come from me
so now you have to be a genius like I'm
not I'm not
realist says that's why it's hard for
all of us to start to change it's so
much information I wish it was easier
step one two three to heal thank you for
everything I know but that's why I
always say start where you can customize
it start with celery juice just
customize it
start with something right I tell people
start with a heavy metal detox smoothie
start with celery you start with the 20
day cleanse start with the 369
you know
the you know start with a 369 of any
choice or start with the monocleanse or
start with the morning cleanse maybe
just the morning cleanse maybe look at
the protocols for just your symptom or
condition take the book to your doctor
or practitioner your favorite
practitioner ask them to help you with
the book all kinds of different things I
know I tell people a lot of different
stuff
when people aren't feeling well
physically it can be angering
I mean come on you guys know that come
on
MD on YouTube you just have to stay
steeped in this info and really study it
gets me emotional because that's what I
have to do
like in my own personal experience I
have to stay steeped in it
you know because it's a lot of info
every time Spirit of compassion says we
have to do another book
we have to get these Bibles out there
for people so that they're here 30 years
from now 40 years from now
50 years from now that these books are
here
Spirit of compassion is always thinking
about me being gone someday
and always like well we have to have
these Bibles here
in hopes that even when they're book
burning down the road
that these somehow survive
there's a IG comment there
see Marcel says celery heavy metal detox
smoothie and brain shot therapies are
helping with my caffeine withdrawal feel
much more relaxed after taking them that
is amazing by the way congratulations
here's a comment on IG
all right
from Mad Maddie mad healing mad Maddie
made healing that's a cool handle
all right
silver from weed and Counting what
you're sober
you're 20 days sober from weed
and Counting
amazing
that's incredible
I never judged anybody who smoked weed
by the way I don't smoke weed but I
never judge anybody I do fool around
every now and then and I make a joke and
I'm like
this is good stuff man
let me get it rolled up
some good buds this is Sage
this is Sage
some really good buds right here man
[Music]
this is Sage it's gonna go on our anger
shifter
so I could be yep the books need to be
re-read over and over I'm rereading all
of them and I amazed at how much I
forgot muck till Freedom says
anger is not always bad
depend
there is look there is obviously
a healthy reason
right to get upset I'm not saying it's
it's it's bad to be like angry or upset
that's not it I'm saying though that we
can't stay in a perpetually angry place
if we have a spark of anger inside of us
because we feel we're not justified or
in Injustice Justice occurred it's a
natural experience and emotion
but what's not natural to us is the
metal inside our brains that gets
affected from when we have that anger
and that's the part I'm trying to help
people with because we got to take care
of ourselves
anger can spur
action
there is a healthy level of it and I
know that like I'm pissed off I want to
do something about that
but we're talking about when it feels
like it's past that
and if anybody wants a healthy small
bout of anger to propel an action to
justify something let's get the metals
out of your brain so they're not melting
during that process many get stuck in
constant chronic anger and that's a
whole nother thing
when people aren't feeling well
physically it can be angry is that true
is that true if you don't feel good
physically can it be anchoring
because there's a physical reason not
just because we want to be angry there's
a physical reason why we get spurred on
into mystery chronic anger all the time
if you're chronically sick plus you're
also experiencing any of these factors
trauma heavy metals or an overloaded
liver
the feeling of that chronic unwellness
can act as a trigger for these
underlying cause of chronic anger if
you're not feeling good and you got
Metals in your brain man you could be
stuck with chronic anger happening in
your life many get blamed for it not
managing their motions that's what
they're blamed for you're not managing
your emotions
you're angry because you're not managing
your emotions you're crappy at managing
your emotions and it's sad because dude
you don't know what's inside their head
you don't know how much metal is inside
their head and how much trauma they've
had and everything else
don't be punishing people because they
can't manage their emotions don't tell
them that they're not good at managing
it
you think they want to be angry you
think people want to be angry
you don't pun you can't punish people
for being angry I get it that we want we
want to punish people for being angry
shouldn't be angry but the point is is
what if they're really suffering they
really don't feel good physically what
if they're that one person that gets
blamed for not managing their emotions
right when it's not their fault they got
they literally have all this this
trauma and medals and
their brain needs help
physically no one knows that their
electrolytes are down their metals are
actually causing problems nobody knows
foreign
problem that hasn't been addressed
they can't
think
yourself
out of that
it's hard to think yourself out of that
if you have a physical problem that's
not being addressed you can't just wheel
yourself out of that so easy I'm gonna
I'm gonna try to think myself out of
this so fast
so we're doing the anchor shifter
because that
has
phytochemical compounds synergistically
working together to hit the emotional
centers of the brain to help somebody
get relief while they're fixing other
problems
homely said all the anger management
classes not based on real knowledge
exactly it's not like you go into your
anger management class and they're like
well Mr Ferguson
I know you're really angry because
you've been on the toilet constipated
every day you can't go to bathroom Mrs
Ferguson made you come in because you're
angry every day
so we're going to try to rethink
you out of this
Mr Ferguson's like I can't go to
bathroom that's why I'm angry I'm on the
toilet for four hours a day trying to
push out of bowel movement
that's why I'm frustrated and angry well
we can rethink this differently Mr
Ferguson
you said Mr Ferguson twice today hmm
wgreen when you read and explain it it
takes on so much more meaning thank you
for taking your time to explain this I
am trying my best and of course the
mattress service I wonder if I lost a
celery juice book guy the guy who said
he got the celery juice book and it's
his first time here is it always like
this I hope he's still here
mommy says your information is the truth
that I have been searching until I am
here in this world
really
so thankful for your work like
homecoming I'm I'm honored you're on
YouTube
okay you guys
honestly the information's mind-blowing
every time I re-read something I'm just
like what
you know every time I reread something
it's just it's incredible
I was just hitting that brain
all right so what do you want to do do
you guys want to do half time do you
want to do the robot this is where I
lose the celery juice book guy the guy
that's brand new that just came on here
we're live right now this is an actual
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
this isn't the normal lives I do
[Music]
[Laughter]
you guys are there the robot
you wanna robot dance
yeah
don't do it the way I do it I completely
hold my breath because I'm trying not to
move
[Music]
doing a little robot going on
who did I lose from that I hope you guys
are still here we're having fun
no one can stop me from doing a robot I
don't care
no one can stop me from doing the robot
doesn't matter
to me
it's fun for me I like it
all right
let's make the anger shifter I need it
today
I do I do I really do need it today I
really do
all right so what's the ingredients in
the anchor shifter do you guys know
it's a half cup of tightly packed fresh
mint
right
but before we get started right
let's read about the shot
that's really important and I actually
forgot to read about it all right
okay you guys ready
use the anger shifter
if you have unexplained bouts of anger
or anger surges that seem to arise
without cause any of you have that I
just want to ask that question
do you guys have that happen at all I'm
just curious
right yes mint is easy to grow
unexplained bouts of anger or anger
surges that seem to arise without cause
is that happening
because I know a lot of people go
through that that I've seen out there
okay use this shot if anger surges
have a cause if you have an anger surge
that actually has a cause use the shot
then too totally to totally use a shot
if you have an anger surge that has a
Cause
you can use a shot if you have anger
surges that don't seem to have a cause
at all
someone just said oh Iggy said I got the
giggles
anger about
okay use this shot if you've got anger
about being sick
what I like about the anger shifter
all kidding around seriously when you're
sick with chronic illness and you don't
feel good
and you've been on mattress Island couch
Island for a long time and you've been
every doctor you don't feel good you've
got all these symptoms and conditions
this but you're getting angry about it
like all of a sudden you're getting
angry about it that's a time to use the
anger shifter
so using and your shifter if it's about
being sick the anger or injured you're
you're you're pissed off you're injured
or dealing with health problems and
chronic illness you're pissed off but
you got chronic illness you're having a
pissed off day where it's like okay
that's the day I'm pissed off that's
what's happening use the anger shifter
that's why Spirit has it here
use this shot the anger shifter
if you have moments of unhappiness
frustration
or irritability that that Bubble Up from
with inside so if you got that
irritability and frustration that's
bubbling up inside and it's coming up
and you have moments of unhappiness use
the anger shifter for that here's one
right here use the anger shifter
if angers that's triggered from being
wronged in any way
such as from disappointment or betrayal
betrayal
so if you're somebody that
you know
you're being triggered because of
something disappointment and betrayal
you're being wronged in some way and
that's what's happening then you can use
the anger shifter
here's one right here
use the anger shifter if you have
confrontations or disputes with others
if you ever have a confrontation or
maybe you're on the phone with the phone
company
and you wait it for an hour
and then all of a sudden they hung up on
you
before anybody even started talking to
you or you were on the phone with the
phone company for an hour and a half
trying to fix a problem
and they finally started helping you
and in the middle of it it hung up on
you
and they didn't call you back
use the anchor shifter
if you're angry about world events so if
world events are pissing you off you're
at a point where you're like oh my God
how stupid can things get now
who is running this world
how dumb
are the leaders in this planet on this
planet like how dumb are the leaders of
this world
like
why is the world doing what it's doing
and for what real reasons is it
happening right if you're really pissed
about the world
you get a moment where you're saying I'm
just so pissed about the world right if
that's the case use the anger shifter
right
I see you guys commenting about that
Darkness uh etc etc or whatever I see
all that coming up right now right
I'm holding my tongue because
I feel like that in this world
they'll just take your tongue out like
back a thousand years ago in the middle
of the Dark Ages right and they'll just
cut your tongue off
cauterize it with
a hot poker
foreign
Debbie says on IG the brain books are
life-changing I've been doing the brain
shots daily and I'm doing the advanced
heavy metal detox smoothie and the
extractor smoothie the advanced heavy
metal detox smoothie
that is amazing
so you can use this anchor shifter you
guys if you're pissed off about world
events and wondering why the world is so
effed up for real
and why is it happening like that
why is Darkness
saturated into the leaders of the world
making the world like it is
okay
here's one right here I you know what
this one's last but not least
this one's last I swear to God but not
least I swear to God
use this anger shifter
if your anger is towards yourself
if you're angry at yourself
use the anger shifter if you're pissed
off at yourself
which
I get pissed off at myself periodically
I'll be like geez aw
and the anger shifter is definitely
satisfying there's two books right here
you're gonna want both of them they're
both critical it was one book how to be
put into two big Bibles
people are asking about the books right
now that's why I'm mentioning it they're
saying which book do I get well there's
two brain saver books one protocols and
one brain saver you need them both it's
critical take a look when you get a
chance if you're in the U.S oh my God
these two right here are literally
almost 50 off I think one already is
it's 22 the other one's like 28 or
something but incredible the pricing's
insane
over 600 pages each I promise you this
when you start reading the brain saver
books you can't go back to the
I can promise you this once you start
cracking into these brain saver books
you will not be when you read the other
health books out there you'll be like
what
what when you read these mark my words
when you get into these two books you'll
just be like and then you go back to one
of the other health books you're just
gonna be like
huh
there's nothing here in these other
books like there's nothing there like
what these are just eat better books
these are legendary books when you see
these and I can say that because it's
from above and I was the messenger you
can still sign up to the challenge
because the challenge has barely started
worth day five out of 20 days God help
me please God
God
help me get through the next 15 days of
this challenge
anyway
all right so you can still sign up you
can still sign up
we're day five the medical mean brain
shot therapy challenge go to
medicalme.com and sign up if you can
okay
you can still sign up
all right let's make this
and don't worry I am in it for the full
20 days of this cleanse I'm just going
to tell you right now
foreign
cup of mint fresh mint tightly packed
let's do it
and listen I wasn't making fun of
anybody who's using weed I realized that
most people using weed are really just
hurting bad
emotionally and physically they have
real physical problems wrong with their
brain and they're using the weed to
medicate and I'm not making fun of them
I'm not
um
I got a friend named Bryce
and Bryce is totally stoned every day
out of his mind
and he sits on his couch
his wife left him
tightly packed just a half cup so I'm
putting a decent amount of uh French
fresh mint in here
so anyway Bryce's my friend Bryce his
wife left him
this is a real story though by the way
even though you know how I come on here
as rice right
but it's a real story though I do have a
friend and
he didn't do anything but smoked weed on
the couch
and his wife just walked in one day
the pizza boxes were everywhere and his
wife walked in and said
I'm out of here
all right we got some mint in there
incredible quarter cup tightly Pat
packed fresh Sage
and he doesn't know he doesn't know why
it happened and I told him
there's only so many years when you're
finally out of college
that you can just smoke weed every day
and every night or every night where
chances are
your girlfriend or your wife is just
going to be like I can't take this
anymore
this is going to be really strong this
anger shifter man it's just gonna be
strong
I'm actually scared on how strong this
is going to be maybe that's a good thing
I'm actually spooked this thing's gonna
be Wicked
that's a lot of sage I put in there but
it's tightly packed and it's it's from
it's going to be tightly packed because
I kind of measured into what I'm going
to do that's not usually up to you so
much I know half cup of fresh or thawed
frozen mango
all right
it's common on IG right now is the Omega
Juicer from Amazon
the same as the one from Omega go to the
Omega company
okay because it's not on sale on Amazon
I got to shut this down because I'm
worried someone's gonna get the juicer
and it's not gonna be on sale the mm
1500 and the mm900 are on sale at Omega
juicers.com the link is in the
description the link is in the profile
see mm 1500 is what I'm using it's an
incredible juicer it's cold pressed
masticating juicer that actually
squeezes more juice out of the produce
so you save money and if you're juicing
celery every day and you're juicing
celery and greens and all that your pulp
comes out dry
and you're saving all this money it's
really really incredible right so it
pays for itself there's people that
claim they're saving 80 a week 100 a
week on produce fifty dollars a week on
produce eighty dollars a month on
produce it's incredible
um look what it got out of these herbs
okay I'm just gonna show you do you guys
okay this is really critical to know
I Juiced some mint
I Juiced some Sage
I didn't even juice the stems okay
okay that's super dry right there
the pulp
and look how much juice I got out of two
herbs
you can't get juice out of herbs
it's so hard you need more and more with
other juicers this is incredible what
this does
the warranty is 15 years including Parts
15 years
it's insane
anyway you can't buy it on Amazon you
buy it on Amazon you don't get the
discount it's on sale right now
just saying all right let's go let's get
moving let's do the Frozen mango next
that's why I endorse these juicers and
work with these guys because of the food
prices going up
I predicted the food prices were going
up I predicted it years ago before they
went up
and so
what was incredible about this juicer
was that very thing because it it helped
remedy it helped to do something to the
food pricing that was going up okay
so it's really incredible
all right so I think I need some carrot
decks
so
now the blueberry juice
I'm gonna put some blueberries you can
do the wild blueberries the Frozen wild
blueberries right the Wyman's Frozen
wild blueberries I'm just going to add
some blueberry juice in here
fit exact amount
I've got a little touch of that in there
so I didn't put the Frozen wild
blueberries in this time I'm just using
the juice in there because you can
it says it in the book
so now I'm going to look at this carrot
here
and it says one cup of chopped carrots
one cup of chopped carrots
foreign
you guys I really love doing
this with you guys
having fun making this this is the
anchor shifter if you just got on here
we don't close these challenges off from
the public
the problem with that is people from the
public come on and they go what the hell
is he doing what is this what's
happening
this is a free challenge I won't close
it off to the public
in charge
it's free
I don't want to charge for that charge
for programs subscription fees on the
website I don't do any of that
much
no commercials in front of my podcast no
advertising in front of my podcast
so I'm doing uh some carrots
cup of carrots gonna do a little bit
more
some more carrot
are you guys doing it with me or just
watching
let's see I used to be Bryce so grateful
for the medical medium info that healed
and I can be a free person for my family
and for myself incredible incredible
America amazing
all right we're good
now what you want to do because of the
high compression in here that sometimes
when you use something like mango it's a
little softer it takes time to go down
you can spend a little time have a
little patience and it'll go down and
you can push it down
but that high compression makes it so
when you do juicing when you're juicing
juicing
man the amount of money you save is just
incredible
and you can't say that with other
juicers amazing what you'll find is the
pulp doesn't come out sloppy wet where
all your money's thrown out the window
it's thrown out the window with a lot of
juicers because the pulp is sloppy wet
as it's coming out that's all your juice
so you have to put a lot more in you
don't have to do that with the medical
medium
um the mm-1500 and 900 that pulp is dry
like dust dry nothing wet in there it's
on sale you guys
all right so we got a juice right here I
got a lot more than I bargained for in
that one though I have to say
let's get a shot glass out
all right
I'm ready for the anger shifter I think
I'm ready for it
if you don't have all the ingredients to
do it to do this shot or do a shot and
you only have ingredients to do say
another brain shot therapy in the 20
that we're doing or in the 30 that are
in the book you're welcome to do it if
you only have parsley and you want to do
the gut nerve right the gut nerve acid
stabilizer if you just want to do that
one you can do that one every single day
through the 20 days if you don't have
ingredients so pick the brain shot
therapy that you want to choose that's
perfectly fine I'm on board we're just
doing these 20 today's day five it's
anger shifter and I need the anger
shifter fast
I need it fast
[Music]
too much bull crap going on around there
all those
crazy stuff out there in the world too
much bull in the world
too many hit pieces on the medical
medium out there
people trying to Gaslight and Fork
tongue the medical meaning community
trying to make it look like
this isn't the place to be then where
then where because we've seen what
happens when you dump all that charcoal
down the gut
and sodium bicarbonate down the gut and
apple cider vinegar down the gut 99
water machines into the brain all the
bad stuff
[Music]
I'll just just name a few things
the medical immune Community you find
answers there's answers here
anyway the anger shifter
having a little anger talk
before I send the Ender shifter down
way too much BS out there I know
Chrissy says she's enjoying this
challenge fantastic so am I
all right
[Music]
already feeling better
do you feel that
I have this one a lot
and it never disappoints it always packs
a punch
and I can feel it as potent Lisa said
it's potent
[Music]
this one is really strong
the sage in here and the mints combined
with the carrot and the mango it's not
about Flavor I'm not talking about
Flavor you guys I'm talking about what
it does to the brain
it's this combination
and what it does to the brain
information from above phytochemical
compounds working synergistically
together to tap into the emotional
Center in the brain
to rewire it
bartender give me another
I'm waiting
I should be really mad bartender because
I I need another
but I'm not mad bartender give me
another one I've been waiting here for
an hour
I'm a customer in this bar I'm still not
mad I'm still not angry
it feels so good honestly it's rushing
through my body how did you feel with
this shot how do you feel with this
brain shot therapy
post a real post a story or you know
whatever what were your results how did
you feel what happened when you took the
brain shot therapy we're talking about
the anger shifter please share a story
maybe you're doing another brain shot
therapy post a story about that one
maybe you chose another one post a real
tag on medical medium hashtag medical
medium do both of that so I can see it
has to be tagged and at and hashtag
medical medium for me to see it so I can
repost it I'll look out for your stories
look out for your reels look out for
your posts I enjoy reading them and
hearing them and watching them
it's it's so awesome you guys to be a
part of this community with you is so
exciting and so incredible check out the
heel podcast episode I did with Kelly
Noonan course so the heel podcast check
it out when you get a chance okay
um anyway She interviewed me she's a
dear friend of mine and She interviewed
me it was a great talk incredible
informative powerful information
um of course I was being
you know aw
get it so check it out too I posted a
link on all platforms
to heal
that was sorry the heal podcast the
medical medium episode all right
you saw it so Lana says the heel podcast
was awesome thank you for listening to
it thank you incredible definitely
definitely somebody wants to see you
guys
somebody wants to see you guys for sure
and um if you guys can seriously check
out that podcast it is it's really that
amazing it's that informative it's that
great
seriously if you can that would be great
uh me too 787 on YouTube says I felt a
wave of calmness after the shot that's
incredible now what happened was that
the shot is making me feel so much
better and everything I'm feeling it I I
get like shocked out of any kind of
frustration
so anyway
um I have Dr Nesbitt
I'm doing various shots right now Dr
Nesbit
actually is starting to become a
Believer and and Dr Nesbitt what
happened
a surgery went Bonkers this morning he
had a bad experience this morning today
a surgery that went completely wrong he
was so frustrated and so angry that he
he didn't know what to do so Dr nesbeth
called me up
I'm telling I'm saying too much
why am I not allowed to talk about how
bad the surgery went
he says the surgery went terribly bad so
what happened was Dr Nesbitt
asked me what to do and I gave Dr Nesbit
a anger shifter shot and Dr Nesbitt
thought it was incredible did it help at
all Dr Nesbitt
again
where's Hannah
Dr Nesbitt asked where's him okay
and
Dr Nesbitt would you like okay Dr
Nesbitt really does want a shot
there we go
okay good good point there all right Dr
Nesbitt has a shot he has an anger
shifter right now Dr Nesbit is holding
on to the Anchor shifter Dr Nesbitt be
very careful about this anger shifter
because you're about to get me really
upset and angry if you dropped that
anger shifter on everything and then
I'll need another anger shifter to
combat
Dr Nesbitt getting me angry
um Darkness but you get me angry about
once a day anyway right yeah he does he
does he says all kinds of terrible
things anyway he had a bad surgery and
he is now getting ready for the next
surgery right here Uma Kelly says the
other podcast with two girls was really
funny too
oh yeah Sarah Foster and Aaron Foster
you gotta catch those two I'm gonna be
talking about that one pretty soon
as well
um
all right you guys Darkness but can you
try that
Dr Nesbitt is drinking his anger shot
right now
is good yeah he loves it very good I'm
gonna take that from you Dr Desmond Dr
Nesbit stop doctor stop doctor Let It Go
doctor Let It Go Darkness Dr Nesbitt Let
It Go
it's okay let it go Dr Nesbitt stop
Darkness don't
think you're getting me so upset right
now
I'm actually gonna get upset angry and
gonna need another shot Dr Nesbitt stop
you
you're knocking over the juicer Dr
Nesbit oh
God
dark and Nesbitt I'm gonna need this
right now because you
I'm already feeling better
honestly
um the anger shifter
has helped so many people
um I have a friend that actually has
bouts of anger periodically and the
anger shifter literally is a game
changer turning
a friend of mine's life around they're
going through a lot right now a lot of
trauma a lot of emotional hardship
all right you guys all right I'll see
you tomorrow
be there
all right
bye guys