there's no darkness in the world there's
no evil in the world
there's no such thing
right and I'm like
dude what rock are you living under what
bubble are you actually in because
you're in a bubble and I talked to this
dude
right who said it
I said what's your life like he was like
well you know wake up in the morning and
do a smoothie and
then you know I make some eggs and and
then I go and I work out
and I'm like yeah yeah okay yeah and you
know and then I get on the computer
because I got this job where I don't
need to go into the office I'm like okay
the end of the day goes I go to happy
hour I go to my favorite Pub
meet a few people I'm like all right
and then whatever meet up with a
girlfriend whatever I'm like okay and
then at night I'm watching you know some
Netflix or some kind of show or whatever
like okay
I go then why are you telling me you're
in a bubble
why are you telling me there's no
darkness in the world there's no evil in
the world
there's no
terrible cold-hearted human beings in
the world there's no spiritual war in
the world why are you saying that you're
in this bubble you have no idea what's
happening out there not a clue it's
incredible that's how many people think
all right
you guys by the way right here speaking
your truth stabilizer we're day six of
the medical being brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge
which is actually really exciting by the
way so I'm pumped up about this
hopefully more people come on I can see
people are all being kicked off left and
right
come on let's get back back on if we can
and did you sign up by the way I just
want to run this by you this is a free
medical medium Branch out therapy
cleanse challenge it's free which is
incredible you can download your free
guide right here it's a free guide it
wasn't free to put together it wasn't
free to make this whole cleanse
challenge happen that no it costs a team
and money and all kinds of different
stuff and resources but I wanted to make
it free for everybody this is incredible
20-day cleanse challenge right and
you'll see what what we're choosing over
here spirit and compassion and I are
choosing for the shots to do you might
choose a different shot like if you only
have ingredients for the nerve gut acid
stabilizer which is just parsley or
cilantro then that's what you'll do
you'll do that every day and that's okay
right
sign up where I saw that on IG sign up
at medicalmedium.com sign up there you
can get your shopping list get all the
emails that have all the information to
this even if you are not joining and
you're not actually doing this right now
or making a shot stick around because
we're going to be reading about some
crazy incredible stuff information
that's really Advanced and Powerful so
get ready for that okay let me just
start
this is speaking your truth stabilizer
take a look at this for a second here
right that's what we're working on now
let me read what's in there
this shot provides support
around three main areas of Truth get
ready for this
getting in touch with and communicating
your own troops for example
when you're feeling stifled how many
people feel stifled do you know someone
that feels stifled
if you feel like you weren't allowed to
say anything weren't allowed to speak
your truth you felt like you were
stifled
like you just were just shut down and
couldn't could not speak your truth
right
it's this isn't this is a time to use
the speaking your truth stabilizer
here's another thing too if you're not
being heard do you ever have a situation
where you know somebody or you have gone
through this where you feel like you're
not being heard did that ever happen to
you where you feel like you're not being
heard
that's another time to use the speaking
or true stabilizer if you're in this
situation in your life where you're
feeling like you're not being heard
how about this one right here
you are not being taken seriously
have you ever run into that in your life
you're not being taken seriously does
that make any sense does that ring a
bell with any of you guys
how does that work right you're not
being taken seriously think about that
for a moment that's important to know
you can use the speaking or truth
stabilizer stifled and gaslit uh Tamara
Jones says stifled and gas lit man I'm
gaslit all the time man people are
gaslighting my ass on fire man that's
how much I'm gaslit
the amount of gaslighting that happens
to me is insanity I mean they're just
influencers are gaslighting the crap out
of me all over social media I'm like gas
lit they douse me with gasoline and they
light the flame although they like the
match Erica Malik yes or that person
doesn't listen
exactly
you're feeling stifled
you're not being heard
you aren't being taken seriously think
about that easling says me me and me
story of your life I saw somebody say
Story of My Life
Michelle L says I'm never being heard
Erica says every damn day
so every damn day indeed
saw that too
so what I love about the speaking your
truth stabilizer it does something it
rewires the brain it helps to unblock in
each individual person it's
it does something different for everyone
because everybody has a different
version of what's Happening inside their
brain
you're feeling stifled huge one right
there you're not being heard huge one
right there you aren't being taken
seriously
that's a big one how about this one
you're afraid to speak up about
something you're afraid to speak up
about something
that's a big one right there
I noticed that the haters they're never
afraid to speak up they just spew
that's what haters do out there they
just spew that's what they do right
haters
that have an agenda they just spew
everywhere just comes out of their mouth
they're just like spewing and then
you've got all these good-hearted souls
and good-hearted individuals and pure
souls and good people and they're afraid
to speak up
they're afraid to speak up
they're afraid to speak up about
something
but you got all these haters
that have an agenda that just spew
everywhere
they spread everywhere like skunks
like skunks that lift up their tails and
just spray skunk pee urine everywhere
and that's what all these haters do they
just skunks they Fork tongue and they
spew out skunk spray and skunk piss
everywhere right and then you got these
people
that are good people out there
good-hearted Souls out there so many
good-hearted Souls out there and they're
afraid to even speak up
make yourself 29 says they speak my
truth but get on for it oh my God
yeah Lori says reflexology says so much
so that I stopped speaking much
yeah but then the haters
and the Darkness deep you know like the
they got Devils inside of them they're
like they're like possessed with Devils
inside of them
the haters are like possessed they have
like devils in them
10 20 50 Devils just floating around
them and inside of them and they're
spewing skunk piss on everybody every
minute and then you've got people that
are like and they're Fork tonguing every
minute and then you got people that are
good people they care they have
compassion they care about people they
care about other people you see them out
there they care they're good people and
they're afraid to say anything afraid to
speak
German and English that's a cool um
that's a cool handle I am not being
taken seriously
that's what you said there I understand
Lana says that was me before my medical
medium healing Journey felt stifled and
couldn't speak didn't feel heard all of
it but the protocols have healed all of
this and now this brain shot will take
me to the next level and that's what I
wanted to say the brain shot rewires the
brain it de-brainwashes people we're
beaten down so we can't speak up
we're beaten down so we can't speak up
this brain shot therapy helps us
decipher the truth too decipher the
truth to see through it to be like an
Oracle and see through it it helps us it
rewires the brain it opens up a chamber
a chamber of knowledge in and
understanding inside of us so that we
can hear and speak the truth and hear
the truth
it's really powerful
herbal girl has a question how does this
shot change others perception of us
what's incredible about this the
phytochemical compounds right that no
one would know exists because they're
not found anywhere in some science lab
phytochemical compounds in our food
has power that's unimaginable and
untapped we just don't know what it is
so this synergistic
combination of what's sitting in front
of me
helps to unlock the emotional center of
the brain that's been hindered and
damaged
should we get like a rewiring
and that's what's incredible about it
all the destruction on this planet all
the all the
the
toxic toxic
chemicals on this planet
all of the
right
Darkness on this planet
you don't think there's an opposite on
this planet you don't think there's the
light on this planet you don't think
there's
incredible
powerful
magical medicine within the food on this
planet if we have the power
as men on this planet as mankind on this
planet to corrupt and destroy this
planet
systematically destroy this planet you
don't think we don't have something else
on this planet to help us battle that
what I love about the the speaking or
truth stabilizer is it actually helps
to hold your power
to connect to the power you have
so you can hear the truth too it's like
the D brainwasher that's what I love
about this one
and each person may experience it
differently It Could Happen a month
later a week later a day later but it
can drink when you're doing these you do
these once a day and all of a sudden two
weeks later
something happens where you feel freedom
inside your mind
and you're able to hear things
differently see things it's like the D
brainwasher
so check this out
this shot support supports people right
this shot provides support
in receiving the truth for example when
you're afraid to receive the truth about
something how many people they are
afraid to hear the truth oh my God
they're afraid to hear the truth
there's a lot of people that are scared
they're afraid of hearing the truth
if you want to know the truth about
something there's a lot of people that
want to know the truth about something
but their brain won't won't really let
them it's stuck in some kind of gear
where it won't let them
because of wounds and emotional hardship
and brainwashing and everything like
that
you've received the truth and you're
having a difficult time accepting it
there's a lot of people
they receive the truth but they can't
accept it do you know how many people
receive the truth about how bad
something was in the last couple years
you guys know what I'm talking about
right and they can't accept it you guys
know what I'm talking about right
the last couple years
okay
there's a lot of people that
that know the truth about how bad that
was in the last couple years but they
just you they'll never ever no way
that's not possible
I'm fine it didn't bother me it didn't
affect me
code code code code
how about this one learning about Hidden
Truths for example when you want to
expand your understanding and knowledge
of what's happening with the world
around you what I love about the
speaking of Truth stabilizer is because
it opens the door to understanding more
around you like I said this guy I was
talking about lives in a bubble man
lives in a bubble
this world was this big
this big
got up in the morning worked out
had some eggs and some in a smoothie
protein smoothie
worked for a little bit on the computer
or on his job
met up with his friends at happy hour
right at a bar
went on a date with this girl came back
home watched a Netflix movie that was
his that's that's the bubble right there
doesn't even know how bad the world is
in so many ways and how much crap is
going on
and with and what is happening
just bubble that's just one example
right
learning about Hidden Truths
So speaking your truth stabilizer can
open that Gateway open that door to
hearing about Hidden Truths you want to
learn how to read between the lines and
see what others are not seeing how about
that how about being able to read
between the lines so what does this do
this helps our intuition this helps our
telepathic Powers this helps our
spiritual psychic ability this helps our
Clairvoyant skills this helps that you
want to sharpen that you want to sharpen
that like attack
foreign
about Hidden Truths for example when
you're seeking out Hidden Truths
when you are a truth Seeker
a truth Seeker when you want to read
between the lines
you want to see the truth and read
between the lines or you're a truth
Seeker
you want to expand your horizon your
understanding of the truth about what's
happening in the world you want to
expand you don't want to be locked in a
box you don't want when some truth does
fall in your hands you can't see it
because you're just you're stuck and
you've got the brainwashing and
conditioning if you want to break
conditioning speaking your truth
stabilizer
when Spirit of compassion gave me this
one right here this brain shot therapy
right here at a brain saver when Spirit
of compassion offered this
from above I was like what
what do you mean
I was taking down the notes feverishly
on this one Speaking of Truth stabilizer
what are you talking about I was writing
down the notes like this and spirit of
compassion was it's for conditioning
it's for brainwashing it's about
unlocking that emotional center it's
about if someone told you the truth you
wouldn't even see it if you could
because you're all locked up in here
it's about opening that Gateway that
door to hearing the truth do you hear
how incredible this is my mind was
completely blown when I was writing down
these notes for this one right here
it's when you want to read between the
lines you want to build that telepathic
power you want to build that Clairvoyant
skill you want to build that intuitive
nature inside of you you want to be able
to read between the lines you want to
know about Hidden Truths you want to
seek the truth all of that and when I
heard that I was like this is probably
one of the most profound brain shot
therapies that are in the brain saver
books
it can also help build a skin
build a skin
right
so you're not afraid you're not afraid
to hear a truth
a truth that can better your life a
truth that can move you forward a truth
that can break conditioning move that
out of the way the truth that can
literally unlock and start
breaking down that brainwashing that
this world has done to so many people so
the world is this big because they've
been brainwashed
foreign
I want to read I want to read a little
bit in brain saver if you guys got a
minute
I'm going to go to page 12 of brain
saver you guys wanna
this is kind of a little bit
different but it's interesting I thought
it would be just kind of really cool to
read
senso said this is so mind-blowing
another thing too is they're weaponizing
the truth
[Music]
you the term truth they're weaponizing
it right you see that out there they're
weaponizing my truth
somebody might have an experience but
it's not technically the truth it's an
experience they had an opinion but what
they're doing is they'll use that and
they'll just weaponize it that's my
truth right
that's a new technique
this actually helps to clean that up
so that somebody's observation
because here's what happens
a car can be coming around the bend
and run over somebody but one person
doesn't even see it
and another person does the person that
didn't see that car run over the person
is going to say I didn't see that car
run over the person that was my truth
the other person saw that car
run that person over and that person
said no
the truth is the car ran over the person
the other person saying I didn't see it
so my truth is that car didn't run over
that person
the truth stabilizer helps us so we can
see things more so we can understand
them more
we can understand if we've been hurt
emotionally
you might have been hurt emotionally
and not even know it
because we're conditioned
not to talk about it not to
feel it
and you
you shift something in the brain of
rewiring an insults you know what I was
hurt
the truth comes out I was hurt
somebody else with an observation be
like you weren't hurt you weren't hurt
at all
my truth says you weren't hurt and the
person's like no I actually was hurt
somebody asked what book this is
brain saver right here
let me read a little something in here
we're also going to make a really
powerful brain shot therapy one that I
am looking forward to and I just want to
give everybody an introduction right
here to what you just see in front of me
just so we know what's going on if you
don't have these ingredients right now
and can't do this shot right now I'm
perfectly fine and happy with that just
hang out with us it's okay this is free
this is free
so I got some garlic right here I got a
garlic clove I'm gonna dump in there a
little later I want to show you this I
got an orange I peeled it so that's
ready too I got oranges right there I
got turmeric I want to show you a little
turmeric I got peeled man when you peel
turmeric you know what happens if your
injures your hands are going to be
orange it's insane that kind of
anthocyanin right that whole all of them
those polyphenols everything that's in
there right the antioxidants all of it
anyway
and then we got the ginger right I got
the ginger ready for this I also have
basil check that out too basil powerful
herb arugula powerful herb that I use as
a leafy green leafy greens and then of
course lettuce I got a green leaf
lettuce
so these are the ingredients
but we're gonna start reading
all right I'm on page number 12.
I'm in brain saver if you guys don't
mind
I just want to tell everybody who's here
that doesn't have these books get the
books when you can get them free at the
library if you can but they're also like
50 50 off I know the brand protocols
right 50 off amazon.com us okay over 600
Pages they're they're just medical
Bibles each is over 600 Pages it's
insane let's get into it a little bit
your sensory input isn't the only
information your neurons decipher and
pass along
you smell
you taste
you hear
that information comes in and goes
through interior neurons right you smell
something boom your cranial nerves are
taking it in you hear something right
you're you're taking it in you taste
something you're taking it in your
sensory input isn't the only information
your neurons decipher and pass along
they also translate information about
your body processes neurons apply to
every single function your body has so
I'm talking about this for a minute
because we're going to talk about what
happens when neurons get all clogged up
with toxins and then all of a sudden
everything gets skewed in here
and you might know somebody that's like
wait a minute
that person's got some serious toxins
inside the neurons this is really
incredible information right here
neurons apply to every single function
your body has
so your brain your neurons apply to
every function and how healthy your
neurons are determines how comfortable
you're going to be in your mind and body
if you see somebody losing their mind
like their manic
they're running down the street naked
but they're not running down the street
naked because they made a decision to do
a prank
where they stripped off their clothes
they jumped out of their car and they're
running down the highway because they
wanted to
which I still think is probably
something's going on there but if they
but if they're but if it's somebody
that's running down the street naked
right
so your neurons determine how
comfortable you're going to be in your
mind and body that is neurons are
involved in both mental functioning and
your state of health mental functioning
your neurons are involved in that when
you have brain related symptoms even on
the milder scale such as a mild fatigue
or mild brain fog It's really because
neurons can't transfer information
properly to the next group of neurons if
anybody has fatigue now we're in the
whole speaking or true thing but there's
something in here that's interesting
about this if you're dealing with
fatigue if you're somebody with some
type of fatigue and that fatigue is more
than exhaustion
that fatigue is more than exhaustion
that means the neurons have something
going on something wrong with them now
of course we talk about what that is in
the books but
it's transferring information
to the next group of neurons and if
there's if there's something hindering
this pathway in the electricity with the
traveling of that information then you
get fatigue you get it you get you get a
problem you get a symptom
something is blocking or otherwise
impeding the pathway within the synapsis
so the neurons sending out electrical
impulses are not reaching other neurons
that need the information or not
reaching the neurons as intended so what
I'm getting to right now if you have a
physical symptom something's wrong
neurons in the brain with information
are trying to send that information to
areas in your body if your fatigued
something's going on with the central
nervous system your neurons okay
you can see this in everyday life when
you're telling someone a story about
apples and find out that the whole time
they thought you were talking about
oranges did you ever have that situation
you're talking about apples and someone
thinks you're talking about oranges
any kind of impedement within a person's
neurons can mean that the information
their neurons process gets altered
affecting that person's ability to focus
listener properly properly receive
information from a conversation or story
what I'm trying to say is
if something's going on in somebody's
neurons
and you're telling them a story
this is what happened to me
right
I was walking along the sidewalk I
tripped on a crack in the sidewalk
I fell I banged my head
and got up and then somebody on a
bicycle hit me
going by
I went to the emergency room I thought I
had a concussion
and they're telling somebody this and
this is what the person heard
they were skipping along on the sidewalk
and
hit a guy on a bike and the guy in the
bike went to the hospital
that's the story they heard
you're talking about apples somebody
else is talking about oranges
foreign
is that when you're you're talking about
a story that happened to you you're
talking about experience that happened
to you and you're telling the story to
somebody else and they're not getting it
they're like what happened to you what
you tripped you fell where what what guy
was on a bicycle is that guy okay you're
like no I'm the one that got hurt I
banged my head the guy hit me on the
bicycle I went to the emergency room and
you know you're trying to tell them the
story but but they're not really getting
it all so you have to tell the story
over again I don't know if you've ever
run into that have you ever had that
situation you're trying to tell that
story again
and you you're trying to get them to
understand you
so that person may tell somebody else an
entirely different version and so you
tell somebody your story and that person
tells somebody else a story that's not
the same story
because they're hearing it differently
from you
so you're telling the story to someone
a story that may have meaning to you an
experience that you had and the person
you just told that story to is now
telling a story to someone else
but it's not coming out the same
it's coming out differently
and it wasn't correct
then that person may tell someone else
with an entirely different version of
the original story that was told to them
this is how gossip and rumors can be
twisted and turned into hearsay as the
story goes from person to person it goes
through each person's contaminated
impeded blocked or diminished neurons
and the story changes
this is how a story can go from person
to person to person and the way the
story started out is not the way the
story ended
so the original story somebody spoke of
went through
all these brains
so the story you just had about your
life
went into somebody else's brain
and when it came out of their mouth
to someone else it went into that other
person's brain
and then it went from their brain out to
somebody else and went into somebody
else's brain
the story's changing each each time as
it's going along the story is not the
same the story isn't the original story
from where it started
it has altered
it's not the same story
it reminds me of a person I know that
worked on a cruise ship
something happened to them on that
cruise ship
they told somebody that was also working
on that cruise ship
it went to that person and then that
person told another person that was on
that cruise ship
and by the time it got around to all the
people who worked on the cruise ship
it got back to the original person and
it was an entirely different story
and there's a reason for this
because people have brain problems
because people have neurons that are
toxic
have all kinds of different short
circuiting going on in their brain
all kinds of different blocks in their
emotional centers of the brain all kinds
of different injuries in their brain
they look fine they seem fine but this
story changes as it goes along
so it goes into this next part this is
interesting though we're in brain saver
right here if you guys gotta admit it'd
love to read a little bit more as
electricity travels through an impeded
neuron system and this is this is really
incredible in for info when you think
about it it can become diminished so as
electricity travels through
people's neurons and people's neurons
are dirty
they get their toxic neurons
it diminishes meaning that electricity
within the brain is no longer traveling
at its full capacity
that is a group of neurons can receive a
fully charged electrical impulse and and
then in the process of assimilating and
registering that electricity which is
filled with information
and sending it through the synapsis to
another group of neurons electricity can
be diminished when electricity is
diminished the information within it can
be skewed changed and altered so what
happens is when you're someone's hearing
something
when they're hearing something
okay
what yeah
what happened to that person
all right
all right you got it okay I'm gonna tell
somebody else what
they fell into the water
somebody had to pull them out and save
them all right
yeah this person fell off a cliff
yeah fell off a cliff
yep I someone I don't know someone
helped him
really person fell off a cliff and
somebody helped them all right let me go
let me go tell somebody that
hey this person was hanging off a cliff
they were rock climbing I think and some
helicopter had to come and get them
oh really the helicopter had to come and
get them they were hanging off the cliff
okay let me tell somebody else about
this this is unbelievable yeah that the
Coast Guard had to come and help
somebody that was like they fell off the
cliff and they were they were at the
rocks at the bottom of the cliff and the
Coast Guard had to come yeah exactly
and that's how it works
Health list says the fact that we can
have contamination is such Advanced
information you won't find that in
neuroscience
I'll tell you what you find in
five top foods that are really helpful
for the brain one is Cacao chocolate
science is actually saying chocolate's
getting better for the brain Than People
another one is mushrooms you know the
kind of mushrooms
that's another one too psychedelics
another one is something that helps your
tear telomeres you're telomeres we're
finding that genes are are a big role in
our brains
another food source for your brains is
apple cider vinegar everybody should be
on a shot of that a day
and number five
some red wine
because red wine is the greatest of all
I bought a Vineyard a matter of fact
Melanie Belling says I am a teacher for
communication and that makes many
communication problems so clear
I am at your service I'm trying my best
to message the information from above so
that teachers like you can teach
incredible and I'm sure you're an
amazing teacher Beverly Harvey says how
can you tell the difference between
someone who is an evil soul and someone
who acts badly because of toxins and
metals in their brain oh my God that's
an incredible question and I'm going to
screen sheet that question because I
want to do a podcast episode on that
question
and then have Spirit of compassion
answer it because that's going to be fun
okay okay okay I lost my spot
I lost my spot sorry about all this
all right electricity can carry
tremendous amount tremendous amounts of
information
electricity you guys that's your
thoughts electricity in your brain
carries a thought
it travels
through your brain that electricity
electrical impulse has information in it
so the electricity running through the
brain is more than just a hot wire it's
not just life-giving vitalization hot
wires keeping us alive electrical
currents no it's not just that it's
information that's in the electricity
itself and then information has to
travel from neuron to neuron so that
information goes from one part of the
brain to another part of the brain and
if you got toxins in there that's when
that information go to one part of the
brain goes the other part of brain gets
skewed up you're talking too fast now
electricity traveling through your brain
can even carry information you won't or
don't use
that's interesting right there
electricity traveling through your brain
can carry information you're not even
going to use
it's there it's there for the taking
with the electricity and we let it slip
by because we're focused on another
piece of information I'm focused on this
candy bar I want to eat
but in that same piece of information I
I see a candy bar
I'm at Whole Foods I don't want that
candy bar right there it's it's a
healthy one it says it's healthy it
doesn't have any added sugar or anything
like that
I want to grab that candy bar
but in that same moment you're you're
thinking that that Pete that wire that
hot wire
that let's glimpulse has something else
in there
something else is in there you ready
what's in there is that candy bar I
don't think is good for me
because I heard somewhere maybe even
from the medical medium
the chocolate is actually really toxic
but nobody knows that
but yet they're not accessing that piece
of information they're only accessing
I really want that candy bar and that's
the only part they access within that
information on that neuron
we're trying to tell someone something
that we're getting from that electricity
and at the same time leaving out
information that's within that
electricity as well I'm only going to
tell you the parts of the story that I
want to tell you I'm kind of leaving the
rest
I'm going to tell you what happened the
pickup truck
rolled into town
and the tire blew out of that pickup
truck
but I'm gonna leave out the rest of that
information you know the truck ran over
some nails
it's so strange how our brains work it's
insane
we're trying to tell someone something
that we're getting from that electricity
at the same time leaving out information
that's within that same electricity as
well we may feel there was something
more to say oh my God here's what
happens if you ever have something on
the tip of your tongue
we call it on the tip of your tongue
right it's on the tip of my tongue
what the heck was it gotta tell you
something I gotta tell you something
yeah yeah no no I already told you that
no no I already told you that
I told you about that this is something
else what is it what is it
what am I thinking right now
do you ever have something on the tip of
your tongue right
it's on the top of my head somewhere
it's in the tip of my tongue somewhere
it's somewhere what was it
we may feel there was something more to
say yet we don't know what it really was
because it has already passed us by the
reason why we actually don't know what
it is in that moment it's on the tip of
our tongue it's because it passed by
already in that electricity through that
neuron and we didn't grab it as it was
passing by we did not access what that
was it was on the tip of my tongue man
and I didn't access it is what happened
we did not grab it out of that
electrical grid that it was passing
through that neuron it passed it was
there you knew it was there you know it
was there
what was it
were you going to say something else
your partner or companion or friend says
and we may reply yeah I was so busy with
other thoughts I can't remember what it
was we're not having a memory lapse I
just don't have a good memory I can't
remember what it was I was saying what
the hell was I thinking or saying I was
saying something I know where it was it
was on the tip of my tongue my memory
must be going I'm losing my memories
what was happening
you weren't losing your memory you
didn't have the memory laughs
it's like medical medium said this
that's not what medical medium said
do you guys see that out there wait I
want to ask you guys this do you guys
see this out there
medical medium said this
but medical medium didn't say that right
it happens too
I did everything medical medium and
didn't work it did not work for me
you didn't do everything medical medium
I did everything medical medium it
didn't work
I mean if I only was a fly on the wall
the I would see with people who
have said that that evolved that like
there's people on there that are paid to
say that all over Instagram they're paid
to go on there and say that and they
don't even do anything medical medium
and if I was to fly on the wall for the
people that do do some medical medium
stuff a little bit of stuff and they say
I tried everything medical medium I did
that it didn't work and here flying the
wall and you see what they eat and you
see what they do I'm not judging them
but if you see what they eat and what
they do
uh they had everything happen they've
went and gone they've also gone
we've also done this they've also done
that
they've eaten this
they've gone here they've gone there
I've tried everything medical medium and
it didn't work
you know
okay I just want to read a little bit of
this
it's crazy some of the stuff
you didn't have the memory lapse that
was what I was talking about okay you
just
did not access or couldn't access that
information that was passing by and
there might be a reason
those same people that say I tried ever
here's what's crazy here's a funny thing
right here okay I know I go off topic
sometimes I can't help it it's not
really off topic it's on topic you ready
there's some people out there that'll
say I tried medical medium and it didn't
work
those are the same people I find out put
lemon juice in their celery juice
those are but they think
they did it right
or those are people that like put water
in their celery juice or
we're only drinking four ounces of
celery juice a day a cup of celery juice
a day
eight ounces or something you know what
I mean and they say I tried all medical
medium
brain neuron problems
you know can also make it like that a
lot of people they're sick they don't
have look a lot of people are struggling
and this is
this is why like when people
say things
like that and it's not really accurate
to what's happening I never freak out I
just feel bad I feel bad because I know
the person if they're not a paid troll I
know the person actually thinks they are
doing everything medical medium so I'm
not judging them I mean yeah fly in the
wall sure and you'll see what they're
doing and it's like oh dear lord what
like what do they you know what I mean
you see that right and it's like oh no
they're not doing medical medium and
then or all of a sudden they'll do a
post out there or something and you'll
see you'll see it that way too and
you're like
so what happens is that but they think
they are they think they did they think
they did the medical medium stuff
they like got rid of like
dairy products for like a month and
they're like I did medical medium
but their brain neuron problem kind of
like falls into it whether they then
they convince themselves I did medical
medium and then they go on social media
like no I did medical medium
yep I did not mean it didn't work for me
don't do it it's bad it doesn't work
because they weren't underst they
weren't able to even understand the
information I mean honestly
I'm gonna tell you this right because
I'm not a rocket scientist
I'm not an educated medical doctor
I'm not a um whatever
this is this is a lot of information
so I can't judge people if they can't
really like uneven understand what
they're reading there's people out there
that said they read the book and I'm
like what
and they're eating an egg sandwich
see
no no I read the book and they're eating
an egg sandwich I said you know that you
know I talk about why you shouldn't eat
eggs in in the books like you did what
do you mean I didn't even I missed that
part
okay damaged neurons can change thoughts
altering how someone perceives
information
damaged neurons
can
change thoughts so that someone's
perception of what they're hearing is
like right
that's because damaged neurons mean
altered disorganized and poorly
reorganized electricity so here's what
I'm saying it's electricity that's all
kind of like
all distorted it's electricity
that's disorganized then reorganized
then altered
as that electricity travels through
synapsis and heads to another group of
neurons
information in that electricity could
become disorganized before it enters a
new group of neurons information
right
can like get reorganized and go to
another group of neurons
Vegeta says a lot of people think their
symptoms
sorry I'll start this again a lot of
people think their symptoms are detox
symptoms when that isn't the case
correct
whoa like this is a hot spot right here
this is no joke I'm actually working on
a detox podcast right now I'm working on
one it's not for the faint of heart it
is a serious episode and it's kicking my
ass right now because there's so much
information in this episode that I'm
just like oh
a lot of people think their symptoms are
detox says
on YouTube symptoms when that isn't the
case if you are doing what medical
medium recommends then anything beyond
very mild symptoms are from something
else
it's very wise
okay
check this out too and if any of the
neurons in that new group are damaged
hindered or injured when the information
gathered by that electricity gets
disorganized once again and it leaves
another group of neuron so okay let me
just say this
the information is traveling through
electricity it hits a group of neurons
that are all clouded up with toxins then
get scrambled and then leaves that group
of neurons and enters another group of
neurons
so it's not just brain tissue that
Harbors thoughts and controls controls
how we feel and how we physically
function electricity itself has also the
power over our thoughts and physical
control it's not medical research and
science has no idea the electricity
Harbors a thought
they think it's the thought it's just in
the brain tissue
one job of neurons is to eventually pass
along information to the brain's
billions of glial cells where
information stays stored cataloged and
organized if glial cells are clogged
contaminated saturated distorted or even
mutated from poisons and toxins that
disconnect and break down can occur
between your neuron system and your
glial cell system glial cells can lose
their ability to properly store
information so basically your glial
stores storage glial cell storage can
get all contaminated
and really toxic and when thoughts are
stored in that contaminated toxic Arena
that's another problem all on its own
some neurons in the brain not all have
the ability to spot check and
cross-reference new information with old
information so we do have a safe fault
in here where some neurons are like
correct corrected corrected correct it
correct it there's neurons in our brain
they're like no we're here to correct
all that skewed information it's amazing
Who would know this
if you have a hard time I'm hearing this
more and more if you have a hard time
thinking or believing
that these eight incredible books of
information
life-saving information came from above
if you have a hard time believing that
and that's in your way like you you're
just like this guy's hearing a
voice
right if you're having a hard time and
you believe that
if it makes you feel better just think
I'm a genius
it's not a voice
and I'm a genius
anything to make sure you get the
information in this resource so you can
protect yourself your family friends and
heal so just you can be like
he doesn't hear a voice he's just a
genius then find whatever it takes
I can promise you this I'm not a genius
definitely not a genius
I wish I was that would be pretty cool
some neurons in the brain not all have
the ability to spot check and
cross-reference the information like I
said when healthy when okay when healthy
these neurons have infinite access to
glial storage so here's there's neurons
in our brain that have access to our
memories in the gliobank electricity
shoots out or waves from these neurons
rolling along real cells to gather
information and then the electricity
filled that real cell information rolls
back to the neurons that is utterly
insane
get ready for this when electricity hits
a damaged neuron on the other hand small
outward explosions occur off the neuron
kind of like salt kind of like solar
flares off the sun these flares enter
adjacent brain tissue and glial cells
Gathering bits and pieces of information
and then subside and re-enter the
neurons okay that is like what the heck
when that information came down
from above I was just like how do I even
talk about this
so when electricity hits damaged neurons
it explodes
and small explosions occur and
leave
and enter
into uh into the glial cells Gathering
bits a piece of information and coming
back
since the neurons by the way
20 years from now whatever it is or
maybe even tomorrow a podcast doctor
will be talking about this this they
won't have a study that actually shows
anything they'll say they do or
something or not even they'll just use
this 20 years from now this is just
going to be literally the Forefront of
brain inflammation
we're we're at a really difficult
situation now medical medium and our
team and everything else
cooling Spirit of compassion where the
thefting and poaching of medical medium
information for Sciences use is utterly
at an unbelievable level right now
including
people in Alternative Health in every
world
and the poaching and not citing has
become actually disgusting it is at a
point where
you guys
I can't even go there right
anyway there's so much information here
I'm just going through it a little bit
so I'm on page 14 of brain saver
so maybe let's cut through a little bit
more if you guys have have you know it
in you
meaning like all of us here because we
want to make the shot we want to make
the shot
the reason we can each experience the
same event so differently from each
other is because of our damaged neurons
leading to disorganized information
someone can say no I
saw a spaceship
it landed behind those woods
and another person would be like that
wasn't a spaceship
that was car lights
coming off the highway the distant
Highway
another person's like no I saw a
spaceship you don't get it it really did
land I saw what happened it had lights
on it and that spaceship came down it
was like
and landed behind those woods and then
this other person who saw the same thing
is like no I didn't see a spaceship yeah
but
yeah but it was there no I saw
headlights you know the truck was
getting off the highway way in the
distance down there and I saw flashing
lights from it you know that's your
perception that's what you think you saw
but there was a spaceship that landed
behind the woods and there really was a
spaceship that landed behind the woods
so the reason we can each experience the
same event so differently from each
other is because of our damaged neurons
leading to disorganized information in
the end we may not all give an accurate
account of what happens so that person's
like no there was no spaceship that was
car had lights another person's like I
promise you behind that behind that
small mountain is the spaceship that
landed in those woods Carrie Pearson
said it's so us exclamation point I just
saw another big article
sitting citing your information and not
crediting you but citing Stanford oh I
got it citing my information to Stanford
and it was word for word your info yeah
they're doing that all the time right
now it's so sad because that means no
citing means no one will know where it
came from but they'll think that they're
smart
and then when someone mentions that
mentions mm they'll be like oh that
Medium God he's not smart
it's actually really bad
and then that person will go off and do
bad stuff to hurt themselves and they're
sick for another 10 years because
they'll never trust the medical medium
in a million years because they heard so
much bad stuff by the way you guys the
hit piece is coming out of me
periodically over the years and the hit
pieces that are on their way because
that's what's just always happening to
me with all the just stories
and lies is unbelievable the media has
never ever represented well actually no
that's not true there has been some
media Outlets that have that have had my
back but for the most part most all
don't
you know and definitely not fully
say we were camping out by a lake with
friends in a flashing light flew through
the sky one person may say I was there
and it was a firefly
someone else may say
I was there too it was a falling star
someone else believed it was a distant
headlight from a truck farther off
toward the horizon
one person thought it was a firefly
another person's you know thought it was
a falling star and somebody else thought
it was a truck it's a different thing
one than the spaceship thing I was
saying but all the same
this understanding of our neurons
impeded functioning is why when we ask
if someone's feeling okay we should
really ask how's the electricity in your
brain it's like are you okay today how
you feeling today it's more like
how's the electricity going through your
neurons today
are they disorganized
how are the neuro how are your neurons
today
have any of them repaired from your
night's sleep have your neurons repaired
from your night's sleep
have your glial cells been heating up
too much lately
are your neurons saturated into toxins
today communicating about our brains at
this level would bring about a whole new
understanding of our health conditions
and well-being
[Music]
all right
we're in this incredible speaking your
truth stabilizer that was just really
really incredible killer brain
inflammation
that you know that I want to show you
from Spirit of compassion but we're
doing speaking your treat stabilizer
right now
that information I just read you
is
really profound
mind-blowing when I wrote that
information down
I was mind blown
all right we're good speaking your truth
stabilizer
I'm gonna put the brain back together a
little bit right there
foreign
all right
let's do this
I have my juicer in front of me
look
it's no secret
I get asked about celery juice
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
of times it's a wonder I haven't lost my
mind completely right
because the questions are this
can I I'm doing celery juice and I put
lemon in it I doing celery juice from
the store
that was in a bottle you know what I
mean whatever
I'm doing this all these things and then
what juicer do you use what juicer do
you use and I get questions like that
over and over and over again anyway this
is the MN 1500 I'm using right now
mm-900 is another incredible juicer
um
and so every day it's like when is the
sale when is the sale when is the sale
so there's a sale right now on the 1500
900 just letting everybody know if I
don't say it what's going to happen is
after the sale is over people are going
to ask it's 20 off right now it's an
opportunity for someone
you know to actually get an incredible G
sure so why is it a great User it's cold
press masticating juicer which is
incredible
it's saves people money the food costs
are rising
they're Rising now here's something I
wanted to say real quick before we make
this job
I could have started a medical medium
juicing company 20 years ago
okay and been asked to do so and
literally I could be known as the juicer
guy and that's not what I did and we
don't want to do that
but food costs were rising and I noticed
the juicers out there
we're not squeezing enough juice out of
the out of the produce and people who
need to use these medical machines to
heal and get better
don't have a lot of money
sure rich people get sick too
okay and I get it and it probably rich
people who have a billion dollars can
buy all the produce they want and it
doesn't matter what juicer they use I
guess
but the point is
is that the prices Sonia said celery
prices went up too like the food costs
are insane right
but I don't want people to lose chances
of using medicinal tools that can help
them heal so I got involved with the mm
1500 mm-900 for a reason because I knew
through Spirit of compassion that we
were again gonna get a huge food cost
increase in the world and that's meat
that's beef that's grass-fed beef that's
Dairy that's eggs that's wheat that's
fruits that's vegetables that's nuts
that's seeds whatever it is
whatever anybody eats on this planet
rice beans whatever it's up boots McGee
says aw is it's totally true I even had
rose-colored glasses thinking I did all
medical medium my first years and looked
back and I was eating dairy and gluten
all the time it boots McGee thank you
for saying that you're so awesome
and I really appreciate it seriously
you're on YouTube
and thank you it means it means more to
to me than anybody knows thank you for
that
and by the way I'm proud of you very
proud of you
so anyway
Spirit of compassion predicted that food
costs were going to go up and if you're
like oh well then I won't get the juicer
because I don't want to spend money on
produce no food costs are going up for
all food everything beans rice peas
grains Dairy meat fish it's all going up
eggs whatever here in egg eater it's all
going up Carrie pierce it says the Omega
mm is saving me so much money I bought
it on payments and it is paying for
itself every month in the dollars I save
I swear to God
I'm saving money when I use the mm 1500
and mm-900
I know because I've used all the other
juicers and I had to buy more heads of
celery more things and More Produce and
I got less juice so there's these
spinning basket juices out there and
everybody's like oh those are the ones
to get don't get the mm juicers get
these spinning baskets that are
you know promoted by whatever
influencers involved whatever the
whatever it is right and
but what people don't realize is you got
to be rich
in my opinion you gotta be
freaking rich because those just you got
to put a lot more produce in those
juicers sure it may feel like it's
easier and you got your basket of juice
but you have to put a lot more produce
that's what I've learned in all the
different juicer centrifuge ones and
everything
I'm only talking about this because
food costs are actually going up higher
and higher
if they're not coming down
so it's like but we need ways to heal
ourselves we need medicine makers and
Medicine machines if I if I ignore the
food costs going up then I'm actually
being a jerk
because
it's like
we heal ourselves through our food right
we heal ourselves through the foods we
eat that's one of the ways we heal
ourselves and if I pretend
that food costs aren't going up
and never talk about it that's
because I'm noticing that with the
podcast doctors out there a lot of
people in alternative world they're not
talking about that
like the influencers who have money
they're not talking about that because
it's not hurting them
when they buy their produce and whatever
no one's talking about it it's like what
are we trying to hide it
it's like it's like demented the mm9 900
and 1500 are in the description and the
uh bio
too so just letting you guys know anyway
I just thought that this was something
that we shouldn't like pretend doesn't
exist so noticing that people
influencers of people want to help
move-in podcast doctors so they're just
not even talking about it's like what oh
that's right because it doesn't affect
you you got money for all the proofs you
want by the way there's a new omega this
is an Omega Juicer
Omega juicers.com right the link is in
the description they have and plus
there's a hotline now for this juicer
for customer service so it's a new omega
medical medium support line
okay it's in the description
it's just so you know and if you have
these juicers and you need a part
something's wrong whatever it is because
we juice like nobody's business like the
medical medium Community juices like no
one's ever seen I'm talking about holy
crap the kind of juicing
no here's what juicing used to be it
used to be someone just buying a juicer
it sits in the kitchen goes in the
closet they take it out once a month
that like we use these machines like no
other people in the medical medium
Community use juicers daily sometimes
three times a day usually for their
families they're juicing all day long
and they don't
they don't just use a juicer once a
month
or once a week or once in a while
all right
but I just don't think it's right
because I notice that
no one's talking about the produce and
the meat and the whatever industry going
up in price in the health realm and
health world no one's talking about it
and I'm like why why are you not talking
about it
it's like a car when a car you use a car
and you beat the hell out of a car and
you use that car and you drive you get
200 000 miles on that car it's gonna
need some parts changed every now and
then and we beat these juicers to a pulp
and so there's a 15-year warranty on
this juicer
the powertrain the engine and there's a
15 year warranty on the parts
other juicers usually only have a two
year warranty on the parts especially
the ones the spinning baskets and all
that crap right anyway I wanted to tell
you guys
that's what I noticed I was like I know
this is like a kind of a moment where
we're talking about this but I know this
nobody else in health like all the big
gurus out there the health gurus out
there and the YouTube doctors and all
that they're not talking about like the
food prices going up it doesn't have to
affect them they got plenty of money
they buy what they want to eat
but all I can tell you is
it affects the chronic wheel
all right right we're going to make the
hey
what's am I speaking am I speaking the
truth stabilizer now before I'm even
getting the truth stabilizer in me
I had one earlier
I had a treat stabilizer earlier this
morning
Lynn Western says we have used the
warranty several times and they take
care of us every time the warranty is
awesome the new hotline for the medical
median juicers is a great benefit to all
of us
the hardcore juice daily people Lynn
thank you
all right you guys let's make an excuse
what am I going to say once I drink this
what kind of Truth telling am I going to
say when I actually get this in me right
now within the moment
oh my God I might say all kinds of crap
all right
let's turn this on
I'm a little nervous I got some ginger
right here
one inch piece Ginger coming right up
right there dropping it down to shoot
yeah
two inch piece of fresh turmeric coming
up
boom
boom dropping it down to shoot
a little nervous one small clove of
garlic going down the chute
boom
garlic down the chute
half cup tightly packed fresh basil that
basil is really potent stuff
half cup tightly packed
oh man we're gonna run some basil
through here this is no joke actually
foreign
okay
half cup tightly packed arugula
one cup roughly chopped lettuce
such as green leaf or butter leaf
why am I yelling the juicer is quiet
this isn't those loud juicers if you're
if you're juicing for your family this
thing is so quiet it doesn't wake
anybody up in the household you can
whisper and still use this juicer why am
I yelling
getting the lettuce in
one more
another piece here okay and then one
orange peel
where's my fuel door there's my peeled
Orange right there already peeled
I'm going to send this orange down if
you guys don't mind I'm just cutting it
up a little bit
some pieces
so one orange
peeled here
nice
there we go incredible
amazing what you're gonna find with this
you'll see
the pull okay as it comes out of this
juicer
okay
stride
much drier
than the other juicers right
that's where the money's at
you would need three oranges
to get the same amount maybe even less
three oranges with the other juicers now
you can take your time you might have
some pulp when softer fruits go in with
this high compression you might have the
pulp come up here for a little bit you
can take your time and turn it on a
couple of times and it'll actually suck
it down eventually and you can add other
stuff too you know through it and it'll
just clean it right through
but but the amount saved is unbelievable
from this process
I'm not kidding like it's incredible
actually
foreign
like it's a lot more juice
that's the other thing too if you're
using the mm1500 the mm-900 you're going
to get more
from the ingredients that you're putting
in for these brain shots or any kind of
juicing you do
I actually saw there was someone who
showed me um something that was on
television one of the main networks and
they were doing a little juicing on
there
and the amount of produce they threw
through their juicer
one of the you know whatever thing which
is the amount of carrots everything it
was a joke what they got in the end and
I was like sitting there like oh my God
all right
get ready
you guys got your shot glasses ready
shot glasses
the 1500 also does sorbets hummuses
nut Butters nut milks salsas
how many I'm gonna even try a guacamole
in this machine I actually want to do a
guacamole in this machine I'm actually
pumped to do that all right you guys
let's get ready to pour these shots I
got enough for the easy couple okay
people ask what the difference is
between the 900 and the 1500 that's the
difference right there
[Music]
where's Dr Nesbitt
no no
all right come on now
the only thing with this one
[Music]
I feel this one just rushes right to the
brain really fast right to the emotional
center of the brain and it just blows it
up because what it's doing is it's
releasing stuff so you can think clearer
hear clear everything this is really
you yell at aw
[Music]
I'm serious
foreign
the truth is I wanted to do the robot
but I forgot
[Music]
I just didn't say anything about it but
now I'm talking about it
I was upset because I didn't do the
robot today
it was on my mind
first thing that comes out of my front
of my mouth
um
incredible
all right
[Music]
I just sent down two shots why did I
send down two shots
bartender give me another bartender give
me another
so good
[Music]
hold on let me see if I can find Dr
Nesbitt
where's Dr Nesbit
[Music]
you might want a shot
I don't know where Dr Nesbitt is but
[Music]
your husband might want a shot
Dr nesmet would you like a shot
[Music]
Dr nisman hangs around with a lot of
Stuffy doctors
we love doctors here everybody ask your
doctor what's right for you
what else should I say
uh Dr Nesbitt says ask your doctor
what's right for you and take the
medical medium books and information to
the doctor
[Music]
it's important have your doctor help you
with the information see what the doctor
thinks do what your doctor tells you
and um Dr Nesbitt
Dr Nesbitt wants to try the shot
Dr Nesbitt we did this yesterday and I
don't know if it was a great idea
but uh what do you think pretty good oh
nice Dr Nesbitt does like the shot there
you go you're drinking it and this holds
your horses hold your horses
chickens hold your chickens Dr Nesbit
um
oh my God that shot is so good you guys
incredible
Dr nesmond hangs around with a lot of
Stuffy doctors they buy Vineyards
you want me to do my doctor invitation
Elite core Awakenings over there
hellcore Awakening says on YouTube these
brain shots are so powerful they really
are they really are they're really
helped me they've really helped me
change and heal thank you medical me in
SOC
Dr nesbitt's wondering why you're not
thanking Dr Nesbitt
he's wondering what happened wondering
Wishing on YouTube says I love speaking
your truth stabilizer it has helped me
say yes I have been chronically sick for
decades
are you trying to get me emotional but
now I am healing with medical medium
like no more migraines and still say
it's after naysayers question me that
was naysayers those silly naysayers
Carrie Pearson says your brain shot
music is the best I want to play it with
every brain shot
Agostino says on YouTube the ability
medical medium has to speak about
serious stuff and still make
light-hearted humor out of it is
something else
I try my best
how about a glass of wine
and some some cacao to go along with it
Brent Winters I wonder how many
relationships could have been
could be saved if people had this info
that is very interesting Brad and
extremely inquisitive and and very true
Lynn Western says I love this special
challenge days
blessed to have 20 days in a row this
was day six what do you mean there's 20
days in a row I have 14 more days in
this
and I'm excited to have 14 more days of
this because I wanted to I want to be
with you guys talk about the powerful
information you know have a laugh or two
um Dr Nesbitt is tired of drinking the
shot he wants to Dr Nesbitt Let It Go
Darkness Let It Go the doctor doesn't
stop Dr Esmond recognize me you're not a
dog
that gives me you're not a dog with a
stuffed animal or a bone or tennis ball
Dr Nesbitt you're a chicken you're a
doctor for God's sake doctor just let it
go
whew
um
Mama Small says I know this cleanse is
working I've had so much sadness come up
the past two days as heavy metals are
released and emotions are also being
released over there on YouTube
how you guys doing on IG Dr nesmid is
here he says that he has a surgery
scheduled later on today
he's doing and
appendicite epidectomy right
oh Dr nesbitt's removing a prostate
later
that's one surgery scheduled
okay and
and even a stomach bypass that's not
good Dr Elizabeth can you teach people
who get stomach bypasses than if they do
medical medium information
they can avoid that surgery Maybe
okay what did you feel doctors let's
talk about it what did you feel what
were your results what did you
experience Dr Jessica where you go back
to surgery Dr nesbit's going back to
surgery oh geez
okay you guys share your stories if you
can on your reels and your stories and
your posts tag a medical medium and
hashtag medical medium bulks at the same
time so I can see it so I can see it and
then I can repost and share it
um what did you feel what was your
results what happened what did you
experience with the stabilizer we have
14 more days to go check out
medicalmedium.com it's we've really are
really upgrading and upgrading
and adding to that website check out my
telegram I'm leaving exclusive messages
and you know what I had so much truth
serum
truth serum here
I am going to leave a telegram message
later on this evening an exclusive
message on Telegram and God only knows
what's going to come out of my mouth
okay
you guys incredible
amazing I feel when I have these shots
do you guys feel that you feel like
rushed through you do you feel it in
your head do you feel it
bartender bring me another I saw that
Allegra
foreign
bartender
bring me another
alcohol free
love liberty dream says since I started
the brain shots I feel like a switch has
turned on in my brain that's what it
does
it says it in here it says it in here it
does it does stick problem on IG it says
it in here
but really that's what's happening
okay okay okay I
all right
I'll see you guys tomorrow
for day seven don't miss it check out
medical meme podcast at Apple podcast
and check out the podcast episode I did
on the heel podcast not my podcast the
heel podcast I did an episode there with
Kelly Noonan Gore's amazing friend of
mine and she got me talking on there
all right you guys I love you dearly