therapies don't always taste good
because it's just about the medicine
right but this one I happen to like I do
love this brain shot very much I use it
very much we're also going to talk about
micro dosing today
get ready for that you might want to
fasten your seat belts get your seat
belts on click them in
because we're gonna be talking about
micro dosing
talking about micro dosing is definitely
going to piss a bunch of people off but
that's okay because I don't know I just
gotta say the words from message the
words from above and we'll see what
happens
hopefully everybody's strapped in and
ready for the ride but today is about
finding
your true purpose stabilizer
day 20. oh my God day 20. okay
how many of you guys have gone 20 days
and if you haven't like I said yesterday
it's okay go three days five days that's
okay
but how many of you have gotten 20 days
we are
on the 20th day incredible finding a
purpose stabilizer I am making it today
I got my berries in front of me I got
the right well blueberry powder I got
the parsley in front of me I'm ready to
go let's talk about microdosing and
we're also going to talk about the soil
I want to prepare you we're going to do
a little bit of some soul talking too
psychedelics
that are considered plant medicine have
gained popularity recently with the
theory that everything is okay if you
micro dose it
don't worry everything's okay you're
micro dosing it right that's the theory
out there
now we're very confused in the health
World about what plant medicine actually
is
it's a trend to take something toxic and
put the term plant medicine in front of
it
so what the trend is is you take
something that's toxic to the brain
damaging to the brain and then place the
words plant medicine in front of that
toxin
and then it's okay
now it's okay
very interesting right
it's a trend to take something toxic and
put the term plant medicine in front of
it as if that makes it not toxic or even
not dangerous so when you stick plant
medicine in front of something it makes
it so it's like not toxic not dangerous
not damaging to the brain
totally fine
are you guys sure you're ready for this
on my page number 151
and I'm in brain saver are you sure
you're ready for this okay because I
have not talked about micro dosing and
we're doing a little bit on it right
we're still going to do a lot more on it
but right now we're going to cover some
Erica Malik life after this challenge is
going to feel a little empty
it's over the 20 day
the plant medicine label right
plant medicine label
is like an excuse to use plants that
have chemical compounds that hinder our
body hurt our body or set our healing
back yes I said it set our healing back
truth
as long as we put it in that plant
medicine category
it's plant medicine
a substance has immunity and is
considered a safe viable way to heal so
what's happening right now in the world
of micro dosing in the world of plant
medicine they're using the term plant
medicine to safeify it
to make it safe to safify it
that's what they're doing now it's
interesting really really the term plant
medicine should be all about fruits
that's plant medicine leafy greens
that's plant medicine
herbs uh-huh herbs
wild foods and vegetables
that are not mind altering
or adrenaline surging that's remember
that word right there adrenaline surging
keep that in mind
sources of plant chemical compounds
so what's happening right now micro
dosing is very trendy micro dosing plant
medicine
that's damaging to the adrenals is
actually trendy right now
that's not plant medicine that's just
something toxic that hinders and damages
the adrenals and the Brain
and liver
so really the term plant medicine should
be all about fruits leafy greens herbs
wild foods and vegetables that are not
mind altering or adrenaline surging
that's the next note right there get
ready for that fashion your seatbelts on
for this ride we're just starting
we're just starting
adrenaline surging
that's what Ayahuasca plant medicine
psilocybins a lot of other plant
medicines do cacao
adrenaline surging
sure it's a fun ride for some not
everybody it's a fun ride it's an
adrenaline surging ride
Aurora says can you explain what is
microdosing microdosing is where they
take something toxic like a psilocybin
or right Ayahuasca or something
I I can name some others too and I think
I will and if you put it in smaller
dosages because what happened with
Ayahuasca is originally
people would take large dosages of it so
when you go to an ayahuasca ceremony
right you would drink a bowl of it
you would you would Blitz and blast out
your mind so bad you wouldn't even know
who you were you'd be screaming and
rolling around in the dirt vomiting
pulling scratching your eyes out
I've had people come to me years ago
that scratched their own eyeballs out
during an ayahuasca ceremony would I
mean scratched they were blind forever
they dug their eyeballs out
with their hands
so what happened was too much of that
happened too many people got injured too
many people got hurt too many people got
brain damaged so they started to lower
the dosage with something no one thought
of
after all those years it was realized
maybe it should be a smaller amount
maybe it should be a tiny amount
and so micro dosing took on a whole new
world where it's micro dosing only do a
little bit of a toxic poisonous mushroom
only do a little bit of
Ayahuasca only do a little bit
Lolita's uh zat says I was Heavy in
Ayahuasca for many years and it would
it would end up destroying me for a long
period of time
oh sorry and it wound up destroying me
for a long period of time Elite I
totally understand so I'm just
explaining a little bit about the micro
dosing
and how that works
I mean honestly
and you know what's cool telling you
guys because I don't think a lot of you
guys get mad about this stuff but before
before I was like censored and stuff
right Shadow band and everything else
and
open to a large large Arena of people
seeing it man people would go berserk
right they go berserk it's incredible
how things work you talk about
Ayahuasca people get angry you know and
they still do out there
um let's go
so really the term plant medicine should
be all about fruits leafy greens herbs
wild foods and vegetables that are not
mind-altering or adrenaline surging
sources the plant chemical compounds
plant medicine should be about
blackberries
which is an incredible form of plant
medicine
plant medicine should be about wild
blueberries wild blueberries
blackberries are almost wild cultivated
blackberries are almost wild they're so
strong they're the alternative if you
can't do like the wild blueberry or
something like that right I talk about
the alternative the Blackberry is is
it's not it's not a wild blueberry but
it offers still partial partial
phytochemical compounds and partial
anthocyanins that are almost in that
wild state
plant medicine should be about
blackberries wild blueberries lemon balm
that's plant medicine
lemon balm
Rosemary Ginger thyme right it's a lemon
balm right there
Rosemary
Ginger thyme celery
celery is plant medicine
spinach
that's an incredible run that's
incredible
leafy green
an incredible
one
cilantro can't say enough about cilantro
and shiitake mushrooms
those are just a few examples instead
plant medicine is being used to give
benediction psilocybin mushrooms also
known as magic mushrooms or shrooms
ayahuasca
even
cacao
like cacao ceremonies intense cacao
consumers right
matcha tea and other green tea
let's go into the next section playing
with poisons this is really cool the
problem we have with both alternative
and conventional medicine we have a
problem with alternative medicine what
there's no problem with alternative
medicine Alternatives it's perfect
there's a problem with conventional
medicine
the problem we have with both
alternative and conventional medicine is
the same problem we have with Discerning
what plant medicine really is
no one knows why anyone lives with
chronic symptoms and conditions it's
obvious it's evident it's factual
spiritual path to true love says is
microdosing like Homeopathy nope it's
not Homeopathy it's not like Homeopathy
good question
this is an important part I'm reading
right here so check this out very
important part
no one knows why anyone lives with
chronic symptoms and conditions fact
fact
alternative medicines guessing games we
know that it's been guessing games for
decades
conventional medicine which cause
unknown with everything
marjor herb I know one guy who did it
and he was not even able to go home
family picked him up from the United
States and took him home to Europe
I know many people who have done it
Carnage is unbelievable
Spoils of War are unbelievable with it
it's really a sad thing all right
no one knows why someone has anxiety
depression bipolar I'm sorry but nobody
knows
I mean if you have the medical medium
books and you learn the truth about why
somebody has these things it's awesome
but Lana says Erica yes very scary I
didn't know about Anthony back then but
I know I learned what was exactly
happening to me it was damaging my brain
no one knows why someone has anxiety
depression bipolar disorder or OCD no
one knows why anyone has brain fog
fatigue or the Myriad of neurological
symptoms that we explore throughout this
book and the other books
medical media books medical communities
May categorize a given struggle as
autoimmune
that's not the same answer that's not
the answer
autoimmune still means we don't know why
anybody has any of these symptoms
conditions or health struggles so
autoimmune is not the answer
autoimmune means
your body created an auto antibody
to go and destroy your organs
without your permission
autoimmune is not why people are sick
I talk about this in the medical medium
books
pathogens are what's getting into
people's organs and injuring organs
it all falls into the same pot of
guessing game soup
the conventional doctor doesn't know why
you have depression
yet offers an antidepressant
the alternative doctor doesn't know why
you have depression
yet offers you a better diet
a regular exercise routine
the recommendation to get rid of
processed foods and the instruction to
take some vitamin D a multivitamin and
some fish oil
while not every doctor's visit will
yield these exact recommendations
whatever the varying recommendations are
they still won't be based on knowing the
true underlying why of your suffering
perhaps the doctor believes gut health
is causing your depression that candida
are sibo or leaky gut or microbiome is
to blame
ring a bell anybody perhaps the doctor
believes you have a chemical imbalance a
neurotransmitter issue such as a
dopamine deficiency whatever the case
it's still a case of we don't know why
you're sick
we don't know why you have depression or
chronic symptoms
Spirit of compassion just blows my mind
who talks about that who even who even
talks about this
no one
the same guessing game technique has led
to a widespread interest in psychedelics
and microdosing
Nobody Knows Why anybody's sick
getting the connection now
alternative medicine doesn't know why
anybody's sick
conventional medicine doesn't know any
why anybody's sick they both play
guessing games conventional might say
try this antidepressant try this
anti-anxiety Med try this antiocd med
try this antidepressant again
conventional alternative medicine
might say hop on the table get a few
needles thrown in your back
go off to the you know go off to the gut
doctor take a microbiome thing
head to the uh you know naturopath get a
new diet go to the functional medicine
doctor and get a test
a blood test but in the end
we're in this position where people with
severe depression still won't get an
answer
or other conditions still won't get an
answer so what that leads
it's a case of we don't know why you're
sick we don't know why you have
depression or any chronic symptom so the
same guessing game you guys the same
guessing game technique has led to
widespread interest in psychedelics and
microdosing
conventional medicine is talking about
using psychedelics now
conventional medicine is so lost with
why people have problems mentally
that they're trying to tap into the
Psychedelic movement
conventional medicine wants to
encapsulate and create and synthesize
psychedelics
and offer it for mental health
someone searched for anything to try any
answers leads them to the door of the
darker side of plant medicine it's the
darker side it's kind of like the dark
web
you have no answers you've been there
you've done that you tried alternative
medicine you tried conventional medicine
you feel like you're losing your mind
you feel like you're sick and you
stumble across micro dosing the darker
side of medicine plant medicine
I said for years that just because
something falls under the umbrella of
ancient
doesn't mean it's safe or perfect
in the ancient days
people would sacrifice people all the
time
a thousand people would go up
on a cliff
someone would come
half a thousand people strapped in
to a big wooden log a pole and they
would literally cut open everybody's
hearts and they would take out the
hearts of a thousand people
and throw the heart into a pit of fire
we're on page 152 we're in brain saver
reading about microdosing
it was ancient does that mean it was
good
does that mean it was great
sacrificing humans sacred ripping their
hearts out of their bodies cutting their
chest open the rib cage just explode
open because if you cut perfectly right
just the right fashion the rib cage just
pops
and it opens up the door like and that's
what they used to do for sacrifice it
they did that all over this planet two
thousand years ago three thousand four
thousand years ago
even later than that
your chest pops open your heart's
beating while you're still alive and
then they cut your heart out throw it in
a pit of fire it was an ancient practice
was it a good thing it was ancient so it
must have been good anything ancient is
great nothing wrong with anything
ancient at all
once it's under the umbrella of ancient
or ancient medicine or ancient whatever
it's great what about all the Mercury
elixirs that were given to people what
about Quicksilver
all through Europe in the 1700s in the
1800s they offered Quicksilver everybody
was drinking Mercury where did they get
that advice they got it from Chinese
medicine Emperors would drink would they
would drink Quicksilver it was just
Mercury elixirs right that was an
ancient practice
that led into Europe using Quicksilver
so Quicksilver was was the medicine for
anybody who was sick didn't matter if
you were a baby didn't matter if you
were an adult didn't matter who you were
you go to the doctor and you drink a
whole glass of straight Mercury you lose
your mind
and you don't even know who you are you
leave and you're tremoring and shaking
and your brains and your eyeballs almost
pop out of your head
that was the practice
but since it was ancient
must be perfect must be amazing
over the years I've heard this hundreds
of times the family reaching out to me
because their daughter or son was at an
Ayahuasca or other psychedelic ceremony
and barely made it out alive and it was
still to this day and still to this day
they're suffering from brain injuries
an IG
eni says I've watched my friend using
Ayahuasca slowly lose his mind every
time he did it then he started licking
frogs
that's another uh thing too by the way
is the Frog poison I forgot to talk
about that I've got him on the heavy
metal detox and it's really making a
difference because it's bringing his
brain back
frog poison is another thing another
micro dose
practice
that's such a neurotoxin a frog poison
it's the craziest thing
Amber says my dad took a lot of L LSD
in the 60s and he is the most depressing
person I'm sorry to hear that
there's of Ayahuasca or other
psychedelics will say the practitioner
leading the ceremony was the problem
whoa but don't worry my ayahuasca
um practitioner my Ayahuasca Shaman I'm
not it's not about shamans being bad or
good or practitioners being bad or good
it's whatever my Ayahuasca Guru
does it way better my Ayahuasca gurus in
LA
and does it for like all the cool people
he's the best
it's you know yeah you had a bad trip
you had a bad Ayahuasca dude
but you know what I hang around with the
cool people in LA
all right
I know all the who's who
so I got the cool shamans and the cool
Ayahuasca gurus and we don't really get
hurt
yeah I've heard that effortless Endeavor
says have you seen the leading experts
in Psychology are now totally promoting
psychedelics I am I talked about that a
minute ago where
conventional wisdom is heading there too
I know
yeah because they're desperate people
are sick and when you're sick and you
can't find anything that works you can't
find the right
protocol to help people with all these
different conditions
you don't know the answers
you don't have the answers
protocols see protocols you don't have
the answers
and when you don't have the answers out
there yeah even conventional medicine is
in the top psychology you know experts
are going to be playing around with
psychedelics of course they're desperate
desperate to get somebody something
but they're just gonna
they're just gonna have them up
jumping on Trends is what they're doing
they all do this science says it's great
but down the road once billions are
damaged and mangled
science will say it's not good anymore
but science never pays any prices
just the people
foreign
Defenders of Ayahuasca or other
psychedelics will say the practitioner
leading the ceremony was the problem and
that you have to be careful who you
choose to guide you
I've heard that one a lot in the
Psychedelic realm you didn't have the
right guy guide you with the Frog poison
but now you can't speak or talk because
it totally screwed up
your brain stem
this is not to disrespect anyone
involved in Ayahuasca ceremonies or any
kind of indigenous technique of
spiritual healing
foreign
because that's what also somebody will
someone will say to be like oh you're
just what are you harping on indigenous
people
because Ayahuasca was originally a whole
indigenous thing is that what you're
doing medical media
so this is not to just disrespect any
involved in Ayahuasca ceremonies or any
kind of indigenous technique of
spiritual healing indigenous cultures
have also grown bananas
it's interesting right
indigenous cultures have grown bananas
that's a plant medicine
indigenous cultures have also grown
spices such as vanilla bean cinnamon
turmeric and ginger
there are non-toxic these are non-toxic
and have healing properties plant
medicine
while some of these can be self-limiting
meaning that large quantities can be
irritating
like spice they are not dangerous
our brain does not see them as an enemy
nor does our immune system or body or
adrenals at the same time whether we're
an indigenous culture or not we can all
grow eat and play around with poisons
many non-indigenous people become guides
or practitioners who administer
psychedelics
it's really important to know this
information rising out of the ashes says
oh my God I had a friend
that did that don't have contact with
her because she lost it reality and she
got so spaced and so paranoid so sad
what I mean to address here is the
person who's looking for answers to
chronic illness the person who's
desperate to try anything and gets
further injured in that process Landing
a life of much more suffering and
hardship than they already had with
their condition
people in their lives may pass it off as
a bad trip sweep it under the carpet
first of all I gotta say something be
really clear here I'm not just talking
about somebody who does
a whole bunch of acid has a really bad
trip and everybody's saying I'm not I
don't do drugs I don't do drugs I micro
dose with like a careful with a careful
guide and and that's not doing drugs
people have to understand that like this
is this is
a really important
part of it all
because someone's going to say that's
not me that's somebody that
is doing some heavy drugs
and they lost their mind because of a
bad trip
but that's not what I'm talking about
here I'm talking about every day people
who aren't doing drugs they don't
they're not about doing drugs they're
looking for answers and they get pulled
into this whole spiritual aspect of wait
a minute the answers are in the
spiritual experience you're going to
have when you do some micro dosing it's
safe it's a small amount it's not like
it used to be you're not going to be
tripping like you're on acid and people
are LED into this but that's what I'm
talking about people in their lives may
pass it off as a bad trip because
they'll have a bad trip from that too
sweep it under the carpet and call it
their Journey
saying it was supposed to happen
here's something really sad to know
right now
is that when someone does get injured
in a retreat
after doing ayahuasca
everybody else
tells them
it was supposed to happen it's part of
your journey
the person's like going home
with an injured brain paranoia severe
OCD
severe delusion
adrenals completely fried
brain fog crazy brain fog they're going
home like wait a minute I thought this
experience was supposed to be good I
thought this was supposed to be good I
thought this was supposed to be good and
then everybody at the retreat's like oh
that was supposed to happen that was
your journey that was your spiritual
journey you're going to learn from it
you're going to grow from it
how do I know this that's what I've seen
happen so many times
and that they had to learn something
meanwhile it was an injury and not a
positive experience of any kind for
anyone
it was just a flat out injury
it wasn't
a positive experience and now it's about
how do we recover from that
maybe what maybe no one even realizes
that their brain health is declining
from injury
whether a decline that continues over
time after one trip or a steady decline
with each psychedelic experience another
problem that happens if you're not
taking care of your brain
it can decline over time from this stuff
I told you guys have to fasten your seat
belts for this ride
micro dosing new marketing for
psychedelics
I'm in the next section I'm on page 153
of brain saver this is really good
information for day 20 of the brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge this is the
last day of the 20-day challenge an
incredible day finding your purpose
stabilizer why are we talking about
micro dosing we're talking about finding
our purpose because that's another
reason why so many people lead to micro
dosing because they're trying to find
their purpose they feel sad they feel
lost they feel insecure about everything
in their life and they go to try to find
their purpose through psychedelics
maybe you know somebody
microdosing the new marketing for
psychedelics the landscape around
psychedelics has changed in recent years
the mistakes of the past consuming High
dosages of psychedelics are less common
like I was saying earlier they don't do
big bowls of Ayahuasca and everybody
takes a huge sip of it they do small
amounts they even put it inside little
candies and other stuff you know the
game
too many obvious injuries have occurred
and how now there's the term microdosing
to clean up the mess
the term microdosing was created to
clean up the mess
it's unbelievable
we talk it up as though if we micro dose
we give ourselves permission to partake
don't worry it's only micro dosing it's
okay everybody's doing it
it's like a new level of stupidity
happening
let's see Chef Tien it says I was
injured and told it was part of the
journey also told the dose was too much
such BS
thank you for leaving your comment that
was on IG
we give ourselves permission to partake
as if it's now a controlled environment
because micro dosing is controlled
that's how we're supposed to be led to
feel
oh it's micro dosing I can handle that
it's control and since everybody wants
control over themselves it's like no
that's controlled so
sounds like a small amount it it's
probably going to be fine
term microdosing makes us feel safe
it makes us feel safe
it's like ah don't worry it's only micro
dosing
so the human psyche microdosing also
implies that there's some scientific
nature involved like someone figured
something out
so it's like oh my
ayahuasca
practitioner Guru
Shaman my Ayahuasca guy says it's micro
dosing so he has it all done so there's
a science behind it there must be this
great science behind it when it's not
there's nothing behind it it's just a
smaller dosage it's someone's kind of
like shimmying up
accounts bookkeeper says on YouTube this
is true both my brothers who passed away
from these substances were blamed by the
community of substance user they were in
as being flawed or being too sensitive
or too too susceptible
my God
this still my heart pours out to you
it really does
it starts getting me upset because you
know
yeah
I could read into it pretty deep and
it's it's rough
um
check this out to the human psyche micro
dosing also implies that there's a
scientific nature involved but there's
none
we feel secure in the sense that there's
some type of Science advising it well
there must be like some scientific setup
on that
don't worry conventional medicine is
taking psychedelics now and they're
going to be making their own
prescriptions and dosages and everything
else and you can call it micro dosing or
whatever you want to call it
right don't put the science behind it
they'll just make a smaller dose or
something
really interesting
so here's a comment Laquita says it just
seems like this is a little extreme
it doesn't have to be a yes this is good
or no this is bad there's so much Nuance
to psychedelics I'm not sure how helpful
this is
well we're getting into pretty soon if
you can stay on here
we're getting into what psychedelics do
to the brain which is actually really
important but I don't know if you were
here a couple of minutes ago when I was
reading some of the comments
some families were destroyed
some people died
life was lost and some people lost their
minds just with the few comments I'm
reading from people's experiences
laughs
and
I'm all connected into the world of like
who's who out there and doing different
things and people are micro dosing out
there
that's just what they're doing and
people are getting injured by it
actually injured
so what's the nuances
some dude had a good
had a good thing about it and
or some person had a good thing that
happened with it and just that's a
Nuance don't worry about the other
person who gets injured
I don't know what those nuances are
what about if somebody's scale wasn't
tipped yet and they go and do it
you follow those people later in life
and guess what their problems are worse
or you follow the people that are
offering micro dosing and psychedelics
you follow them later in their life see
where their life is in 10 15 years ask
them what they're doing now chances are
they'll be like I don't do that anymore
that stuff really screwed me up you just
don't know you don't know what the
future brings you don't know the people
that are actually doing it how like 10
years later they're like I can't even
touch that stuff I did that stuff and I
think it screwed me up but you won't
know
I I I appreciate your question but hang
on because I want to talk about you know
if you could stay here I want to talk
about the rest of it about the brain
we feel secure in the sense that there's
some type of Science advising it that
some types of study has occurred and
proves efficacy
as you've learned about scientific
studies
they're really just theories combined
with never-ending games of trial and
error done by people
done by a person
science are people
science isn't this machine this massive
machine
where it's this big computer base up in
the sky in the heavens and it knows
everything and that's science so science
can never be wrong it's this big giant
orb that's floating up in the atmosphere
that knows everything
science is a bunch of people screwing
around paid money to screw out in a lab
hoping that human error doesn't blow at
every second which it does
Gabriella I lost three friends because
of Ayahuasca I nearly died as well
Gabriella I'm so sorry to hear that
truly
but apparently the other person that
commented said well you can't really
whatever I seem to nuances and
I respect everybody commenting I'm just
saying that it's it's it's just like
as you learned about scientific studies
they're just theories combined with
never-ending guessing games trial and
error from humans
labeling drug
use as micro dosing provides a sense of
safety to a wider variety of people it
opens up the gamma to a whole bunch of
people who are sick and nobody knows why
they're sick nobody has an answer to why
they're sick their mental health is
declining they're suffering they tried
everything that they can find already
nobody knows why they're suffering
emotionally and mentally they're
struggling out there
and then psychedelics is the new answer
microdosing is the new answer
it's just another total just screw me
over kind of deal and that's just the
way it works it's sad
now it's tempting to many more people
who would never partake in this someone
would never partake in any of this stuff
but when you label it micro dosing and
kind of put like a little bit of a
science behind it it opens a door for a
huge Floodgate of people to be like all
right I'll try it
Dr Nesbitt doesn't even do psychedelics
but he's here today and he's actually
going to be talking about microdosing
and other things and the prescriptions
he's he's taking that he prescribes
himself
on IG
yemri says how come I connect it to my
soul
and felt unconditional love for the
first time when I did Ayahuasca could it
be that even though it's a toxin it
connects you to a source we are coming
to that in just a minute will you please
hang on for that answer it's actually
coming the answer is mind-blowing
now it's tempting to many more people
who would have never partaked and and
didn't feel like they would partake
unless they had some kind of Science and
monitoring to it which makes you feel
like micro dosing is science it's no
longer just a niche crowd Meech crowd a
people who go into the desert sit around
a campfire and drink a whole bowl of
psychedelics
it's no longer that anymore that still
exists that's still happening but it's
not like that anymore it's this micro
dosing thing marketing has now made it
seem like science has been applied to
psychedelics
it hasn't
a tactic that pulls in a much bigger
crowd
a hippie dude in his basement
putting droppers of ayahuasca
on M MS
and calling it micro dosing
there's no science to that
the term microdosing acts as a safeguard
it makes someone believe that the person
and I like hippies I'm not happy I'm not
anti-anybody
whatever
said a doctor the other day call me a
hippie because I have a ponytail
let's have a bun
I was like what did you just call me
so you go like the hippie do going on
you're like a hippie I go yeah sure
whatever
fine
it doesn't bother me it's great the term
microdosing acts as a safeguard it makes
someone believe that the person offering
a therapy and using the term microdosing
knows a lot it makes you think that they
know a lot especially when you're
younger you're younger and there's just
an older dude who's the shaman or the
guru that's playing around with the
micro dosing the Frog poison and stuff
and here you are you're 22 years old and
you're just like whoa I'm here my
brain's totally messed up I want answers
I want a spiritual experience and it's
like you got this dude he's 30 something
years old he's an expert at micro dosing
and he's putting exact amount of fraud
poison on whatever and he's putting the
exact then you're just like whoa yeah
good luck
breaks my heart it makes someone believe
that the person offering a therapy and
using the term microdosing knows a lot
that they're very smart or well educated
in the process they're offering well
educated
maybe that's true to some degree that
the person offering a micro dosing
technique knows a lot about the theory
yet even if you know a lot about a game
it's still a game
there's still a wake of people injured
from psychedelics people who went into
microdosing therapy with migraines for
example and ended up with migraines that
were far worse coupled with additional
symptoms
I know people that went into
microdosing
safely
so they called it
and ended up and ended up
with some worse migraines what
psychedelics do is put the body in a
crisis state
get ready for this
when we go through a crisis State and
come out of it we change in some ways as
a person
critical
critical to know this
huge piece of information from above
what psychedelics do is put the body in
a crisis
state
wait to hear this when we go through a
crisis State and come out of it we
change in some ways as a person
what I'm about to read to you that's
coming up
believable
it's like surviving a 10 car pileup on
the freeway
your car flips over two or three times
and you seem to walk out of it with a
mild concussion while others around you
died
there's something that happens inside of
us when we survive any kind of crisis
and that falls into spiritual change
and when we induce ourselves with the
toxic chemical compound that throws our
body into chaos I'll ask anybody frog
poison psychedelic psilocybins
after it subsides we feel we spiritually
grow
keep on going
on IG
Julie
I did one of those ceremonies it ended
in disaster for me awful do not go near
anything like that
if it wasn't for me doing medical medium
info it could have ended really bad for
me
asanya says wow this is truly waking me
up
okay here's the next part
remember I said fasten your seat belts
just get ready for the ride
I might need some lemon balm which is
plant medicine
good stuff
addicted to survival there's an
addiction process that occurs with any
dose of psychedelics did I hear what I
said there's an addiction process but
wait you hear this there's an addiction
process that occurs with any dose of
psychedelics the addiction to
how did we survive that
that was a heck of a ride
and my spiritual teacher told me how
much I've grown by doing it
and I think I'm ready to do it again
does that ring a bell
anyone
especially when my spiritual teacher
told me how much I've grown by doing it
there's an addiction process that starts
to occur
One Of The Addictive aspects of
psychedelics is the adrenaline surge
that occurs when the poisons enter our
bloodstream this is a big one when that
adrenaline's surging
as the poisons because the poisons enter
the bloodstream and your adrenals just
explode that is a spiritual
like experience all on its own because
it's life or death
adrenaline being released that's your
adrenals exploding like releasing piles
of fear and Chaos adrenaline
it's so addictive
One Of The Addictive aspects of
psychedelics is the adrenaline surge
that occurs when the poisons enter our
bloodstream when any kind of poison
enters the bloodstream our body has to
release a steroid compound
to soften the blow so the brain hearts
and lungs don't take the hit so hard
when that poison enters your body that
micro dosing poison enters the body
a steroid compound has to be released to
try to save your brain
Carrie Pearson said this is totally
mind-blowing thanks aw and SOC
a dose even a micro dose of psychedelics
is no different
as our brain starts to get poisoned by
micro dosing it sends an emergency
signal to the brain stem and then out to
the adrenals
looking for the adrenals to save its
life
okay
when that microdosing poison enters the
bloodstream your brain is begging your
adrenals to save its life
that's the spiritual experience
your brain
is desperate for steroid compounds
it's begging the adrenals to flood
everything it has
to try to save itself
an intense adrenaline blend is released
to stop Strokes from occurring when
you're doing ayahuasca
and other psychedelics
and blood clots from forming
adrenaline is the blood thinner
when your body goes into chaos when
you're getting the microdosing and
psychedelics
microdosing of psychedelics
your brain begs for the adrenals to save
its life so that strokes and blood clots
don't occur I'm unpaid someone asked 154
brain saver
foreign
the left hand upper paragraph could read
along with me
left side
an intense adrenaline blend is released
to stop Strokes from occurring in blood
clots from forming
in part by thinning the blood and in
part by opening blood vessels back up
with steroid compounds as the vessels
are closing from the poison
when you're putting in the Frog poison
when you're putting in the psychedelics
when you're putting in all this crazy
psilocybins when you're putting in the
Ayahuasca your blood vessels start to
constrict from the poison inside your
brain
your brain calls out for help to your
adrenals your adrenals release a steroid
compound to try to stop your blood
vessels in your brain from constricting
so they don't close up
and create a stroke
I probably think this is one of the most
profound pieces of all of this
is as your adrenals have to flood all of
this adrenaline which is just crazy fear
and Chaos steroids and they have to get
to the brain in time so that blood
vessels in your brain don't close up and
in your heart so blood vessels
throughout your body don't close
why are they closing because they're
poisoned
why do we need that blood thinning
effect question mark because our immune
system responds to any poison in the
body as a foreign invader
and it tries to stop the foreign
Invader before it gets to the most
critical places in the body such as the
brain in the heart and the lungs
our immune cells try to devour check
this out when you put Ayahuasca in your
body your immune cells are trying to
devour it
which can actually create a blood clot
because it's attacking the poison
desperately to try to stop it
four four Starlight on YouTube my friend
died from aneurysm post-psychedelics
you don't want to hear that it's just it
just kills me it's it's heartbreaking
Reiki with Daria says I did Ayahuasca
once was not planning to but convinced
my Shaman convinced by Shaman I trusted
prayed for no trips I was just coming
for energy healing offered during the
ceremony a month later my health issue
started so the tip the scale was tipped
the scale was to talk about how that
happens our immune system is built with
knowledge in it our immune system has
Intelligence by the way you guys our
immune system is highly intelligent it's
the most intelligent
you gotta see all those little immune
cells if they were little brains
our immune system is built with
knowledge and information in it to take
risks to protect us our immune system
knows
that a kerosene like corrosive substance
adrenaline also known as epinephrine is
coming its way in seconds
to dissolve the clot which will separate
the immune cells and try to open blood
vessel passageways so there's less
constriction and poisons can leave the
brain and body so check this out
your immune cells when you're on the
psychedelics jumps on the Psychedelic
poison and that's where the blood clot
starts happening
your immune cells are jumping onto the
Frog poison psilocybins the ayahuasca
they're jumping on it and when those
immune cells jump on it they Clump
together
at the same time they're clumping
together the poison itself is
constricting blood vessels throughout
the body and the Brain
and then the adrenaline is coming and
your immune cells know adrenaline is
coming and it comes in to blast the
white blood cells off the poison and
thin out the blood so the blood vessels
start to open this is a highly Advanced
information this is medical medium info
information from above original and
unique and it will be probably just
taken and poached like everything else
along the way does that of the medical
meaning books and not cited back
but then we'll just keep on putting new
stuff out over and over because spirited
has an endless Treasure Trove of
incredible information to save lives and
what I'm talking about goes against the
trends
and that does mean no favors
everybody else puts their tail between
their legs in the health movement
they put their head down
and they just go with the trends
so you never have any friction
but I have to watch over the chronically
ill and have their back
because it's a somebody has to have
the back of the chronically ill
eat better crap and all the other stuff
is all fun all fun and games but
people have gone through hell and back
they've been through a lot we have to
always remember that
chronic wheel have always been swept
under the carpet
mistreated
now adrenaline isn't kerosene
but it's corrosive
it's not paint thinner yet it has a
similar property as paint thinner and
kerosene in it
that can start to dissolve and break
down a blood clot that's thickening
that's why when somebody has a stroke
from a blood clot their adrenaline
starts to race and their heart does this
adrenaline's flooding into their
bloodstream to try to dissolve a clot
says our immune system gathers around
the poison in this case with psychedelic
substances and tries to eat it up and
absorb it a large number of white blood
cells surround the drugs poison chemical
compounds
the white blood cells start to group
together and become a clump that can get
caught in blood vessels
that's a blood clot
from psychedelics then adrenaline enters
the scene and starts to break up that
clump
I was like oh I just did some micro
dosing and has no idea this is happening
inside their body
just did some micro dosing
light codes on YouTube it's hard being a
student in the field of counseling and
the only one against psychedelics
Hey Brother
right there with you
heal infertility on IG wow the
explanation is remarkable I did magic
mushrooms once and my brain felt fried
for months after I was 20 years old
IG health of Hannah I am getting chills
all over my body while listening to this
it's powerful information and it's
mind-blowing information
this chaos
this chaos is part of the addiction to
psychedelics this is part of the
addiction
this is part of what gets people to come
back they don't know this is happening
inside their body but this is part of
the addiction
even to micro doses of psycho
psychedelics or any other poisonous
substance this is the chaos part of the
addiction to psychedelics that
adrenaline release into the bloodstream
to thin the blood and protect the brain
in that moment from the onslaught of
chemical compounds also saturating the
brain creates extreme adrenaline highs
at the same time these poisonous
chemical compounds the psychedelics
such as the ones found in psychedelics
start hitting neurotransmitters in in
neurons and and a hallucinogenic effect
occurs even if it's mild
the brain affects we associate with
these substances both the adrenaline
High and the hallucinogenic effect occur
because of what's being consumed is
toxic the hallucinogenic experience
is what we're talking about the
aftermath is that we're coming down off
that adrenaline High our body is in the
process recovery as the poisonous
chemical compound is dissipating and we
survived it we survived that micro dose
foreign
it's not exactly the same as recovering
from a party where you got completely
drunk and stoned and puked in the
bathroom all night and then spent the
next day in the stupor of a hangover yet
there are similarities and it's very
addictive
you want to go out again
next week
get totally shit-faced
totally puke all over the toilet seat
it's addictive page number is 154
rain saver
whichever substance sends your body into
survival mode remember that survival
mode
their parties you'll never forget
whether it was around a campfire doing
micro dosing and psychedelics
experiences that become etched in your
Consciousness you'll never forget it the
parties we never forgot aren't cures for
depression anxiety brain fog fatigue or
neurological symptoms they only worsen
them
one of the saddest parts of psychedelics
is knowing a 25 year old or 28 year old
who doesn't have any idea why they're
sick
he's seen a number of doctors tried a
number of medications can't find relief
mentally or physically and then stumbles
into the world of this can heal you
physically and spiritually it's one
thing
if you're not healing
so you take some junky vitamins try a
range of animal protein and plant-based
diets try a few different therapies and
healing techniques try conventional
Pharmaceuticals and you're still stuck
and you're still sick that's a better
place to be than getting caught up in
the world of psychedelics believing that
maybe you have a spiritual block that's
keeping you physically ill
what
so the saddest thing is like a 25 year
old a 22 year old a 28 year old whoever
are old right they have no idea why
they're sick
and they stumble across these micro
dosing things
and they get told you could heal
physically and spiritually
this is different
than if someone was just taking junky
vitamins
trying a range of animal protein diets
and plant-based diets try different
therapies write all the different
therapies and techniques
and that can be bad but this is still
different trying conventional
Pharmaceuticals
and you're still sick that's a better
place to be than getting caught up in
the world of psychedelics believing that
maybe you have a spiritual block
how many lives were destroyed from
people thinking they had a spiritual
block and meaning take psychedelic it's
okay to think you have a spiritual block
it's okay to think you have a spiritual
block I'm not totally denouncing that
I'm not totally saying are judging that
that's okay it's taking a poisonous
substance
because you think that
Roni gets free on IG I took mushrooms in
college and got sick immediately and
threw them back up lied to my friend
saying I was feeling it and didn't take
any more thank God
that's where it goes wrong a lot of
people lie to friends so they other
friends don't think
that they're weak
and it's why tons of stories out there
right you hear it
it's why it's how drugs are protected
out there too so a lot of people out
there it's not what you did when you
were saying you were feeling it but
there's other people right that could
have told you it was going to be great
and it made you sick and the other
people that were you know that told you
it was going to be great
they could also be lying right
you were just telling see you were just
telling your friends you were with but
you didn't go out there telling a whole
bunch of other people it was great but
there were people out there that do
they'll tell everybody it's great
they won't tell people what really
happened and that's why there's tons
tons that's why there's not tons of
stories out there there's a lot of
stories out there people getting hurt
but there's there's not tons of them and
tons of them because people don't want
to be uncool
and they don't want to you know
look uncool
Siana says you literally are saving
Humanity one person at a time aw no one
else on the planet could say that
Toady toad official
it's a pretty cool handle
what makes people feel like they had
incredible spiritual experiences
adrenaline from going into survival mode
yes I was just reading about that
foreign
it's from the brain dying it's basically
a near-death experience
even on a small micro dosing level it's
you may not think it's a near-death
experience but your brain and your
adrenals and your body think it's a
near-death experience
and your soul is scared to death of
what's Happening
and so that makes that spiritual
part of it all
when we lose time and we're exhausted
and we don't have answers that
are working or helping the next easy
sell is it has to be you you're the
problem
this is a spiritual issue
you're the problem
you're sick because you have a spiritual
issue and you're the problem
a mental and emotional problem
the psychedelics will shift something
within you
bring you spiritual growth
take you on a spiritual journey where
problems can be solved so the outcomes
of how you feel physically and
emotionally can improve and be healed
that's what they tell you
this is uncool for me to say this
this is so uncool for me to say
right here
when we lose time and we're exhausted
and we don't have the answers
and nothing's helping check this out the
next easy sell is and this is really
uncool that I'm saying this
it has to be you you're the problem
this is a spiritual issue a mental and
emotional problem the psychedelics will
shift something within you bring you
spiritual growth see I'm not supposed to
be saying that bring you spiritual
growth take you on a spiritual journey
where problems can be solved so the
outcomes in how you feel physically and
emotionally can improve or be healed
what I'm saying is people out there are
being told this and that's uncool for me
to stick that in the light
I get hate and hit pieces constantly
written about me there's always a new
hip piece coming out on me always it's
been happening for years because I bring
life-saving information out there out
there to everybody and it goes against
the money and the trends
but that's really really
annoying
when I read that part
to the world of the microdosing money
world oh it's all free
microdosing is all free all those
psychedelics is all free everything's
free no it's a money it's an industry
the micro dosing industry is a money
industry so when I say this right here
the line that they feed
everybody to get them to do micro dosing
when I say that I'm not supposed to say
that because it's just uncool for me to
say it
but it's the truth
I wish SOC sometimes doesn't put things
like that in there because then I get
more stuff more hate but SOC said it's
going in long-term damage is not worth
the trip
you guys this isn't over
there's a section in here called every
addiction starts with micro dosing
there's a section in here called the
ultimate price
oh
[Music]
this thing has got more information
you gotta read this
all right let's make the shot
[Music]
making the shot then we're reading Souls
goal
after the shot we're reading this you
guys want to hang you know what it is a
special day it's day 20 and I just want
to do a little extra reading and
and this is this your Soul's gold it's
on page 261 of this book right here I'm
gonna make the shot and then we're going
to read this after
all right so let's look at this shot
which is incredible finding your purpose
stabilizer right here so let's look at
this
use the finding your purpose stabilizer
if you have the sense that you're
missing out on something and you don't
know what it is
if you're somebody that's missing out on
something but you don't know what it is
but that's the feeling like you're
missing out on something
this is a great
incredible stabilizer right here
try this shot if you're feeling lost or
out of place do you feel lost do you
feel out of place try to finding your
purpose stabilizer
try this shot if you have a sense of
sadness
a sense of sadness that you don't even
know why is there just this mystery
sadness that comes over us try the
shotgun
try this shot if you don't ever feel
satisfied are you in that place where
you just nothing is satisfying
try this shot if you feel you're not
living your life
You Were Meant To Live or you're not
fulfilling your destiny
try the shot if you feel like you're
lost you've lost your free will or you
want to access your free will
that's amazing
try the shot if you're feeling
unproductive
finding your purpose stabilizers if
you're feeling unproductive just get the
drought and just do this
I mean ask your doctor what's right for
you if he's okay with you eating berries
and parsley
finding your purpose stabilizer try this
shot
if you don't
know where you're going in life
samima says and this shot takes you on
what kind of trip
I like that question a lot
not the trip that Ayahuasca takes you on
or psilocybins or frog poison
or an OD of cacao
finding your purpose stabilizer you can
try it if you've lost meaning with
anything or everything you're doing
did you lose a meaning
I mean
I can even get hit with that a little
bit
you're working for God
like so many of you do like everybody
right you're working for God
and
then some hate comes
to try to slow you down and he said why
am I even doing this then
why and then you gotta reset and be like
I know there's reasons
it's about saving lives
Justine and Justina says this shot
changed my life I left music and became
a health coach I never felt happier and
more aligned incredible on IG amazing
memisub says your light blast brought
purpose back into my life can't wait to
try this shot and there's going to be
another light blast I don't know when
yet but you have to keep on the lookout
when we heal and get free of toxins and
toxic heavy metals and pathogens and
we're fueling our brains and bodies with
the right things we reconnect to our
soul and purpose too the purpose
stabilizer is really interesting though
because it's uh
blend of things no one knows works
together it's not any berries it's
specific berries with the parsley it's
information from above of how it really
helps it's designed to go into the brain
and make a difference all right
and it's specific amounts and specific
ingredients
all right you guys I'd say we get fired
up did this quarter cup
fresh
or thawed blackberries
quarter cup
so these are frozen blackberries
they're not
fresh they're frozen and they're thawed
out
so letting a quarter cup of these in
there we go
so a quarter cup of fresh frozen
raspberries
they can be fresh or frozen I'm using
Frozen
they're thawed
thawed frozen raspberries you gotta thaw
them out
if you don't thaw them out
you're gonna have like some kind of
weird ice cream
you're making it's not gonna squeeze out
a lot of juice if it's if it's actually
not thawed
so I'm sorry if I haven't said that so
I'm putting both these quarter cups in
here
okay
next is quarter cup of thawed frozen
strawberries
and I'm trying not to make a mess today
because I tend to make a mess
is what I do
I don't know about you guys but I
actually do make messes
and then a quarter cup of tightly packed
and I'm listen I'm mixing the blueberry
powder though in the end in this
situation
so now I'm going to use some blueberry
powder you can use fresh or thawed wild
blueberries
but I'm using blueberry powder I'm going
to mix in
later
so what I'm doing is the berries
especially when they're frozen they take
a little time and I'm going to run some
parsley and now
this juicer is incredible because you
would have to use a lot
of berries to run through
a juicer to get the juice out of berries
and what I love about the juicer is it
actually squeezes so much so there's a
lot of compression but it's so worth it
so I'm going to put some parsley in here
we go
these parsleys have big stems so I'm
kind of putting it stem down
there we go
and if you tightly pack these you just
need a little bit more here
let me get these down in here
there you go
put this last one in here
now this is your purpose stabilizer
finding your purpose stabilizers
there we go
fantastic
so I'm just squeezing a little bit more
juice out of here
now you'll find the pulp is really
extra dry with berries
Lucas
Lucas Thompson down there
you demonize psychedelics and push this
garbage
foreign garbage
really
is parsley garbage
Lucas Thompson says don't buy into it
ladies
there's Frozen blackberries and
raspberries garbage
I'm just confused here
kind of confused at that one do you have
a better comment do you have a better
hateful comment
this Lucas can you give me another
comment that I can actually understand a
little bit like maybe some other hateful
one
if you got another one is what I'm
trying to say because that one really
sucked
because it's hard for me to kind of even
go along with that one for fun because
parsley
is incredible plant medicine
and berries are unbelievable for our
health so if you say that I demonized
psychedelics but push this garbage throw
another comment I'm just waiting to see
if it comes up like you got something
else
call me ugly or something I don't know
something that's like a better one than
that
I don't know
I'm just saying
right so what I'm doing is with this I'm
gonna
what I love about the screens
if you have a strain or a screen with
this one you can just kind of like
massage what's left through
Lucas buying this is like buying a get
rich quick
patreon box
Lucas are you okay are you doing too
many psychedelics
Lucas I'm gonna try to call you right
now I just need the phone ring Lucas I'm
gonna try to call you
just hang on I'm going to give you a
call I'm gonna give you a call right no
Lucas do you have the do you have the
um
do you have my kitchen number over here
at my house
Lucas call me now
Lucas give me a call
foreign
powder in a second too
but Lucas is calling really quick
Lucas give me a call do you have my
kitchen phone number
I think we just DMG that no we didn't
but you have there it is you have the
kitchen number just hold on
foreign
thanks man
dude what's with all the hate
yeah
it's okay for everybody else in the
world to like recommend a juicer but I
can't
do you realize like this is the only one
out there that actually saves people
money
yeah
so
what calm down the psychedelics you're
mad about that
are are you doing the Frog poison are
you doing the psilocybins
what are you doing are you doing
Ayahuasca Lucas Lucas listen to me
yeah
Lucas people can get my books for free
Lucas I can start my own Juicer Company
tomorrow a medical medium juicer line
like my own company
I can sell 5 000 programs
yeah instead of just read I just read to
you Lucas for an hour for free
uh-huh Lucas Luke calm down Lucas calm
down
okay
Lucas
ask your doctor
what's right for you
that's what I would do I would ask your
doctor what's right for you
ask your doctor if the psychedelics are
right for you
see
does your doctor approve of your
psychedelic use
it if you think taking these
psychedelics is
ask your doctor if it's okay that's what
I recommend
that's my advice friend to friend is ask
your doctor your doctor knows best if
your doctor if your doctor says to take
this psychedelics it's up to you and
your doctor
Lucas you're actually really cool
you're an awesome person
you are
yeah
thanks man I appreciate it
I am ugly
I know I'm ugly that's that's fine that
was a good one that's much better than
the other one
yeah blackberries should try them
raspberries yeah strawberries you should
try them
uh-huh and parsley Lucas
you can try parsley Lucas but just if
your doctor says it's okay for you to
try parsley you can try parsley
okay a doctor says it's okay for you to
eat berries and eat berries
but do what's right for you and what
your doctor says okay Lucas I gotta go
all right
yep thank you for calling and you're
really nice actually you're actually a
really nice guy
I'm actually honored to know you and
honored to have this call with you
you're actually a really nice guy Lucas
all right
thanks so much for commenting all right
bye
all right
oh my God I gotta mix in some wild
blueberry powder
foreign
says there are many scientific studies
and trials being done at the prestigious
colleges such as Stanford University
that are showing no adverse effects and
very successful results look it up don't
just take this guy's word for absolute
truth
do your own research
huh
so you mean that science has never made
a mistake before
that's interesting
didn't science make the hugest mistake
in just the last couple of years
science like I I'm confused the science
never makes a mistake because
I thought science was Some Humans they
were doing trial and era with air with
theories and then science then
crushes that scientific study and then
they're wrong there then they're wrong
there then they're wrong there it's each
hypotheses over and over and over again
I didn't know science like was the
end-all
that's great
now that I know it I was educated that
science
can never be wrong
my God they're doing studies on
psychedelics oh then I better run out
and get some psychedelics because
science is studying them
whoa
that's actually a really good idea
all right I'm gonna pop in a little bit
of
um
well blueberry powder in here
this stuff is insane
this is insane insane insane
Brad Danielson this is a great therapy
need a pink phone
now what you'll see right here I wanted
to show you guys something right check
this out you see the clump
do you see the clump right there
ready
do you see the clump
look
vimorgy
doesn't put
anti-bonding or anti
caking agents
see that that's how incredible the
company is the only one that I know of
that doesn't put anti-caking and
anti-bonding agents in here get guess
what all the green powders out there and
all the different powders
because remember she has like incredible
powders right all the mushroom powders
all the green powders
there's undisclosed hidden caking a
anti-caking agents and anti-bonding
agents inside those powders undisclosed
and not on the ingredient list right
here
and this is why I endorse these guys
never do this
this is incredible the only company I
know so far
that doesn't use the anti-bonding and
anti-caking agents that you don't know
you eat because if they don't they don't
list they're allowed to not list it on
the label
and Bemidji I want to see a clump once
in a while and sometimes you won't see
clumps it's just so fresh but it's
incredible
Wren says my son loves the comps he
thinks they are like candies
foreign
says as a scientist I believe in you
Lucas
you there
a few okay
hey
um there was a scientist
right here commenting and says he
believes in me
and the person is a scientist
yeah
so kind of take that for a second
put that in your Bonnet that feather in
your cap there or however you want to
see it
that doesn't make sense Feathering your
cap
listen Lucas not only that
right someone said that scientists at
Stanford are working on psychedelic
research and that I should read the
study
and I had a scientist on here a second
ago that just said he believes in me
yeah
well you're welcome bye
[Music]
anyway I just put the wild blueberry
powder in here I was just telling you
and you guys know why I endorse these
guys and that's one of the reasons which
is
unbelievable
and that's the difference we're talking
about no hidden undisclosed
people don't realize this they don't
know what this is they don't know that
when all the green powders all the fruit
and vegetable powders all of the
mushroom powders all the greens green
powders all the powders
undisclosed hidden caking agent
anti-kanking engine I can't say that
anti-taking agents and bonding agents
say that like four times in a row really
quick
they don't use that
Cindy Layman says Lehman says the
massive f up
that was the last three years is brought
to you by the science laugh out loud
Cindy yeah but science knows everything
holding the light I'm a scientist too
and believe in you
and love your info for healing me and
Humanity holding the light
is a scientist on YouTube
that's incredible thank you for being
here and all kidding around I can't tell
you that does that that means
more more to me than you know like
seriously like you know I know I fool
around a lot and everything but I'm just
trying to say that
that means a great deal to me
I don't take that lightly at all
Lucas Lucas you're back
oh no wait that's a different one wait
I don't know
that's a different Lucas it's a
different Lucas Lucas
it's a different Lucas
brazaka yep
that's right a Lucas with a K nobody
can't break medical mediums Bond
because everything he says is working
okay
I'm sorry you guys I'm really sorry to
do this
Lucas
another Lucas was on here yes
and he says
something entirely different
just take a look at the comment when you
get a chance
I won't bother you anymore
filmsley says
homsley says science is really like you
said the opening of a discussion it is
in your books
if only people could remember that
all right guys
finding your purpose stabilizer
the music
[Music]
you know this is day 20. it's a longer
episode we're live right now
and we're still going to read your
Soul's gold so everybody hang out for
that
oh God I just love this one
it's easy to lose track of your purpose
it's easy
to lose track of it
[Music]
hmm
why does this one taste good
because they don't all taste good we
know that
here goes Juliet
and send it all the way down
[Music]
bartender give me another
oh day 20.
now that says
an IG I am a functional medical doctor
and recommend you to every patient and
use your info for them
God bless you seriously amazing
then thank you thank you
foreign
I don't throw those words around lightly
it's very special to me more than
anybody knows
oh my God I can't get enough of this
shot
so good
[Music]
all right I'm gonna read a little bit
real quick
[Music]
amazing
so I'm going to read
your Soul's gold and before I do that I
just want to say you guys what's your
experience with this what do you feel
leave a real story
tag on medical medium hashtag medical me
at the same time so I could see it I
would love to share it
okay so I'm in thyroid healing if you
got a couple of minutes
and I'm reading
and I'm reading your Soul's gold
since gold was discovered
it has had a magnetic pull on us one
that goes far beyond any monetary worth
as a child
did you ever wish for a gold star on
your paper at school
I did
I never got a gold star
because I'm not a genius
as a child did you ever wish for a gold
star on your paper at school
it wasn't because
you could take it
to the pawn shop and get cash for it
you yearned for that cheap sticker
because of what it represented
achievement worthiness approval
as a child did you ever wish
for that gold star
because it was like
you did good there was something about
it
if you have a grandmother's favorite
locket or ring
again
it's not the dollar figure behind that
gold that gives it a special place in
your heart it's the spiritual meaning
appreciation Nostalgia loyalty love
and do Olympians go for the gold because
of the market value of the metal
do Olympian athletes take their gold
medal to the pawn shop no they spend
their whole lives training to win
because of what the price stands for
blood sweat tears Spirit Will and
tension
and sacrifice that come together into a
moment of human greatness
when spiritual and emotional meaning are
connected
to a piece of gold or other treasure
its worth is on a level above price tags
the Knights Templar went searching for
the Holy Grail not because of the money
they would get for this gold vessel
but because of the mystical significance
it was said to hold as the cup Jesus
Christ drank from at the Last Supper
though the knights turned up hundreds
and hundreds of gold cups
they were cast off as worthless because
they didn't hold the power it was all
about the spiritual meaning the gold
cups weren't the cup Jesus Christ drank
out of
I'm here to tell you
that you don't have to go on in Epic
Quest
earn anyone's approval
inherit a family heirloom
learn to high jump or have an
overflowing bank account in order to
claim the world's most precious treasure
gold
Platinum diamonds sapphires the Holy
Grail the Ark of the Covenant Noah's Ark
even the Beatles lost album
none of these hold a candle to your
Soul's gold
and gems and jewels that you already
carry inside of you
yes you
I know it's been a struggle to deal with
health problems or great loss or
hardship
I understand where you might have
suffered as you wondered if you were
aging before your time
if you thought you were calling it quits
and if your body was giving up on you or
even working against you
I can only imagine what you've gone
through in your search for answers
it's probably left you defeated at times
lonely despairing
and doubtful of your own worth know this
it's not your fault
you didn't deserve any of it
you didn't create your illness or
imagine it
you're not a bad person
you can heal and move forward
all that time that symptoms were
limiting you
they were giving you something too
that compassion you gained from being
vulnerable
that wisdom that came from watching life
at a distance that faith
that there had to be an answer
that Supreme patient
patience of putting one foot in front of
the other
these are yours to use for the rest of
your life
losses
struggles wounds suffering pain
sorrow fear
hardships trials
letdowns
and battles are not are not what any of
us would choose
when they visit us
no
we get our greatest tools and treasures
those tools and treasures can be heavy
to be in touch with the world suffering
is not easy just like a bag of diamonds
and gold it can weigh you down which is
why it's time for you to come into the
spiritual significance of your
challenges because when you attach
spiritual meaning to your Treasures
it makes them light as light
itself
you've been picked out of the crowd as a
special person who can change the world
because you hold power
illness
try to hold you back
you probably experienced symptoms along
the way and this may have gotten you
labeled with a whole bunch of different
names for what was supposedly wrong with
you
yet the plan of you being picked on
backfired
instead of being constrained
you were pushed forward and forced to
grow and develop in your soul and spirit
you gained understandings and insights
that brought you closer to God
that's your Soul's gold right there and
thyroid healing
that has tremendous meaning in my life
and I hope in yours my blueberry dreams
on IG says aw the Betrayal and broken
trust shot
has helped me cook
my brain down and stop getting stuck on
thoughts about the people that have
disappointed me in my life
not even therapy could help this
it's gonna make me get emotional not
that one
Tammy says
clinical trials often times contradict
each other
they always do
that was me adding they always do you
say clinical trials will back up what
you're saying question mark I bet at the
same time you can find clinical studies
that won't back up what you are saying
exactly I remember many years ago
studies where Garlic's good for you
Garlic's bad for you Garlic's good for
you Garlic's bad for you studies saying
Garlic's good for you again nope still
you say Garlic's bad for you what is it
Aurora says these 20 challenge days is a
retreat for me
and did not need to spend
any money in luxury hotels
that's a relief to me
because that was the point
20-day free medical mean brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge I'm getting
sad because this is it 20 days
this is it
um
I want to say a couple things
um but you know what Dr Nesbitt said he
was on his way so let me just
uh Dr Nesbitt Dr Nesbitt
Dr Nesbitt do you want to say goodbye to
everybody on the 20-day challenge at all
it's Dr Nesbitt is he coming back here
Dr net the thing about Dr Nesbitt
just uh
things about Dr Nesbitt is he
he self-medicates that I don't think
it's a good idea I tell him it's not a
good idea but he is a surgeon and he is
a doctor so I don't I can't tell him
what to do you can't tell Dr Nesbitt
what to do Dr Nesbitt
um
yeah no we got we got a lot of people
here today this is a really good time Dr
Smith can you tell everybody what's
going on
Dr Nancy doesn't agree in micro dosing
he says he as a doctor he thinks it's a
bad idea
yeah but you gotta tell them what you do
Dr Nesbit is gonna tell you what he does
Dr Nesbit doesn't visit his doctors in
his Clinic anymore because they're
always trying to give him what he thinks
is Direction that's not suitable for him
being he's a surgeon and a certified
psychiatrist he says he's been
prescribing himself medication so he's
one of those doctors he prescribes
medication to himself
and uh
he says that he's having good luck
lately he's been on a few different
medications
um
that sounds good you shouldn't be
telling them this Dr Nesbitt says he's
not going to talk about it anymore he'd
rather talk about psychedelics he said
that he had a patient come in
yeah
yeah Dr Nesbitt said he had a patient
come in
is that right am I am I telling the
story wrong you told me the other day
it's okay he had a patient come in and
they came back from a psychedelic
retreat
no
they came back from a campfire that's
the second time there was a retreat
right it says yes it was a retreat it
was a retreat our Facebook has been done
a lot of medicine Pharmaceuticals right
now he says he took a bunch he's been
having he's been taking sleeping pills
at night he's having a difficult time he
says nobody should do that he said they
should talk to their doctor
about whatever they're doing
Dr Nesbitt says that he is tired
he says that the patient came back to
see him
he has a Psychiatry practice and the
patient had extra brain fog
the patient after eating psychedelics
ate a big pile of dirt on the ground at
the campsite
there was a worm in the dirt
he said there was a worm in the dirt and
a toad in the dirt and the patient
started biting the Toad's head off and
eating the dirt
Dr Elizabeth said that's correct
he said that the patient he says he's
seeing this patient
um tomorrow again for another uh session
the patient bit a Toad's head off
and then he jumped on the patient jumped
on
another person that was at the ayahuasca
ceremony
he jumped on the person and he took the
Toad's body and he tried to put it in
that person's mouth and he held him down
on the ground
what did he was he losing his mind Dr
Nesbitt he started screaming he said he
started screaming
and he started spitting all the dirt out
of his mouth onto that person on the
ground and then another person at the
Psychedelic Gathering jumped up
grabbed him
dragged him down to the pond
and threw him in in hopes that the water
at the pond would wake him up out of his
trip
Dr Nesbitt said in the end they said it
was a spiritual journey
the person who got injured on the ground
that the patient jumped on
that person set was told
at the Psychedelic Gathering that it was
just her journey
and not to worry if
his patient jumped on her
and shoved the Toad's body in her mouth
and she almost choked to death
and she hurt her shoulder really bad and
everybody at the Ayahuasca Gathering
said that it was just part of the
spiritual journey and it'll give
everybody spiritual give her spiritual
growth
Julie B Lee says he's making stuff up
left and right fake news for sure
Dr Nesbitt is insulted
Dr Nesbitt doesn't make anything up Dr
Nesbitt is a certified surgeon
and Dr Nesbit is a certified
psychiatrist and he's telling a story
I'm sorry G lay B
that you don't like Dr nesbitt's story
yeah no I know that person was probably
at the same place I know I know
Dr Elizabeth says it actually happened
sorry to say that but it actually
happened
um anyway let's make a long story short
Dr Nesbitt says
the woman who was injured
um woke up the next morning
had a really bad rash on her face
and a really bad sore throat
and went home that day early before the
next
ayahuasca
Gathering was going to happen that night
oh my God
one crazed Dyer says one one craze
doctor says
well sir one crazy
Dre says the catchphrase your spiritual
journey has become the new Trust of
science
um that's actually ingenious and that's
brilliant and that's true
Dr nesbit's not happy about that though
because Dr Nas Dr Nesbit is all about
science
there are things that you want it you
want me to do the imitation of the
doctor at your clinic be sure it's
doctor at your clinic or is it somebody
else
I like a glass of wine
is there a glass of wine anyone oh
is this a glass of spirits here is this
a glass of red wine
okay so you guys
can I just say Jill F says
what an amazing 20 days with UAW thank
you for all you do and share with us so
much love and appreciation for you gonna
miss these days together I am going to
miss it too was 20 days of a lot of fun
um getting healthy getting stronger
getting everything getting nutrients to
our brain oh my God the shifters the
stabilizers right I mean the exposures
like incredible Julianne says I'm sad
the 20-day brain shot challenge is over
thank you for the great information I
plan to re-watch your videos and do the
shots
hmm Dr Elizabeth says thank you for
supporting aw and thank you for
being so awesome
you guys I think this is probably a bye
bye
and I don't know all 20 days will be on
medical medium.com you can do it for
free
there's no charge
what there's no charge but I'm a podcast
doctor there should be charges for
everything programs subscription fees
oh I should have lots of advertising in
front of my podcast yes I can make
millions of a podcast doctor yes it's my
career I'm gonna find a niche marketing
career is
foreign
says I hate how they keep saying things
are bad then change their minds I'm so
grateful that your information is truth
and it will never date or change and if
you know medical meme information is
consistent doesn't contradict itself but
you know what a heck of a lot of eat
better books and eat better doctors and
podcast people and and health
influencers and podcasts Health
influencers change by the week and the
month and the year they got more colors
than chameleons that can change their
color instantly they're doing one thing
then they're doing another then they're
doing another and they're doing another
by the way science takes medical mediums
information and Dr nisbet's getting
upset because he says yes it's true Dr
Elizabeth does say science is poaching
medical meme information
okay
this has been a long day 20. and uh Dr
Nisbet says bye bye bye
I wish Donnie the donkey was here but
Danny nangi just
he's Donnie the donkey hasn't been in
the mood
all right
Dr Elizabeth says bye doctor said Dr
Nesbit doesn't like the episode where we
talk about Mike the chicken and his head
being chopped off
foreign
he says he can't stand that episode so
he's telling everybody to not watch that
medical medium brain shot day
he says don't watch it Mike the Headless
Chicken
um the whole story about Mike the
Headless Chicken still has him upset and
he's been scared since he's worried I'm
gonna chop his head off and see if he'll
live that's what Dr Nesbit said
Dr Nesbitt I'm not going to do that I
would never chop a chicken set off
plant life
lean says yes my urologist agrees with
your info incredible
incredible
okay you guys
I will see you
God bless you
thank you for joining the free challenge
I had a great time
truly
and I'm so proud of you all and that's
really the one thing you know I've been
fooling around with the phone and
everything but I'm really proud of you
guys and that's like a fact
it's the truth
I I mean honestly I'll talk about it
next time we even talk about everything
keep a light heart
Keep On Healing and I love you guys