[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
medical mean Brave job therapy cleanse
challenge
you guys
EMF and 5 G exposure
let's get all the devices out
nice
you guys exciting time
we're doing it in math and five G
exposure shot got my ingredients here I
got my brain saver books about you guys
here we are right there brain saver
greatest books in history hands down I
could have my own opinion because it
came from above I can judge it just like
anybody else but you will be blown off
your seat when you're reading what's in
these books and we're in the brain shot
therapy challenge which is incredible do
you guys you guys see it do you guys
read the lines do you read the lines in
these books in between the lines and all
around through these books packed with
information
incredible really and today is the EMF
5G exposure shot that's the one we're
doing let's take a look let's get there
now
you guys doing you know work on your
devices you're on your computers you're
on your phones that's what I am I'm
doing it all day long every day man and
that's the whole thing so let's go and
take a look there it is
EMF 5G exposure shot right there
so you just entered the medical medium
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge day
four if you're unaware of what's going
on stick around so you can learn because
it's going to be exciting there's so
much information here it's really
incredible all on its own so
the AMF 5G exposed shot let's talk about
that for a little bit ready okay try
this shot
if you spend a lot of time on computers
and computerized devices
so you do this shot if you spend a lot
of time on computers and computerized
devices right
so that's that okay how about this one
live near a high voltage area
does anybody live near a high voltage
area most people do most people do right
so let's see what else we got too here
right
all right
we got how about this one spending time
talking or texting on cell phones are
you guys doing that
spending time talking texting on cell
phones right I got my cell phone right
here
and
I'm doing it all the time I'm like
I got the phone I even put don't put
your phone to your ear I like it on
speakerphone but I'll even put the phone
to my ear all the time I mean I will do
that
but I have this EMF and 5G exposure shot
is what I have okay traveling by plane
is anybody traveling by plane that's a
whole nother one all on its own so
anybody traveling by plane right that's
another thing too
live or work close to others while
they're using devices so you live with
people that are using their devices
you're living with people that are
actually using their devices so that's
another thing too you're always around
them they're always doing using their
devices right the whole bit okay
spend your day within several feet of a
router how about that one so spending
your day within several feet from a
router
living near a cell tower and at this
point now
this point now we're all living near
cell towers it's very few of us that are
kind of so far from a cell tower but get
this if a cell tower can reach
your phone
or your devices it doesn't really matter
too much how far that cell tower is away
right
so that's something right there to
actually be concerned about all on its
own all right so we got that
so we're doing the EMF and 5T exposure
shot now here's the thing this is going
to be really exciting because it's that
powerful
and the medical mean brain shot
therapies are giving people direct
relief which is incredible instant
relief so let's go and look around here
for another little spot to talk about
so medical medium brain shot therapy
that's where we are now
so
we're in the actual
we're just moving through here you guys
these are big books a lot of information
so medical mean brain shot therapy so
here's what's incredible about it that's
exactly where I was a minute ago
so here we are
your brain and body have a quick
response to the liquid aspect the highly
absorbable rate of what's happening when
you take these shots it goes right into
your blood vessels right into the nerves
right into the bloodstream fast quick
that's part of how they work but that's
part of the incredible magic of how they
work
so it's quick delivery right into the
blood vessels right into the bloodstream
which is absolutely incredible all on
its own medical medium brain shot
therapy is Uncharted Territory never
been done before no one has tried this
because they won't know science can't
figure this out food science can't
figure this out nobody can figure this
information out it comes from above I
would never be able to figure this out
these work they offer instant relief
because the information is coming from
above because no one would know to put
potato
which celery and parsley together in a
certain level of ingredients in the
combination in the order they are to
make it work so it stops EMF
from affecting you and 5G from affecting
you
and that's what's incredible we would
never know it's not possible there's not
going to be trillions of dollars
invested in scientists trying to figure
out putting these three together to
create this that's what's incredible on
its own Anthony people at work told me I
look more calm must be the medical mean
brain shots which leads to another
interesting piece of information right
here many people don't know what issues
they have within like we walk around
we're not really sure what's going on
and why we're dealing with so many
problems right they don't know what's
broken inside of them like what's broken
that needs to be fixed
so with medical medium brain shot
therapy you don't need to know what's
wrong for these shots to help you that's
the whole point you can do these shots
and then something happens later like
wait a minute I'm more calm
or wait a minute I'm thinking better
or wait a minute I'm stronger feeling
wait a minute I have more energy wait a
minute I don't need to nap wait a minute
I'm like going strong all day oh wait
I'm not thinking obsessive thoughts or
hold on a second something shifting
something's changing in me and it's like
all these things happen
so with the medical medium brain shot
therapy you don't need to know what's
wrong for these shots to actually help
you
that right there is mind-blowing these
shots will find a way to help you that's
what's incredible about it you take the
medical meaning brain shots they find a
way to help you
how powerful is that
and that's it's almost like just send
the shots down and let them find their
way if we don't know why we need them
that's one reason why the medical medium
Branch out therapy cleanses some of
which methodically take you through the
different brain shots can be such a
revelation that's the whole point these
shots are like Revelations for so many
people you take the shots
and if you do them every day or you you
choose to do a different shot each day
or stay on one Revelations happen
epiphanies happen things like you it
comes to you it's like oh my god look
what's going on that's the magical you
know incredible
um Angelic power of all of it it's just
it's like working with the light when
you're working with the brain shot
Therapies
with medical medium brain shot therapy
however you decide to use it you venture
into Uncharted Territory with your
healing and that's another incredible
thing hazeling says I made this shot
this morning and it surprised me made me
feel very peaceful immediately and I
felt more relaxed doing work on my
laptop after well that's the thing I'm
using this brain shot we're doing right
now because I'm sitting there
I'm sitting there on my computers on my
devices right I'm on my phone like on
and off all day long and I'm using this
shot every day
Ellie says I was so surprised to see raw
potatoes in the recipe would have never
guessed it I would have never guessed it
no one I don't think would ever have
guessed it it because it's information
that comes from above like we don't know
then that's what's incredible about it
Abby Doom says after yesterday my mind
was my own more than usual I wasn't so
into fretting about anything or
everything
well that's the obsessive thought
shifter that was a powerful one ah that
one hit me real nice and real hard it
was like incredible when I took that one
down I was just like whoa the rest of
the day I was feeling it I did another
one later on and then I did one last
night and I was like and here's what's
crazy they build upon themselves they
build upon like each one like they even
get stronger or something it's it's so
different than what anybody would expect
I thought that raw potato was poisonous
uh no it's not poisonous so I hope that
clears that up for you the
misinformation that's out there it's not
your fault you think raw potato is
poisonous that's the misinformation out
there
it's really incredible
so when it comes to these medical
meaning brain shots it's good to explore
there's 30 different brain shot
therapies you can do One A Day for 30
days you could do it for 10 days you can
explore it's so exciting cynette says
the grief shot helped me I lost my 23
year old son of fentanyl poison oh God
I'm so sorry truly truly there's there's
I I hear that's happening a lot out
there it just it just kills me it just
breaks my heart and I'm so happy that
you found a little bit of Peace in the
shot
you know
the thing is about the brain shot
therapies is that when Spirit of
compassion was giving me that
information it was all about like what
people need in the moment to give them
relief for their suffering great
suffering that so many people are living
with right now and these shots are for
people who are really they're just
really in that place of struggle and
suffering great loss
Renata says following your shots and
happy to tell I got so much energy thank
you aw and SOC that makes me happy
because energy is something that we feel
like we're losing these days so many
people are in a loss of energy
struggling with energy and that's
amazing I'm so glad you're getting that
right there all that counts so important
medical medium brain shot therapy is
Uncharted Territory like I was saying
before never been done then ever in our
history these books are making history
right now through the greatest books of
all time judge for yourself get them in
your hands you guys you could still sign
up to the brain shot therapy challenge
don't feel like you're missing out it's
a free challenge if you just came on
here and you're like where am I here's
the medical meeting brain shot therapy
challenge
medicalmedium.com or day four go to
medicalmedium.com and get your free
grocery shopping list and the
information you need so you can do this
challenge we're only day four we're
going 10 days
and every day
is just incredible and Powerful but
we're only day four so really it's
exciting so sign up if you get a chance
check out check out the mm1500 too when
you get a chance and before we move on I
want to say something about the mm-1500
what I'm seeing out there and it's kind
of sad is I see I can't sit there every
day and tell everybody about the juicers
I don't have time
so I can't I mean it's been months I
think since I even talked about them and
the problem is with that is that other
juicers companies they'll advertise to
the medical medium communities and
they'll sell them crappy juicers that
will lose not save them money and it
breaks my heart they'll sell them
juicers that have like spinning things
in them and baskets and all that stuff
and what happens is that if you want to
save money for the future because food
prices are going up look into the
mm-1500
look into the mm-900 because it squeezes
all the G like almost every bit of that
juice gets squeezed out so when I make
the shots I'm using less the problem is
with the juicers that are that are like
the juicer companies that are breaking
into the medical medium communities to
try to you know run ads and and
basically sell their juicers because
they they know that this is the place to
be because all the sharks out there know
that this is the place to be
they'll sell you a juicer
that doesn't save you money and doesn't
pay for itself it breaks my heart but I
can't sit there and be the juicer guy
where I'm
trying to show you guys a juicer every
single day of my life I can't I have to
work I have to I have to get you the
information in the books and everything
else I can't be the guy the juicer guy
trying to like show you a juicer every
day so you don't get ripped off out
there
so what I'm trying to say is when it's
the mm-1500 if you already have a juicer
fine but I'm saying this for people that
are actually getting suckered into
buying juicers that won't give them all
the maximum juice it kills me because
it's like okay
food costs money these ingredients cost
money
and what's happening is like with these
juicers not all Omega juicers the
mm-1500 it has a compression to it and
squeezes more juice out of it so that
you get more shots for your money you're
buying less produce for more shots less
celery for more celery juice
I don't want to sit here and talk about
a juicer all day but I have because we
have so much to cover but I'm trying to
tell you guys that the Sharks got into
the medical medium community
and they scam everybody and then you
lose money and produce is going up and
you're juicing and losing all your juice
and it's it's breaking my heart I had to
say it I have to but someday
if you save up it's no big deal this is
20 off though someday if you get a 1500
or a 900 mm 900 1500 you can save so
much money it's paid for itself and paid
for itself and paid for itself over and
over again I don't even know what to say
let's see Sunny says yeah my juicer only
made one and so much was wasted exactly
but here's the thing the sharks have
come into the communities if you guys
can just be aware of this
I can't keep track of it all I can't I
can't protect everybody I'm trying but
the sharks get in
and they're gonna sell you these juicers
and everybody's gonna be using juicers
and throwing all their ingredients out
all their stuff like they're gonna need
so much more and it's gonna cost them so
much money
um doodle love says if it's so funny
when I see sharks bashing you but then
right after they bash they parrot your
info oh my God that's all they do out
there they all try to step on me and
then they take the information I wish I
could say names right now but I'm not
that mean of a person where I could you
know what I mean but I wish I could give
you all the podcast doctor names and
everybody of what they've done and what
they do Meanwhile we're the community
that's getting people better it's
actually psycho
um Meg says I have noticed my celery
Bunch goes further since I bought the
mm-1500 exactly so what I'm trying to
tell you guys and this is critical the
sharks have come in with juicer
companies and ads they're trying to
poach the whole medical medium Community
everybody's buying these juicers that
are different they're likes the spinner
things and this and things and all that
in it right and and what's happening
love my Omega mm-1500 Chloe amazing
what's happening is you're going to lose
money
you're going to lose money
you need your juicer to pay for yourself
you need your juicer to work for you to
work for you I'm just being honest and
that's what happens the juicer works for
me the juicer works for you meaning it's
there to save you money so it pays for
itself
if you buy juicers that are you they're
all they're all trying to bust into the
medical medium community and go on the
juicer ride
and and just poach all the people and
sell them juicers so if you already got
suckered and tricked think about in the
future maybe you correct the mistake
later down the road or whatever you know
and when you're making these shots and
juicing your celery you're you're going
to lose so much money on those juicers
that's what I've learned because I've
tried them all I know the ones that
people have and still they don't compare
to the compression and the the mm 1500
and 900 I have to say this because I got
I guess I got lazy with the juicers in a
sense where I've been too busy trying to
get the book done too trip busy trying
to get everything done and I can't keep
up with everything because I assume
everybody knows these are the best
but then all of a sudden the Sharks come
in and everybody gets taken and then
they're spending this much more for
their produce and it's unfair and it's
ripping them off and it makes me sick
that's so sad
so anyway
let's move on to it
if I'm excited
the brain shot therapy is about that
absorption it's also about the
ingredients being put together all of it
that's critical really incredible the
whole process so let's go into some info
really quick you guys so I'm in brain
saver right here
okay these are the two books do you have
one
and
I'm in this little section here called
coexisting with electricity so I'm in
the EMF chapter here's the incredible
thing about the brain saver books
right
it's EMF information nobody knows about
EMF information nobody knows about I'm
saying that because everybody in the EMF
world thinks they got it down and thinks
they know everything about EMF
so if you look out there it's like
almost like you think it's all figured
out about EMF it's not that's the
incredible thing about Spirit of
compassion that's incredible thing about
the brain saver books information that's
unique
and brand new original powerful comes
from above and the EMF people once they
get their hands on this are going to be
parroting it and not citing it back so
the new information about EMF and I've
put EMF information out there in the
last 20 years in 30 years
so some of that is already out that was
originally from mm right
we're doing it again we're putting
original EMF information out there
and once again it will be stolen shortly
and then put out there as if it's been
known or something so let's go into it
coexisting with electricity when it
comes to
electromagnetic fields
check this out our brains can actually
adapt to certain electrical currents
that are around us in the last hundred
years our brain
science doesn't know this EMF people
don't know it
our brain adapts
to EMF
certain EMF
so we actually adapt to EMF
not always but check this out incredible
information so when it comes to
electromagnetic fields our brains can
actually adapt to certain electrical
currents that are around us in the last
hundred years
so when electricity happened and
everybody's homes got electricity
we've been able to adapt to those
electrical currents
really important to know and the EMF
people don't know this
our brains have indeed adapted to EMF
produced from electricity
so our brains have adapted to EMF
produced by electricity
electrical wiring buildings electrical
panels and appliances such as
dishwashers refrigerators ovens stoves
do you guys have dishwashers
do you guys have refrigerators do you
have stoves
do you have ovens
so r
brain has adapted to electrical wiring
buildings electrical panels appliances
dishwashers refrigerators ovens stoves
electric cars lights power strips and
surge protector protectors and air
conditioners heaters washing machines
and dryers
our brain in the last hundred years has
learned to adapt with electrical
currents out of all those things
information unknown to anyone right now
in history you're getting out of this
book right now and it's mind-blowing
but there's some we're we're not done we
ain't done
with this form of EMF we've adapted in
such a way that when the power is out
even if the temperature is comfortable
many people tend to go through mad
withdrawal
unknown to research in science unknown
to the EMF crowd experts unknown to the
scientists
that when we lose power in our home
apartment house
building
we start going mad
with withdrawal
critical to know
we start losing it
when we lose our power
we've adapted to power in the last
hundred years to such a degree that we
start losing it without power and if you
think you know somebody like oh I know a
dude that camps out in the desert he's
got no power he's got a truck
most likely he's got a truck and he's in
that truck once in a while getting his
power fix
getting his power fixed so if you're
like oh no I know people just just cool
crowd that hangs out in the desert and
they're just around a fire and they're
just like Off the Grid and they got no
power around them they find power
periodically and they get a fix
because the withdrawal can make you go
mad we've had a hundred years of
adapting to power to electricity
is this not mind-blowing
when I heard that from Spirit of
compassion in my office when I was
writing that down
I think that was a moment when it was
like 4 30 and 5 o'clock in the morning
and I was feverishly writing the
information and trying to get it right
making sure every word was correct and
then throwing it back at Spirit of
compassion saying is that correct is
that what you said and then writing it
writing it and the information that came
through was
our brains
and our children babies in the womb
in everyone for a hundred years has
adapted two electrical magnetic fields
with electricity to appliances to
everything I just mentioned
in here earlier if you just got here
watch this from the beginning it's
mind-blowing
and so when we lose our power
we don't feel peaceful maybe for a
little bit but that peacefulness starts
to wear off and we start going mad with
power withdrawal
and that's why even people who are are
like they try to live off the grid long
enough they're still back in their truck
and they're still using their LED lights
and they're still doing things because
they get they draw from it because they
can't handle it fully
so Danny says we have this in South
Africa it's called load shedding
the city cuts out power to save money
and you can feel the difference when the
power is no more anywhere you feel the
difference you feel the withdrawal right
and I almost think the energy companies
are just doing it to just mess with us
because
you know because they know we probably
react but they don't know what it is
servina says oh my God I always wondered
why I'm so stressed when the power goes
out even when I Juiced all my juices for
the day and everything is okay and
you're sitting there and you're like
okay the power's out but it's only going
to be about for a little while but you
actually get really upset right because
we're going through withdrawal nobody
knows this information it's brand new
it's getting out now it's in these brain
saver books but the brain saver books
are packed like that it's it's just it's
all incredible but either way this is
the first time
this is getting out in the world nobody
knew we've adapted to that electricity
for a hundred years babies included
babies in the womb pregnant moms all of
it and we're just born into it we've
adapted and we're born into it and when
that power goes out we lose that power
we go through withdrawal and can even go
mad at at certain points depending how
long that withdrawal lasts
with this form of EMF we've adapted in
such a way that when the power is out
even if the temperature is comfortable
like you're saying and everything's okay
you got your juices done everything's
great you go through withdrawal it's not
and it's not withdrawal from having the
luxury of an employ of a appliance
here's another thing all on its own so
it's not withdrawal from having like
being without the luxury of an appliance
of some kind
it's not that
it's withdrawal from the EMF itself so
it's actual EMF withdrawal that's what
we go through when the power's out
that's incredible because our brains
have learned to coexist with this type
of EMF so here's the whole point our
brains have learned to coexist with this
variety of EMF so when it's gone
we're going through it it's like a drug
so it's almost like we've been drugged
for a hundred years with this type of
EMF and electricity and then when it's
pulled from us you guys you feel it
Sandy says I'd get upset when power goes
out I thought it was internet withdrawal
nope it's electricity withdrawal that's
the main thing right there
herbal Ministry said I tried explaining
that to a doctor once and they had no
idea what I was talking about
okay you ready because it only gets more
intense
as you know well in this book like the
brain story if you guys have read this
our brain is made out of electricity
think about that
our brain is made out of electricity you
guys
just letting you know
while it's not the same electricity that
powers our homes and appliances get
ready
our brain's electricity has learned to
coexist with this EMF admitting from all
this outside electricity so that our
brain can continue to function optimally
so check this out our brain has adapted
because if it didn't our brains would
not work anymore it had to coexist with
the electricity that's around us
foreign
all this information is blowing my mind
but is it blowing yours or is it just or
is this all in just it's just me being
too excited or something
okay
when you head to a spiritual Retreat
okay when you head to a spiritual
retreat in a shack that has no
electricity or you sit in an open field
with no electrical conveniences nearby
it's an experience
you're going through withdrawal
you go to a retreat
and you're like
ah so nice out here I'm with like-minded
people
we're just talk we're sitting around a
campfire right now breathing in all that
smoke which isn't a good idea it's a
totally bad idea by the way but either
way we're out here
and you're going through a trawl
and your brain is learning to adjust and
live without the EMF so your spiritual
it's Retreat your spiritual Retreat that
so many people go on is really without
them realizing this is about them living
without EMF and their brain's
coexistence with it
tell me that's not unbelievable
music says is this why my neighbors
always argue and yell when the power
goes out
I mean
I don't know your neighbors
but I can
definitely bet that there's a good
chance that it's happening because of
that
now coexisting with the everyday let me
just ask Spirit of compassion
yes they argue any Spirit of compassion
just said to me your neighbors argue
anyway
and they have fights anyway but when the
power goes out the fights amplify swear
to compassion just said
spirit's saying they have fights anyway
I don't know if I I don't know if I've
done this with you guys like this but
it's it's actually you know I try not to
do this
so I'm asking Spirit of compassion
one starts the fights more than the
other
and
it happens like every Sunday they get
into a fight but when the power goes out
it gets just amplifies because of the
withdrawal so that's the spirit of
compassion to set
but I'm not spying I don't know where
the dampers are and I'm done a spying
I'm just helping you with your question
now coexisting with the everyday
electricity around us and what is one
thing let's not confuse that with the
EMF admitting from dangerous high
voltage scenarios so here's another
thing
this is the MF that we live around every
single day but I don't want you to be
confused with a dangerous high voltage
EMF situation that's at a base station
so don't confuse that base station
with what we're talking about we're
talking about appliances your house your
apartment power going out the
coexistence of you and that EMF your
brain and that EMF that's different than
pulling up to one of those power
stations with all that power crap going
on and boom that that high voltage
shooting out that's another story
we're not like adapted for that
that can affect somebody differently
okay get ready for this this next
section is just incredible if you
thought that was incredible this next
section is incredible
and I'm on page 240 of brain saver you
guys just come came on here you guys can
admit the brain saver books
when you get a chance
then there's radio frequency EMF
which is more aggressive than regular
EMF radio frequency EMF is more
aggressive than regular EMF
with radio frequency EMF we're no longer
talking about simple electricity being
used to power an appliance
so radio frequency EMF is not about an
appliance running or your electricity in
your home
we're talking about devices such as
computers and cell phones inter
interacting with wireless internet and
cell towers that's what we're talking
about now hello
hello
don't put the phone right up against my
head okay what should I do put on
speaker
all right is that better
so we're talking about devices such as
computers and cell phones interacting
with wireless internet and cell towers
these are radio frequency emfs a lot
different you guys Danny says love this
Celia music said well now I know the
truth
other sources of radio frequency EMF
include microwaves smart devices and
radar facilities that's an entirely
different situation that's something we
have not adapted to
there's even cell tower exposure when
you're not using your phone you can shut
down your phone and shut off your phone
and those radio frequencies are still
there so people say well I'm not going
to have a phone in my life I'm just
going to throw my phone out I'm just
going to shut it down you're still going
to get hit with the radio frequencies
every day because we can't avoid those
cell towers they're going through our
houses they're going through our
Apartments they're going through our
dwellings they're just going through
right
so we're getting exposure that way
anyway these radio frequencies coming
from cell towers enter our brain and hit
our neuron so check this out you don't
even need you don't have to be on your
computer you don't have to be on your
iPad and whatever your phone you don't
have to be on that you're still getting
hit with the radio frequencies it's
still going to come from the cell towers
and be hitting your brain
that's just how it is here on planet
Earth right now this is what it is here
on planet Earth I'm just letting you
know like that's what planet Earth is
now
so there's even cell tower exposure when
you're not using your phone you can shut
down your phone your devices the radar
the radio frequencies are still there
traveling through every single Home and
Office Building
Susan said the cats get weird when the
power goes out they too have to adapt to
electricity for a hundred years exactly
Sue said can you please describe what
the withdrawal symptoms are like
I will in a couple of minutes that's
really that's a great question
so we're getting exposure that way now
here's the thing these radio frequencies
coming from cell towers enter our brain
and hit our neurons this exposure is a
bit more aggressive than your typical
appliances inside your house so this is
different people think it's the
electricity inside their house that's
giving them EMF problems really when
it's really just it's radio frequencies
shooting through their home from their
cell towers whether you have a device or
not that's why I love this shot we're
doing if you just came on here we're
talking about 5G we're talking about
um EMF we're talking about that stuff
and this is this is a radiation chapter
too wait till you read this whole
chapter and read about radiation it's
it's insane
yet as aggressive as cell tower exposure
is it is not as harmful as other forms
of radio frequency EMF exposure that
we'll get into in a moment so let's just
talk about this I'm saying about the
cell tower stuff but even though that's
harmful it's still not as harmful as
other things so harmful
just and you can toss your devices in
the garbage it's not going to change a
thing
that cell tower radio frequency is
beaming through everybody's house and
apartment and dwelling everywhere you
can't stop it it's not about your device
or not throw all your devices down the
street down the road whatever in a in a
pond in a lake it's still going to be
the same radio frequency going into your
house all day long
Irena says this information is so unique
it can only be from above true because I
am not a genius and a genius can't come
up with this information it is
absolutely mind-blowing thank you Irena
you guys know I'm not a smart guy I
never went to college I never went to
whatever
right I mean but you know what it is I'm
a good listener I can take down the
information given to me word for word
and then I have to learn it just like
everybody else I have to become my own
expert just like you guys have to become
your own expert with the medical media
books
I'm just a messenger
people parrot that now too by the way or
is I don't know what it was someone's
telling me if there's this influencer
dude it's got a really big ego
and um he's out there selling his
supplements and all this other crap or
whatever he's doing he's got a huge ego
now he's saying I'm the messenger I'm a
messenger he's just taking like
everything from medical mediums like
you're not a messenger
if you don't know what a messenger is
dude
anyway
you would be mind blown how much info in
the health field today
that comes from medical medium like SOC
and spirit of compassion that's out
there now so you think about it all the
new information I keep on putting out so
many people don't even realize it's from
my my information or SOC from three
years ago five years ago ten years ago
15 years ago you wouldn't believe how
Bleak the Alternative Health movement
was 35 years ago it was literally a
desert it was dry it was Bleak there was
nothing there I had to put so much out
there and so much out there taught
doctors taught people taught Health
practitioners taught thousands of people
lectured travel did it and got the
information out there there's so much mm
info that's out there now people don't
even realize where it came from I've
been doing this for over 35 years all
right let's go into the like let's go
into the like crazy place on this that's
just unbelievable right
okay
so we're getting exposure yet okay here
we are in recent years our brains have
been learning to adapt to cell tower EMF
because of radio frequencies we're
exposed to from the military
so in recent years our brains have been
learning to adapt to cell tower EMF
because of radio frequencies were
exposed to from military
military bases including classified
military bases around the world send out
radio frequencies that travel across the
planet and away from our planet into the
atmosphere this has been developing
since the 1930s so our brains and
neurons have been learning to adapt so
our brains and neurons have already
they've already been learning to adapt
to certain radio frequencies
because they've had to because of the
military radio frequencies that have
been happening since the 1930s it's
interesting
get ready for this our present-day cell
towers are more aggressive than
old-school radio frequencies
that also still exists by the way
whether 5G now or 6x
6x
see what's happening is
Spirit of compassion told me that where
they're going to go after 5g's they're
going to call it 6x
SOC gave me that incredible information
it's going to be named 6x
and you know what x stands for right
six
so in the future but you know what
they'll probably change it now because
they're not going to want to like
make the prophecies come true in every
angle right so they'll probably like oh
better not let
you know yeah so she get that prophecy
so
whether 5G now or 6X in the future
transmission technology continues to
send stronger signals still these towers
mere presence is not totally where the
threat Lies when we're talking about EMF
exposure and the possibility of
compromising our brain health so what
I'm saying is even with all that that's
not where the main problems are
[Music]
okay
still these towers mere presence is not
totally where the threat lies as I was
saying again our brains are learning to
adapt to cell tower waves moving through
the environment
what we haven't adapted to is using a
device that's connected to a cell tower
we have not adapted to using a device
connected to a cell tower when our cell
phone is turned on and especially if
we're using the phone there's additional
radio frequency coming to our phone and
that's additional radio frequency to
which we have not adapted is why there
is an EMF and and 5G shot right here on
the table that's why you see the three
ingredients that's why it's in the book
because there's some some things that we
don't adapt to and that's when we need
that EMF and 5G shot you guys should
tell people about these books let them
know get the word out there about these
two brain saver books
if you feel up to it
because I know a lot of you guys don't
feel good and you got enough on your
plate I understand
um when your cell phone is off my cell
phone is on airplane right now but when
your cell phone is off where you turn it
off
do you guys find this interesting am I
boring you guys I hope I'm not boring
you guys
am I boring you guys about all the cmf
crap and all this 5G stuff
because I feel bad if I'm boring you
guys
hmm all right
oh halftime intermission
who wants to the robot with me
[Music]
foreign
that's fun
Lanes up everything
we're an EMF we're in the 5G exposure
shot right here
excited love the robot
you guys doing the robot so okay let's
go into slip when ourselves okay ready
this is good what we haven't adapted to
is using a device that's connected to
the cell tower when our cell phone is
turned on
and especially if we're using the phone
there's additional radio frequency
coming to our phone
so you shut your phone off
put your phone somewhere there's still
radio frequencies coming from the cell
tower
and they're just going right through the
house right through the apartment and
they're hitting us okay
they're hitting us
so
all right let's find our spot all right
when your cell phone is off
that pinpoint radio frequency EMF has
dissipated pinpoint is what I'm talking
about so here's how it works your cell
phone's off you're not getting pinpoint
radio frequencies coming from the cell
tower when your cell phone's off you're
getting General overall
radio frequency still beaming through
the home you turn on your phone now it's
pinpoint
see the difference
you're getting pinpoint
that pinpoint radio frequency is
dissipated and now you're back to being
surrounded by the radio frequency
everyone is surrounded by unless you're
totally Off the Grid living on the side
of a mountain with no cell towers for
many miles and then if you're living on
the side of a mountain and there's no
cell tower for many miles you're going
to get very little of that cell tower
frequency but you're never going to be
able to use a phone or a device ever
you guys I'm getting this incredible
information from the brain saver books
right here a lot of new people coming on
and they're like what's a brain shot man
hey this dude's kind of wacky what's a
brain shot therapy
what's the brain saver books should I
get one
so there we go
I just came back from a retreat man
all I know is I went bat crazy
after there for about five days and I
had to run into the town and get
and get some
snacks at the gas station I felt so much
better when I was standing in the gas
station
is that because there was power at the
gas station
okay guys see these are the books right
here check out
all right let's keep on going here
the pinpointed radio frequency that
comes to a device when it's connected to
a cellular network is why when using a
cell phone it's important not to have it
pressed up to your ear that's why you
don't want it pressed up to your ear
that's the whole point
you can press it up to your ear if your
phone is off
you can press your phone to your ear
when your phone's on but that's a
different story like the radiation
that's a different story and I talk
about that in this book but here's the
thing when you're on a phone call you
don't want to press the phone to your
ear because it's pinpoint cell tower
it's a pinpoint
cell tower hit
that's the difference right there
if you have your phone off and you press
it to your ear no big deal if you have
your cell phone on and you press it to
your ear you get a little radiation I
talk about in the books but here's the
thing
if you have your cell phone with a call
you're getting a call hey Mac I want to
talk to you and you put it to your ear
now you're getting a direct pinpoint to
your brain coming from the cell tower
that's the difference right there
so you want to talk to somebody on
speakerphone and you want to have your
phone away
so that the pinpoint goes to your hand
so the pinpoint goes to your hand you
see what I mean you guys we haven't even
done the EMF shot but I can't wait to do
that EMF shot hopefully
hopefully
it tastes good because these shots
they're about
results and some of them don't taste as
great because it's medicine
you guys got to read the rest of the
book I'm just I'm scratching the surface
in here I didn't finish this section
but I want you to know you can read the
rest of the book I didn't even finish
the section
and the books are just both books you
want to get because they're one book
so make sure you get both books and sale
on amazon.com 40 off right now
um us all right let's go
so we're in the brain shot therapy you
guys we're doing entry level brain shot
therapy cleanse we're doing 10 days this
is day four this is the entry level
brain shot therapy cleanse make sure
you're drinking 50 ounces of water
through the course of the day don't
drink the 50 ounces right when you send
down your brain shot so when you send
down your brain shot don't drink the 50
ounces
um right then too at the same time so
don't don't do that right
it's like don't wash it down with water
you do your 50 ounces throughout the day
the minimum minimum 50 ounces of water
throughout the day this is your entry
level brain shot therapy cleanse
for this challenge though we're doing
one to three shots you can choose to do
one shot a day I'm doing three shots a
day I did three obsessive thoughts
shifters yesterday I'm doing three EMF
and 5G exposure shots today
use the same shot that would be amazing
so it would be EMF
in 5G brain shot therapy three times use
the same one
incredible
all right
let's talk about this for a little bit
you can choose 10 days 20 days 30 days
in the entry level cleanse I am doing a
10-day brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge with you guys it's 10 days
we're day four okay
we're moving along amazing
so much incredible information okay
these cleanses are imperative to what
we're up against today EMF and 5G is an
example right there these are important
the brain shot therapy cleanses go just
beyond the physical they hit the
metaphysical that's the whole point it's
doing both this is allowing us to
achieve enlightenment when we're getting
rid of the stuff that shouldn't be in
our brain we're protecting our brain and
we're healing our soul that's how we
achieve enlightenment that's one of the
biggest ways of doing it is huge right
removing poisons from our brain opens up
that door which is really incredible now
here's the other thing that happens with
the medical medium brain shot therapies
and you guys are going to see this your
intuitive skills are Clairvoyant skills
your telepathic skills
your skills as being a Seer start to
develop so if they're in there in you
they start to get enhanced I'm letting
you know so if you're as you're doing
the brain shot therapy cleanses like
we're doing this 10 day one that
Clairvoyant power that skill that
telepathic psychic intuitive skill
starts to build on itself as well now
here's the whole thing with the brain
shots they build on themselves as well
too not just your abilities of brain
healing but everything
which is really incredible
so we're in the exposure shots EMF and
5G is an exposure shot and we are in the
exposure shots right now important to
know these brain shots can be
administered before an exposure during
during an exposure shortly after an
exposure or even days weeks or months
after an exposure
now I'm around a lot of different EMF
I'm around computers around all kinds of
stuff so I'm going to do this once in a
while for me but there's a lot of brain
shots that I like to do but I love this
one so many details in the books so that
you can read all the details and get the
information you need but it's in here
about all of this
okay
let's see what we got maybe we're gonna
go and make this shot
and we are going to do that all right
you guys
EMF 5G exposure shot
let's go
let's get the juicer out
as I was saying before I feel bad for
people who've been tricked into juicers
that aren't going to save them money
and I do feel bad I can't the problem is
I can't keep up with everything telling
everybody like what they can do
or I'll just be literally talking about
the juicer every day and as much as I
want to like get that information out
there it's really hard and I feel bad
this has a compression this isn't metal
grinding touching each other this has a
compression literally that saves you
money so that you get more juice and
when it comes down to any juicing you do
it's critical that you get that juice
out that's the whole point and that's
what the mm-1500 900s do 20 off right
now I'm letting you know because I feel
bad I see what's happening and so the
sharks have come into the communities
they're selling them bum juicers in my
opinion that aren't squeezing the juice
out and I feel bad for everybody so just
letting you guys know Pamela says yeah
but watch the shark buy the mm-1500 but
sell the shark Brands I'm sure they
already have I'm sure the sharks are
using the mm-1500 to save that money and
at the same time they're selling the
crappy Brands so I'm just letting you
guys know spread the word and if someone
said well I've been tricked by the
Sharks and I got the wrong one say well
down the road when you get the right one
think about how much money you're going
to save and you're going to pay for both
the bum juicer that you got and you're
going to pay for the good juicer that
you got
all right here we go we're making this
this is an interesting one right here
we're going to do with parsley to start
with quarter cup of tightly packed
parsley
stirring this on
it's a quiet juicer by the way you guys
it's incredible quarter cup of tightly
packed parsley
so I'm packing it in my hand because I
kind of all these years I know what like
what that is and what that equals
there we go put a little parsley in
there
so we're putting a little bit of parsley
here we go
now we're peeling a raw potato
[Applause]
I'm gonna grab a potato out of my potato
bin here that's a nice potato very happy
you want a half a cup potato I'm gonna
do a quick peeling right now because I
did not peel it ahead of time
and you can Cube it you can kind of chop
it up in one inch half inch cubes
whatever and that's what we're gonna do
so I'm peeling this potato back
getting the skin off
because that was the direction from
Spirit of compassion
there we go
all right I'm cutting up my potato as we
speak
this is not a juice this is a medicinal
shot
brain shot therapy isn't juicing it's
creating medicinal shots
putting a half a cup of the potato down
in here
and then we're going to get a celery
stick one stalk of celery stick to two
stalks the reason why it's one to two is
someone might have a really small celery
stick which happens
it's really small
here we go
amazing
[Music]
I'm actually really excited about this
been needing this shot I've been needing
this shot I really have
foreign
[Music]
there it is
so much of us are surrounded by
exposures we just don't understand
it's rid of compassion has taught us a
lot
in these brain saver books you'll get
information you've never heard before so
we can be empowered because that's what
it's about you don't want the wall
pulled over your eyes you don't want the
carpet pulled out from underneath your
feet
you want you don't want to be Bamboozled
and tricked and duped you want to know
what's going on and you want to know
what's happening around you
[Music]
here's the first step
it's incredible how you feel the results
come on tingles everywhere tingles
the tangles are here for this one
hitting me now on the second sip
hitting me right now on the second sip
[Music]
Pretender give me another
I said bartender give me another please
incredible incredible
and I can feel that
there's phytochemical compounds that
come from the earth that's in that root
that's in that root right here in that
potato in that Spud that sits down in
the Earth and the Earth is grounded
it's grounded you guys a potato picks up
that grounding but when you put that
grounding nature of the potato Spirit of
compassion says and you mix it and no
one would ever know this and you mix
that grounding nature of that potato and
you mix it with the trace mineral salts
in the celery so you have the trace
minerals with the grounding nature right
and the rich rich nutrients of the
parsley when those three are put
together you're arming yourself and
protecting yourself from EMF in 5G it's
incredible I could feel it going down
I'm very in touch with what I put inside
my body
I've had to do that my whole life
because the spirit of compassion and I
will tell you that when I was taking
down this information and I tried these
myself I was blown off my seat and I
could not wait for you guys to learn
about these brain shot therapies I could
not wait it's a blessing from above a
blessing from God a blessing and I'm so
happy about these they're miraculous I
can't say it enough this has been
absolutely incredible you guys
I don't even know what to tell you it's
been that amazing and so listen all I
can say is this is day four of it brings
about therapy cleanse
I got a question from sues can you
please describe what the withdrawal
symptoms are like of course
you can get sadness come over you when
the power goes out fear come over you
you can also get a sense of feeling like
stress Underneath It All like the stress
starts to build even when everything is
okay the stress levels start to increase
when the power is out so stress in the
body start to happen blood pressure go
you the pulse tends to go a little
higher than normal when the power's out
these are some withdrawals there's even
more you guys this is incredible medical
medium brain shot therapy cleanse day
four are you guys going to be with me
for day five Christy bacon says oh my
God I'm crying thanks so much Anthony
and SOC incredible Cheryl said I would
get about 12 ounces from a whole bunch
but now with the 1500 I generally I get
really close to 16 ounces and sometimes
more you guys the difference is
unbelievable with those other juicers
that that are broken into the community
the Sharks ripping everybody off
you're getting less juice cost of
produce is up the cost of food is up the
mm 1500 pays for itself and you know
what it's not about a juicer it's about
all the good stuff and everything else
but I have to talk about the juicer
because of what the sharks have done I
thought everybody knew what juicers that
were the best I've been talking about
them for a few years now but I hope
people know and spread the word that
you're getting ripped off with the other
juicers and that this is the one to save
up for it's 20 off right now letting you
know right now you guys I'm asking
everybody have you tried the brain shot
what did you feel what were the results
you had that you experienced please
share a story a post a real at Medical
medium medical medium tag medical medium
I'll see you tomorrow because we're five
day
of the medical medium brain shot
challenge the brain shot therapy
Challenge and I am blown away I don't
even know what else to say seriously
hands down
right now hands down these will be the
best books and they are now in all-time
health history I'll tell you
be the judge grab one of the podcast
doctor books and go through those eat
better books and see there's nothing in
there grab some of the books that are
out there and help to see that there's
nothing in there read what's in these
books and you be the judge and know
they're the greatest books of all time
history all the medical medium books
have been I can judge it because the
information comes from above I could
have my own opinion you guys will be
blown away this is unbelievable there's
12 books in one there's a hundred
recipes over 300 symptoms and conditions
there's the brain shot therapies the
heavy metal detox
um cleanses all of it it's incredible
you guys
I'm doing on telegram
exclusive messages audio messages on
telegram so I'm doing them almost every
day exclusive telegram messages sign up
to my telegram so you can hear those
messages I'm not doing them or anywhere
else my God these shots are unbelievable
they power me up like I can't even tell
you I can't I
gotta dial it back a little bit what is
going on these shots are incredible who
who would have ever known that
combination of what it does comes from
above that's why in 15 minutes I'm going
live
in 15 minutes I'm going live on Dr
nesbitt's account he's allowing me to do
it so it's Dr nesbitt's Tick Tock
account and which I'm on now right now
and it's Dr nesbitt's Instagram account
for some light-hearted fun hopefully Dr
Nesbitt doesn't say anything too crazy
and too wacko Hopefully Dr Nesbit
behaves himself because he's been
drinking so you know what I'm going live
on Tick Tock in a little bit where I'm
Tick Tock live now on Dr as it's got but
I'm going live again and going live on
Instagram see you guys tomorrow for day
five the medical medium brain shot
challenge these shots are making me go
incredibly electricity moving and
everything we're doing the mold exposure
shot tomorrow for day five
the mold exposure shot tomorrow for day
five have your brain saver books tell
everybody about them
it's incredible seriously
got to do the robot with me
[Music]
foreign