anybody who is energy deficient
that's a deficiency that's happening out
there people don't talk about they don't
people are lined up at the coffee shops
they're lined up
at all of the coffee chains and they're
just like getting their coffee people
have their coffee going on at home they
got their espressos
they got their Kombucha Tea which is
caffeine based almost every one of them
the point is is that everybody's
searching for energy but they're looking
for false energy
they're looking for fake energy
and they're looking for stimulated
energy coming from a drug source
everybody is feeling malaise and
listless and tired
almost everybody in the world right now
and the people that say I don't have any
energy problems I'm not listless I'm not
malazed I'm not tired I got plenty of
energy and you ask them what are they
doing what are they eating every day and
they'll be like well I have my iced
coffees I have my espressos I have my
coffee in the morning
and if you took that away from them
they would go into withdraw
and they would go into that withdrawal
and they would actually be like whoa
I do have an energy problem
you ask them what else do you do to be
like matcha
tea green tea
black tea
they're always searching and seeking for
energy from drug sources
and they don't even realize it because
there's a severe energy deficiency
in the world
anyway you guys day 17 unbelievable
energy shifter is what we're doing
which is incredible I use the energy
shifter very much so yes I am looking
for energy absolutely why I work 20
hours a day yes I burn the candle at
four ends you better believe it but I'm
not going to use caffeine and I'm not
going to use coffee or anything like
that the minute I start getting a little
tired the minute I start getting a
little worn out because I'm a human
being I totally go with the energy
shifter but the energy shifters for a
lot of reasons I got to talk to you
about how incredible the energy shifter
is we're day 17 of the medical medium
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge I'm
Anthony William the medical medium nice
to meet you happy to know you guys this
is incredible really
because we're almost to the end of 20
days is this even possible did we did we
almost finish a 20-day brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge it's insane
man
if you haven't done it make it a three
day for you a three-day brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge just three
days that's all just a three day if the
20 days scared the crap out of you just
do a three day download your free
grocery shopping list go to
medicalmedium.com and make it a three
day that's it incredible
why not all right so
I want to read a little something so I'm
going to go there now I'm in brain saver
Julie Greenwood said I've done this
yesterday and today tastes good and
certainly increased my energy lifted my
mood was fantastic Heaven Sent amazing
George says I needed my chocolate every
night
I don't blame anybody for that you gotta
realize I don't judge anybody I don't
shame anybody for chocolate and matcha
tea and caffeine of all sorts and coffee
and iced coffees and espressos I don't I
don't blame them they're doing it
because they either got hooked onto it
early on in life like an addiction so
they're cooked hooked on the drug or
they're doing it
because they don't feel good brain fog
focusing concentration issues all of it
so they're jacked up on caffeine I don't
blame people one bit nature heals on
YouTube says I hated red peppers until
this drink I'm really glad that you like
red peppers now because I like red bell
peppers too I have one right here can
you see it uh on IG you probably can't
see it but you guys could see it on
YouTube and everywhere
eurek says I stopped drinking coffee two
and a quarter years ago when I started
my medical medium lifestyle don't have
an energy problem amazing a lot of
people
in the health world
quit their coffee because of medical
medium information
I was blasted for going against the
matcha tea and the green tea blasted for
actually you know doing this publicly
and talking about much tea and green tea
and the coffee and everything else in
the you guys remember you guys may not
remember this but the crap I got for
this right here
I got my coffee honey it's organically
grown it's fair trade uh roasted from
the finest farmers in the finest Farms
we pick our Beans by hand and then we
roast them twice and we make such a fine
tinted roast on our beans honey this is
an incredible coffee you just picked up
you know what happened was when I did
that and I talked about how bad caffeine
was and how it was destroying adrenal
glands destroying people's brains really
like causing problems wreaking havoc why
people were on that caffeine the
caffeine industry causing all these
problems and I put out the podcast I got
so much crap so much crap from the
Alternative Health movement so much crap
from the podcast doctors so much crap
from everybody who's selling everybody
and marketing stuff and affiliate stuff
and all that from all those different
groups of people from the mushroom
coffee people to everybody the crap I
got was unbelievable including
censorship left and right and Boo and
Bob like every everything it was crazy
you guys were talking about energy today
I'm kind of jacked up because I cheated
on day 17.
I cheated
I had a cheat day so I'm gonna have to
come clean with this
what I had this morning was an energy
sifter and I did it already today
because
and I'm trying to calm myself down but
we're gonna do I'm gonna do another one
which is really exciting and I can't
wait all right all right calm down calm
down calm down
all right if the Bashir says I stopped
all caffeine last Thursday whoa now on
day seven of headaches more withdrawal
is rough I rarely get headaches so
assume this must be withdrawal symptoms
I would probably agree ask your doctor
what your doctor thinks but if that you
know if that was a family member that
asked me that pretty recently okay
believe it or not family member asked me
that who got off their caffeine and
contacted me I said yes that was
withdrawal creating the headache all
right
so I am here you guys let's read a
little bit I'm excited
glucose and glycogen sounds boring
glucose glycogen guess what
without glucose we we die that's it
without glucose in our bloodstream we
die
so yeah it's boring as hell
but it keeps Us Alive it keeps us going
glucose and glycogen your brain is an
organ that needs food just as much as
your stomach needs it
your brain relies on that food
which turns into energy to function
what food does your brain really need
what does what does your brain need
I don't get it slaughter a pig does your
brain need all that fat from the pig
meat
does it does it need all that fat from
the hog that was slaughtered
is that what your brain needs kind of
curious
what food does your brain really need
glucose
it needs glucose
our brain is mostly made out of glycogen
that is stored glucose
our brain is a glycogen ball
we get our first glucose and glycogen
through our mothers
while we're in the womb
if you put a pregnant mom on a keto diet
a real keto diet
and don't have any of that beautiful
glucose that you need from sweet
potatoes and potatoes and carrots
and fruit and bananas
if you put a pregnant woman
on a carb-free diet
the baby will be damaged
if you've been a pregnant woman on a
keto diet a real keto diet the baby will
be damaged
making a lot of friends today once again
seaweed hero good to see you making lots
of friends
we get our first glucose and glycogen
through our mothers
while we're in the womb and then through
breast milk
breast milk is it is defined by its
natural sugar content what
there's sugar and breast milk huh
that's impossible
breast milk is defined by its natural
sugar content
comparatively
it has little fat and protein
breast milk has little fat and little
protein
and that bioavailable Sugar creates the
building blocks of a baby's brain
so when the baby's born
the baby is Reliant upon
glucose in the mother's breast milk
that glucose in the mother's breast milk
is the building blocks to the baby's
brain for development
if a newborn isn't able to breastfeed
those beneficial sugars
come a bit later from ingredients like
fruits and sweet potatoes in baby food
if you put a baby a newborn baby on a
keto diet
lacking carbs and sugar and glucose
that baby will starve to death
very interesting
isn't it
that's why formulas have sugar in them
by the way
so I think science realizes
that the babies they tested the original
formulas on that had no sugar in them
probably didn't fare so good
a portion of this early Glide by the way
they did studies back in the 1940s and
1950s
and they didn't care what happened to
the babies
studies were scary as
they were so scary
they took human beings
and you signed up your baby
and you thought okay no big deal I'll
sign up my baby
and they took babies and they did that
they would give babies different diets
and see what develops
that's what they did back then
Untold Carnage man
a portion of this early glycogen which
is the sugar right you guys the glucose
is permanently sealed off
creating actual brain tissue what does
that mean
developing babies
are drinking the breast milk or the
formula with sugar or whatever
they're getting that early glucose
because it's developing brain tissue but
here's what it's doing that early
glucose Supply and science and research
doesn't know this part right here
I don't have to cite my publisher said
well you're not taking it from anywhere
this is original unique information from
above
so we can't we can't have you cite
anything medical medium because there's
nothing soluble in here it's all
original unique information in these
Bibles here these eight Bibles
what happens is the original sugars
from the mom when the baby was in the
womb
are the building blocks to brain tissue
then when the baby's born
and the baby's breastfeeding
the baby's getting more continual
building blocks
creating new brain tissue permanent
brain tissue so a portion of the glucose
turns into hardened glycogen
which is the permanent brain tissue
foundation for the baby
those beneficial sugars come a bit later
from ingredients like fruits and sweet
potatoes and baby food a portion of this
ready a portion of this early glycogen
which is the sugars the glucose is
permanently sealed off so that means
that sugars from the breast milk that
the baby's ingesting a portion of that
goes to the brain and then becomes
sealed off and becomes permanent brain
tissue
foreign
if you don't believe it's coming from
above this information then I'm a genius
if you don't like thinking I talk to a
voice and that's just inconceivable
then I must be a genius just think I'm a
genius get the information learn grow
and heal get the books be it Advance
with the information and heal heal your
loved ones and you don't have to think I
hear it from above just I'm a genius
then
but please cite the information back to
my geniusness
if you can
a portion of this early glycogen is
permanently sealed off creating actual
brain tissue which science and research
does not know
stored in such a way that it will never
be disturbed in the future
to a degree your brain keeps adding to
that foundational glycogen storage as it
continues to develop through childhood
teenage years and your early twenties
glycogen tissue is the figurative meat
on the brain's bone
it's that early glycogen that's the meat
on the bone
that's what it is
it's an original early glycogen storage
that becomes the permanent resident of
the brain
if someone were to tear into your brain
as though it were a drumstick like eat
it like
if they were going to do that like tear
into the brain like I had a good brain
abroad here
they were to do that
that gray matter flesh would be made
from pockets of decades old glycogen
it would be made from decades-old
glycogen so if you were to tear into an
adult's human brain
and tear into that and crunch into that
and eat the brain right
if you were to do that
you that would be old glycogen you're
eating you're eating glycogen from
decades ago
sugars are your brain's place of origin
your brain also starts to collect
glycogen in storage bins to be used for
fuel
the spider web of glycogen connective
tissue is a safe haven for new brain
cell development it's how brain cells
are birthed
their birth
in that glycogen spiderweb
is there any fat in a healthy brain
that's in a healthy body
so let's talk about that a little bit
because you'll you'll see you'll look
into things if you're like keto science
says our brain is made out of fat it's
90 fat keto says you know that our brain
you know ancient man I love when they
throw that ancient crap around all the
time like anybody knew what anybody did
in the ancient world like anybody even
knew
like what everybody's always like
ancient medicine what or how about this
one ancient Chinese medicine are you
kidding
they gave Emperors Mercury elixirs that
was the medicine of the time Chinese
medicine was Mercury you drink toxic
heavy metal that was Chinese medicine
and you know what else everybody thinks
herbal medicine was everywhere Native
Americans were using some herbal
medicine yes but can I just say this
Chinese medicine they used bugs
if you go into the old Chinese medicine
apotheses that were resembling what used
to be it was all wings of of toads legs
of toads wings of butterflies it was all
like
um it was all fish dehydrated fish
pieces fins of fish and then it was like
bats and bat wings and it was like bird
feather crushed it was all of that you
go to you go to Apothecary in China
and back then alternate medicine and
this happened it sent for centuries it
was just nothing but bugs and critters
claws of Critters claws of bugs Wings
bones bone dust it was all of this like
just the pocket theories were nothing
but all of that there weren't a lot of
herbs I'm sorry to say that that came
from later on
later on isn't that incredible some
people say oh ancient it was ancient no
not really
not at all
I just love when they do that Ancient
Man ate this oh really were you there
you know
it is recorded though
that that in Chinese medicine the number
one the number one Elixir treatment and
cure was Mercury
Emperors went mad they were given Doses
and doses of mercury to try to cure
their ales that is actual
historically true
so I'm kind of tired when I hear this
all the time you see on social media
you know when I take information from
above and it goes in these books and
nobody never even knew anything about it
someone would be like oh that was
probably ancient no
that was ancient fists this is what you
hear it's it's insane
is there any fat in a healthy brain
that's in a healthy body
yes
it's time to research you want don't
want to tell you that the brain is just
made out of all fat now alternative
medicine is like ah the brain's made out
of fat it's all fat now oh really
it's interesting
yes there is extremely low levels of fat
compared to what science and research
theorize you ready theorize
science and research are
basing a theory that the brain is loaded
with fat that's basing a theory
is there any fat in a healthy brain
yes
but there's extremely low levels of fat
compared to what science and research
theorize the fat in the brain is a small
fraction of the brain itself
the fat in the brain is a small fraction
of the brain itself that's important to
know get ready for this
the healthier the person's brain and
body are the smaller the fraction of fat
that resides inside the brain
the healthier a person is
the lower the amount of fat resides
inside the brain
the more unhealthy of the brain and body
are the higher levels of fat that reside
inside the brain so if someone is really
obese
they're going to have more fat in their
brain
get ready for this
this is incredible information by the
way
the cadavers that medical science used
to determine a basis for how much fat
resides inside the brain where cadavers
of older age
and of the poorest health
the cadaver's brains were atrophied and
what was replacing the atrophy were fat
deposits here you ever eat chicken
before have you ever eaten did you ever
eat chicken
did you ever buy a roasted chicken
did you ever eat a roasted chicken
this is super Advanced information right
here by the way
from above super Advanced information
it's in the brain saver book you really
should get these brand saver books page
number 412
have you ever eaten a roasted chicken
do you ever find those fatty deposits in
the roasted chicken
those yellow yellowy strands of fat
deposits
the more unhealthy the chicken was and
raised the more the fat deposits were
if you purchased a regular conventional
chicken that was caged up and fed all
this crap
and got it nice and plump and you cut
open that roasted chicken and you ate
that roasted chicken like yum
you would find a lot more of the yellowy
hunks
of fatty deposits all throughout the
chicken
but guess what you don't see the
chicken's brain
because the chicken's heads are cut off
by the machines right
so those heads just get discarded
probably ground up and thrown into dog
food or whatever
canned dog food the point is is those
chickens brains were filled with fat
the unhealthier that the chicken is
the more the brain of the chicken is
filled with fat
just like the chicken itself and then
when you eat a lean bird maybe a wild
bird what about wild pheasant
Wild Quail
Partridge if you've ever eaten a wild
Partridge you can't find fat on the
Partridge
you can go through the Partridge and be
like this Partridge is good and eat it
right down to the bone
and you won't find a lot of fat on a on
a partridge that's caught in the wild
so what they did what science and and
research did
was when they were looking at brains
back years ago to look for a composition
they were picking old people that died
old obese people that died
their brains had fat deposits riddled
all around the brain in and around the
cavities including inside the cavity
where that gaping hole opens up inside
the middle of the brain as the brain
atrophies as people get older and
healthier and unhealthier and their
brain starts to die
they tested brains that were old
and decaying and atrophy and filled with
fat
they didn't take
a 20 year old's brain who was eating
healthy
and use that
back in the 1940s they took somebody
very obese who died a terrible death of
sickness and illness whose brain was
atrophying they cut that cadaver open
and they took that person's brain
and that's what they did
should I have taken the energy shifter
first like I did because I did an energy
shifter first and I flexibly wound up
Ava says Ava Sheridan says Oh wow was
wondering why it was so hard to
determine how much fat was in a brain
not studying healthy brains
they don't study brains anymore for fat
versus not fat this was done in the 40s
they did that they concluded their
science in 1940.
they took old deceased people who had
atrophy and they were overweight totally
obese in 1940. that's who they used as
the cadavers they don't even they don't
even check anybody's brains for fat
anymore
now because people are so much on the
fat diet and everything oh healthy fat
they just assume oh they're Brands made
out of fat sounds like a good one
and nowadays people are really unhealthy
and children are getting more fat in
their brains than they ever did before
everybody's getting more fat in their
brains than they ever did before it's
like that bad roasted chicken from a
conventional farm that was pumped up
with all kinds of stuff and fed all
kinds of bad food and bad feed
and you don't see that chicken's brain
they cut it off they cut that chicken's
head off that chicken's head off went
into the basket and that was it
gone went down the chute
that chicken's brain was filled with fat
they don't study chicken fat and brains
like they don't take animals and say
well this animal came from somebody's
backyard that was big that was feeding
off of bugs and lettuce and we're gonna
check that chicken Sprain and then we're
gonna check it compared to this old
chicken that was like fed all this
garbage and crap
they don't even do that science just
lets everybody down they never do
anything right with practically almost
everything
brains were atrophied and what was
replacing the atrophy were fat deposits
and and the cadavers they used fat repl
here's when you age and you're not
taking care of your brain
and you're obese
it happens this life is hard
and and you're not taught to take care
of yourself maybe you don't have the
resources you're just having really
difficult time in life and if you're
older you're obese your brain's
atrophying
there's a lot more fat inside the brain
and even if you're not obese there's
more fat inside people's brains now than
ever before because of unhealthy brains
but regardless there's still a fraction
of fat compared to not
neuro ion says can people be absolutely
healthy and still have some fat beneath
the skin
we all have a little bit of fat inside
of us absolutely naturally occurring
it's not about not having a scrap of fat
inside the body that's not it but yes
there's healthy levels of fat that
people have inside you know their body
but got to keep in mind
a fatty liver is really bad
that's bad
and that's important to know that gives
you a window on how it's not good to
have fat inside our body it's true
it isn't 60 of the brain made out of fat
it's much lower
it's not 60 percent
it's supposed to be much much lower
so let's talk about this a little bit
the fat inside the brain of a healthy
person should be roughly the same
percentage of fat as in every organ in
the body did you hear that part
that's important right there that alone
Bethpage says can you be skinny and have
a fatty brain yes because you could have
a fatty liver and be skinny
you can have a toxic overburdened
fatty liver
and have too much fat occurring in the
brain that you're not supposed to have
the fat inside the brain of a healthy
person should be roughly the same
percentage of fat as in every other
organ in the body just like when
someone's liver becomes unhealthy and
starts to take on additional fat and
becomes a fatty liver your brain can
take on additional fat and become a
fatty brain
the brain can do the same becoming an
unhealthy brain that takes on additional
fat and becomes a fatty brain
instead of Medical Science understanding
that the same thing that occurs to the
liver can happen to the brain they
theorize that the brain is supposed to
have that much more additional fat
in truth a healthy 20 year old in good
shape does not have a brain that's made
of sixty percent fat
why is that
the roughly 60 percent fat inside the
brain that medical research and science
claim
is not all omegas
so here's the real trick of the trade
out there of science and research and
alternative science right
healthy fats healthy fats good for your
brain all omega-3 your brain's made out
of fat your brain's made out of fat your
brain's not not made out of
Omega-3 your brain fat isn't made out of
Omega-3
there's microscopic amounts of Omega-3
in the brain yes and that's healthy
small small deposits of Omega-3 the fat
people get in their brain creating a
fatty brain isn't Omega-3
the roughly 60 percent
of fat inside the brain that medical
research and science claim
it's not all omegas
the fat that accumulates in the brain is
the same as the fat
that's in a sick liver
which is also not all omegas and that's
what's interesting oh omega-3s
gotta get your omegas your brain needs
your omegas they need those Omega-3s oh
you got a fatty liver oh you must have
too much omega-3 inside your liver
no it's not Omega-3
it's garbage fat
that's inside your liver it's garbage
fat
oh your brain
your brain's got a lot of fat in there
oh it must be all Omega-3s are you
kidding me your brain's not filled with
omega-3s
your brain has garbage fat in it
why am I yelling
why am I so loud today
the fat that accumulates in the brain is
the same as the fat that's in a sick
liver which is also not all omegas
when people have effect when you get
diagnosed with a fatty liver
you're in the waiting room you're
waiting for your diagnosis the doctor
wants to come in and see you
the internist wants to come come and see
the GP wants to come and see you
well I have something to tell you sir
Mrs Johnson
I want to talk to you about your
diagnosis here from what it looks like
from all our blood work and
and the biopsy we did also on your liver
sorry about that
it looks like ma'am you have a fatty
liver
foreign
no it's not Omega-3
what is it it's garbage fat
same thing in the brain
garbage truck
the fat that accumulates in the brain is
the same as the fat that accumulates in
a sick liver but they're not diagnosing
a fatty brain it's medical medium
information they're not they're not
diagnosing fatty brain out there
they'll say fatty liver
they'll say fatty liver but they won't
say fatty brain instead they will accept
the higher levels of brain fat that are
happening in people's unhealthy bodies
they're getting fatty livers even if
they're skinny and they're getting fatty
brains
I'm Dr Wiggy woggy here
fatty liver
excuse me what's your question
your question is it must be all Omega-3s
I don't know
I'm just thinking fat is good good is
fat good Fat's good you can eat more
avocados and nuts and seeds and get all
the omegas you want
but I'm wondering maybe that might make
your liver fatter
I don't know is your brain filled with
fat
the fat that accumulates in the brain is
the same is the fat that's in a sick
liver which is also not all omegas guess
what news flash
to all doctors
it's not a megas
it's not omega-3s
that person with the fatty liver doesn't
have a fatty liver because it's filled
with Omega-3s that person with a fatty
brain which they don't even know they
have a fatty brain is not filled with
omega-3s
it's fatty deposits of what
Spirit of compassion used for a word
because
when when the information is being
messaged from me into these books after
hearing the words I have to use soc's
word
which is its fatty deposits of
unproductive fat I call it garbage fat
are there omegas inside a healthy brain
yes there are
do they play a role question mark yes
they do
I'm reading from brain saver
page 412
you gotta have the books get the books
tell everybody about the books
if they can't afford they're on sale at
amazon.com us right now if they can't
afford it uh for this the book on sale
which is incredible both books are on
sale
then go to the library get it for free
if you can but they're 42 off and 50 off
on amazon.com right now it's insane
just a forewarning
your mind is going to be blown
can you handle it
that's the question because
the information just the blood draw
chapter alone just the eating disorder
chapter alone just the OCD chapter alone
like I can't even tell you these books
are unbelievable it was one big book and
now it's two big books had to be cut in
half
foreign
energy shifter today I'm looking forward
to another energy shifter I had one this
morning
are there omegas inside a healthy brain
question mark
yes
do they play a role question mark yes
they do
it's a small role
the role these Trace omegas play inside
the brain is the same role they play
inside all organs inside the body
since when did they totally screw
everybody over with this one
they made like
omega-3s
and omegas were critical for the brain
But the irony is it's critical in its
small role for every part of the body
Omega-3s in the same way that liver
needs the omega-3 the spleen needs
omega-3 your pancreas needs the omega-3
your brain needs it your heart needs the
omega-3 the same way but for some reason
they centered it all on the brain
because it was like
a way to
BS more and more people like they knew
brain science or something
you wake up one morning and you have
really bad brain fog and you can't think
and you're walking around and you feel
like you're going insane and you go to
the neurologist and the doctorates of
the neurologist another doctor and
everything you'll see how fast brain
science really works
you'll see what brain science even is
it's
ma'am we did an MRI everything looks
okay uh maybe you just need a rest
you're overworking oh you're not working
that hard
um let's see brain science brain science
all the trillions of dollars so-called
going into brain science uh ma'am you
have let's see you have brain fog it
feels foggy you you focus and
concentration issues
um you have a hard time understanding
what I'm saying or speaking hmm we
didn't MRI hmm we did blood work hmm
maybe you need more healthy fats because
that's what this article says over here
when I look online in this article maybe
you need Omega-3s ma'am you'll see how
fast brain science works when you get
sick
says every sentence of this book is
mind-blowing
is
it's filled with so much important
information this book is the most
important book of our time fill the true
answers to our elements
in the antidotes to heal us and the
antidotes to heal us
[Music]
the role these trace minerals play
inside the brain is the same role they
play inside all organs in the body they
act as insulation for cold temperatures
boom
research in science had no idea that
omega-3s
are an insulator for the entire body
from cold temperatures
that's Advanced Medical information
right here from above in the book
two years from now you'll be hearing it
out there as they thief and theft and
take and steal and poach this
maybe next week at this rate
omegas inside all organs including
inside the brain are there to act as a
mild barrier inhibiting the body from
going into shock too fast from cold
temperatures
nobody knows and medical research and
science alternative science none of it
knows that the omegas are in every organ
they're there
to inhibit shock
from drastic cold temperatures that
happen really quickly in someone
say Laura says I'm 5'9 and about 115
pounds and have so many conditions and
symptoms of a fatty liver
and yet glorifying the importance of
fats for the brain doesn't save us
for the brain fats are a small tool with
a relatively small purpose compared to
the major significance of Sugar's role
in keeping you alive
the role that Sugar plays in the brain
is monumental
compared to the significance of fats
for one
there's that glycogen storage acquired
in baby hood that I talk about before if
you hop down here now
on this live please go back to the
beginning sometime when it's posted
for one there's that glycogen storage
acquired in babyhood childhood in young
adulthood that keeps the brain healthy
and prevents atrophy
being starved of glucose for too long
shrinks the brain
it's one reason why millions and
millions of Americans are suffering from
brain issues and it's another reason why
you can't do a keto diet
a real keto diet like they tried years
ago
you'll notice keto diets have sugar in
them now
huh I'm confused why is it called the
keto diet then you can't go into ketosis
if you're eating foods that have sugar
in them and avocados part sugar
you can't go into ketosis with an
avocado but they brought avocados into
the keto diet the pre-keto diet did not
have avocado in it
and people lost their glucose their
glycogen storages in the brain
keto diets now have berries in there
berries have sugar in there they're
sugar and berries why is that allowed in
the keto diet now
because the old keto diet actually
killed a bunch of people
I talked to one doctor that said whole
bunch of his colleagues and he didn't he
didn't buy it at all a whole bunch of
his colleagues were doing the keto diet
back in the 80s back in the 90s when
they were doing just keto where was you
aren't allowed sugars you weren't
allowed carbs you weren't allowed honey
you weren't allowed berries you weren't
allowed any of that and they lost
patience they died because when they
followed that rule they starved to death
in their brain atrophied
the same way with the carnivore diet now
huh why is the carnivore diet allowing
honey in it now
because a whole bunch of idiots that got
tricked into the you know carnivore diet
meaning where they're trying to sell
carnivore programs they're trying to be
like carnivore experts where they only
do animal meat by itself and that's it
they couldn't hack it because you need
sugar for the brain they were going off
their carnivore diets and binging and
then going back on their carnivore diets
does it sound familiar
staying away from carbs and sugar and
then binging and then having to go back
on no carbs and sugar
even though meat has a tiny bit of sugar
in it in the blood of the meat it's
still not enough to actually purpose
how much someone needs to do or use
their brain
and so they were bumping into walls on
the carnivore diet
and so they were adding berries now
there's berries in the carnivore diet
there's berries in the keto diet there's
sugar in all the Ketone carnivore diets
how why because you couldn't survive you
would die you would literally die your
brain needs sugar it's critical
foreign
it's either the information from above
or I'm a genius because they took that
information from medical medium in the
carnivore diet peeps now they do medical
medium sugars berries and raw honey and
whatever
because they know their brain runs on
sugar they know because the medical
medium info because science doesn't talk
about it out there about how that works
Rita
oh my god wow Anthony I'm relearning
everything now I was listening to
months ago
and he was talking about straight keto
and blueberry smoothies
staying away from sugar well
steals a lot of medical medium
information
and then humors his crowd with it
as if he knew the information before but
he doesn't
and yes why are they doing blueberry
smoothies now why are keto diets doing
blueberry smoothies
interesting
why do people want to do a blueberry
smoothie uh medical medium information
the wild blueberry smoothies and notice
people are talking about wild
blueberries now out there
as if we didn't already talk about it
forever
Donna s says I was on a carnivore diet
keto diet for years and that's when I
got so sick Donna or people who did the
carnivore diet to the letter and died
there are people who did the keto diet
years ago to the letter and died
the reason why is because they had no
glucose to their brain anymore they
followed it to the letter they didn't
binge they stayed on it until they died
people get some results at first when
they cut out all the garbage in the
processed foods and they do a mono diet
of just meat by itself they feel like
they have found the Panacea for five
minutes and then it all goes downhill
after that and they're on raw honey and
then they're on berries and then they're
redesigning their carnivore diet they're
redesigning their keto diet what are
they turning it into in the end they're
turning it into the medical medium diets
that's what's so crazy
foreign
but yet they make a lot of mistakes
because they don't have all the details
being starved of glucose for too long
shrinks the brain it's one reason why
millions and millions of Americans are
suffering from brain issues
as brains are degenerating and reducing
in size those in the health movement
should be saying whoa
we need to get the diet truly right we
need to get sugars back to the brain
the brain's electricity does not run on
fat it runs on sugar
Cold Light spring and now people think
your info was always out there it's
insane
yeah that's a that's actually a tactic
and a strategy
that's what they do like if I talk about
all these incredible details about fat
if they hear fat out there they'll just
like oh wait that must have been out
there because of the word fat like they
don't even realize the concepts and the
in the info and the details it's just
that's a trick to get you not to listen
to Medical medium information so they
can steal it too there's people in the
medical medium community that healed
every illness in their medical meaning
like with their medical medium
information here right that they used
right that was offered to them for free
and they they used it and they healed
everything
and then
but they want to steal it so then
they'll say oh fruits and vegetables
have always been around
medical medium I I can just you know
what forget it
yeah I healed through medical media but
now I'm going to go out there and say I
didn't feel for medical medium I healed
because I knew how to eat fruits and
vegetables it's not that there are
people who have been on fruits and
vegetables but they have to find this
information to heal
it's interesting
if you're listening to this live alone
you know the info it's not out there
there's so much intricate detail in this
live right now in this moment
it's a tremendous amount of details and
it's intricate it's comprehensive just
in this alone right here
like all the books in the lives in the
podcast right you guys know
yeah
the brains of electricity does not run
on fat it runs on sugars too much fat
actually gets in the way of the brain's
electrical grid system fatty brains make
electrical grid system go
overheat and cause problems
foreign
this is why only a small percentage of
fat naturally occurs in a healthy brain
glucose helps reduce heat and keep brain
tissue cool this is why someone would
someone with toxic heavy metals in the
brain
causing a condition such as bipolar
because you know in the books if you've
read the brand saver books or heard
medical meme information throughout the
years you know that Metals create the
bipolar diagnosis in the end when
someone's up down up and
and they get a diagnosis of that
foreign
this is why someone with toxic heavy
metals in the brain causing a condition
such as bipolar often has such a strong
sugar craving people with
that diagnosis of bipolar have a really
craving craving craving to sugar
with the increased heat from the toxic
heavy metals the brain's own adaptive
cooling nature is diminished plus excess
fat in the long term can lead to
unhealthy fatty tissue in the brain
which increases brain heat what this is
saying is more fat in your brain the
more brain Heat
when that happens the brain which again
is formed from glycogen starts to
shrivel up and break down as fat
increases and builds up so more fat
builds up in your brain your brain
tissue starts to shrivel up more fat
tissue starts to shrivel up you end up
with more fat in your brain and less
brain tissue
taking what's the the brain taking
what was the brain tissue space so your
brain shrinking but the fats taking over
the space this is powerful information
its brain is atrophying
but yet
fat in and around the brain is taking up
the space of where the brain was
at the same time heavy metals oxidize
and maladies such as Strokes Alzheimer's
and Dementia can occur more easily fatty
tissue buildup in the brain is not the
same as someone being overweight just
because someone is overweight
doesn't mean they have a fatty brain and
that's an that's interesting so that's
clarification it's a detail that's
important from above
if they if they're eating healthily
it doesn't mean that just because they
have weight on them they have a fatty
brain
and just because someone isn't
overweight doesn't mean their brain
tissue is free from fatty deposits you
could be thin and still have a fatty
brain
they could still have an unhealthy brain
that contains large deposits of fat
tissue whether someone is overweight or
not with a low-fat diet and the
healthiest foods there won't be this
High increased
fat tissue in the brain
probably Wren says oh my God yes giving
up fat helped me so much in overcoming
my panic attacks and mood struggles
right there on YouTube IG official card
says I will be 51 tomorrow and look 30
thanks to UAW congratulations on your
birthday tomorrow amazing
foreign
going on a low carb diet for an extended
time
on YouTube Annabeth Lee maybe the people
with light steel maybe the people
with light steal it and then tell it to
people
who will be saved so then the spreading
of these info is taking good turn
doesn't it question mark So what you're
saying Annabeth is maybe people with
light in them steal it and then they
tell it to other people who will be then
saved so then the spreading of this
information is taking a good turn
doesn't it is that the question Annabeth
no because here's what goes wrong they
don't cite back the source so it becomes
just a bit and a piece
and then that one bit in the piece isn't
enough because you're still going to do
all these other things that are going to
tip their scale
they're still going to stay sick because
they don't have enough of the
information from the original Source
it's not being cited back to the
original source is what's happening
it's really bad for people who are
trying to heal and who are chronically
ill it's like
you're out there you're looking for an
answer you're on your hands and knees
you're praying to God even if you didn't
even believe in God to begin with since
a lot of people they turn to God when
they're at The Darkest Hour when they
weren't even God fearing or believing
God anyway and they're just on their
hands and knees they're praying to God
and they're like I don't have any other
options I'm using hope I lost this I
lost my job my loved one left me I have
all these problems I can't pay these
doctor bills I'm so sick I've tried all
the alternative medicine hacks I could
possibly find I've been to functional
medicine doctors I've been a herbalist
I've been to Chinese medicine doctors
I've been acupuncturist I've been to
Do's I've been to naturopaths I've been
to herbalists I've been to shamanic
healers I've been everywhere I've tried
Ayahuasca now that's my only like
leftover thing I can possibly do is just
just Blitz my brain out with Ayahuasca
and I don't know where to go anymore
because I have now 50 symptoms and
building and people don't know really
what's wrong with me I'm told I created
it with my thoughts I'm hold my bodies
attacking itself I'm told I'm a bad
person and I just need to rewire my
brain I've tried everything under the
Sun including meditations and everything
else and I am just sick and I don't know
what to do and I'm at my darkest hour
and I'm at my darkest point in my life
and then if you find a tidbit that was
shared somewhere for medical medium
information but not cited back to all
the incredible things you can do and the
info to learn and know what it's about
so you can heal and grow you just get a
tidbit you're gonna like oh that's
interesting I'll try that at the same
time I'll try that wild blueberry I'll
take my charcoal that this other person
said to take or the same time I'm having
my wild blueberry for medical medium
that I don't know it's for medical
meaning info because it was never cited
back to you know him I'll take my wild
blueberry thing
eat my wild blueberries and I'll also
take my Pearl powder my ionizer water
which is poisoning the brain uh my
charcoal my shilajit that cost like a
hundred dollars for just a little speck
of it which doesn't do anything for
anybody and I'll just do all this stuff
and it's just endless
but what happens is that people steal
the info to make them look like they
know more that's why they do it too out
there they don't want to cite it back to
medical meaning because they want to
steal it so they look like they know
something because that's what happens
the podcast doctors are stealing so much
info from here because they don't have
any info of their own so they're taking
it and then it makes them look like
they're really smart and so they can say
these few talking points and then people
go oh my God Epstein-Barr wait a minute
uh Metals toxic heavy metals and it
makes them look like they really know
what they're talking about but they
don't and then you just can't get
anywhere then they talk bad about
medical medium on their on the same time
oh reliable source says medical meme
information should not be trusted a
reliable source says medical medium
shouldn't be trusted that's a real a
reliable source says this
no we're gonna steal his info and use it
but we're gonna step on him on at the
same time and then the person if they're
told it's medical medium to begin with
right they may be like oh that person
said reliable sources to stay away from
medical medium so they can't get help
that way anyway or if they use the mm
info
and they don't even cite back the source
the person's gonna never know where to
go to get help it's endless it's like
whatever
I mean that's one way to that's just one
angle of it there's so many different
aspects of how it's all done now
why should I even care
well Spirit of compassion told me when I
was younger you have to care
you have to care about the suffering and
the people who are really really
struggling you have to care about the
people who can't find an answer
I remember when I was a little boy and I
said the spirit of compassion I don't
care
I just want to ride my bicycle
I want to just grab a fishing rod and go
to the pond
and I don't want to know about what's
inside somebody's body and I don't want
to know
why someone's suffering because I'm six
years old and I can't be bothered with
this right now and SOC said to me I'd
better care and I better learn how to
care fast
and I never forgot that lesson
because Spirit of compassion told me
this you don't understand Anthony when
someone
their health goes down hell
it's everything to them and I was
listening as a little boy and I said
what do you mean it's everything to them
and spiritual passion said to me you
don't get it you're not in their shoes
so you're not going to understand it
you're not going to understand what it's
like when you've been to 12 doctors and
15 doctors
and you're really sick and you're almost
bedridden and no one has an answer
and SOC said Anthony you don't
understand what that is you have to
learn what that is because that is
everything so you have to care and so I
spent my life
connecting to that and so when people
don't cite something back that could
save their life to the original source
of the info or they steal it to just
make it look like they know better
to get some followers or to sell
programs it's sad
it's just really sad
instead if they gave the original credit
to Medical medium information and stop
talking crap to tear mm down and people
would get what they need but the evil
tactic of stealing info and then trying
to talk bad about medical medium keeps a
lot of people from healing and even
trusting the information
well well we need to have time for that
one and I need energy shifter it's
heartbreaking truly heartbreaking
I have to say so you guys we covered
some powerful information incredible
information about the brain about how it
works about breast milk too about a
baby's brain developing all of it
there's so much info in this book I
can't even scratch the surface
you guys
[Music]
Rita says Anthony you look great today
honored
robot
[Music]
you guys God bless you too
incredible information honestly it goes
on and on and on whoa
my God this part here coming up
[Music]
this part coming up is insane
it's about Trace mineral salts
this is incredible information right
here there's this one section here I'll
read this one little section right here
trace minerals are not just physical
tangible minerals
like in the food right trace minerals
have connected to everything above us
beyond the Earth our atmosphere is
filled with trace minerals
outer space is filled with trace
minerals I'm on page 414 of brain saver
this is wait to hear this
this is incredible
everybody thinks trace minerals is just
something that's like in
a food
when they hear it when they learn about
trace minerals being inside of food
so there's macro minerals inside food
there's trace minerals inside food okay
so they think well that's trace minerals
inside water there's macro minerals
inside there's solids inside water right
you have solids inside water you have
macro minerals inside water you have
trace minerals inside water it's part of
the solid group inside water
trace minerals are not just physical
tangible minerals they have a Godly
presence so a trace mineral isn't just a
tangible like metal because that's what
these are mineral Metals they're
different
trace minerals are not just physical
tangible minerals they have a Godly
presence
trace minerals have connected to
everything above us
beyond the Earth our atmosphere fear is
filled with trace minerals outer space
is filled with trace minerals
trace minerals can be dead or trace
minerals can be alive and active
the frequencies and signals that come
down from the universe
on the bridge that neurotransmitter
chemicals are extending stimulate
activate and ignite trace minerals
inside our brain
into life giving them in order and a
direction to directly attach themselves
to neurons and restore neurotransmitter
chemicals so this is talking about how
Trace Metals work that are in our
atmosphere
they're all around us it's incredible
Rumble
see
Michael Drew
medical medium was The Missing Link
that I was searching for for years
incredible
hey guys let's make an energy shifter
let's do it I'm bringing it to the
energy shifter right now
I'm in brain saver
let's do it foreign
I have the energy shifter earlier
before coming on
I think I'm going to do that more often
is what I think I'm going to do
Carson says this is why healing is such
a spiritual experience once you start
getting enough trace minerals you truly
feel connected to something higher truly
one and Powerful amazing reason
so energy shifter use the shot when
energetic strength is required for
example
you can try this shot
at the midpoint of a long day when
you're desperate for an energy boost
you can try this shot Jasmine says on
YouTube this shot really works
I've done it a few times and it gives me
Steady energy during the day
incredible
use a shot when you feel unbalanced as
if you don't have enough energy
use the shot
if you're feeling that your energy is
off
and you're not on point
that's a good time to use this shop for
sure
that's incredible Rita LaFleur says
Anthony I would love it if you could do
these videos more often to teach us
you're wonderful I'm honored you feel
that way
thank you Rita
God bless you
use this shot when removing caffeine
from your life
if you're gonna dump the caffeine like
if you're going to be like you know what
I don't want to be a slave to caffeine
anymore
I don't want to be in Chains to keep
chains that caffeine industry just puts
us in I don't want to be the caffeine
industry is statistic
I don't want to be like
the caffeine industry's marketing point
you should read the caffeine chapter in
these books
it's sick
use this shot when removing caffeine
from your life
use this shot when you want to wind down
at the end of the day so you can
recalibrate rest and retire for the
night
the energy shifter is also ideal for
overactive or underactive adrenals that
are exhausted from excessive adrenal
output which
I mean come on let's just be honest and
face it
there's so much going on in everybody's
lives and what's happening in the world
it's easy to just like be burning
adrenaline and burning adrenaline
use the inner shifter energy shifter
if low blood sugar
hypoglycemia is occurring
Sensations such as edginess exhaustion
feeling emotional for unexplained
reasons
like does that ever happen to you guys
where you feel emotional for unexplained
reasons
use this energy shifter if you feel
emotional for unexplained reasons or
starting to get triggered easily
so if you're starting to get triggered
you can use this
which is actually really incredible
seba says on IG out of this whole
challenge I've done mostly energy
shifter amazing it helped shift my focus
to cleanse more and to start to start a
new schedule helped me feel good
amazing
I'm IG
the bertrude said this shot helped me
survive my work schedule amazing
well I recommend right now
for myself to grab the juicer the
medical maker the medicines machine
the medicinal maker
I am grabbing that getting it ready it
is plugged in
and now I have to cut some stuff up so
let's do that here
quarter cup of chopped carrots a quarter
cup
so I'm going to chop up some carrots
really quick here
I'm gonna get a quarter cup going
oh yeah that's great
that's great what else is on this I know
what I'll do is I'll chop it up now a
half cup of chopped raw sweet potato
huh
I like that
half cup the chopped sweet potato please
coming right up
this is a very large one it had smaller
ones before there's withdrawal caffeine
withdrawal protocols
chocolate psychedelics all kinds of
other stuff inside brain saver
rain saver protocols and brain saver get
both books gotta have both the books if
you have one of them
go to library get the other one out for
free if you have if you have only one of
them go to amazon.com get the discount
whatever but yeah
so I'm just cutting these pieces of
sweet potato right here so I'm gonna get
a half a cup of sweet potato
going
it's amazing
excited so I got my carrots ready I got
my sweet potatoes ready we're doing good
half half a cup of chopped red bell
pepper
foreign
just a bad habit
I toss my food in the air a lot of times
in the kitchen and
let me take out the center piece here
there we go
all right half cup of
chopped bell pepper we got it
it's like almost the medical medium
cooking show that's what this is
reminding me about a little bit
okay and then the other one is pineapple
so let's get this rolling
that's right
almost tricked myself
it's got some carrot in there first
foreign
carrot juice the reason why
is because people like would do just
carrot juice right they'd buy carrot
juice gallons of carrot juice it's rid
of compassion said it was never a great
idea this is different it's a small
amount of carrot juice mixed in with
everything else
make sure whatever you're using that's
frozen
is thawed out
make sure it's thaw because if it's not
thawed and it's still frozen it's not
going to create any juice you're just
gonna have ice cream
foreign
so make sure you do that that's
important to know keep that in mind all
right all right so there's some carrots
in there
now we're gonna head to raw sweet
potatoes
nice
I'm really happy you guys like this
drink
I'm very happy
the one thing about the one thing you
have to realize is this is a synergistic
combination
of wild Foods herbs
fruits vegetables leafy greens right
done done in a way that no one would
know it's from above the reason why
these have an instant hit
and Sensations and results that happen
for people
the reason for it is because it's
information from above signs of research
does not know alternative medicine does
not know that it's exactly the
phytochemical compounds that come from
this specific group in the amounts that
makes a difference in somebody's life
and that's what's incredible about the
mm info right it's not beholding to
bad ideas that are out there it's not to
hold into that it's free from that it's
from above so it's free from all of that
which is really incredible okay let's
get some pineapple in here
nice
now I'm using Frozen pineapple I'm just
letting you know
I defrosted it so it's defrosted so keep
that in mind
okay put a little bit more in here
nice
amazing
now what I do is
give it a little time to get through
because what you're doing is you're
saving money with this juicer
because the pulp comes out so dry
now what I notice when people juice
carrots with other juicers it's sloppy
wet and you need bags and bags of
carrots
and you don't need that with this it's
incredible
it's why I endorse this machine this is
the mm-1500 the mm900 1500 are amazing
this is the one with the full
Nutritional Center and everything it's a
mega check it out link is in the
description link is in the profile
so to get this much juice comparatively
what I noticed with all the other
juicers that I've been through this just
to get this much I would have to use
loads of produce that's not an
exaggeration I would have to put a lot
of carrots in a lot of sweet potato a
lot of bell pepper to get even that much
juice and that's where people are saving
money and that's critical
food costs are going up every day
you're going up every day I'm going to
save this because I'm going to make
another energy shifter later I love
knowing that I'm saving produce I could
do more energy shifters for less money
you know when you're buying produce
so it's incredible
it's less wasteful everybody's you know
always worried about waste and stuff
well it's less wasteful how amazing and
what you'll notice is
that's dry pulp it's so much drier than
the other machines so you're not
throwing your produce out the window and
that's what's incredible about it
and people say well juicing you know
you're wasting this you poop this out
you would poop this out if you ate a
carrot it would just go out in the
toilet
so people don't realize that you know
and I talked about that many times you
guys know
but I'm not going to bring the poops out
today because that's what I've always
done when we talked about this is I
bring the poops out I'm not going to
bring the poops out although every part
of me wants to run to the other room
where I have a lot of props and go grab
the plate of poop but I'm not gonna do
it
wait a minute who said that poop was a
prop that was real poop from my friends
that we dehydrated and I'm using as a
prop all right
[Music]
can't help it
anytime poop comes into question
[Music]
Dr Nesbitt also likes talking about poop
man
[Music]
this is one of my favorite shots of all
time the energy shifter
I'm not gonna lie
I drink a lot of the energy sifters
because what I do is something that I
don't think other people should do is
they push themselves past their
limitations
and then I use medical medium tools
to enable me to push me past limitations
[Music]
God I love that
love it
incredible
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
oh my God it's so good
how many of these do you guys drink
you guys I need a thumbnail
I need a thumbnail for YouTube and stuff
for the website
I need a thumbnail just hang on for a
second
[Music]
here's a thumbnail right here
why do I have to spill things
here's a good thumbnail right here
[Music]
oh my God I love the energy shifter the
energy shifter though it makes me say a
lot of silly stuff so I don't know
I don't know if it's a good thing to do
you know
it makes me talk really silly
bartender
[Music]
give me another
bartender
[Music]
oh Mr William coming right up would you
like another energy shifter
Mr William we put a little bit of some
psychedelics in this energy shifter I
hope you're okay with that I I don't
want any psychedelics in my energy
shifter can I get the one without it
just kidding Mr William this energy
shift is for you thank you bartender
amazing
I have so much energy right now
and it's ridiculous
you guys are you doing your energy
shifter how much energy do you have
right now from that energy shifter
it really is an incredible resource
I mean I just love it
I love it I love it
whoo
Dr Nesbitt
foreign
Dr Nesbitt um try not to knock over
the table because she's gonna have it
sit down with you guys for a second okay
I'm
educating myself says I'm now
I now shout bartender in kitchen all the
time oh dear
um what does Dr Nesbitt show
Dr Nesbitt says he shouts
he shouts when he has his shots of
Ivanka he says
send it on down that's what he shouts
out
um Shan star from IG says I am learning
so much from these lives thank you aw
for doing these lives
Dr Nesbitt says he's tired of these
lives
he actually doesn't want to do anymore
he comes here and he says he comes here
to visit to sit down and have a drink
even though I don't drink alcohol Dr
Nesbitt does he says he comes here to
blow off steam
and he says every time he's here now
we're do we're live
Dr Nesbit it's good though you can come
on here and you can talk to everybody
Jennifer says how much should we drink
all of it some of it you're drinking
many I'm so confused yes Jennifer you
can have one
and you can save the rest
for some reason I am getting carried
away and I am drinking two or three and
you can do that if you really want to
too and you can even space them out
Saint Sue says this shot was better than
any stimulant Med I was prescribed
Dr Nesbitt stop Dr Nesbit
Dr nesbit's actually upset saying sues
doctor
no no don't don't Dr Nesbitt says
whatever you were prescribed in the past
he's sure your doctor was thinking
good of you he's saying
Dr Ness is very upset because he's
prescribes lots of medications
Dr Nesbitt is a board-certified
psychiatrist
and he actually doesn't believe in all
of this hogwash he says all the time
he likes straight good old medications
he likes good old cow meat and
medications
Polly Wren says I did a mood shifter
today and I am in a very good mood makes
this Live extra funny
um
Dr nesmond meat is fine if someone wants
to eat meat medical medium information
is not anti-meat if somebody wants to
eat meat
that's so we're not we're not against
animal protein here so why are you
saying that
he says for no reason he just wanted to
say that we're pro-plant-based and
pro-vegan too you can be a fish Aryan
and come here
if you are on fish alone and you're just
doing fish Aryan you know like
breatharian you have breatharian really
works
sure
unbelievable
if you're a fisherian and you come here
to Dr Elizabeth we welcome everybody
Michael xrage says hi Dr Nesbitt
um I think that overall
you know I think overall that people
have to realize that
um
Dr Nesbitt says
ask your doctor what's right for you
he says ask your doctor what's right for
you should Dr Nesbit say he doesn't
believe in any of this hogwash he called
it
he says he just likes hanging out with
me
that's all
although Dr Nesbitt did have
a trauma shock and loss stabilizer
recently and he says it helped him
greatly rise with Melton oh my God had
the best experience with the energy
shifter yesterday while being in the 369
my brain was supercharged and I had
energy off the chain like the
battery bunny
Dr Nesbitt says how dare you talk about
the Energizer Bunny which is a personal
friend of Dr nesbit's Dr Nesbitt did a
surgery on the Energizer Bunny
if the Bashir says the energy shot is
one of my favorite tasting drinks
Dr Nesbitt
Dr nesbeth said don't make fun of bunny
rabbits the Energizer Bunny I know
you're not making fun of bunny rabbits
just Dr Nesbitt he doesn't know what
he's thinking right now because he's Dr
Nesbitt had a few too many vodkas
Tiffany shacklett says I quit coffee
after your podcast
Dr Nesbitt says
congratulations
he says he prefers you on coffee Dr
Nesbitt
what are you saying she quit coffee
yes
no no one should be drinking coffee
really
yeah
Pilots
Dr Nesbitt
when you're on a plane you want your
pilot to drink coffee
um yeah but if your pilot needs to drink
coffee then your pilot's not feeling
well to begin with and doesn't have any
energy or Clarity and he needs coffee to
make he or she clear and that's kind of
scary all on its own
Nicholas Russell says celery juice
replaced my coffee I once drank it night
and day
huh
my God
incredible
Jesse Lane been on coffee
nope
been off coffee for two years Jess I
almost did you wrong man
I read your comment wrong and said been
on coffee
I'm so sorry you've been off coffee
amazing
you think that's funny but yes yeah
Robin Marie says we like hanging out
with you too oh Robin thank you for
being here
um
Dr Nesbitt says
enough is enough
Dr Nesbit says enough is enough
he's a
Dr Nesbit you need an energy drink
Dr Nesbitt
why
Dr Nesbitt The only thing is you might
get orange
Dr nesbian wants energy
good job
okay Dr Nesbit just had some
Dr nesby do you feel it
you feel it yet
Melanie I drank a full pot of coffee a
day now since aw for three years no
longer oh my God that's incredible you
were no longer a slave to the caffeine
industry the think tank
you know you guys they actually the
caffeine industry has a think tank
because caffeine is used in
Pharmaceuticals too
Dr Nesbitt
Dr Nesbitt says he agrees
caffeine's in Pharmaceuticals he's a
doctor he can say so
I'm under
the umbrella
of
a board-certified
psychiatrists and a board-certified
surgeon
he says he will
give me guidance as we're here
um
Carson said these mushroom coffees are
just a way to keep people hooked yeah I
know it's actually it's actually just
terrible all of it's terrible
this this is the light heart of part of
the show
this is the lightheart part of the show
right
we're all trying to keep a light heart
someone just got mad I had a I had a
chicken here just don't hurt Dr
nesbitt's feelings he's just he's just
being light-hearted and we're just being
lighthearted it's okay
you don't have to get upset at Dr
Nesbitt a lot of people are struggling
out there and are suffering out there
and they need a little lightheart fun
stock nesby came along
you don't have to get mad at him
yeah the world's a hard place and Dr
Nesbitt
all right Dr Nesbitt says he wants to go
he wanted Dr Nesbit poster
okay guys
Dr Nesbit is saying bye
yes Dr Nesbitt that is your um tick tock
that's your Tick Tock uh account
yeah
we're using your Tick Tock account
you don't mind right
hopefully there's a few people on there
senso Studio said this is the best time
of the day learning and hanging out with
you all guys learning hanging out with
all you guys thanks SOC and aw thank you
for hanging out with us I'd hang out
with you guys all day
the innocence by Dr Nesbitt okay
thank you guys
you're redoing your telegram so you can
get on my telegram awesome I leave
exclusive messages on Telegram
I will see you there sometime
um subscribe to my telegram check out
medicalme.com