I was born
and right when I was born had
pharmaceutical applications now I don't
have any toxic heavy metals I never had
any medals passed down from generation
to generation I never had any Metals
passed down from my family line
no okay
talk about toxic heavy metals right now
this is day seven medical medium brain
shot therapy cleanse challenge but we're
talking about Metals this is a big deal
because people have Metals I'm going to
read about tattoos in a little while too
which is really interesting too now I'm
not anti-tattoos if somebody wants a
tattoo I don't like judge anybody for
tattoos for having ink quite the
contrary quite the opposite actually
because people like tattoos they get
tattoos but I'm going to talk about why
we're doing the
toxic heavy metal exposure shot exposure
ly exposure that's the word right there
okay so it's important to know we're
talking about exposure and what happens
with tattoos so you're going to want to
hang out for this show what happens with
tattoos is they give you continual
exposure for years to come that's why I
like not only just a heavy metal detox
right smoothie and heavy metal right
cleanse right in the brain saver books
not only do I like that I like the
exposure shot because the exposure shot
is grabbing on to new exposure you can
have an old tattoo
but it's releasing brand new exposure
every day
for the rest of your life I see people
that get tattooed on their face they get
tattooed on their neck they get tattooed
behind their ear they get tattooed on
their neck
they get their head shaved and tattooed
on their scalp and their hair grows back
over it but I see people they get a lot
of different tattoos if your tattoo
we're gonna cover a lot of stuff man
this is gonna be a great show
if you get your tattoo here
behind your ear
that toxic heavy metal is being released
closer to the brain
it's critical to do the exposure shot
ask your doctor what's right for you
it'll take my advice
take the book to your doctor and listen
to your doctor so we're talking about
toxic heavy metal exposure you guys
I'm excited about this and I have some
ingredients in front of me the whole bit
we're on day seven the medical me and
brain shot
therapy cleanse Challenge and guess what
it's free you can download your
information at medicalmedium.com letting
anybody know if you think you want to
join if you don't want to join you you
want to just hang out we'll party we'll
have some fun that's fine too but if you
go to medicalmedium.com you can sign up
to the cleanse challenge to the brain
shot therapy and you can download your
free grocery shopping list get all your
information it's incredible we're doing
20 days
they were on day seven so
I'm gonna go to page 23 of brain saver
now if you don't have a brain saver book
fine
fine fine
it's okay
I got one right here and I'm going to
read a little bit about toxic heavy
metals and then we're going to talk
about tattoo shortly after that I hope
you hang in there for this episode
because I am not going to disappoint
today there's always information from
Spirit of compassion that's mind-blowing
Emily Marshall said hi aw just sent down
another speaking your truth stabilizer
from yesterday wow was that did you hear
the telegram message I left the telegram
audio message I left that was shortly
after I sent one down
and then I was on there talking Lana
says the speaking your truth shot was
like changing for me and my BF
I love that brain shot speaking your
truth tables I love that powerful brain
shot
it's it's really it just blows my mind
you know all of it so I'm in brain saver
if you don't have a book read along with
me here if you have a book read along
with me here
if that made any sense all right page 23
right here
exposure to toxic heavy metals is all
around us
you don't think so
if you took an antibiotic
you got toxic heavy metal exposure
if you took an antibiotic 10 years ago
you have toxic heavy metal exposure if
you took an antibiotic when you had your
ear infections when you were five years
old six years old seven years old you
had your bronchitis ear infections or
anything else and you took your
antibiotic I'm not saying don't take
antibiotics or whatever that's not what
this is about ask your doctor what's
right for you I'm saying
you had toxic heavy metal exposure
we're not taught about it so we don't
learn to recognize our sources of
exposure
we're not taught to recognize the
exposure we're not
so we don't learn to recognize our
sources of exposure if we're not taught
about it how do you recognize your
sources
they're much closer than we think toxic
heavy metals have plenty of avenues to
enter our bodies
from toxic heavy metals that we breathe
we breathe them in every day every
single breath we take has toxic heavy
metals in it courteous
the evil doers dropping it out of the
sky on us
okay
I don't like to be the messenger of this
information but it is what it is
it falls out of the sky every day
every single day you took a jog one
morning you're breathing it all in
that's okay we can still Empower
ourselves and do things for ourselves
so it's around us
Nicole McCullough says best info ever
exclamation points and best cookbook oh
my God
over a hundred recipes in these brain
saver books this is more than that
from toxic heavy metals we breathe to
toxic heavy metals that we eat we don't
eat toxic heavy metals
it's falling out of the sky on the grass
that the cows are eating
toxic heavy metals are falling out of
the sky on the grass that the grass-fed
beef cows
are eating
toxic heavy metals fall on the courtyard
of every chicken
that's
pecking around grabbing bugs and things
like that and everything else toxic
heavy metals are everywhere they're in
our water they're in our air they're in
our food you can't avoid it on the
planet industrialized Metals float
amongst the skies in the atmosphere drop
everywhere on the planet
you can't avoid it but that's okay
that's okay
to toxic heavy metals that we drink to
toxic heavy metals that we bathe in to
toxic heavy metals that we touch or
apply to our skin
that's right
simply touching aluminum foil or a
battery can be enough for their mining
particles of metal to leach into our
bloodstream this isn't about fear and
Chaos it's about
becoming empowered and doing something
about it I would like to know I don't
want to live my life not knowing I don't
want to go about my days not knowing
I want to know everything what about you
guys I want to know what's around me I
don't want to just ignore it like it
doesn't exist
I I get it some people do there's a lot
of people out there they just don't want
to know what exists they want to ignore
it they don't want to think that it's
even possible but I want to know
Courtney M.A says she wants to know
people they can live in Bliss or
ignorance or whatever we want to call it
they just don't want to know what's
happening
and that's not to mention the metal
particles we can ingest from food
prepared in certain metal cookware or
food and drinks served in metal
containers I do not smack a metal
utensil out of a friend's hand
if I see them use a metal utensil
I don't Smack it out of somebody's hands
you know I don't
oh because empowerment
is being able to also live in this world
and actually do something about it
when I know I'm doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie
and I know I'm doing the exposure shot
if I happen to use a metal fork and I
get a little steel
rubbed off
I know I'm doing something about it
[Music]
toxic heavy metals can be at our in our
indoor ear
or outdoor air check this out right air
fresheners spew toxic heavy metals
that's why I say we should pull them out
of the plugs the walls throw them in the
trash right air fresheners
that you're spraying
right let me spray the couch let me
spray the chair let me spray the carpet
the air fresheners right have toxic
heavy metals in them so when you're
breathing you're like
ah wild flowers
fake wildflowers
[Music]
that's that metal that's metal in there
colognes and perfumes
I like the smell of that
oh man I don't like the smell clone or
perfume but the smell of that cologne
and perfume Nettles
people need to know they need to be they
need to be taught like that's metal your
smell
toxic heavy metals can be indoor or
outdoor air especially if we're in the
presence of toxic fragrances oh I said
it in here I was ahead of myself scented
candles that's another one scented
candles
people don't realize how much metal is
spewing out of there yes in that
fragrance that's blowing out of a
scented candle that's burning out of a
scented candle right
then you got pesticides and then you got
the
Trails up in the sky
we even annoyingly put toxic heavy
metals directly into and onto our bodies
with certain cosmetics
Pharmaceuticals
Beverages and other products right
you know like this is well-known
information and I will cite that this is
not mine this piece of information
meaning this is all my information from
above right it's very compassions
information but you know the Wizard of
Oz
the movie
okay in the early 20th century
and the Wicked Witch of the West I think
had a green face
okay and you can look this up out there
it was a copper
application that made her face green
right
so for that movie
they did an application of copper on
that actress's face
and
from what The Story Goes her face stayed
green for her entire life
from that copper right
and when we think about that that's
really highly toxic
so it was a makeup made out of copper to
make your face look green
but when people don't realize is copper
it's really industrial lies copper that
same industrialized copper that was in
her makeup
to save copper that people use copper
mugs and stuff out of
the same industrialized copper
that when you do copper utensils copper
mugs copper jewelry right you don't want
to play with copper
and there's too much copper available to
play with
we are all high in Copper
not only high in the trace mineral
copper because it's the least
deficient mineral on the planet in every
single food
so not only are we not deficient in
Copper Trace mineral coppers but we're
saturated and toxic industrialized
copper
we have not only do the humans on this
planet have an abundance of Trace
mineral copper in US
from the earth we also have too much
industrialized copper in US
people don't know this that's medical
medium information
that's mm info I don't want to confuse
that with the Wicked Witch of the West
when she had the copper makeup that's
not MediCal medium info when she had the
copper makeup and all that that's known
out there
laughs
Kelly Burke that repost from the gal
speaking on your TG message was so
harmful it really was
it was so it was so you know yeah
yeah a shout out to BG compassion Randy
G for that you're real and and response
from the telegram message that I did
last night it meant so much to me and
Kelly that's what you're talking about
I'm pretty sure yeah I mean honestly
it was mind-blowing
thank you
I mean I was all choked up
um watching
um Her speech about it all and it was it
was incredible
toxic heavy metals are everywhere
we can apply it on our skin with
cosmetics
still in there it's still in cosmetics
it's still in everything is what I was
trying to say
Pharmaceuticals Beverages and other
products
you'll find extensive details about
toxic heavy metal exposure in this book
I just read that right there
we are getting toxic heavy metal
exposure at a minuscule level on a
continual basis
so we get it every day on a continual
basis so we are exposed
it's not like we're drinking a gallon of
leaded gasoline we're not doing that
Mariah says Where can we find the real
go to Medical mediums IG right on
Instagram
check out the reel
we're getting these exposures repeatedly
in our everyday lives a little bit here
a little bit there you might look at a
single exposure and think no big deal
everybody looks at a single exposure if
they're aware of that single exposure as
if it's no big deal that's what we do we
don't really
understand it or we don't really care
and we don't really see it as a big deal
that's how it works with toxic heavy
metals and that's how they get you
that's how the evil doers on the planet
get us too it's always these small
amounts through say Pharmaceuticals or
through some other Avenue or the food
chemistry business or whatever it is
industry out there like all of it we
just get it little bit by little bit by
a little bit
Death By A Thousand Cuts its exposure by
a Thousand Cuts is what it is to
exposure by a Thousand Cuts
you might look at a single exposure and
think no big deal just like people will
often think of a micro dose of
psychedelic drugs huh we mentioned that
in here pretty funny there's a micro
dose chapter inside this book that'll
blow your mind
get it blow your mind
no pun intended though
so people think just like no big deal
with a micro dose of psychedelic drugs
is no big deal because of the trendy
advice about everything in moderation
we're getting poisoned with toxic heavy
metals in moderation
I'm in the brain saver book on page 24.
right here
Incredible Book
we're getting poisoned with toxic heavy
metals in moderation and that may not
seem significant until you step back and
look at the bigger picture repeated
exposure adds up and if we don't do
anything about it if we don't do
anything about that repeated exposure it
adds up adds up and then it bites Us in
the butt
at a certain point the toxic heavy
metals in her brain and body accumulate
they do they accumulate
at a certain point
inside her brain and her body
until we reach a large poisoning at some
point later on in life yes
although we still won't know it's toxic
heavy metal poisoning when you have
depersonalization anxiety depression OCD
bipolar schizophrenia
memory problems
focusing concentration issues
Alzheimer's dementia
will get older region expiration date
where everything goes wrong from
collecting so many toxic heavy metals
inside our brain and we'll never know
what did it we hit our expiration date
we have an expiration date
we do
and
it's Death By A Thousand Cuts here on
planet Earth
and planet earth has a lot of Darkness
on it so there's also death by one cut
too on planet Earth
by evil people and evil doers but death
by a Thousand Cuts
even as someone who lives in a bubble
and they don't know really what's going
on and they don't have too many worries
in the world or they have a lot of money
or whatever it is and they're just doing
their thing every day they're still
getting a death by a Thousand Cuts
everybody is here on planet Earth
Nicholas Russell years before my
grandmother's death the last time I saw
her she had no idea who I was and
wouldn't even look at me damned medals
truly I mean the mm info about Metals
creating dementia and Alzheimer's out
there in the world's powerful
information because at least we know and
we can do something about it for the
future we can do something about it for
the future
because you know now so
that's how it works we have to somehow
get enough people to know and I feel
terrible for so many people that may not
have known through the years I've seen a
lot of people have so many difficulties
Tracy says what's the target audience
for this book
the target audience
I mean the books are made for the
chronically ill for people who have been
through hell and back people who are
also
they've been sick for 10 years they've
been sick for 20 years people who
have seen it all done everything 10
doctors 20 doctors Specialists
neurologists everything
the brain saver books are incredible
books
I guess if you want to use the term
target audience I've never used that
term but if you want to use that term
that you were mentioning I would say
it's for people
who have been through enough seen enough
and they they need the answers
and
honestly it's for anybody of course
who's sick but
like we've talked about before spirit
and I
if you first get sick chances are you're
not going to grab a medical medium book
you're going to go to a doctor then to
another doctor I want people to go to
their doctors
but before they grab a medical medium
book and bring it to their doctor that's
going to be a while so people have to go
on the Merry-Go-Round they have to try
every Trend and everything from coffee
enemas to sodium bicarbonate poisoning
too
alkaline National Water machines which
only create more heavy metal toxicity to
everything they have to go through all
that and then microbiome tests and they
have to do fecal matter transplants
implants and they have to do all that
before they find the medical medium
books they have to do all that and then
some and they're still having their
neurological symptoms and finally they
say you know what
I'm just going to try one of those
medical medium books
I could talk about that all day
singing sweetly says a decade ago I had
amalgam fillings taken out and I
remember having such a bad emotional
experience for months after that and had
no clue what happened
from the Mercury outcasting
see
um kalasha says it is okay to drink
heavy metal is it okay to drink heavy
metal detox smoothie
if we have an amalgam filling in our
mouth
I'm wanting to have mine removed but not
sure if I can start this movie first
or I should wait till it's out I have
doctors ask me that question all the
time and I recently told a physician who
was asking me that for himself and for a
patient of his and I said to him that it
was fine
absolutely in fact
um I have family members that have
amalgam fillings from
100 years ago whatever and they do the
heavy metal detox smoothie every single
day ask what's right for you ask your
doctor what's right for you
um but I do
um I did talk to a doctor recently about
his amalgam filling and his patience
amalgam filling and they're on the heavy
metal detox movie because what what it's
doing is it's Gathering any metal that's
being released from your amalgam
fillings every single day that's that's
recent exposure so what we're doing here
is we're talking about the toxic heavy
metal exposure shot right now right
but that's like recent exposure because
when Mercury is leaching from amalgams
it's its recent exposure every day a
little bit every day right
but that's the same thing with tattoos
there's Mercury and Tattoos there's
toxic heavy metals and Tattoos so that's
that's everyday recent exposure
and that's what I like the exposure shot
too so but the heavy metal detox
smoothie I recommend for family and
friends that have amalgam fillings
regardless yeah
but ask your doctor what's right for you
I have recommendations in the book of
how
not to just take out all your amalgam
fillings at once
I talk about information about how to
you know like what would be
a good way of getting amalgam fillings
out of your mouth so I do have
information in here too like I talk
about
if it's broken or falling apart
right that's a great time to get it done
you know I talk about that but I I also
talk about if someone has a whole bunch
of amalgam fillings in their mouth and
they're not causing like the tooth is
still okay the Magnum filling is still
okay
that I tend to tell family and friends
you know you leave them in but if they
do want them out if someone does want
one out
I tell family and friends
don't take them all out at once
on the same day
you know I've seen people get like 12
out or 20 out in one day
and that's medical meme information
SOC has recommended not to get
20 out in one day so that but it's in
the books that information in detail
okay
so let's keep on reading a little bit
this is powerful information I'm excited
let's move on a little bit to the next
part I was going to read which I'm going
to look for now
so
I'm going to go into a different section
let me see here
okay ready guys
first of all if you just arrived we're
in the branch shot therapy class
challenge we're day seven you can still
join we're doing 20 days guess what it's
free you don't have to
you don't have to pull your pockets out
you don't have to get your wallet and
your purse is out it's free just letting
you know sign up go to medicalme.com
you're wondering what I was doing I was
trying to pull my pocket out here and
all right so we're talking about tattoos
I know a lot of people have tattoos I am
not
shaming anybody for a tattoo far from it
you want a tattoo that's what you want
you go get a tattoo if that's you if
that's what you want to do I'm not even
be I'm not even being sarcastic at all
on any level people have ink
so many people have ink okay and
um
I'm just telling you that if people have
ink that's what they got all right
totally understand but I want to talk
about it for a little bit for a minute
tattoos are a source of toxic heavy
metal exposure now before I go any
further I'm sure a few of you might be
like
that's
because medical meme doesn't understand
I get cruelty free ink vegan ink and
it's cruelty free
and my you know tattoo guy tells me
there's no Metals in it
that's
ink has to have metal in it or it's not
going to show itself through your skin
when the sunlight or light from your
house or light from your room hits it
it has Metals in it
that's what causes it to pop and reflect
light
Through Your Skin if tattoo ink didn't
have Metals in it
you would wouldn't be able to see the
details of your tattoos
that's why as your tattoos age
as years go on the metal is aging and
leaving the skin that's why tattoos fade
as you get older the reason why your
tattoo doesn't pop
when you got you got your tattoo at 20
years old
popping meaning it pops you see it
because of
of toxic heavy metals
but then when you're 50 years old
or 60 years old it doesn't pop anymore
it fades right
it's fading because so much of the metal
is leaving
the skin and it's been going into your
bloodstream for 50 years 40 years
Macaulay says remember when you made
that video with a big tattoo on your arm
yeah I do yeah
there's a whole bunch of tattoos on my
arm
I do remember Uma
thank you for reminding me that's pretty
funny
it is I put info about toxic heavy
metals in all ink and now science is
trying to write it write about it and
you'll see articles being put out now
even saying organic ink
2 has Metals in it so by the way
the
metal free ink Theory
okay that was out there
right first of all the awareness that I
put out there about ink having metals
alarmed the tattoo ink world
right so the tattoo ink world started
shifting gears and they started moving
they started moving to cruelty free
tattoo ink which is
um which is a different type of vegan
ink and all that right all these
different ones and they moved to that
and they're like well this these are
better inks these are better inks then
everybody's like what do they have metal
in it oh no these don't have that they
all have metal in it right
but I got I got a lot of
for blowing that one up I got over the
years
telling that info that piece of
information messaging out about how ink
has metal right it caused a lot of
problems and then
all the people who got Inc
from so-called better sources
were upset because it was a better ink
quality but still had battle in it and
then they felt tricked and jaded so then
I got a lot of for that because
there's a whole bunch of people a whole
bunch of vegans
and you know and keto animal protein
people who got ink
and then when the word got out that
their cruelty free ink still has metal
in it I got a lot of again
see so people have no idea how much crap
I get
Jason P says so a tattoo would be
invisible without Metals no not
invisible but that's a good point Not
Invisible it just wouldn't pop and the
detail wouldn't be there
the detail
and it would fade really quick fade
really quick like say you're 20 years
old see Jason say you're 22 years old
whatever 25 years old maybe you're 30
whatever say you're 30.
and you get a brand new tattoo
if there wasn't metal in it
it would fade really quick it would fade
in weeks and in months a couple years
you just have to be fading
but the reason why metal is in all
tattoo ink is so that that reflection
occurs metal reflects light
so you can't just put metal free ink in
your on your neck your face your hands
you know I know a lot of people get ink
on their their Knuckles and stuff they
get them on their fingers their Knuckles
right
they wouldn't be invisible then it just
would fade quick and it wouldn't pop
Erica Malek says if someone gets their
tattoos removed are they protecting
themselves from further especially my
recommendation is don't get tattoos
removed
unless you hate the tattoo that much and
you're somebody that like you know Ben
loves Jessica
and you know you guys break up and all
of a sudden somebody's so upset like
Ben's so upset he can't take it anymore
and he's got two choices he can tattoo
over Ben loves Jessica
he can tattoo over that
or he can remove it
that's up to him you know but the late
the laser removal of removing toxic
heavy metals
from your being removing your your
tattoo sorry the laser removal of
removing your tattoo can make the tattoo
Leach fast
the Laser's not getting rid of the metal
is pushing it into your bloodstream
that's why
a friend of mine had like removal laser
removal of a tattoo
he was so sick and he's like why the
hell am I so sick and I'm like because
you just got all that metal dumped into
your bloodstream fast that stuff's going
to your brain going to your liver
so
like right now tattoos are in big time
right
it's not just for like the Navy and the
army
in the Air Force
the tattoos aren't just for bikers right
they're not just for bikers anymore
they're for like football players
they're for like you know they're for
basketball players football players
they're for soccer players like
everybody's Inked Up they're for
everybody right
so but what I see when I see everybody
getting that much ink I'm like holy crap
and everybody's got a sleeve
all the football players have sleeves
I'm like dude
if you don't learn about how to get
medals out of your bloodstream
throughout your life that stuff is going
to go to the brain
and yours is going to be you know
dealing with Alzheimer's
I see all the NBA and all like NFL and
everybody and they're just Inked Up from
their arms are Inked Up they're Inked Up
in the whole body I'm like what
it's like oh man sure you're in shape
now you're working out you're an athlete
pro athlete but down the road you gotta
get the medals out
medical medium I just want to say this
medical medium is not common sense
because there's nothing common about it
it's mind-blowing information that sets
the stage for the frontier of all
alternative medicine at this point for
the most part
it sets the stage for information out
there because it makes sense
so mm info is not common sense mm info
just makes sense there's a difference
right there it's like whoa that
makes sense right like that kind of
thing like whoa
I've been swearing a lot ever since I
did
the Sarah Foster and Aaron Foster
podcast
episode
they were swearing they got me swearing
and then swearing a little more because
of it
I have to let them know anyway
Health with Liz is laughing right now
look the point is what I'm trying to say
I'm not done with tattoo talk though you
guys I got tattoo talk if you're not
interested it's okay hang out we're
doing the shot exposure shot because
you've probably got metal exposure from
doing all kinds of other stuff
it just makes sense the medical medium
information it's not common sense it
doesn't contradict itself and only puts
all the details together and builds upon
itself
the laser removal
for ink so you can get rid of your
tattoo pushes the metal
a laser going over your skin cannot take
the metal out of your body magically
you know whatever that laser whatever
that tattoo is I know a lot of people
have words written on their ribs and
stuff it's like like that that scripture
like a big thing with tattoos is
scripture it's like a whole sentence
going across the ribs the whole sentence
going across their back right we I
noticed that a lot of guys and girls
they're getting like they're getting
um they're getting words of wisdom from
somewhere like a quote or something from
somewhere and they have it written over
here on their forearms maybe they have
something like
you know some cool quote right
not making fun of it I'm just saying
that that's how much ink is out there
it's that many people have ink it's
people you don't even expect to have ink
and they got tattoos everywhere
it's okay to have a tattoo
but I think knowing
more about it is also really okay think
about that
so
um
yeah
helpful as words of wisdom right people
have the scripture on them whatever kind
of like you see it I saw somebody like I
saw somebody pretty recently right on
social media and they had like a
paragraph written on their chest it was
like a paragraph and it was written all
like nice
I was like
that's fine you can get a paragraph
written on your chest or your back or
something but
what's going on is this so back to Jason
you said that would the ink just
disappear be invisible that's what it
was be invisible if the metal wasn't in
there no it wouldn't be invisible it
would just be blotchy
and fade it looking
early on
especially later on like turn to crap
that's what it would be
so tattoos
okay for example okay
historically check this out
right indigenous cultures using tattoo
ink
right handmade batches
and then they would take a sharp
Sharp
Hardwood
pencil and they would Pierce her skin
with the ink
to make tattoos
right
people don't realize the mixture they
used
were deposits of metals
that they mind their self and ORD their
self
okay
so indigenous cultures that you that
made tattoos
going back
would unearth deposits of minerals
and they would crush it
with anthocyanins
right color
that they would get from plants
then they would but but it was metal it
was all metal
and they would
push it into their skin and then when
the wound would heal
you would see your tattoo clear as day
Sun hits it clear as day boo now in
modern day
it's manufactured
by the industry
and metal has to be in it
in order to make it pop
am I driving you guys crazy today
I'm driving myself crazy today all right
on IG laugh out loud I have a ton of
tattoos I'm so grateful for this
information because my neurological
symptoms were getting out of control
explanation points this info has
literally saved my brain incredible I'm
happy happy you're here thank you for
that comment on IG
I think I missed your handle I think it
went up
um
I apologize for that so the point is is
that what I'm saying is it's okay to get
tattoos if somebody wants tattoos that's
not it it's just that it's constant
exposure to mental so when we do things
to take cheer of ourselves and today
today is all about
the brainchild therapy and it's all
about the toxic heavy metal exposure
shot so that's what it's about today
Lisa loft house
on YouTube
I do hair explanation points heavy metal
exposure every day explanation point so
thankful to have heavy metal detox
smoothie and Lisa I don't want you to
quit your job
I'm not telling you you have to quit
your job
exactly you're doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie every day you're grabbing
on to that exposure every day Natasha
gray medical medium info is the only
information that makes complete sense
amen
I tell Spirit of compassion all the time
why do you make so much sense
all the time
okay so let's read a little bit about
tattoos oh tattoos tattoos the teaser a
source of toxic heavy metal exposure the
ink from a tattoo is basically On A Time
release you know time release right time
release
ink
Is On A Time release inside of us
leaching metal slowly from the Derma
into the bloodstream over a lifetime
from the bloodstream those toxic heavy
metals find their way to the brain
so when we get ink on our body
slowly it's just going to the brain
every day for the rest of her life
from the bloodstream those toxic Metals
find their way to the brain where they
end up residing in brain tissue
as of today there are no sources of
tattooing that are free of toxic heavy
metals I repeat
so every time when somebody like throws
it at me and they have I mean honestly
if we weren't so shadowed
and we were open to like whatever it
just anybody just pop it on whatever
that's browsing through um IG or
whatever we weren't so shadowed
oh my God people would be so peed off
right now with me talking about there's
no heavy metal free ink there are so
many like hipsters going to their like
tattoo people too and they're being told
there's no metal it's cruelty free blah
blah blah and they're just they just
don't know
so as of today there are no sources of
tattooing that are free of toxic heavy
metals not even tattoo inks that are
vegan and cruelty free
in order for tattoo ink to be seen
clearly through the skin they're half
there have to be metals
inside the tattoo ink as light hits your
skin from the Sun or any source of light
it reflects off the metal
inside the tattoo ink under the skin
that reflection allows a tattoo to pop
and be seen clearly
why am I yelling
as the years go by and Tattoos toxic
heavy metals are Time released deeper
into your bloodstream tattoos fade
the light reflecting off your body ink
doesn't have as much to reflect off of
anymore that's why it fades throughout
the years toxic heavy metals within the
ink were what gave the tattoos their
clarity
here's a cool paragraph right here I
hope this makes you feel better
if you already have tattoos
you don't have to remove them
please do not worry and think you have
to get all your ink removed do not do
that in my opinion in my personal
opinion I would recommend against that
unless you have some tattoo that says
something on it that you just don't want
anymore so badly and you already planned
on removing it and that's your life and
that's your body and whatever but I mean
I'm not saying you have to do anything
Rhonda says louder for the people in the
back
that's really funny if you already have
tattoos you don't have to remove them
instead make sure you're following
medical medium protocols to stop up and
expel the metals as their Time released
into your bloodstream so the metals
don't build up in your brain
ask your doctor what's right for you
take the book to hit your doctor him or
her
Julie is the light says why does the Sun
make mine fade
the sun doesn't make a tattoo fade
the Sun
Tans the skin
so
and the tanning of the skin can make it
seem like the Tattoo's fading if you get
no sun whatsoever
at all
the tattoo won't be faded if you had the
tattoo for a very long time it's
naturally fading
because the metals are leaving the ink
if you choose to remove a tattoo because
you don't like your tattoo anymore the
procedure could release more metal into
your bloodstream faster
so following the heavy metal detox guide
guidance from chapter 44 and 45 will be
wise then two after you consult your
doctor on what's right for you
so we we've read some cool metal stuff
you guys there's so much information
about toxic heavy metal exposure in
these brain books it's it's incredible
really how much is in here I'm just
scratching tattoos for God's sake I'm
just scratching tattoos
that's all I'm doing
I'm not even like there's so much
information
I got like information in here about
vaporized heavy metals that's
interesting
I got all kinds of information in here
samples of toxic copper exposure I can
talk about copper exposure a little bit
because I think people have a lot of
toxic exposure but you know what we
might do that on one of our other ones
coming up
okay
so all right so let's head to the heavy
metal detox explosion oh oh half time
half time pull it together
you guys want to get the robot
[Music]
robot
all right
we're moving on let's make the shot
you know what I could talk about toxic
heavy metals
forever talk about them and talk about
them talk about them but I also want to
show you this really quick too
let's show you the shot we're doing are
you guys you got your book this is Page
462 right here
462. right here
toxic heavy metal exposure so let's read
about that a little bit real quick
this exposure shot is especially geared
page 462. this exposure shot is
especially geared for recent exposure
for toxic heavy metals
helping to stop toxic heavy metals from
settling deep in the body
this shot can be used as an additional
therapy to the heavy metal detox
smoothies
thank you
heavy metal detox
additional to that which are geared to
extract toxic heavy metals that have
already settled in the organs while
providing ongoing support for toxic
heavy metal exposure in the bloodstream
lymph or intestinal tract
ideal times to use this toxic heavy
metal exposure shot include
just so you know science of research
only think that you have toxic heavy
metals in the blood if it could be
tested there they don't believe it's in
the organs science and research doesn't
know what's in the organs it's medical
meme information
ideal time to use the toxic Head Metal
exposure shot include when you had
dental work done
I know what some of you guys are
thinking you're thinking I didn't get it
amalgam feeling removed and I didn't get
an amalgam filling installed I had a
ceramic filling installed aw therefore I
don't need to use the exposure shot for
that
having dental work done such as getting
Mercury amalgams fillings removed or
getting new fillings of any kind
including all composites
if you just went to the dentist and you
had Composites put in
you still need to do the exposure shot
because all composite they all have
metal in them all Composites they all
have that in them any dental work
procedures
ideal times to use a toxic heavy metal
exposure shot
when you had fluoride treatments
retainers
or braces
if you had retainers
braces done fluoride treatment so you
might be saying hey W I don't do the
fluoride treatment sorry I know
fluoride's bad for me I I shouldn't do
it but you had fluoride treatments when
you were younger that's when you might
want to think about the heavy metal
detox smoothies and so forth and all
that
Alzheimer's and Dementia being toxic
heavy metals caused this medical medium
information some doctors in science are
taking it but no studies can back it up
and no studies were done to show there
were Metals in somebody's brain they
can't even determine it therefore
they're making it up if they wanted to
claim science is behind it it's not it
comes from medical medium information
any paper they've ever showed or an
article saying that Alzheimer's is
caused by toxic head metals does not
have a study to back it up
there's no way to determine or test for
that it's not even possible you would
have to follow an Alzheimer's case from
the day they were born from when they
were they were in utero from when they
when they were birthed all the way to 80
years until they died with Alzheimer's
and you would have to study their entire
life all the way for 80 years and then
when they died you would have to cut
open their brain and you would have to
actually do an analysis on the metals
and you'd have to biopsy their brain
along the way as they were alive and you
know biopsy in the brain as they were
live for 80 years wouldn't be a good
thing so what I'm saying is there is no
test there is no study there is no
identification or any study test or any
peer review study that shows Metals
cause Alzheimer's dementia it is medical
medium information it came from above
because therefore that's where it came
from because yeah they didn't do a study
and I've been talking about it for 35
years
okay
thank you guys
for hanging in there check it out have
fluoride treatments like I said
retainers or braces
apply this exposure shot if you eat
cooked food on a grill
or from another type of cookout
use the exposure shot if you consume
restaurant food or beverages at coffee
chains ooh coffee chains coffee chains
coffee chains I will have my double
mocha soy latte
double Triple Espresso cold coffee ice
coffee drink please
in your toxic metal contaminated water
that would be fantastic
oh my God thank you
I'm ready for the day
I got an Alzheimer's and Dementia
chapter and brain saver it is packed
with details that will blow your mind
when you read it about Alzheimer's
dementia and the truth about what metals
do in all of it did you guys read it yet
oh my God I read it the other day
because yes I have to read these books
I'm not a genius that can retain all
eight volumes of information from Spirit
compassion above
I'm a regular
person with just an ability to hear the
words and write them down but it's not
like I can remember every single word in
all of these books
I'm not in Einstein
I'm not just saying this I'm not just
saying it's the cause
but I'm saying I'm not just saying that
Metals cause Alzheimer's and Dementia
that's one aspect that I'm saying how
how it causes it it's mind-blowing
it's the how and why okay
metal Expo heavy metal detox exposure
heavy metal exposure shot
if you consume restaurant food or
Beverages and coffee chains
where town or city tap water is used in
food and drink preparation
hence every single coffee chain
use this exposure shot if you breathe in
air fresheners fragrances perfumes
colognes scented candles detergents or
fabric softeners
we're going to create a fabric softener
that has a smell that only grows for the
next hundred years
put one sheet of this fabric softener in
your machine
and it'll smell like this terrifying
dangerous deadly chemical that's
produced in a chemical plant somewhere
it's gonna smell like potpourri
Burma Polo says hi Anthony my
one-year-old boy loves celery juice
heavy metal detox movie and your shots
love from Germany thank you and thank
you for support in Germany thank you and
bless your heart seriously
Michelle
braces and then retainers for 30 years
duly noted understood
it's not easy it's just not easy
use this shot
If You Smell Smoke from something
burning
and you do not know the Smoke's Origins
or the purity of whatever is burning so
here's how it works
on planet Earth there's always something
burning
and it's not always just plain old wood
for instance when they try to die out
fires forest fires
which they need to do they dump a powder
on the forest fires that powders got
metal in it and then it smolders up and
burns right and then it goes in the
atmosphere
it's the point I'm trying to say is
when people are burning fire pits
they're burning plastic and garbage
people just burn a lot of stuff
the
um
the food industry
Burns row covers that are plastic
from you know for after they produce
food each year
say the Divine says what about metal
plates from surgery we need to remove
them yes
I recommend not removing your metal
plates from surgery unless your doctor
wants to remove your metal plates for
some reason for surge for after surgery
or from surgery
what I recommend and I've said this
before if someone has nuts and bolts in
them if they got titanium nuts and bolts
holding their ankles together and
they're and they're they're spying
together and they got rods in their back
keeping their back straight or they got
a cage around their metal cage around
their their disc their broken disc and
whatever it is that they have metal or
they got a plate in their head I only
recommend
right I only recommend
exactly like the heavy metal detox
smoothie and for family and friends or
anybody that knows anybody that has any
kind of metal in them from surgeries or
procedures
from car accidents to all kinds of
injuries and they got metal inside of
them like screws and nuts and bolts all
of that I've always said that's fine
it's it's just that's when the heavy
metal detox movie is so great it's
Gathering any metal that could be
leaching that's the whole point
but ask your doctor what's right for you
you know
take the book to your doctor but no I
don't recommend like ever telling
anybody hey you go take all your nuts
and bolts out then why no you ask your
doctor unless your doctor is doing that
anyway that's another story that's
whatever you and your doctor decide but
I've always told doctors that I know
that have asked this question
and friends and stuff that have like a
rod in their back or something from a
bad injury
or collapsed you know vertebrae or for
some reason that that yeah heavy metal
detox smoothie is great
foreign
we got some more stuff to read Nicholas
Russell where else can you get this kind
of info nowhere
that's so true you can't get it anywhere
and I'm not trying to boast I'm like you
guys
I have to learn it too
I just have to try to message it to you
guys but I have to learn the information
when SOC gives me the info I have to
learn it all
yeah
and what if I wasn't even interested in
anything in health
I heard the voice growing up
right as a child Spirit of compassion
giving me the info but what if I wasn't
interested in any of this
it's not even interesting to me like any
of it like metals and
neurons and heavy metal detects what if
I just want to paint
what do I just want to like paint and do
art and paint Landscapes and this is not
what I even want to do it doesn't matter
I'm still forced to do it thanks to
Spirit of compassion
but I do it with a smile and I'm at your
service
okay ready
toxic heavy metals exposure
like I said if you smell something
burning okay if you get your hair done
in a salon that's a great time to do
this exposure shot if you get your hair
done in a salon
if you are exposed to synthetic
fragrances you know those walk into a
store or something like that and you
smell you walk down the aisle at the
grocery store Whoa man the aisle with
the toiletries holy crap you walk down
that aisle with the toiletries and
you're just like hammered by that stuff
it's like huh eyes burn you feel like
your face Burns off when you walk down
down that aisle now do you ever do that
you're walking down that Island you're
just like oh my God dear Lord what is
this
here's one toxic heavy metal exposures
with you spend time in or near an area
recently treated with pesticide
herbicide or insecticide spray and
fortunately
they keep on releasing genetically
engineered mosquitoes
we wouldn't have a mosquito on this
planet they're putting them here now
they raise the mosquitoes
trillions and trillions and trillions of
mosquitoes and they release them into
all environments on the planet that
could house and harbor a mosquito
and then they sell mosquito spray to the
governments to spray on all the villages
and towns and cities on this planet
they create the problem by raising
genetically engineered grown modified
mosquitoes and then they spray
to try to keep them down
where are we going today here's one
right here if you spend time Outdoors or
after firework displays if oh I love the
fireworks
fireworks little dogs cringing and
shaking everywhere it's like the
fireworks the fireworks
I'm gonna go and blow off a crap ton of
fireworks it doesn't matter if the
neighbor's dog is scared to death it
doesn't matter don't worry
just the Neighbors being
morons don't worry doesn't matter if
every single cat and dog in every house
is shaking to death we're gonna blow up
more fireworks
if you're exposed by fireworks
um yeah there's there's definitely going
to be a lot of metal exposure because
fireworks are loaded with metal it's in
the air when you breathe in oh honey
look at the fireworks that's such a
pretty one up there I love the smell of
all that gunpowder oh the gunpowder's
developed and made where on the other
side of the planet where they just fill
it up with all these Metals in the East
oh incredible all these fireworks are
from an area where they just put Metals
in it honey it smells so good let me get
all those Metals in my brain oh don't
worry about it if the dog dies of a
heart attack next door who cares
foreign
by the way I wanted to tell you guys Dr
nesbitt's not showing up today
um Dr nesbitt's best friend is showing
up today so I just wanted to let you
know that
after we make the exposure shot which
we're going to make in a minute
which we're going to start making now
why do the dogs shake oh my God they're
traumatized
he's killing their nervous systems
okay okay okay let's make the shot
uh like I said Dr husband's not showing
up today but uh Dr nesbitt's best friend
is showing up today
um you might know Dr nesbitt's best
friend from Dr nesbitt's Channel where
Dr Nesbitt was with Dr nesbitt's best
friend
all right
let's get going on this
okay you guys I got I'm getting I'm
getting distracted it's not a good thing
right now for this okay
all right half cup tightly packed fresh
cilantro my favorite
my favorite
love cilantro but I love answering your
questions though that's the whole point
gonna have some cilantro go in here
half cup tightly packed cilantro I've
already measured this to some degree I
have a great eye on this don't worry
incredible
a little bit more because if you tightly
pack that that wouldn't have been much
yeah
let's put the cilantro in here
big stem
so what we're doing here is we are
making the heavy metal exposure shop
okay
what's next
third cup
tightly packed arugula
I just wanted to say these are sentences
synergistically combined specifically
the phytochemical compounds in this very
blend of ingredients
is what counts from Spirit of compassion
that's why the brain shot therapies are
mind-blowing and that's why people get
results they're instant relief for so
many people
because it's how they're designed you no
one would know to put any of this
together to make these results happen
for people you guys like
people are having miraculous results you
guys know and so it comes from above
here we go
if that was tightly packed really
tightly packed that'd be like roughly
around there those are small arugulas
half cup wait a third cup
finely chopped
cabbage
using a red cabbage
and I'm looking for my knife and I'm
going to find one real fast
bear with me here
gonna shred up a little bit of cabbage
now I'm going to use two tablespoons of
wild blueberry juice that you can use
the wild blueberries if that's what
you're doing there we go boom
really excited about this one
amazing all right so I'm gonna do two
tablespoons of oil blueberry juice I'm
Gonna Knock in here
you can use blueberries two tablespoons
of wild blueberry juice or you can use
wild blueberries but not regular
blueberries
they don't get the metals out
they don't
okay one of two stalks of celery I'm
gonna use one stock
half to one complete peeled Orange
or tangerine
if you like you can do a tangerine that
is a very large orange right there very
large orange I'm gonna peel it real
quick if you guys don't mind I actually
forgot to peel
free
this episode by the way we're live this
isn't pre-recorded
giving everybody that 4-1-1 about that
okay I'm gonna peel a little bit more
because we're only going to use half of
this because whoa this is a really nice
sized orange we don't need
yeah nice
boom
get that down in here
went down nice
all right Manny asked can you use wild
blueberry powder yes you can
this is the toxic heavy metal exposure
shot one of the brain shot Therapies
I want to make sure I got everything in
it I didn't forget anything
all right
and then
a half teaspoon of spirulina
and that goes in after
nice boom
is this insane
is that insane by the way is that crazy
is that crazy
it's dry nice and dry that's how you
save money the juicer's on sale by the
way mm 1500 mm 900 incredible juicers
just incredible all right
it's over
oh
okay guys now I'm going to put a half
a teaspoon
a spirulina and you guys know I work
with uh Omega on that but here this is
the spirulina I'm using right the best
one there is no question in my opinion
by far I've talked about this so so many
times over the years like the best
spirulina there is is the Bemidji just
so you know
and I'm going to show you the powder
right there
by far the most incredible
I have ever seen on the market
for so many reasons
okay I just don't want to go into it
because there's so much to talk about
with this spirulina
I mean I can go like crazy with it
it's that incredible so I'm going to put
a half a teaspoon in here that's what
I'm doing dropping it in here I'm gonna
mix it up
so that's the vimergy one right there
and it's V as in Victor i m is America
ergy I work with these guys right fully
endorse these guys for the four reasons
that I always mention which are
unbelievable
all right
so I'm gonna move the juicer out of the
way
mixing up the spirulina into this shot
there we go
foreign
[Music]
I gotta say something
when you know you can do something about
the exposure that we run into when you
know you can do something about it when
you actually can use your free will and
actually do something about it
it's a big deal
[Music]
where you actually have the ability to
empower yourself and actually do
something to help yourself
move forward
there's nothing better
um
I really love this one
because I know that any exposures I've
had recently
I just feel really good about getting
this down
I'm gonna send it down
[Music]
all those tattoos I got
all the sleeves I have
I'm Inked Up from here to here
my legs for my feet
to my hips
[Music]
and now
I'm not Inked Up like I'm not Inked Up I
don't want people think I'm in depth
from my head down to my toes I'm not
Inked Up
I'm gonna pour one more shot because Dr
nesby's best friend is going to be
coming soon
it tastes so good doesn't it Kelly Burke
says it tastes so good it tastes so good
it's crazy
cold like spring how many shots is that
it's incredible
I mean that's that's a decent amount of
shots I got from that batch
I love that I love when
certain items have more juice in them
and I said to spiritual fashion when
I was writing down all the information
that that's just gonna actually happen
you're going to have like this cabbage
is really juicy
bartender give me another
[Music]
bartender
give me another
bartender make sure
this kind of Spirulina is in there
please what bartender you used another
spirulina I can't trust that it could
have hidden ingredients it could have
natural flavors it could have hidden
things in it they're not disclosing
bartender it has to be this one right
here is the only one I trust
the Bemidji one by far hands down
incredible you guys this has been
amazing I think what I'm gonna do is I'm
going to move this juicer over for a
second here too
and
I'm not gonna juice again but Dr Nesbitt
has a friend
a friend that's arriving
uh Donnie Donnie come on out
Donnie
it's okay it's okay it's your first time
I know it's your first time
I know it's okay don't worry about it
it's okay Dr Nesbitt you you've already
been in one of his videos come on Donnie
come on out
you guys
um Donnie the donkey I just hope you
give him a warm welcome because honestly
Donnie is actually really nervous Donnie
was videoed
right with Dr Nesbitt remember
you know with the song
you know that whole thing well Donnie
Donny
Donnie says he doesn't drink any of
these shots Dr Nesbit does once in a
while but Donnie says he doesn't drink
any of these shots
you guys
um Donnie's worried because you've been
seeing Dr Nesbitt for so many years now
that you're not gonna like Donnie and he
was scared Dr Nesbitt is indisposed
right now he couldn't come
Dr Nesbitt got plastered last night he
drank a bottle of Jack Daniels which I
do not recommend anybody to drink a
bottle of duck Dr Jack Daniels
anyway Dr Nesbit
um
he drank too much last night is what I'm
trying to say so he's not here today uh
anyway
Donnie Donny calm down Donnie Donnie
what's wrong are you okay Donnie
you're excited the thing is that Donnie
Donnie likes to eat he likes to eat
things out of hand like he he likes to
have Donnie likes to have like carrots
and stuff like that he likes to have
like things and you just gotta open when
you feed Donnie anything you got to make
sure you have your hands open where your
palms are open because if you don't you
know what can happen if Donnie Donnie ow
Donny bit my finger Donnie
okay what happens if you don't have your
palm open you know you ever been to a
zoo done a good job
Donnie
Donnie amazing Donnie the thing is with
Donnie is that Donnie did I just take
one of those away from you okay
Donnie says that Dr Nesbitt is the star
and Donnie likes just being like in the
back seat as his best friend
all right I think we gotta go
uh memmy Stubbs says please give a pep
talk to people who fell off the medical
mean wagon but still believe in you and
all this I will Donnie
I'm gonna I'm gonna give everybody a pep
talk now you can go Donnie's going okay
I'm just telling you guys right all
right
um
I do want to give a pep talk
I do want to give a pep talk about that
I want to I want to talk about that
okay
no one knows what it's like to be in
your shoes
if you fall off the wagon whatever that
is so say you're doing celery juice and
you fall off the wagon and you stop
drinking celery juice but you believe in
medical medium information and believe
in celery juice
it's okay
I understand believe me I understand
no one knows what it's like to be in
your shoes
your hardships what you've been through
your stresses your struggles the people
you may live with the people you may
know whoever your friends are the
challenges you've had in your life
and resources and everything else
no one should be shamed no one should be
blamed no one should be judged
if you're doing the medical mean 369 or
28 day cleanse or monocleansing you fall
off the wagon but you believe in it
the pressure people get from their
friends and family the pressure people
get from
just social media the pressure people
get alone is so hard and then
the emotional comfort of food the
emotional comfort of what you went
through in your life someone could go
through so much emotional abuse in their
lifetime when they were younger and they
run to comfort Foods someone else
could be living with someone who's had a
lot happen in their life it's someone
could be around food that they used to
lean on as a comfort food and it's hard
to stay on the wagon the point I'm
trying to say is it's okay
if you fall off the wagon and you can't
get back on for now the addictions are
strong out there I completely the
chemicals and the MSG and the natural
flavors and the addictions in the food
that people didn't even know was there
check out the medical meme podcast the
natural flavors podcast please check
that out if you get a chance the point
I'm trying to say
like Nicholas Russell said we've all
been there
absolutely
and it's normal it's it's okay if we
fall off the wagon it's okay it's okay
you know because
I don't know what it's like to be in
your shoes you're falling off the wagon
there's reasons there are reasons why
that you might not even be able to
identify there's reasons why
I'm not in your shoes
I try my best to feel what it's like to
be in somebody's shoes but I do not
blame you one bit if you fall off the
wagon no one I blame no one if you fall
off the wagon just get back on if you
can when you can no shame no judgment
get back on the wagon when you can when
when you feel like you can when you feel
like you know what I can do it now I can
do it I can try it
when the time comes and you can
educating myself said I burnt the wagon
many times and educate educating myself
and that's serious that it's coming from
educating myself because I've seen your
comments I've seen you out there you
know the mm info and if you burnt the
wagon many times I totally get it
wave world
one go says but we stand up again that's
right we do
it's not easy
to live on planet Earth
for what we're always up against
and
how we were raised or
kind of experiences we had along the way
everything plays a role
it doesn't have to be all or nothing
either you know the All or Nothing thing
on the exercise and I'm gonna do
everything perfect don't do everything
and it's I throw it all away I'm just
gonna do whatever I need beats in pizza
and stuff extra so it doesn't have to be
all or nothing it could be
I'll still do a little bit of medical
medium until I can do more I'll still do
a little bit more until I can do more
it's okay it's okay
I want people to know that
truly
remember that
Scott Becker my brother turned me on to
aw
he felt that protein is needed in the
diet of an athlete
can you please address this
well it's the thing is okay definitely
gotta listen to the medical meme podcast
said Apple podcast for sure like I talk
about that so many ways in so many
different directions and on Rumble I
have a protein law episode on Rumble so
it's a protein law episode it explains
it really good and Liver Rescue Liver
Rescue OMG I talk about
protein in here oh my God
cleanse the heel I think I talk about it
in there too for sure
the information is that's crazy about
that I'm going to Clemson heel for a
second I'm looking I'm looking
these are just huge Bibles and forgive
me
um to look for a second I'm really sorry
about this blah blah blah critical
cleanses and don'ts the body's healing
power living words underdogs right
intermittent fasting the juicing versus
fiber debate God this book is so
incredible
cleanser heal is such an insanely
Incredible Book
it is really amazing what about the
microbiome whoa
so make Troublemaker Foods your guide to
choosing a cleanse oh my God all the
different cleanses powerful cleanses
this is incredible information in here
whoa
I just honestly
I just love these books there's protein
information in here in various in
various chapters actually too I'm
popping through Liver Rescue really
quick as well
just I just love looking at these table
contents it's just so insane
liver enzyme guest tests dirty blood
syndrome weight gain mystery hunger this
is so packed with information
it's really incredible how much is going
on here so many amazing plants
um out there in the community by the way
you guys incredible comments in the
community
um about trying the brain shot therapies
and experiencing the power of the brain
shot Therapies
all of that and I'm honored all that
you're doing the work you're putting
into have you guys tried the brain shot
have you tried the heavy metal detox the
heavy metal exposure brain shot have you
tried the truth one have you tried these
how do they make you feel
what was your results what experience
did you have please at Medical medium
and hashtag at Medical medium tag at
Medical medium and hashtag medical
medium so I can see it so I can repost
reels and stories and posts if you get a
chance and you guys if you love the
books leave a review too if you love the
books amazon.com leave a review if you
want if you love the books right that
would be incredible too brain saver if
you read that one
Jerry Jerry's girl said I've been
brokenhearted for weeks started
following you and it helps the heart oh
my God
hey guys
incredible information
um see
we are fighting for our lives every day
what Pie Pie eats
that got me emotional when I hear you
guys are fighting
because I know so many of you have gone
through
just some
just some just some intense stuff
throughout the years
books are packed with protein law
information
right the protein cold wide spring the
protein craze is insane it is
it is
it's the most protein rich
diets in the world meaning the diets out
there are the most protein so-called
Rich diets in the world why is everybody
sick
people are eating tons of protein but
why do they end up at the neurologist
why didn't the protein cure them
if protein is the answer to everything
why is everybody sick
everybody's getting protein
I just saw recently a guy that ate like
the best protein shakes on the market
just died of a heart attack
did the protein kill them
why didn't the protein stop them from
dying of a heart attack
if protein is the answer why is to why
are there 300 million Americans with
symptoms right now like sick
follow medical media on telegram for
exclusive telegram audio messages
check out medicalme.com
and check out medical medium podcast at
Apple podcast and look out for imposters
I'm an imposter my name is medical
medium I'm an imposter
yes I can do a consultation for you just
just here send me back this email
there's imposters saying that all the
time it's insane
be careful for the imposters look out
for the imposters they DM people and
they ask them for money
yep
I love you guys
a heart my brain my soul
my heart a body my spirit I love you
guys
foreign
see you guys tomorrow day eight we're
doing the relationships breakup
stabilizer
that's going to be an incredible one
relationship breakups stabilizer
did you ever have a breakup yes we need
the stabilizer we need it love you guys