people want to have intuition let's make
the intuition more potent more powerful
people say they're psychic
then let's make that psychic power more
powerful
so many people
they'll say out there
that
they thought about their friend and then
their friend called
right in that moment
it's like what was it
was it the friend that knew that or was
it you that knew that but something
happened right
something happened or when someone says
I know that was just gonna happen I was
just thinking that I just saw it in my
mind
I must be psychic I must have some kind
of spiritual power I must be really
connected I might be telepathic then
let's make it stronger
let's make it more powerful
everybody has
psychic abilities everybody has
intuition everybody has telepathic
Clairvoyant skills everybody has
something deep down inside
something inside of them
it's there
so let's make it more
powerful
let's make it stronger
let's make it more effective
I just want to say
and we're talking about the wisdom and
intuition stabilizer medical meeting
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge we
are day 13
OMG 13 days we have made it through this
free
cleanse challenge
we have seven more days to go
just so you know I'm excited so let's do
a little bit let's do a little reading
let's talk about some powerful things
what I love about this shot is if you
even think you have a speck
spec
of Supernatural ability
even a speck like you think
that you heard a voice in your ear for a
second or you think you called a shot
before that shot happened or you think
something
you think your dreams
have answers in them if you think you
have a fiber
a
microfiber a speckle a speck
a power intuition telepathic Clairvoyant
anything psychic
then you should be doing the wisdom and
intuition stabilizer
enhance it and enhance it grow it and
grow it make it stronger and make it
stronger is what you should be doing
all right let's find out
let's first of all the recipe let's take
a look at that really quick I'm a brain
saver I want to take a look at this
wisdom and intuition stabilizer right
there
we're day 13.
that's what we're making what do you see
before me you see some wheatgrass juice
right here hopefully you can see that on
the camera you see some spirulina the
vemergy spirulina you see
some yellow squash you see some Sage you
see some blackberries
that look like raspberries but they're
blackberries
and you see some oregano
and you see some wild blueberry juice
too
so we're making this all right let's
let's do a little bit of reading let's
take a look see what we have
in store today in front of us
foreign
so I'm in a section
called your Soul's voice I would love to
read this to you you can still join the
challenge by the way we're only day 13
of a 20-day medical meeting brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge you can join
now for free go to medicalmedium.com see
the link in the description you can
download the free grocery shopping list
how incredible is that how amazing is
that all right
and you can join and it's free once you
sign up you get the emails providing
information all of it getting you ready
for this or day 13.
you get daily recipes in the emails too
chapter 14 brain saver protocols
page 552.
what is a soul
do you know
does our soul even exist
does it
is their soul just air
that floats away
and that's just our soul
was having a soul all along created by
our imagination
is it your imagination that created a
soul all long
it never existed
it's just air
it's thin air
let me just say this
let me make this clear your soul does
exist
everyone has a soul
it is the voice of your entire existence
this isn't just our existence here
physically here now
our existence just isn't what's on
social
it isn't you just
hopping in your car and driving
it isn't just us communicating now
that's not just our existence
your soul is the voice of your entire
existence think about that for a moment
entire existence means
way before now and way in the future
your soul retains knowledge of all the
events that have occurred in your life
your soul holds a record retains
knowledge of everything that's ever
happened in your life here
foreign
that contains the meaning of your
physical existence if your physical
existence has any meaning at all your
soul contains that record of it
if being here physically right now has
any meaning me standing here in the
moment talking to you you being right
there commenting
and watching this
if there's any physical existence right
there your soul contains the meaning of
it
your soul harnesses every Journey you
have chosen or experienced and not
chosen
in a physical living form every single
experience you have chosen in this
lifetime
your soul harnesses every Journey that
you have had and if it's an experience
that you did not want to partake in if
it's an experience that somehow you were
in your soul still harnesses that
Journey
your soul sustains itself and lives
forever
that means that when we leave here
you're not
gone
your soul sustains itself and lives
forever long past being here
long after the physical part of us has
perished so if we perish
your soul lives on
it never dies
it doesn't matter if you like your soul
you don't have to like your soul
you can hate your soul
it doesn't matter if you love your soul
doesn't matter if you hate your soul it
doesn't matter if you don't believe in
the Soul's existence
or believe you have a soul you don't
have to believe you have a soul you do
not have to believe in your Soul's
existence
you can be somebody that doesn't believe
you have a soul and there is a soul or
Souls don't exist they do exist or not
you don't believe it on any level
it doesn't matter because your soul is
more powerful than what you believe your
soul is more powerful than you
your soul
is more powerful than you
you can hate your soul and that doesn't
matter your soul is more powerful than
that you can love your soul sure your
Soul's more powerful than that believe
it or not you cannot even believe your
soul exists and your soul is more
powerful than that I'm on page 552.
of this incredible Bible right here
guys just got on here we're talking
about the soul
your soul is more powerful than you
your soul is more powerful than your
Consciousness in your present state of
being
you wake up in the morning and you're
conscious
consciousness
is in gear
you're thinking
you're living your life
but your soul is more powerful than your
Consciousness in the present state of
being right now your soul is more
powerful than the brainwashing you have
been conditioned with here on Earth did
you know that that your soul is more
powerful than the brainwashing that
happens here on Earth
there is a tremendous amount of
conditioning in brainwashing here on
Earth right now happening to everybody
and guess what no matter how brainwashed
you get down here no matter how
conditioned you get down here your soul
overrides that it's way more more
powerful than all of that
Amanda Parr says can I start any time
once I sign up indeed you can Amanda and
I'm happy to have you aboard on this
free
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
your soul is more powerful than the
brainwashing and the conditioned
that we go through here on Earth because
your soul has been far away from Earth
at one point
conditioning and brainwashing cannot
hold your soul down because your soul
hasn't just been here on Earth
your Soul's not governed
in this earth-bound bubble
of our human created environment
so whatever happens
in this environment
this human conditioned brainwashed
creative created environment whatever
happens does not govern your soul
because your soul has been somewhere
else before it's not EarthBound
it's not governed by this Earthbound
bubble we live in this bubble so many
people are in of our human created
environment
your soul is more than you
it is your light
your soul
is a light
shines bright
your soul is a light that did not start
here on Earth but started above and you
have to remember that our soul did not
start here
our soul started above
your soul is much older than your
physical body how old are you
20 years old
30 years old 40.
are you 50
60 70 80 90.
how old are you your soul is much older
than your physical body
and get ready for this
fasten your seatbelts
your soul is much older than your
physical body and has memories and
information from the past to which you
don't have conscious access to
your soul has the power to lead you on
your way even when it's under fed and
broken by the people around you or the
world we live in
your soul is a light that can help you
lead the way even with all of the crap
we are faced with down here on Earth
your Soul's leftover fragments still
hold the power and the glory that
brighten the way on the darkest path it
can't be stomped out
your soul cannot be stomped out
when we voice ourselves here on Earth
sometimes we find moments when we
transcend the confusion here
and what we're speaking is more than
just our own truth
it is a common truth that unites us with
others one that may even go beyond words
this can be our true powerful voice it's
a soul voice that's different
your Soul's voice
is much more powerful
than any other voice
reading out of protocols by the way
someone asked
many times the truth spoken on planet
Earth could be flawed
is that true
can I ask you guys is that true at all
many times the truth spoken on planet
Earth could be flawed
because human nature tends to bend the
truth to provide a game and a ledge to
hold on to
so truth is manipulated and spoiled with
deception
is that true
many times the truth spoken on this
planet Earth could be flawed because of
human nature tends to bend the truth to
provide a game
do people play games
I want to know
are there people out there that love to
play games with people's lives or
they're they're people out there that
love to play games in general
do people manipulate the truth use it as
alleged to hold on to
and use truth as deception sure
evil
takes the term truth
shapeshifts it
and uses it as a weapon
because that truth is spoiled and filled
with deception
this is a survival mechanism used by all
walks of life
from the bottom tier to the top of the
hierarchy
your soul holds authentic truth
untainted
pure regardless of whatever survival
mechanisms we tend to adapt here on
Earth your soul holds the truth
and carries it on
your soul holds authentic truth that's
the difference all of your souls hold
authentic truth that's the difference
right there there's no games
your soul doesn't play games
and your soul doesn't play Truth games
your soul
has authentic truth
pure regardless of whatever survival
mechanism she knows survival we tend to
adapt to here on Earth your soul
knows better
your true Soul always knows better and
is wiser than the truth games played
here on Earth your soul is wiser
than the truth games played here on
Earth
how many times have you heard well no
it's truth but it's really just a game
and it's not totally true how many times
have you heard that out there
but your soul
supersedes the games in your soul
is a light that's more powerful
than the games and the deception played
here on Earth
your true Soul always knows better and
is wiser than the truth games played on
Earth
inside each of us is this even truer
more potent voice than our Earthly voice
so inside of us our soul is a more truer
and potent voice than her own voice
inside of our soul it's much more
profound
the true truer voice is elevated above
the voice we know to come from a deep
place within
because as strong
and is important as our true deep
Earthly voices because it is important
our Earthly voice is important
it can also be mixed with hurt and
sorrow
and distrust and confusion and
misinformation
we could have a strong voice down here
on planet Earth I see it out there but
it could be a strong voice projecting
misinformation we can have a strong
voice here on planet Earth and we can
actually project a strong voice that's
of hurt and that's of sorrow and
distrust and confusion and
misinformation
together
the truest voice we possess can never be
swayed by trickery and you know what I'm
talking about our soul that's different
that's an entirely different voice
our Soul's voice it can't be persuaded
persuaded by misinformation it can't be
tricked by misinformation are true true
Soul's voice can't be
tricked by deceit it resides in all of
us it is your soul
and it can't be tampered with by
conditioning brainwashing and it can't
be tricked by the sea in misinformation
that's your true soul
you can hear somebody's true voice
spoken but that doesn't mean it's their
true soul but their true voices is
spoken
and they could be saying something
but it could have misinformation in it
of course
the games that we're up against and the
brainwashing is insane down here in
planet Earth but our soul is immune from
that completely it's immune from the BS
that we have down here
our soul has a sound
nobody knew that
Spirit of compassion
gave me those words when I was in my
office
I think it was like three o'clock in the
morning
and Spirit of compassion said write this
down
I said I'm getting kind of tired
I haven't slept
I've been writing for hours
I said the spirit of compassion it
better be good
because I need to go to sleep soon and
spirit of compassion said write this
down
our soul has a sound I wrote that our
soul has a sound and then I woke up
from a tiredness and I sparked up and I
was like what do you mean our soul has a
sound what are you talking about
his spirit said our soul has a sound a
sound we can't hear
with our physical ears
I was hooked when I heard that
an IG
sgm [ __ ] says wow I am feeling what you
are saying thank you
I sparked up
when I heard that
my mind was blown
that three o'clock early morning
when spirit said our soul has a sound a
sound we can't hear with their physical
ears I was just completely intrigued
Beyond and then spirit said a sound that
Rings true through time and space and
then I realized are you kidding me a
sound or Soul has a sound that Rings
through time and space does that have
something to do with the traveling does
that have something to do when we die
our soul travels through time and space
when we die our soul Rises up out of us
and travels through time and space
when our soul leaves our physical
body and transcends upward
a noise is made
when we die
we no longer talk
but as our soul leaves our physical body
and transcends upward a noise is made
a sound
the sound is energy
and the energy of the soul is powerful
a fireball of light
as the soul travels the noise is the
sound of the Soul
piercing time itself
time changes
when we pass and our soul leaves us
our soul is no longer in the normal
time that we know exists
and our soul makes noise as its piercing
time itself
for time no longer exists for the soul
once a soul has left the body
somebody on IG
cat attack says this is so beautiful I'm
getting so emotional
thank you for being here
celery Cindy says incredible information
Alexandra says love this thanks for all
this powerful information
where our soul goes there is no clock
when I heard that from Spirit of
compassion
I just couldn't believe it
it was so incredible
I was ready to write down every word
where our soul goes there is no clock
the home our soul goes back to can't be
governed by time because time is
different for every planet
time is different for every solar system
time is different for every Galaxy
and if one planet or solar system ceases
to exist then time stops for that planet
or solar system yet our soul cannot
cease to exist is that insane
I just want to read that again I when I
I have read this not only written the
words down but I have read this
not only through the editing process
of putting the book together
I have read that so many times and I
still I'm still Blown Away
where our soul goes there is no clock
the home our soul goes back to can't be
governed by time because time is
different for every planet every solar
system and every Galaxy and if one
planet or solar system ceases to exist
Does that mean their soul ceases to
exist no of course not then time stops
for that planet or solar system yet our
soul cannot cease to exist this Earth
can blow up this solar system can get
trashed
by a massive meteorite or asteroid
heading our way it could annihilate the
entire solar system there are asteroids
out there that are bigger than the Sun
that could actually drive through a
solar system and destroy it and break it
apart and crush it and the solar system
won't exist anymore
time stops in that solar system the
minute the sun explodes or dies out and
all the planets break apart you have to
know that there is no planets going
around the Sun anymore
that is what time is
the planet circling around the Sun
if an asteroid came through the solar
system and destroyed every planet there
is no time anymore in that solar system
but yet if you are on the planet Earth
when that solar when that asteroid came
through and destroyed the planet your
soul your physical body would die but
your soul would not die that means your
soul isn't governed by time do you know
what I mean like when when I heard that
information from Spirit of compassion it
was mind-blowing your Soul's got
governed by time
that means if the solar system is
crushed
by anything
our soul is in governed by time in that
solar system because it never was
governed by time anyway that means we're
governed by the clock every day I had to
come on here at certain time of day to
talk to you guys we're governed by time
but our soul isn't completely off the
time scale
our soul needs to live on and it does
without the constraints of time
time
has no bearing upon our souls
our souls are that powerful
I don't think anybody realizes how
powerful their soul really is if time
itself has no constraints against our
soul
so then Spirit of compassion went on and
said our soul is an energy force that
isn't conquered by what's here on Earth
it's all about conquering on planet
Earth
it's like that on social media one one
influencer wants to conquer the other
one one uh one Health Guru wants to
conquer the other
one company wants to conquer the other
right
everybody wants to conquer something
here on Earth
one evil government wants to conquer
another evil government what every
single thing is about conquering on
planet Earth that's all it is conquer
conquer
our soul is an energy force that isn't
conquered by what happens here on Earth
how do you like that our soul
can't get conquered
by all of the competition and games
played here on planet Earth your soul is
free from that it can't be conquered on
any level
it is a universal
oh this is incredible right here the
spirit Spirit of compassion just
foreign
compassion always
says God
and mentions God
it is a universal
god-conceived law
that her soul has it right and safely
right even if our Consciousness
connected to our brain has it wrong
when Spirit of compassion told me that
line itself
I mean how
our soul is an energy force that isn't
conquered by what happens here on Earth
it is a universal God conceived the law
that our soul has
it right and safely right even if our
Consciousness connected to our brain has
it completely wrong
and here's one of my favorite parts
of this scripture
because Spirit of compassion
doesn't write Health books
Spirit of compassion writes scripture
wrong cannot enter and destroy a soul
that means if a missile blows
people up
it still cannot enter and destroy a soul
that means if you've been hurt or
betrayed it still cannot destroy your
soul
what really matters in the end
is the truth of our soul
because it is our forever existence
forever
ever
amen
forever
because it is our forever existence and
overrides what we are
and we're here in life on Earth so
whatever we were here
in life here on Earth whatever we were
it doesn't matter
the soul overrides that
and continues to exist no matter what
and I got a quote in here our soul has a
sound a sound we can't hear with our
physical ears sound that Rings true
through time and space
we're doing the wisdom and intuition
state stabilizer I know that everybody
feels they have something special
if you don't feel that way you should
that you have something special inside
of you
if you're someone that doesn't feel like
you have
a fiber or spark or Speck of intuition
Clairvoyant Powers telepathic ability
psychic abilities if you're someone that
doesn't even believe you have a speck of
that
it's there
what I love about the wisdom and
intuition stabilizer
is it helps to enhance that I'm going to
go and read that for a minute here a
little bit
foreign
stabilizer because that's what we're
doing right here
I'm excited about this
administer this powerful tool
when you're trying to improve your
intuition
so if you're somebody and you're trying
to improve your intuitive skills you're
trying to improve your intuition
this is the stabilizer for you
administer the wisdom and intuition
stabilizer if you want to get the most
out of your meditations are you somebody
that meditates
Are you a meditator
do you practice meditation
Kim Blair what's in what is the name of
the book Brain saver
and brain saver protocols it's one huge
book it was divided in two
and
can get it for 22.28 at amazon.com us
they're incredible books when you read
them you'll be mind blown if you thought
you were a health expert or you think
you're a health expert I forewarn you
when you read these books your mind is
going to be blown absolutely blown
you'll find out that you really weren't
a health expert and you'll find out how
much there is to learn it's actually
humbling these books are humbling and
I'm not saying that because it because
it's me that's not it it's from above
the information
and it humbles me
administer this powerful tool
if you're trying to build up the
strength of your psychic ability
you might not want to build up the
strength of your psychic ability you
might be somebody that doesn't want to
build that up
Jen just said can't beat the price on
those books oh no you totally can't
I didn't have to put the books out I
could have just done programs and sold
them for five thousand dollars a piece
and just done and just done a program
per every three pages could have been a
program
be a billionaire in a few years
I didn't want to do that I put I put the
books out for free you can get to the
library for free
use the wisdom and into intuition
stabilizer
if you're trying to build up the
strength of your psychic ability if
you're somebody that doesn't believe
you're psychic that's okay it's fine use
it anyway
but if you want to build up your psychic
ability this is a very helpful tool
if you want to make the most out of your
meditations if you're somebody and
you're actually meditating you're
practicing meditation and you want the
most out of that meditation this is the
shot you should make every single day if
you meditate every single day you should
be using the wisdom and intuition
stabilizer every single day to help you
with your meditations
foreign
I don't own all the grocery stores in
this in this country
and around the world so when you go by
stage at the grocery store I don't get a
cut
if you buy yellow squash and some
blackberries at the grocery store I
don't get a cut
it's important to know like this is a
tool that's there for you
Laura says we Are Spiritual Beings
having a physical experience
Lana says would that mean that even
Hitler's Soul has is right
I'll do if you know what I hear so much
stuff about Hitler on and off throughout
the years of course
a lot of people say that Hitler's Hitler
wasn't a bad person
they're wrong
a lot of people say he was just he was
just kind of staring you know you know
he's in the wrong course his journey was
not right things like that you know
people but there's a lot of
misinformation about Hitler out there
people say that he was good he was not
who's evil
but I'm gonna do a podcast eventually
talking about like good and evil and how
that works and how that works with with
souls and everything else
okay and then
use the wisdom and intuition stabilizer
if you're trying to gain sight and
vision through your third eye
to see what others cannot see now you
can call it your third eye you don't
have to call it your third eye
you can call it anything you want
it's just that people recognize it as
the third eye right that's what they
recognize
that they feel their Consciousness is
here right
so you can call it anything you want you
can be like you're trying to gain sight
and vision through your third eye to see
what others cannot see or you're trying
to gain sight and vision through your
subconsciousness
that others cannot see
foreign
use the wisdom and intuition stabilizer
if you want to strengthen your spiritual
connection
with above
what's above to you is above God to you
then use
this tool
if you want to strengthen the spiritual
connection with God is it the Creator
for you then use this tool for that is
it the light for you above then use this
tool for that is it God's
you're somebody that believes it's God's
then use this tool for that if you're
somebody who believes that Jesus Christ
then use this tool for that use if you
want to strengthen your spiritual
connection with above use the wisdom and
intuition stabilizer
use this stabilizer if you feel you're
lacking in intuition
so if you're somebody you feel like
you're lacking the intuition
or you're disconnected from your
intuition use the shot are you somebody
that's feeling that way
use a shot if you want to get the most
out of your yoga session
are you doing yoga a lot of people are
use this
stabilizer
before your yoga session
or spiritual training or gathering are
you doing spiritual Retreats spiritual
Gatherings use this stabilizer then
use this wisdom and intuition stabilizer
if you're seeking wisdom about any topic
such as something occurring in your life
Christina Brad says what can we use
instead of yellow squash please can we
use green zucchini yellow squash in
Europe is not easy to get
you can try a um a green one it's not
perfect but there's hopefully there's
enough there
where you can use um
is there Frozen
yellow squash
and the Frozen vegetable section of the
freezer the freezer of the markets
because you can use that
there's a phytochemical compound
specifically in the yellow squash
that helps
that's why but you can try a green one
if you're seeking wisdom out of any
topic about any topic or something occur
in your life and last but not least if
you're seeking answers that pertain to
you and the ones around you use this
shots if you're somebody that's seeking
answers in general
then use the wisdom and intuition
stabilizer just in case on your journey
as you're seeking answers the wisdom and
intuition stabilizer can help you
decipher and discern it can actually
help you discern so here you are you're
seeking answers for your loved ones but
you know what you're not sure what those
answers are one is should my loved one
get the surgery or not or should my
loved one do this or try this or should
I take this job should my loved one take
this job or not or should I take this
job or not I don't want to make a
mistake in my life I'm having problems
trusting I've been injured before with
trusting so what do I do and then so
that's when the wisdom and intuition
stabilizers agree time to actually send
down and take because it can help give
you some clarity before you're going
into something or before you're doing
something
foreign
says no you can get Frozen yellow squash
in Europe
oh sir you can't get Frozen yellow
squash in Europe you're saying
I would try the green one
I would
and then keep everything up Joe what I
would do though if you do the green
squash
but you can't find blackberries and then
now you're trying to use raspberries
then that that's getting too far off
course
or if you can't find Oregano
um but you're using Rosemary or
something you just you can't really go
off course too much
you have to it just has to be that day
where
you know and the wheatgrass can be
frozen I have a frozen option right here
it's on medicalmedium.com's directory
supplement directory magaloon.com that's
the Frozen one right there that I'm
using because I don't have any of the
fresh grass in the moment
Iona says I buy my yellow squash online
in the UK wow
awesome
all right guys
I think we can start making this shot
that's what I think
I'm gonna move things over a little bit
here
will it still work if you're missing
ingredients
the question is is it s like ingredients
because if you're missing ingredients
then no it won't work
it won't work I just won't so we're
gonna come back says it won't work if
you're missing ingredients maybe if you
switch out like an ingredient to
something that's still in the same
family we might be able to skate by like
a green squash on this one but if you're
missing ingredients in these Branch out
therapies and you're doing plural
ingredients then no it's not going to
work
it might partially work
it might work a little bit but it's not
going to work work like the kind of
effects people are getting like the
miraculous stuff that's happening that
is that is really specific to what's
going on with what you need I mean I
wish it was more versatile but that's
not how this medicine works
foreign
can the wheatgrass be powder and the
Doom says nope it can't has to be frozen
or fresh
and
um but yeah it would have to be frozen
or fresh
April test this great live today aw
thank you for being here
all right
fire up the machine let's see if we can
do this
let's go
Soul talks really deep
God blows my mind I mean I'm still I
don't know about you guys but I'm still
kind of like mind blown from that
information
I mean I was just like you feel it
through your whole body and my mind just
is like what
it's incredible all right
let's start out
um
I'm gonna I'm gonna add the wild
blueberry juice
probably a little later it says start
out with one tablespoon of fresher
thawed frozen wild blueberries you can
do a powder or you can do the juice I
have the juice handy which is which is
really fun
says one teaspoon of wild blueberry
juice okay now I could drop it into the
my juicer here I could drop it in it'll
go right through the screen so that's
fine you might have a juicer it doesn't
work that way so you might want to put
it into your container instead
fairytales.com says is wheatgrass okay
for people
who are many years ago diagnosed with a
wheat allergy before gluten-free
movement yes it's it that's what's right
for your doctor but I've recommend it to
family friends and and other doctor
friends that I know that it's okay
because it is gluten free
so I'm adding a little bit of that
down in there you don't have to put it
in here you can add it to your container
I'm just putting it right through
because this kind of tissue you can do
that
all right next one is quarter cup fresh
or thawed frozen blackberries
these are frozen and they picked them a
little early but they still work
so the company that froze these
blackberries did pick them
what seems to be about a week too early
for my berry picking expertise
so I'm dropping in a quarter of a cup of
these
you guys don't mind
nice
all right so after that quarter cup
tightly packed Sage
Sage is so strong I'll tell you so I'm
making sure I get this in here
it is so strong
so I'm dropping in a quarter cup in
there should be about that
pretty incredible really all of it is
quarter cup tightly packed oregano
here's my oregano
now there's some big stems on here I'm
trying to get the big stems kind of away
a little bit they're really strong these
stems
you can get the leaves off the stems if
you want
um if the stems are too thick
okay
it's really potent stuff
the mm-1500 is incredible it's just
coming out like so it's coming out dry
right that drive hope look at that
other juicers don't do that that's how
you save money with the food costs going
up you guys know you know how the mm
1500 works it's only the 1500 and 900.
okay that's why I've endorsed these guys
because it's saving people money if I
can save people money every day while
they're juicing then I endorse it 100
and you know it's it's incredible
and it's 20 off right now it's insane
just letting you guys know all right so
I got the oregano in there
now I'm gonna go with the wheatgrass
two teaspoons
some wheatgrass juice in there
you can add it at the end
I think I'm supposed to add it in the
end but I threw it in there all right
let's go and then half cup
yellow squash
again my squashes in there
foreign
here we go
amazing
because it is
a quarter teaspoon of Spirulina I'm
gonna put in at the end
that I'm putting in at the end so let me
put that over here
all right
incredible
now I love love love
this incredible brain shot have you guys
been trying this one at all in general
not outside of the of the brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge right
laughs
I have a job
and the job is to make sure I have the
shot glasses out here
and it's the job I fail at
how's that possible
why did not why did my intuition fail me
where I forgot to have my
shot glass ready
that's okay
because now I'm going to fill that shot
glass
with the wisdom and intuition
stabilizer
[Music]
amazing
I noticed when I have this one
I get like funny feelings like right
from the store
[Music]
boom like it's hitting
[Applause]
[Music]
I get a funny feeling in my arms with
this one
it's my arms
and even like in my chest right here
that's strong
[Music]
it's strong
just let it let it take over
let the synergistic combination from
Spirit of compassion the combination of
phytochemical compounds I've known by
research and science how they work
together with these ingredients
and I forgot the spirulina
the spirit just told me
[Music]
gotta put the quarter teaspoon in
foreign
that's why I always say how lucky I am
[Music]
because
I have a voice that tells me
when I mess up
[Music]
[Applause]
bartender give me 10 of these
Maybe 20.
[Music]
I saved it just in time
oh bartender give me another place
[Music]
and I might get ready and just pour
another
incredible
have you guys
have you guys done this one before I
noticed that
foreign
I noticed that
it hits me after the fact the hardest I
feel a little something during it but it
hits me after the fact the hardest
like after taking it after administering
it
so with me every time I do the wisdom
and intuition
brain shot
it hits me like 10 minutes later
5-10 minutes later
and as each minute goes on it starts
coming over me it starts coming over me
like what do you guys feel like let me
know your results to what you feel and
how you feel poster real post it into
story
or a post
tag at Medical medium or hashtag medical
medium I would love to know what your
experiences are so I could take a look
and see I would love to share it if we
can incredible but it comes over me
so if you're gonna do a meditation if
you're gonna do yoga if you're going to
do any kind of spiritual practice or
whatever it is make sure when you take
this
that you wait a few minutes before you
start that yoga before you start that
meditation just wait a few minutes let
it just ride in and just and and take
over like that's what I would do
how much is that juicer Brooklyn asks
what's the name this is the mm-1500 from
Omega so Omega o-m-e-g-a this is the m
right
and it saves it saves people money which
is incredible
um Priya says you're such a good guy
with a heart they don't make M like you
anymore they don't make me like anymore
what you notice about what the juicer
saving money is critical with food right
now so what you're going to notice that
you won't see with the basket juicers
and the centrifuge juicers and all those
those are those you just pour money away
you just throw money away you just burn
you burn your dollars away
this right here you buy less produce
so it's a cold masticating juicer but
that's not the key right that's part of
the key so your nutrients are definitely
preserved which is incredible but the
difference here is the high compression
so what you're noticing right there with
the pull
is you're noticing it's dry you see that
if you've ever Juiced before just before
you'll notice that you you'll never
there's no juicer like those basket
juicers it's just like you got to be
rich to be running those at the rate of
juicing every day that's just for
someone who juices like once every six
months and pulls it out of their
cupboard
but if you're going to juice for like
medically reasons medical reasons you
need something to save money and the
warranty
the warranty is insane this is why I
endorse these guys 15 years on Parts in
powertrain plus okay there's a hotline
an mm hotline 2 at Omega so I'm just
letting you know what's up
I'm gonna send this one down now I'm I'm
feeling all kinds of funny feelings
and and you know what's we know what's
crazy is that in the medical medium
community
people juice like no one has ever Juiced
like no one has ever Juiced in any
communities and these are the juicers I
can endorse because they can take a
beating not cut if you put a spinning
basket juicer or a centrifuge juicer or
those other juicers through the kind of
abuse that the medical medium Community
creates on the juicers they wouldn't
survive and they don't have the
warranties after two years
and um and so it's it's not just juicing
once a day in the medical medium
Community introduces like all day long
many people so it's not just juice right
um it's not just like juicing for a week
and then you put your juicer on the
Shelf somewhere it's not just you juice
for a month the medical meme Community
juices constantly and there's a big
difference huge difference right so
people get sold into juicing for a
minute hey it's January it's like New
Year's resolutions I'm gonna do some
juicing they go and buy something that
looks fun and easy to use that you know
whatever affiliate program crap or
whatever it is and they get those
spinning basket juicers and what happens
is
they just use it for a little while and
put it away and when you're using it for
medical medicinal reasons
and you're dumping in a lot of money
into your produce you want to save money
and what this machine does in the 900s
it pays for itself over and over again I
have to say it because it's still so
cool it's just like a car
you put wear and tear and miles on the
car you're going to break apart once in
a while but the difference is the parts
are warranted for 15 years on the
mm-1500 and mm-900 which is insane and
look at this take a loose that's your
pulp
I saw the spinning basket juicer thing I
saw one online people using it and I've
even used it just to just to test for
fun
and all it does is spit out wet pulp
everywhere you throw away money you got
to be rich to do that every single day
you're gonna need like
I don't know 200 in produce a day or
something sick or something you want to
juice that much you'll be just putting
everything in like blah blah blah it's
like a monster just feeding a money
Monster look at this
that's insane
Huntress Divine says aw I went through a
rough time in the last five weeks and
all of the brain shots helped me through
yeah but this shot is my favorite of
them all this shot
is one of my favorites too
this shot is definitely one of my
favorites by far incredible and by the
way
that's the vermergy spirulina you guys
know I endorse these guys because this
stuff is incredible I'm just letting you
know nothing surpasses this supplement
line that these guys have nothing
surpasses it out there
um it's why I finally just said you know
what you get my complete endorsement
because you guys have never broke or
wavered in any of those those cheating
things they do with all the other
companies they do all kinds of great
stuff they put ingredients in that
nobody knows like all this stuff these
guys are incredible man and the
spirulina is the best that's the Bemidji
amazing Lorraine Hendricks says do we
peel the squash no you don't have to
peel the squash keep the skin on that's
fine
you know so I use these you know these
have been in the fridge for a little
while so they're just a little bruised
up and a little beat up
but they're amazing crispy perspective
says I'm fighting my basket juicer right
now with a sad face now you're breaking
my heart can't wait for the mm-1500 to
arrive the basket juicers are such a
scam in the in in on the scene right now
all the sharks try to invade the medical
medium Community with the basket juicer
and now it's like it's so sad like
people are posting and they're posting
using the basket juicers you know like
oh my God how did they get how did that
happen how did that happen because
they're gonna need to spend more money
on produce like who like what happened
you know and that's what they do the the
industries the Sharks come in and they
they mess with everybody and then people
end up losing because of it Lynn Vander
West said my reflux went away then I had
a bad eczema for almost two years but
finally got rid of it too all thanks to
aw and sfc for this fantastic
information incredible
truly is
you guys so proud of all of you by the
way and I don't say that enough I don't
I'm so proud of you guys for all you're
doing and everything you're doing
aisling says on YouTube can we do brain
shots on day nine of 369.
SOC says yes you can
um but
that's what I would recommend a friend
ask your doctor what's right for you
see what your doctor says if he says
it's okay then you can do it Alexandra
Sophia I feel the shot over time an hour
later it gets even stronger the
intuition shot always builds with me
grief and loss
strengthen an hour later wow I could
feel my brain calming more and more I
have to tell you and the thing is is
when I when I get more than one shot out
of it
right and and it's like I wait a little
while and it's coming over me and
everything and then I say you know what
I'm gonna do it again
bartender give me another
and then it actually compiles on itself
and all of a sudden it's like a whole
nother ride a whole nother ride
it's just incredible
can you guys feel that are you doing the
shot right now
did you just do it right are you feeling
that like
I never felt like that from anything
like these brain shots this is
unbelievable
Amy Teeter says
I keep blowing out the green washer on
my G screen I've replaced it 30 times
how do we avoid doing this I wonder why
because I've never blown mine out once
so what I would do is
Amy so what I would do is I would call
them on the mm hotline and ask them
maybe there's another part they need to
replace
that maybe there's another part they
need to replace in here that they
because it's warrantied
and that might take care of it because
I've never blocked I mean I've I've beat
the crap
out of my MMS
I mean I've I actually feel bad I've
I've totally
totally just
beat these to death these MMS and
and I never had the green the green
washer pop out so what I'm thinking is
talk to them and say look is it another
part that might be doing that
so and it just needs to be fixed
Reggie Natura says I burned down
what
Reggie says I burned down four juicers
before my medical medium 900. oh yeah
let me tell you something okay
before the mm 900 and 1500 I had to use
all the crappy juicers like everybody
has to had to right
and I
destroyed those juicers
I I mean every brand you name it every
brand I destroyed annihilated they
cannot hold up to it plus the cost of
juicing was insane
um
so that's important to know that that
the difference has been going on one
night and day on this there's a hotline
in the description of YouTube
if you want to check it out in Rumble so
there's the hotline
number in the description there at
Rumble and YouTube on the juicer
don't let anybody tell you that the
mm-900 mm-1500 sucks or something that's
just somebody actually like trying to
stop you from taking care of yourself
and it's also at medicalme.com the
hotline
I mean because I literally just like you
I burned down those other juicers in the
past just exploded them they were so bad
I've tried them all before the mm-900
and 1500
um was here I had to use all the shitty
juicers and it was just terrible like
seriously
foreign
yes where is grogu Stephanie said where
is grogu
is grogu back there
are you back here
squirrel go back here
where's grogu
why grocer you're not feeling well how
come
grogu
you're not feeling good today
what is going on
Ah that's why grogu
all right grogu's here
um
anyway
well
we had a good time you guys I am feeling
very good with that brain shot running
through my body getting to my brain
it feels really incredible
I love the feeling afterwards too it's
like the sensation afterwards remember
post your real your story
your insta story and so forth tag at
Medical medium hashtag at Medical medium
so I can see it and then repost and so
forth and so incredible you like grogu
grogu's here I'm gonna put Roku back
here
there you go
and you never know AWS Bar and Grill
might get open someday
AWS Bar and Grill has been closed for
now
we shall open it in the future but
seriously you guys incredible Jackie B
proud of you
yep Uma says I see grogu in the
background
you guys okay tomorrow by the way
tomorrow's day 14 you still can join and
if you're dealing with those stubborn
the stubborn colds and flus RSV and C
and flu and everything else make sure
you have your cold and flu tool kit
seriously I'm seeing people suffer out
there it's sad they're suffering
unnecessarily it's awful make sure you
download this at medicalmedium.com
it's so important to make sure you do
that
Sherry Weaver says I had the green
washer pop out before then I looked at
it
I looked at it a shade put it back in
backwards so you're putting that a lot
of people put it in backwards
a lot of people pop it put it in
backwards and that's why it pops out too
so that that maybe that's what it is
because I never had to pop out on me
make sure you have this in your pantry
because it's worth it every time a
friend
gives me a text reaches out to me and
says I caught the flu
I go okay well you got all your stuff
right and they're like no
I'm like okay well great because now
you're sick and you have to you have to
get your stuff maytal says how do I
convince one of my family members to
keep the 900 juicer
they don't get the idea that it works
slower purposely because it's cold
pressed masticating juicer to preserve
nutrients that's why we have done celery
juice over the last four years what
happens is the ones that go quicker are
throwing out all the juice so it's
costing more that's number one number
two it's scorching the juice you're
losing nutrients with the other juicers
that's how it works you lose the
nutrients with the other juicers
right someone just said what's that
Anatomy dummy back there
okay
um make sure for cold and flu and
everything you are prepared because
another round comes around and comes
around there's going to be easy two more
rounds of C of RSV and flu and stomach
flu coming around
um this is the cold and flu tool kit you
can download and you see the seven herbs
and supplements to keep on hand right
there well that's the one so check that
out when you get a chance
foreign
an IG
Mish says aw is not your personal
assistant he provides so much info we
are accountable for looking for it
God bless you truly
God bless you
you're very kind
very kind indeed
yep for sure
incredible you guys you guys we're day
13 tomorrow's day 14. keep that in mind
we're not done and we're not out of the
cleanse challenge yet
we still have more to do we are except
seven more days matter of fact
seven more days
yep
let's do it all right you guys
Hopefully Dr Nesbit shows up tomorrow