hello everyone welcome back it is night
four our final night of the medical
medium Cafe Gratitude popup dinner
collaboration and tonight we're starting
with the man Chef Drew who uh
collaborated with aw on the dishes that
are featured on the menu now Chef Drew
it's so lovely to meet you nice to meet
you as well it's so happy to be here yes
uh since aw started the celery juice
movement now every juice bar restaurant
health food store have celery juice but
what is it like to be the first
restaurant to collaborate on medical
medium dishes well I feel like Cafe
Gratitude you know we have a 20-year
history now and we've sort of been a
Trailblazer in our own way both in the
transformational sphere and the werness
sphere uh we were doing cold brew coffee
and cold press juices you know well
before most restaurants you know 20
years ago but this is a really beautiful
opportunity to kind of build on what was
our traditions in the past and bring the
food and the philosophy of the medical
medium Community out to our Cafe
Gratitude customers as well as sering
your community here you know and having
letting them have the experience of a
place where they can come and eat in a
restaurant environment so it's very
exciting yeah we have just been having
the most incredible week it's night four
our final night now how do you feel this
whole four nights have gone well you
know I think when we originally
conceived it I wasn't expecting it to be
so well supported by the community so
just seeing this whole setup all the
work that you've all been doing and the
way that your community has showed up
and really sort of taken advantage of it
and embraced it has been an incred
incredible sort of enlightening
experience for me and it's been super
fun you know super fun and it's rare
that you find a group of people so open
and happy and supportive and really
committed to health and wellness yeah
it's such an uplifting beautiful
community and I feel like you're
bringing joy and happiness to this
community through a dining experience
that normally they wouldn't get because
you know they worry about the
ingredients on the menu so how does it
feel to bring that joy and happiness to
this community Through dining well I
mean for me as a chef it's providing a
Hospitality experience is always the the
highest you know level of importance for
me and you don't often I I personally
have a diet that's very similar to the
medical medium protocol um some slight
variations but I'm a long-term you know
vegan and I I sort of you know don't
usually use oils and and you know
heavily refined Foods either so my own
food is now being influenced by the this
community and what we're doing here so I
just feel that it's a really great
opportunity for me to build on the the
menu that I've done for all these years
of Cafe Gratitude the work that I've
done in this community and maybe find a
new way to express myself as a chef so
it's been great it is so beautiful like
the crossover of communities uh one
finding out about the other and and so
on now aw has said that you have taken
his recipes to the next level like you
really upped the flavor profile how did
you do that well he's being very
generous for all
um I think that it was an interesting
set of guidelines to work with um in a
restaurant context like I as I said
earlier my own personal diet and the way
I eat and my private life is one thing
but when you're in a restaurant setting
and you're trying to create food that is
going to appeal to a broad spectrum of
people with those I don't want to say
restrictions but with those
considerations right like not using soy
not using vinegars not using corn you
know nuts and gluten and all that stuff
I was sort of halfway there already
because we are primarily gluten-free you
know I don't use any refined you know
vegan foods in in the menu but this was
a way for me to look at um I don't know
how I want to say this but to really go
I hate to use this word cleaner you know
with with everything that we're doing
and um I feel like just slight changes
can make a really big difference in the
flavor the flavor profile of foods so
yeah and there's people that have
traveled here from all around the world
and they're just loving your work well
thank you I mean it's been I've actually
been very surprised by by how well it's
been received and I do think it's
because they haven't had the opportunity
I mean I feel I feel great about the
work that I've done with this menu um
and I'm just really happy that people
are appreciating it I don't know how
else to say it yeah everyone's talking
about the sushi
rolls oh my gosh incredible they're
saying they've never had anything like
it before so can you tell me more about
them well I think that you know a lot of
people when they do a vegan Sushi
especially when you're saying oh we
don't want vinegar we don't want sugar
you don't want to but you know you could
what I did was I looked at it how can I
season this in a way that follows these
guidelines you know so I use some lemon
juice I use a little bit of honey I use
some dull flakes um the pumpkin SE tofu
has been a big hit which is another you
know thing that not many people are
aware of so that gives it a nice sort of
proteiny kind of vibe that that a normal
vegetable Sushi doesn't have we use a
high quality rice um yeah keeping it
clean and simple but playing with the
flavor profile to give it a bit of a
punch you know how long does that
pumpkin food take to is that a process
we marinate well yeah so we get the the
base ingredients and then we marinate it
overnight um so yeah I mean it's not
it's not that complicated no I mean most
tofu people don't realize it's actually
fairly simple food to make yeah yeah wow
and the the Millet tortillas tortillas I
had those on Friday night and the way
they hold together that was a bit of a
journey I mean it's taking us a little
while to get the hang of that I know and
you know we've had a lot of disasters
but I think we finally have got it down
inshi rolling is a new thing for my team
as well but they've really they finally
like having made hundreds now um because
it's been a super popular menu item
they're getting very good at it so well
I'm Blown Away by the dishes that you've
created for the medical medium
collaboration uh we are about to start
with some of our dinner guest and I know
that you're very busy you've got to get
back to the kitchen to make sure
everything runs smoothly this evening so
thank you so much for making the time to
talk to us in the community online it
was a great experience have a great
evening I know you've got a lot of
people to talk to yeah thank you so much
I'll let you go inside thank you you too
hello so now some of our guests are
arriving and we're going to talk to them
and see how they're feeling this evening
how are you going I'm very well how are
you Danielle I'm good thank you what is
your name my name is Jules it is so nice
to meet you now what was it about this
event that made you want to come out
this evening well I know it's a Once in
a Lifetime really um I'm from a small
community in Canada so I never get to
eat out and I'm sure it won't happen
again for a long time so I'm really
excited for this food it's amazing I've
already tried it it's fantastic
yes did you come with anyone this
evening or did you come alone or met up
with friends here so yeah really excited
to dine with everybody and get to know
more people because there's just so many
people in the community that I think
even when I think I've seen everybody
like there's just so many of us and it's
so many M mate that's right what are you
most excited about with this
collaboration between medical medium and
Cafe Gratitude the fearlessness of being
able to order food and knowing that
somebody understands why I eat this way
and what I need to feel comfortable you
know they are creating their business
because they want to provide something
for the people and so the fact that they
meet our needs is just amazing it is
incredible how did your medical medium
journey start how did you first come
across the information I'm lucky enough
that my sister came across the
information actually she was really sick
she needed a lot of help um but she was
not really sure if she could trust the
information yet she didn't know whether
to really take it on or not and she kept
conving in me and asking what do I think
of it and at the time I didn't know
medical medium I didn't understand the
concept so I wasn't super supportive but
luckily I told her I was like I'll read
the book and tell you why I think it's
probably not real and after page five I
said oh my God I think this is it and
from then I just started to implement
small steps every two weeks I give
myself a timeline and say if if if
something happens then I know it works
if it doesn't then I can say I was right
all along you know but and here you are
now gratitude exactly and everything
worked that I tried to this day I've
been doing medical medium for 8 years
and everything he recommends does
something it moves the needle in
miraculous ways wow so what are some of
the health benefits that you found from
using medical medium information and
what were some of the symptoms and
conditions you were dealing with prior
to starting this my worst and severe
most severe condition was mental health
issues I dealt with a lot of depression
and anxiety and OCD thoughts um and even
like dyslexia add and just over like
committing it takes time but when you
commit it changes and so now I no longer
have dyslexia and for me I mean that has
been amazing because it's meant I have
new employment opportunities that I
never had before and just you know it
just it just changes everything when you
can be yourself and succeed when you
didn't have the opportunity before yeah
that's incredible do you have an
encouraging message you would like to
share with the community online sure um
I think really it's it's small steps to
Perfection um or to progress as however
anyone wants to say it and it doesn't
have to be done overnight um we took
years and decades to get sick and so it
takes time to heal and I think it you
just have to commit to it you know and I
see it as a challenge a lot of times of
like how much more can my body heal how
much more can I improve and what changes
can happen because it's it is ulous what
happens I like the way you're saying
that it takes time I think that's really
good to remind people it's not overnight
especially if you've been dealing with
it for a long time but also I like how
you say how healthy can I get or how how
much can I improve that's that's kind of
cool to focus on it it is really cool
and sometimes I think okay I must be
done healing now and then I do another
369 and I'm like oh wow but more
happened like what else could it be that
that changes so it's very cool are you
looking forward to meeting aw this
evening I absolutely am I'm yeah I know
I'm going to be Star Struck and very
nervous but I'm super duper excited well
thank you so much for talking to us I'm
going to let you get let you get ready
for that and the meeting greet and enjoy
this amazing medical medium dinner thank
you so much lovely to meet you too who
do we have next to talk to hello Brandy
so nice to meet you I'm Danielle nice to
meet you what made you want to come to
this event tonight uh because I get to
meet people who are in the community and
I just love being around a W yeah yes
where did you travel from San Diego oh
not very far but not very far so you
could come back to Cafe Gratitude
sometimes yes for this for this menu I'm
excited for the food too because I want
to create it at home oh cool did you
come here with anyone this evening no
just myself oh yeah and have you met
some cool people in line I have yeah yes
yeah but I would I would like to share
too how I found of course we're getting
to that yes yeah let's let's Jump Right
In let's Jump Right In if you're ready
to go we'll go
okay um so my 10-year-old son was sick
he was very sick for 18 months doctors
couldn't find out what was wrong we had
a long list of
diagnoses um he could no longer go to
school he his life
stopped and every day I was working so
hard you know to try to figure out and
we were just being told it was
autoimmune he's going to have it for the
rest of his life um probably managed by
Pharmaceuticals and I just would accept
it it just did not
resonate and um I was sitting in the
garden and I was in such despair I was
really you know it was it after 18
months of every day it was just it was
too much and I came across an Instagram
post about dark circles under from mm
mhm and it within an hour I was juicing
celery for my son I ran to the store and
I had a juicer and I Juiced celery and I
remember giving it to him and stepping
back hoping that he wouldn't just you
know have a that he would accept it and
he did how did he react when he had that
first glass of celery juice he was he
drank it like nothing wow yeah
incredible so he was so thick I think he
was willing to do anything yeah so um I
went all in I took out the no Foods I
was in the K kitchen constantly learning
and learning and learning and non-stop I
mean every time I drove it was a podcast
or something from aw and within a year
he was completely healed and that was
has been over 2 years ago now yeah can
you talk a little bit more in depth
about some of the symptoms and
conditions so he was chronically dizzy
chronically nauseous and chronically
fatigued he was diagnosed with pots
non-infectious intis and citis sibo H
pylori um borderline
pandas
um that's all I'm thinking of it it was
a very it was a very long list yeah and
how has um the medical medium
information helped him improve some of
those symptoms and conditions no he's
completely heal completely healed oh my
gosh with none of that like you're done
with all of that oh my go we're done
completely he has been healed for almost
2 years now I'm so excited I'm sorry if
I missed that I I okay yeah no he's
vibrant he's taller than me and he still
drinks
CJ
um because I'm working on something else
that's totally different but and it's
just important to have so he doesn't
really like the hmds but he'll do the CJ
every day yeah that's that's incredible
because that was quite a long list I can
just only imagine it yeah it was our
whole lives stopped M and when I say
that I mean we didn't go out to dinner
with people we didn't socialize we
couldn't travel
you can't live a normal life and he was
you know no Sports so is he doing the
sports now and having fun he's in two
soccer leagues and three different
tennis places oh wow yeah he's thriving
and so and what does he think of you
being here this evening he went to the
first one and they so I asked them their
impression because you know I'm on
social media I know much more all they
know is what I do at home right and then
they know that a lot of other people
don't in our community
unfortunately and so when we went there
they were so shocked at how many people
cuz there were so many on June 15th the
they were shocked that there were so
many people from all over the world who
came to see him um and today I mean he
just knows it's my thing you know like
this is my happy thing to do yeah and
he's happy for me and he gets time with
his dad oh that's beautiful thank you so
much for sharing that story that's an
incredible story I hope it gives a lot
of people inspiration and hope out there
and you're going to have the most
magical fantastic evening I can tell
already thank you so much so nice to
meet you okay we're going to talk to our
NE next guest that has arrived this
evening hello hi I'm Danielle I'm Rosie
really nice to meet you oh so nice to
meet you too what was it about this
event that made you want to come out
this evening I one just the benefit I
get from um being in Anthony presence M
and um I just feel like every time I
come to one of his events the healing
accelerates but also I want to support
also I've been going to Cafe Gratitude
for 20 years so it's my favorite oh wow
does that mean you're a local no I'm
from Canada Canada but you fly out here
mhm yeah la is a happy place for me mhm
beautiful do you enjoy connecting with
the community before the event start
it's my favorite thing ever yeah yeah
and how did you discover uh aw medical
medium information I
discovered medical medium about six or
seven years ago or when his F he just
had two books at that time so that's the
how how long it was he had um medical
medium and life-changing foods and I was
really struggling I had a fibroid and I
had um many surgeries and so his
information stopped the
surgeries wow so I was supposed to have
um another one and I didn't need it
after I found his info oh that's
incredible so did you first start with
the celery juice and then add on from
there I I did but I um I really
gravitated towards the heavy metal detox
smoothie that was a very important piece
and that was the thing that I was the
most diligent with and then
supplementation and then changing like
removing troublemakers that's that was
my first wave and I feel like every year
I go deeper and deeper yeah so healing
more and more healing more and more yeah
now because we're here at Cafe gratitude
and there's the medical medium
collaboration I've got to ask you what
are you most excited about this evening
oh my gosh okay so I used to love sushi
and so I'm really excited about the the
pumpkin sushi cuz I I don't eat sushi
anymore yeah no they have been a
favorite with everyone that's come
through everyone's talking about the
sushi it's
amazing yeah I can't wait the food I am
so excited but I'll also say going back
to Healing any women out there um with
menopause issues medical medium is the
way there's so many women I've turned on
to Medical medium that are struggling
horrifically with menopause like I went
through menopause a few years ago and
not a single hot flash not a single
symptom feeling so healthy like it is
the way it is the way that is great
information do you have like one bit of
information in regards to that that you
would say is the most important you felt
with your healing uh that You' like to
share with the community online um the
celery juice like I was a little bit
resistant cuz I didn't enjoy the taste
at first like I love it now I was
gravitating more towards the heavy metal
detox smoothie but um celery juice and
avoiding troublemakers is a good start
like that alone will help significantly
and then the more that you can bring in
of the protocols the easier it'll be yes
well thank you so much for talking to us
uh the m and gr is next for you so I'll
let you get back in line for that and
ready for it yes
hello who do we have next hi oh we've
got we got two
people two beautiful souls lovely to
meet you I'm Danielle what's your name
I'm Danielle oh I like your name I like
your Annie is my name nice to meet you
now what made you want to come out this
evening obviously to um see Anthony yeah
yeah how did you first discover his work
interesting question so Annie here is
actually my doctor and she was person
who told me about Anthony and yeah
changed my life Wow incredible how did
you come across it then to be able to
share it it was uh in the in a Hay House
Radio Show I was listening to um a
podcast by someone else and Anthony came
on and within the first 5 minutes I I
knew that was what I've always been
looking for for
years did you travel to be here this
evening yes where from Australia yeah I
I thought I heard an accent I was like
I've got to ask first yes yeah did you
travel from Australia yes yeah we live
in Adelaide in South Australia so wow is
the community growing there in adelade
for medical medium it is it's growing um
I'd still much rather see a bigger
presence so yeah trying to spread the
word yeah incredible do you share
medical medium with a lot of patients
that you work with yes I do on a daily
basis yeah yeah I I I reference his his
um work as well I recommend his books so
yes on a daily basis I feel very
privileged to be able to do that
actually yeah how have you seen it help
people benefit
healthwise oh um in many ways so I was
um telling Daniel about a case where
someone was experiencing a lot of
gastrointestinal issues and I was uh
going to refer this person uh for
procedures endoscopy um uh to a
gastroenterologist and I said well I
said why don't you try these first and I
recommend a celery juice on empty
stomach and um she tried that and three
or four months later she she came to me
and said well I don't need a referral
anymore I yeah I I I I'm better I'm
better I don't I don't need to see a
gastroenterologist wow yeah that's
incredible and what about for you what
are some of the health benefits that
you've noticed from the medical medium
protocol night and day absolutely
amazing it literally saved my life um I
was suffering terribly with anxiety
panic disorders fainting neurological
issues and that sort of thing I couldn't
leave my home um without having panic
attacks and now here I am in La you know
you had a long plane ride too to be here
so that's amazing that you were able to
do all that too yeah cuz I suffered
claustrophobia acrophobia so to be in a
plane would have made me incredibly sick
and so I came here no symptoms no
anxiety no problems whatsoever I was
totally fine wow that's incredible do do
you also use the protocol in your daily
life as well and yes yeah yeah I have S
juice and detox smoothie with s juice
every day and detox smoothie maybe about
three or four times a week when I can
yeah yeah yeah and what benefits have
you personally felt well it allows me to
burn the candle at two ends because I
work quite a lot and yeah yeah and I've
got a young family as well so my kids
yeah always try to incorporate Anthony's
um yeah recommendations in in my family
life as well yeah yeah that's beautiful
now what are you most excited about for
this evening with Cafe Gratitude medical
medium the light
blast mhm mhm yeah was pretty powerful
last night by the way yeah yeah yeah and
what are you looking forward to the most
uh meeting Anthony and talking with him
I came to the June 15th uh events um but
yeah this time I'm hoping to be able to
yeah actually meet him in a yeah a
deeper
I Echo
that for sure and do you enjoy
connecting with the community here love
it it's one of my favorite things about
coming to these events is meeting
like-minded people and hearing
everybody's healing stories and yeah
just connecting with people it's I love
it it's amazing do you think the Cafe
Gratitude having the medical medium
dishes on the menu will help people with
their healing Journey make it more
enjoyable and easier for them 100% yeah
for people to be able to see that you
know eating a healthy lifestyle can
still be you know delicious and fun and
you know we're not depriving ourselves
you know we're actually fulfilling um
yeah exactly yeah
yeah yeah yeah I agree I I haven't been
able to sit in a restaurant and eat like
normal people for a long time many years
yeah for the last s years of been we've
been doing Anthony we've been doing
medical medium so yeah and a lot of
cooking at home but tonight you get a
night off you get to dress up come here
to Cafe Gratitude connect with the
community eat lots of delicious food and
feel amazing afterwards yes it it can
help you he on your healing Journey as
well that's right yeah well thank you so
much we're going to talk to someone else
and we're going to switch out the
mics
e
e e
so I'm back now what is your name Ash
Ash and usra so lovely to meet you so
what made you want to come to the event
this evening huh um we we've been
following medical meeting for a really
long time and we end up coming to the
first event and we had a great time and
we saw this opportunity more intimate um
setting so we we couldn't miss it yeah
and what are you most excited about with
this collaboration between medical
medium and Cafe
Gratitude um I'm very excited to um try
the new um uh medical medium um menu and
so excited to actually you know meet um
medical medium very excited what are you
most looking forward to uh the food um
and the collaboration and having clean
food you could go to a restaurant it's
not easy to find so it's very unique
what they're doing for everybody else um
and yeah just really excited to meet
medical medium and have a photograph of
the first time with a lot of people um
so I'm really excited get to meet him
we're also doing a light blast this
evening yeah really it's going to be a
light that's very exciting too now with
this menu there's so many yum so much
amazing flavor it's so yummy and
delicious you're going to leave here
feeling light feeling full but just
happy and joyful are you also enjoying
meeting people in line in this community
and enjoying to get to dine with your
community here at Cafe Gratitude yes I
actually made a friend from the first
event um ali um and um we connected
instantly you just connect with every in
the community it's actually something
that we all understand each other and we
don't have to say much we just
understand we've been through a lot um
and we have that in common and just like
we know where we're coming from and I
think the community is like one of the
best parts um of this I for years and
years like I was just in and out of the
hospital sick mystery illness doctors
don't know what they take all these
tests same with my mom and um nothing
they're just like you seem healthy but
yet they know I'm very sick they're like
but you look very sick I am very sick I
know you know you know your own body and
no one understood until we found this
for once we feel understood for once
like he's saying um
for the chronically ill and no if no one
even knows what that means like other
people so it's like finally I felt like
I was seeing like friendch should be
like well you look fine or you know they
didn't understand if you can't come out
no understands you're just in bed of
course you want to be going out you want
to be living life you want to experience
things and then it just holds you back
and so many people don't understand that
unless unfortunately they've been
through it so this is something that is
like nothing else I never even knew this
existed um my heart goes goes out for
everybody else who's not met this
community yet and hopefully they find it
um cuz you do feel alone like why me
what's wrong with me um until you find
and applied information I've been you
know out of the hospital it really makes
a difference this the only thing that's
worked for me wow the only thing wow
that's incredible and what are some of
the health benefits you've noticed along
the way how are you feeling now oh oh
amazing energy my uh fatigue is not
longer D I'm not bedridden anymore I'm
living life normally and that's whole
point of this um and the morning routine
is like one of my favorite lemon water
celery I was going to say do you do the
morning routine together or did she
inspire you to start no the opposite my
mom found
him yeah we both do the morning routine
we feel amazing is just yeah the celery
the um lemon water the celery the heavy
detox smoothie summer vitamins
everything oh yeah oh yeah we're feeling
so much better now so much you know
better energy you know we feel yeah
great well that's I'm so excited for you
I think this is great that you've come
out here together thank you so much for
talking to us enjoy the meet and greet
that's about to start yeah yeah get all
ready for that thank you so nice to talk
to you so nice to meet you
too I think we're going to wrap that up
you're welcome to come this way yeah
yeah we're going to take a break from
from talking to some of the guests and
we're going to head over to the meet and
greet it is about to start final night
here Cafe Gratitude medical medium
collaboration let's go check out the
meet and greet with aw
okay
you just you've done so much for my life
and I would never be able to thank you
enough You' changed everything about my
future and who I am as a person and I
just I'm so indebted to you and I mean
whatever I could do to help serve in the
community it means the world I can't
believe it okay and thank you so you you
you've worked hard on your health it's
changed your life I know you have I know
and all the yeah everything you do for
us all the information you share blows
my mind and I just I'm so honored that
you keep doing it and you do it with a
late heart and you make it fun and you
make it interesting and you give us
challenge except when I'm on my rants
love them love them just keep going
Anthony keep going thank you thank you
I'm I'm honored truly okay and and it
means the world to me do you want to
want to get a pcture I do and I also
can't wait for more your spiritual
information to come out because you've
done so much for me we go two two
more amazing thank you I hope you
enjoyed the food thank you so much thank
you welcome
what's going on good to see you what you
got a book put it on this is for my son
Ethan he's been doing your protocol son
Ethan mhm for over a year now he's been
reversing ADHD and acne and he just
loves your work as much as I do
thankfully look at that oh my gosh he's
going to love that thank you so much for
all you do youve changed our
life amazing ways never think you're
enough oh I really appreciate tell him I
really appreciate him okay and all that
he's doing I will yeah send my love I
will he'll love hearing that okay okay
that's good that makes me feel good
because I want him to know of course
yeah I'll let him know here step up a
little bit here thank you it doesn't
have the cover I left it at home it's
been used a lot
yes thank you so much enjoy the foodk
you so much welcome hi oh my God can I
take this book yes thank you thanks for
cre that is a big book thank you so much
for making it and for listening to so
and giving us all this great information
yeah so has been talking a lot in my ear
and uh truly and um I really really
appreciate all your support and
everything let me put the cap back on
for thank you you've been working on
medical medium information you got the
brain saver protocols yes you've helped
me out through depression and through so
much depression can heal it can heal
people don't realize that out there it
can go away yes the fog Has Lifted so
thank you so much that that warms my
heart okay warms my heart truly thank
you I appreciate let's get a picture
okay thank you for coming so
much love your T-shirt thank you very
much thank you very much um my wife
wanted me to give this to you thank you
yeah thank you thank you this is very
special yeah I um uh at first I just
wanted to say how much your angels
telegrams have meant to me I I'll keep
them coming I will I will you know what
happens is at night late at night when I
finally get a moment I I try to do the
telegram then yeah and spirit of
compassion says we're going to talk
about angels and so and but I I will I
will do more I'll ask uh spirit of
compassion for more Angel information
too because there's so much there's so
much but thank you I I I was also
wondering
if if if you don't mind if es said
anything
well let's get let's get a photo here
and
then here you're very very smart person
very intelligent person you're
spiritually connected okay and you're
doing the right things cuz there's times
where you just don't think that but you
are all right keep that keep that in
your heart okay thank you you go
welcome
hey I've been following you since
J since 2016 16 light water the radio
shows oh my God the radio shows and
everything everything and um if it
weren't for you and medical medium
information I'd be toast and I really
just came here in gratitude and I keep
working at it and but you're here all
the way from there till here you you
believe almost a decade okay you
persevered and push through almost a
decade now with all your healing well
I've had 70 years of garbage in me
that's a lot to push out yeah yeah but
but you're doing it you're cleaning up
inside you're getting rid of all the
toxins and poisons I'm so proud of you I
am I am want to get a picture yes I'd
love here step right up here Straight
Ahead
great amazing are you going to enjoy the
food tonight absolutely than you welcome
thank you for coming
oh hey what's going on how are you good
how are you good good so amazing I'll
keep it real short cuz you already do so
much for all of us okay okay real super
short no worries we got going do a
picture this was my son he was sick and
then this is what you and so did oh my
God took a year to heal him with your
information he's smiling oh yeah he's
smiling right there he's thriving now oh
my God he's
thriving that's incredible
that's every reason why I do this okay
that's why yeah so so your son can heal
that's what it's all about it means
everything thank you for telling me
he'll take his whole life with what tell
him I said hi I will okay thank you
thank you for all you do what's going on
how are you how are you doing are you
okay look you're on the red carpet here
I love well I really appreciate that
okay do you want me to take this big old
book you got a note it because is this
for me I'm going to talk to you yet okay
okay do you have a pen you brought one
you got one who's got a pen I oh wait we
got one thank you thank
you I found your information in 2022
that's great 2022 right when these came
out right here this this book this was
the first book I bought but this the
first book yeah yes this is a good first
book to get it's it's the Brain saer
book I got it and you know um so my last
one of the Thousand Cuts the last one
was I got the I therapy and I think I
got po the heavy medals it's not easy
but but you're doing all the right
things okay let's get a photo yeah I
love you Anthony let's hold up your
first book there oh you got that yeah we
go right
here I'm sorry no it's okay it's okay
you're G to get me crying though
I've been doing pretty good I haven't
been crying but here we
go but I I know it can come out at any
moment I hope you enjoy the food okay
thank you very much I'm so happy to see
you should I keep this can I read this
yes okay okay thank you
welcome he hey it's nice oh that's a
that's a
handshake thank you very much for
everything you've done and you know your
information has helped my mom and my
wife yeah and my mom can you tell them I
said
yeah I will definitely tell them and
I've been feeling much better since we
started the medical medium journe did
they get you on it or did you get them
on it she did the girl she's the hero
she got she got me okay she did okay
good good get you sh shape yeah I can't
say enough for thank you for everything
you've done and it's just a
life-changing experience for us that's
amazing apprciate that's amazing I
appreciate you here step right up yeah
sure
thank you I hope you enjoyed tonight
okay thank you hey at you I love those
classes oh thank you love yours how are
you I just want to say I've been waiting
for your information since I was an
insomniac 5-year-old oh my God and the
Catholic information that was not
sitting with My Soul okay so I'm healing
the body but the healing and the answers
are really they they're taking out of
the darkness aw are you sleeping a
little better a little better much
better l b way better I've been doing
the um bringing the um info in for like
6 years but I have a question shoot the
advanced 369 let's get a quick I can't
sleep I get so wired my brain gets so
wired I cannot sleep that's that's
because I'll tell you why it's hey Mikey
want to get a
picture that's because you know when you
do the 369 right it's so healing and it
moves you forward so quick that you're
going to feel the energy it's going to
be energetic it's you meaning like
you're going to feel like all kinds of
different frequencies run through you
because it's rewiring and you may not
sleep as good but then you'll sleep even
better later even better later but I I
need to do them cuz like I've been not
doing well no you you know do what feels
good and a little bit at a time you can
do one one time you cannot but you it it
it's going to come together noral brain
it's like it's actually healing okay
I'll carry on thank you for sure sure
sure thank you a thank you so much I'll
see
you all right you want to go to 50 uh 43
now what does it look like it is a
little bler for sure yeah let's stay
there just to anticipate the drop of
light
I see a book where is that book oh my
God that is so
cool for you for your unsp spirit
information I feel good and strong every
day thank you for coming amazing do you
want to get a picture yes of course this
is your
you also you want to give me a hug yes
and and this is yours don't forget
it amazing are you going to enjoy the
food tonight than for
welcome what's going on hello hello my
name is Kate I want to tell you just
thank you for all your work and I want
to just tell you that I'm also work with
people I'm healer and I need just little
little sign for you like little ination
of this little power that I can share
more and more this for people because
you know it's very hard very hard it's a
lot of it's hard to tell people it's
it's hard for people to listen and but
you're doing the work you're you're
carrying the message right yeah aming I
just want a little blessing from you to
share all this knowledge because I know
what's going on soon with all the people
with all the world and how much it's
important because um yeah sure
thank you so much Anthony for your
work listen you see things other people
don't see that's SRC C me okay keep that
keep that in your heart and realize that
people are not where you are it's very
strong for me to be to feel this
compassion for people and give I know I
know it's difficult but remember people
they're just you you have to have
patience for them okay that's it I see
you have to okay
hey hey anth hi good to see you you how
you doing pleasure to meet you sir yes
nice to meet you help my wife out a lot
here is she getting you on this on all
the good stuff the celery juice the
celery juice but she's kicking you in
the butt in the morning she does make
sure you do it she's one of your hard
hardest she's hardcore on your on your
program there so yeah thank you for
doing that thank you and thank you for
looking after him okay cuz it's also
about getting the family better too and
right tell yeah yeah we we all support
each other so yeah amazing amazing let's
get a photo you guys you fantastic you
ready Straight
Ahead come
a you want to come forward a little
bit oh can we get one more I want one
with him and you you want one with him
come of course go why
not here guys here oh sorry right there
it's gonna go to his head I know
we're thank you for not up thank you so
much bless your heart than I'll see you
enjoy tonight okay good how are you
there what's going on how are you oh my
I met you
KES and I wouldn't let go of your hand
and I kept mumbling and rambling so this
is my second little calmer that's all
right you're very calm I'm trying I'm
I'm less calm you're very calm okay
thank you do you want to get a picture
yeah I do and I believe it or not I have
a question about dogs but I I love dogs
I'm a huge dog fan do you give your dogs
lemon
water I mean if they if they like it
okay I can't I I I I I don't usually the
same reasons we drink it no a little bit
a little bit does help okay if they'll
have it okay thank you so much thank you
welcome anthy hey this is for you oh my
God where' this come from um is this a
Dr nesb It's Kind on Dr Nesbit but it's
the messenger this is Dr nesbit's uh
brother or friend friend he's a
messenger like you and I thought you'd
enjoy him I do in fact I do very much so
this is
wonderful he dances too if you shake him
a little bit okay no that's great I love
that okay this is awesome aome thank you
okay appreciate the gift you know
that you
ready I wanted to ask you something
too can I ask you something to what's
going on I've been uh sick for 33 years
and I've been doing your protocols for
eight okay it depends on which ones are
you customizing it are you trying to do
more I'm working with Dr Nicole okay and
so what you do is there's a lot of
information there it's volume
okay and then but it sometimes it's it
takes just a little bit I'm going to go
outside the box in here and go a little
bit further but but as long as you've
been doing some things for for years now
it all counts okay thank you for coming
to ask can you ask es if he has any
message for me or anything I'm
overlooking in my work I I I think that
there's I think you can do more in there
that's going to feel comfortable so
think think about that when you're
looking at the information there's more
but that's
comfortable thank Anthony
welome
hey I'm Shannon I'm from Mont so glad to
meet you did you come here from Montana
to yes I flew in yest thank you for
taking the trip I really appreciate that
seriously it's a long trip well it's an
honor and uh my husband quick story was
diagnosed with Advanced rare cancer 5
years ago and after three surgeries and
almost dying I we decided not to take
that route I got online I found you and
we've been you been doing medical medium
cane and we're hiking and we're CL so he
cleaned up his cancer doing medical
medium he's
hiking can you tell him tell him I said
hi yes his name is David and going to
see you soon he's going to see me soon
amazing here come here and step
forward wonderful thank you for coming I
hope you enjoy the food thank you thank
you
way what is going on here what is all
this you got some notes yes how are you
I got some questions for
you um you got some questions yeah I
don't think I can go through all these
right now those are some big questions
you can read them later um can you write
a note for that's a lot of questions
yeah you know me can I take this yes or
do you want to hold on to this for now
can hold maybe we can I can hold on to
it okay okay but do you remember what
they are yeah I do are you ready do you
want to take a picture with
us all right right
here there over
here all
right amazing thank you for coming you
want me to hold on to this
okay hey oh so nice to see what's going
on nice to meet you too who's this right
here is this your guy you found him
somewhere
[Laughter]
we we were born in Costa Rica but we
came from Spain we arrived yesterday you
arve from Spain to here to see little
old me yes I don't know what to say I
deep appreciation okay from my heart I
saved your daughter's life so grateful
oh can you can you tell her I said
hi we will excited about thank you thank
you send my love thank you you want to
take a picture let forward here yes
let's get you came all the way from
Spain let's make sure we get a
picture incredible are you going to
enjoy the food tonight it's not going to
it's it it's not going to be you know
the best spanish cuisine but it's going
to be
incredible it is extremely incredible I
swear is different for us too much
me PR this thank you it's I can't eat
enough of it it's so good wait till you
taste it it will not knock your socks
off thank you
again hey hi my name is laa lisia nice
to meet you nice to meet you too thank
you for coming thank you did you travel
far well I was telling one of the ladies
that although I'm only an hour away hour
away and you made it here good good good
I my license taken away by the doctors a
couple of times so okay how did you get
here well I drove cuz I'm doing celery
jues okay oh and you got you're able to
drive now yeah oh thank God okay thank
God here come there and let's take a
little picture bless your heart bless
your heart I can't believe it now you
can
drive it's a big deal too can we do one
with the dog you got to you got a oh my
God yes bring the dog in telling your
friend the last time you paid all the
attention
so we have to bring the dog in
Mikey's got dogs so he yeah he loves
thank you for coming okay oh and she
does detox smothie and celer good good
my dogs do too my dogs do
too oh my God Lemon Ball hey can I have
a hug yes of course of course good to
see you good to see you so good to see
you thank you for coming and making the
trip of course of course long way to
come back I know I mean all the way from
what a Australia EX exactly I know
that's where you are it's a long ride so
thank you for coming thank you I have
some questions I don't know if oh my God
you got a whole bunch of questions am I
going to answer these right now
um oh my God oh my God this is a lot
this is a lot I'm not going to be able
to cover all these right now but I'm
seeing them and in spirit of compassion
seeing them okay you want to get a
picture together absolutely you came all
the way here from Australia can I give
her her phone yes yes I do I do here we
go
you know I'm proud of you okay thank you
for coming thank you so much for
everything you've done for me getting me
choked up here I hope you enjoy the food
can I just ask one more question very
quickly um my doctor Annie was the
person who told me about you and she
came with me on this trip could we
please have a photo with the three of us
where is
she what are you doing waiting there
what is going on are
you okay do you want to get a sure okay
okay dear
Lord what right over
here
that's thank you thank you Dr Annie it's
an honor okay it's an honor it's an no
no my honor to have you here okay and
and making the trip thank you all right
I hope you enjoy the food thank you so
much I spend a little time with you can
I spend a little time with you yeah I
I'll let you go Dani okay thank you
thank you hey hey uh this is for you I
was here at June 15th and you asked for
my number and I gave it I don't think
you ever thank you thank you I'm going
to I'm going to hold on to that perfect
thank you let's get a picture together
just you and I can I ask you one
question though sure yeah I wanted to
ask what's wrong with my son what's
wrong with my son and how can I best
support him well you gave me the number
and then we're going to eventually have
a make a connection somehow thank you
thank you Anthony we have a doctor in
the house right now
doctors are welcome here thank you so
much especially really good ones like
yourself thank you thank you thank
you we have a family here got the whole
crew amazing and a stellar family my God
look at you guys how is everybody
where'd you guys come from West Palm
nice nice
look at you you're smiling you're all
happy you're not crying you're smiling
and you guys too are we going to get a
picture absolutely okay okay how do we
do Mikey how do we do this you you know
the family portraits okay all
right go back this is
amazing
here
of do a great
job thank you that's incredible thank
you for bringing
everybody have good food absolutely okay
okay get comfortable in there okay you
need any help because you got the baby
or anything or need just just let all of
us s
okay have a good one thank
you oh look at you hey good to see you
strong handshake three times uh this the
third time nice to come and I'm honored
means the world uh I'm I'm really
thankful that you were able to handle
this and and stay with it so that we can
have the protocols that we need started
at four yeah I know started at four
years old and I just fought for it you
know I know I had to fight for it I can
hear better out of this year cuz this
one all I hear is Spirit of compassion
telling me about everybody here
including all of these people here and
so it's it's a lot going on but I I I am
here thank you for coming oh you're
welcome do you want to get a picture yes
yes I'll have a picture how old are you
82 you're 8
God bless you you're going to be 83 God
bless you I've been following it for
celer for 5 years or
more see you started at 77 years old
doing celery
juice turning 83 yes you're amazing and
and and you your protocols have allowed
me when a doctor says I have a problem
to take it and fix it without having to
take drugs and that's my goal in life I
don't know what to say well I I believe
I believe that God would provided us you
know we just have to find out and I
appreciate you that you're taking the
time to do that and your life to do it
get yourself comfortable enjoy the night
I will I will so good to see you so good
to see you hi hey so good to see Youk
you so much for everything I have a
question I did celery juice in 2019 I
did it for three weeks I traveled to
Canada so I did it at a juice store got
a bug and now even smelling celery I'm
just like I want to vomit you know what
happens if you catch a flu or RSV or
covid or something right and you were
doing something around that time eating
something it could have been anything it
could have been eating oatmeal eating
something else you're just not going to
want that food when you got sick it
there's a memory and there's a there's
an entire you know a connection with it
with that well because even now today
when I try to do the celery juice I
still and it can last a lifetime a
lifetime oh to get it back is doing
coconut oil and they get really sick
because they catch something and they
may never do coconut oil ever again for
the rest of the it's it's like that you
want to get a picture yes yes
yes awesome I hope you enjoy the food
you're welcome thank
you hey hi nice to see you what's this
you again should I sign yes please let's
see if I have a pen today
thank
you thank you this thank you is this for
me you and fr thank you thank you I will
read it I will read it can i h you I
like your I like your mask H can I HCK
you yes yes yes it's
okay thank you so much you ready
Mikey thank you for coming I hope you
enjoy the food
all the way from Germany nice to see you
again I hope you're fine it's okay I
hope you're doing good thanks yeah it's
thank you for coming again I'm happy
that's my life tell her I said hi yeah
it's okay okay
good
Shir your favorite thank you so much
thank you I'll see
you hi I'm Emily conine yeah Emily hey
nice to meet you who's this here Tim my
husband really hey you gu we appreciate
you so much and how you've dedicated
your life to help people heal and um I
at one point had so much fear of going
blind and losing my vision because of an
eye condition and you stopped it and
it's getting and it's getting it's
improved right it's improved so much cuz
I remember I remember on social right
you talked about the the eye condition
and it's like a rare one and stuff and
they were they were saying it wasn't
going to heal it was wasn't going to
heal and then you turned it around yeah
it's on Emily amazing amazing and he's
healing too you're healing too I love
hearing that my thyroid I had some
numbers mixed up and then and now the
numbers are straightening out that
celery juice my morning oh that's celery
juice it's underestimated it's still out
there what it does the power it has well
it's good to see you guys okay do you
want it to get a picture my life so much
and I'm just so I'm just so grateful for
you it means the world to me okay you
changed my life in many ways it means
the world and your support everything it
just it does want to step up here hey I
I if I can get a chance to see you guys
it's worth every bit of doing this okay
man we appreciate
it all right one
more amazing get in there get
comfortable warm up little try to see
you in Colorado and then a couple weeks
okay you guys got tickets for that no
we're out there so we're going to try
okay okay good
Anthony hey again hey good good hey look
at you good to see you yes yes are you
going to get a light blast are we
getting a light blast
tonight God willing yeah so this is
Thiago and Anthony you know he's non
verbal so he has symptoms and he can't
communicate with me and he can't tell me
what's going on so I have to go off by
what I see the symptoms that I see
Spirit of compassion says belly ache
sometimes that's the spirit says so so
belly ache and it's very hard to express
it but yeah there's no communication so
I go off by the symptoms and I go to the
book and then from there I go to the
protocols so and then he rubs his ear
too once in a while and so sometimes it
gets itchy inside okay so I just want to
thank you for sharing this information I
want to thank so for giving you this
information because I'm a to help him
and give him a better life here on Earth
that's that's that's so important so and
not only that but we're able to live a
better life ourselves because we were
living a living hell for like 7 years
till I found your
information and it's made our life
better I don't know what to say I'm
speechless I don't have the words
because it's everything that's
everything to me okay do do you want to
try to get a picture all together yeah
Mike how do we do a another family
portrait he's a family portrait
expert just come close to
him here we
are what's name
tho he might not listen I love that
name amazing thank you for sharing that
with me about his belly and the ear
thing I will look out for those things
and like he gets he gets some gas
trapped and then that's that that's what
spirit says okay I try my best thank you
love you
guys hey good to see you what's going on
who's this meet you my mom this your mom
yes good to see you guys nice to meet
you again we came to the first of that I
know I know it's good to see you again
do you guys want to get a picture
together y
Wonder so much for everything you do
thank you for being here you guys
changed our life completely means the
world it does thank you for being the
voice for the people who don't I know I
know meaning like it's it's hard you
know we need we need a messenger we need
the information out there are you guys
going to have some fun tonight we're
going to have so much fun you're going
to warm up inside it's a little chilly
tonight hey I'm Lisa o pleasure to speak
with you hey thank you so much for
having us I wrote down two questions is
it okay if I ask you yeah okay okay
first question is will I heal my EMF
sensitivity and if so how EMF EMF always
always heals when you when you do the
right things it always
heals okay people don't stay in EMF hell
forever if they do the right things okay
so you have you have the information and
EMF will heal what's the other question
um so I created an affirmation card deck
based off of the healing path Wellness
step for that you taught us how to do
and I was wondering if you would
autograph my card de of course I would
and there's a card I just wanted to show
you this one I can grab that back from
you so I pair affirmations that you
teach us with activities so people can
remember to do them regularly okay my
favorite one is I work for God and you
say it when you open a door or a window
so I just wanted to tell you thank you
so much that is so beautiful I gave you
one of these at the this is for me this
one is for you I maybe one of these at
your last yes no I know you did I love
that no I know you did that I was just
thinking the same thing could we do one
thing could you do a heart with me yes
so you make a c yes tell me how to do
this you just make a c like that and we
join it together and it makes a heart I
think this might be my first one lower
it thank you so much your heart thank
you for coming
hey you got a great set
of hey you too man awesome that was
awesome uh perform last time we didn't
know we were getting treated to a a
dinner and then a life performance that
was really was he's convincing me to do
another one he's telling me we got to do
another one you guys got and so we we
are you know so maybe we can get more
than an hour practice you guys sounded
good and I mean it's just it just it's
organic and fun and unexpected he
sounded good he sounds amazing that
takes a lot of guts to perform in front
of uh 700 people so well thanks you know
thank you for coming okay I appreciate
let's get let's get a picture
okay not sure which camera okay there we
go here we go
more amazing can I ask you can I ask you
a quick question yeah um so I've often
have like uh dry throats like I lose my
voice when I've go to like concerts
sporting events Etc and then at work
have to talk all the time on Zoom Etc
I'm just wondering is there anything in
particular you would recommend you don't
like honey oh I love honey we drink a
lot of lemonade honey honey and lemonade
water do the honey do the honey without
the lemon sometimes and see how that
feels okay well that sounds like a treat
all right hey thanks a oh my God wait a
minute this is my happiness Guardian
what do you know she tell you what your
name that's amazing do you know the
meaning of your
name your name means your name means
Priceless one and it means strong wield
Warrior thank you for being our
Priceless strong wield Warrior thank you
thank you I won't forget that I will
tell myself that when I'm feeling kind
of down okay that's
perfect okay thank
you oh you got a gift for me from Maine
from Maine
M very interesting and how are you today
doing good thank you for coming do you
want me to sign this oh if you hey Jay
can you take
this that's from Maine the lid has to
open and if you don't mind after my book
a card from my friend who just got
diagnosed with fourth stage bladder
cancer oh you've got even better pen
thank
you that actually opens please say uh
send my love and say hi to your friend
pleaseing a little just your signature
or initials or anything for a little
extra light in the
card oh thank you thank you oh thank you
[Music]
how should I address you how do you like
how would you like me to call you oh
anything you'd like Anthony William aw
whatever works all right and I'm Mitch
on your telegram group wait yeah Mitch
who's on your Tel oh my God that's
crazy I can't tell where I'm
looking thank you for coming I hope you
enjoy the food oh can I ask you two
pretty quick questions
we're running out of time I'm sorry we
we'll we'll maybe we'll get a chance
later on you never know okay hello hey
how are you good good I'm just excited
to meet you that's it I don't have
anything for you to that is wonderful I
am very excited to meet you too no thank
you thank you you want to get a picture
I do yes I want that
too did you travel far no not that far
Las Vegas yeah Las Vegas yeah not that
far I don't know that's pretty far not
really not to see you it's worth it come
on okay okay thank you for coming here I
hope you enjoy the food hello it's so
nice to meet you what's going on good
good I love your celery juice I've been
doing it since 2020 and it's made such a
difference 2020 it's coming on 5 years
no I know but that's when I started back
when the amazing it's a long time yeah
are you still doing it yeah yeah okay
don't stop don't stop awesome do you
want to get a picture
amazing are you going to enjoy the food
tonight M can't wait
to hey I've met you before but I've met
you before but this is I know you look
extremely familiar do I yes that's
that's I'm thank you so much for
everything that you've done and for i'
healed from so much pain and I've been
on crutches I've been on and off and my
God you've helped me prevent a second
knee surgery so it's all been so oh my
God all that matters all that is
important you're standing here right now
you're here you're walking no crutches
right now okay all that is all of that
is huge people don't understand what
that is unless they've experienced it
it's huge but you you get it and it's
just amazing thank you so much thank you
for coming I'm so happy you um you came
here and thank you for the support too
it means the world okay let's get a
picture we see the cover of the oh
yes I'll hide my phone too
thank you for coming tonight get
comfortable have some good
food good to see you you got a book for
me I do yeah I will sign it I love this
new edition yes me
too every time I go into this book here
hold on to this every time I go into
this book it
is just blows my mind
pen I was pulling it out of my purse do
I have a pen thank you for coming you
want to take a picture sure
yeah you want to come up a little
further yeah oh let me there we go okay
there we go you want to come up a little
further sure there we
go amazing thank you for coming you can
enjoy the food oh yes so much hi hey
what's going on oh my God
what's happened I W you know
what no way I know from Angy that's
amazing okay can you hold on to
this do you want to get a pick okay
how's things going great you're doing
okay you know I'm always proud of you
right I know you know that
right you're such a good
kid here ready y we
thank you am I going to see you later
yes okay okay good good this is zy
[Laughter]
Jay Katie hi your tattoos are so cool
thank you I know you always say that but
I always feel guilty no
why my no no cuz you know you know what
to do to keep you know your blood clean
and all that you know would think so
it's it's fine yeah it's amazing well
thank you always being so nice to my mom
your mom's the best I appreciate she's
the best you want to get a picture yeah
of course I do and then I have a
question for the skin
girlies here we go
more thank you so the skin girlies want
to know besides celery juice of course
what are your top three favorite skin
Foods skin Foods yes anything with high
vitamin C so you know orang oranges are
still high in vitamin C that's another
pepp all the things broccoli just a real
high vitamin C that's nothing beats
vitamin C for skin okay noted thank you
thank you so
much hey want thank you so much of
course of course of course good to see
you really appreciate you having us here
today no I appreciate you being here
thank you I do I do amazing do you want
to get a picture I love one thank you do
you want to step forward a little bit
okay
I'm so happy you're here thank you
Anthony did you travel far um we're
Canadian all together you from Canada to
here now I can't thank you enough for
for the trip appreciate it thank you so
much
seriously hi Jana s Jan how are you
can't believe I actually get to meet you
and here I'm here in the flesh of being
on a screen that I've been watching for
eight and a half years the screen with
my kitchen background with the stuffed
animals everything right all the screen
I just you know I'm like so many others
I exist I'm not an AI generated not
individual on in a kitchen I actually am
real good to see you you want to get a
picture I do and I so much to say to you
I knew I'd choke up so I just want to
give it to you I will I will treasure
this I will treasure this so
much J J you want to take a picture
camera thank you get another one I
didn't smile for a second a thank you so
much thank you for coming bless you
bless
you hey hi it's an Anna again you got a
great accent yeah from jimy there's
nothing better it's amazing thank you
for being here thank you
incredible um have you you tried the
food yet have you been here for a couple
of days and you went in and tried it
amazing was it okay it was just
delicious perfect I can't wait for
tonight do you want to take a photo
yeah thank you for coming and taking
that long trip like it means the world
for me too it does it
does what's going on how are you came
again that's good that's good is it okay
to ask you a question
um I've been healing from colitis over
the past 16 years I had it and it's the
recovery is quite good but I my belly
looks like I'm pregnant and you've been
talking to did you tell the doctor about
the mono exactly okay is it just about
keep doing the mono or am I missing
something because it has if your
doctor's happy with it it's a very good
thing to do it's a very good thing to do
to it but it takes time A lot of
intestinal issues take a long time but
then they get better they get better
they get better let's get a picture I
keep doing that thank
you thank you for coming thanks so much
I hope you enjoy the food thank
you hiy hey we got the opportunity to
come a second time good good if yes it's
wonderful um I want to ask you a
question um I have really severe
histamine attacks and I I am struggling
um to get a clue out of it why it's so
severe and maybe you can give me a
hint you you looked into cleanse the
heel and the learning about the chemical
sensitivities I tried to do my homework
yeah yes just you got to keep up keep up
with all the information with that let's
get a picture nothing wrong in our
house it's there the info is there take
it thank you
welcome hi hey hi nice to meet you how
are you you got a coconut water too well
I brought it as a gift because I was
watching you uh in the event yesterday I
was on the plane actually and I remember
you stopped it for about 5 minutes you
were like I need some coconut water you
heard that right I was hot mik right
right and I was like naturally I have to
bring the good those those hot mics they
they get me in trouble they get you
they'll get you I'm in the back saying I
need some coconut water what the heck we
got to deliver so that's that's what I
did so um I'm sure locked and loaded but
just wanted to get that my throat was
very dry I was talking all day long and
then got here and was like I don't think
I drank anything for a very long time
thank you for coming thank you this is
wonderful I I'll have Joel Joel hold
that thank you Joel you want to get a
picture sure and I just had a question
too very thoughtful
too I just wanted to see IFC had any
words to impart on me to help move the
needle in my
healing spirit Spirit of compassion say
that you already are moving the needle
and you're
healing it's already happening yeah but
then
you you then go extreme with things you
do and you push yourself too far ahead
of the healing oh do you understand I
absolutely that's what so says I hope
you enjoy the f I appreciate
it hey hi so nice to meet you nice to
meet you too thank you for taking the
time to talk to all of us I so
appreciate it it's it's my honor it's my
pleasure seriously this is extremely fun
for me yeah to be here and to see you
and meet you okay because usually I'm
trapped in a room and I'm listening to S
so and writing books and that can be a
very uh lonely place so it's good to see
you you want to take a picture I just
want to say I pray for you and I pray
for your safety I'll take any prayers
you can give me all the time thank you
keep doing work yes my safety is always
you know in question so thank
you bless your heart I hope you enjoy
the food thank you thank you welcome
good you guys how are you so Greatful
did you bring did you bring this guy
with you nice to see you again saw you
at amazing this is so amazing to see you
twice I mean you've changed my life for
better in so many ways thank you for
coming seriously I um doctors told me
I'm alive because it's a miracle and I
think angels and God kept me and the
reason was that 7 months prior I started
medical medium so I think you know it's
not me it's not me okay it's I I'm just
a a mere messenger okay and so I I I
wish I was the one that came up with the
information so I could take the credit
of saving your life but it came from
above and my job is to fight for it and
get it to you but I'm I'm so glad that
you that you're like is doing better I'm
so happy about that okay extremely happy
you're a good man you take care of each
other okay he supports me if SSC has any
keep supporting keep
supporting I would appreciate let if SS
has any message for
me very spiritually
connected you guys are very spir both of
you are very spiritually connect that's
what says thank oh let's get one really
here let's go forward you guys let's
step step ahead there you want to go
this way how's that
Mikey wonderful enjoy the food please
okay I'm proud of you both of
you Hi how are you I'm Andrea thank you
so much Andrea Andrea thank you so much
for everything that you do I like your
necklace it's very ni nice thank you
thank you oh this is for you and um you
know Spirit of the most high spirit and
mercy very interesting thank you thank
you that you you are an early reader of
medical medium yes I mean it's just it
resonated with me yeah it it it uh yeah
it it's very deep in my heart do you
want to take a a photo here step forward
thank you thank you
amazing thank you for coming thank you
and if there's anything that you feel
that he might need to tell me I'm open
I'm an open
book
um Spirit of compassion says you're very
regimented with what you do you're very
you have things in order organized you
you write things down you're doing all
good stuff okay so yeah yeah just but
but sometimes you think you need to do
more but you're doing really well okay
okay thank you thank you
what's going on nice to meet you nice to
meet you too just want to say thank you
for everything that you do I've been
able to heal so many symptoms because of
you and I have so much hope that I can
continue to heal so thank Youk you thank
you for hosting this so now I want to
thank you now thank you for working on
things for doing the information for
reading the books okay and thank you for
making this trip yes I'm so excited to
try the food oh my God I'm excited too
because I'm going to I'm going to
tank thank you thank
you hello hello hello I'm Christina good
to see you look at you hey where' you
guys come from Orange County originally
from Lithuania from Eastern Europe
really and then you and then you go to
Orange and then you live in Orange
County yeah yeah I'm bistan nice amazing
thank you for coming yeah thank you so
I've been following you medical medium
the last 10 years and um you have been
tremendous help for my
yes I have a love hate with this book
you do uh I love how it's the most
powerful book in the world in health yes
hands down and it will be um heralded as
that down the road for what it is it's a
prophecy book yes uh but it was a pain
in the butt to write and put the
information down do you want to get a
picture yes thank you what's your what's
your favorite book my favorite book out
of all of them it might be the brain
Savers it might
be you want to walk up here a little bit
closer okay
here can we get one in the middle do you
mind no I don't mind thank you hey look
I'm I'm here for you
guys smile this time yeah thank you
thank you so much did I get a smile out
there you're thank you for being
tremendous light in our Liv thank you
very much Your Heart Take Care okay my
brother thank you very
much what's going on so excited to meet
you good to see you good to see you got
a p you got a book and how are you good
how are you husband my husband I'm super
excited to be here too beneficiary of
plenty of smoothies of and celery juice
maybe
yeah so you're being tortured
you're a good man he is it's great to be
here thank you you want a picture yeah
absolutely let's step forward a little
bit we got to get up here okay thank you
thank
you oh
yes wonderful and then we have one here
yes Jo
cheese no no cheese here no cheese no
there's no no cheese here there's no
Dairy welcome thank
you oh my God we took a picture in the
garage
[Laughter]
yes good to see you do hey I know good
to see you to see do you guys want to
get another one here another picture I
want to thank you so much amazing I I
kind of wrote it down because I was a
little nervous I really yeah can I can I
read this yeah go for it please please
yeah it's kind of tricky
so you know um we're going to do a
really powerful light blast tonight okay
if there's one thing cuz I'm going to
ask I'm yeah there's one thing exactly
to focus on yeah let's focus on the re
renal yeah if we can one protocol I
should
specifically being working toward it I
oh oh is this do you want to hold on to
this though or is this mine no no you
can hold on to it you want to you can
hold on to it me do you have another
copy yeah yeah let me hold on to that my
name's not on it name it's important I
want to have the connection um come over
here yes thank you oh get on yes okay
are we in a good enough spot Mike turn
this way oh that camera here we go
thank you and you're doing you're doing
juices right you're doing celery a
little bit you're doing some cucumber oh
cucumber Let's Do A Little Cucumber
thank you you bless your heart thank you
to your wife I tell your wife thank you
so much she's a good woman she's the
best part of
me for everything you do and how much
time you're away from her and you know
family I appreciate it tell her thank
you please I will I will bless your
hearts okay are for me blue did you make
these These are really cool thank you
thank you I don't want to lose these
Joel We don't want to lose
those hello again hey how are you what's
going on I I saw you guys in the parking
garage too want to get a picture here
come come up in the front I have a
question
hope you guys enjoy yourselves tonight
bless your heart
welcome for for um Spirit of compassion
I've had some eye issues I've had
surgeries that didn't come out right and
I'm not thrilled about having to come
back to have another surgery are are you
going to have the light go to there
tonight I will let's do that okay right
this way man thank
you hey how are you thank you for coming
thank you very much I really wanted to
ask you
something I wanted to ask you about my
hyperpigmentation spots they got like
worse around my eyes do you think it's
maybe because of the sunglasses or the
stuff that is like exposed to radiation
Still Still liver stuff here step
forward here and there's lots of
information in the books to to try to to
you know I
I canot drink a smoothie anymore like I
can only do a monal diet now well look
at look at yeah look at the different
things in there and and if all you can
do is that that's okay it's still but
the liver takes time thank you no no
thank you for
coming hey one more time I uh I have
something for you it's just a GI from my
region of some some goodies for you and
your team okay good um and I wanted to
ask you if you have advice for somebody
with type 1 diabetes that trying to heal
and is a little bit afraid of the
information with sugar spikes and how
can they move forward and you're you're
reading the diabetes chapters and
everything so you got that inform I'm
giving advice to that person but I'm
just wondering if you know they feel
like maybe it's it's hard for them to
trust you know they've got their monitor
and it spikes and how do they how do
they use the information to heal and
feel safe and it's it's it's about
having trust and faith and you just have
to kind of keep on working on them
there's some things that
are there's some things with individuals
where if you can't break that wall down
and crack that it's hard to get more and
more of of the rest and so but you know
you know I do and how can we work on
those I do have a photo already so I
want to just chat with you but I know I
know thank you for coming thank you
thank you thank
you I mean I'm I'm happy to thank you
Anthony I appreciate that you're
I have to step on this a right here
you're on the a okay thank
you
sorry thank you thank you seriously you
know I appreciate you I do
appreciate Anthony Williams good to see
you such a pleasure such a pleasure nice
to see you it's an honor to meet you
honor to meet you too okay thank you
guys for coming thank you for having us
of course of course to be here can you
hold this for a sec it's a very
interesting shape we have it I wonder if
this was a natural shape or they
actually worked on that one wow do you
feel anything cuz I know you feel things
I know you feel things light here let's
go in the I I put a little light into
both those let's move forward here
should we go on either side of you sure
yeah Center all right yes all right
right here
guys thank you guys seriously I I have
one question what she doesn't sleep very
well what is one thing we can both kind
of do sleep better insomnia are you hard
on yourself with your
insomnia probably I am we have to let
that partk go okay okay we can't be we
can't we can't fight ourselves
throughout the
night just get what sleep you can and
over time the PTSD will alleviate and
I'm going to talk more about this okay
thank you thank you so
much hey brother hey how you doing how
you
it's good to see you yeah thank you it's
been a while you know yeah thank you for
coming yeah yeah yeah I see you and I
appreciate you you've done so much and
done so much for my life I appreciate
you too you know that right of course of
course your books are profound you know
which is your favorite book uh it's
tough but it probably cleanse the heel
it's one of my favorite books I'm caught
between brain saver and cleanse the heel
I don't even know what to do it's great
great great well let me put my arm
around you
two
more thank you for coming any tips for
me you know what you're doing oh thank
you come on thank
you you're so honored to meet you oh my
goodness this is my daughter Lauren I'm
Jackie this is Lauren what's going on
nice to meet you doing your stuff well
Lauren has she's probably the best story
ever she has epilepsy petite M epilepsy
and uh 15 years of a journey four
different world-renowned neurologists
also the same thing keto diet anyways no
no changes you know we probably probably
cut them maybe 75% some I mean 25% 50%
some days but anyways long story short
is that she did the Smoothie first she
liked the taste does probably half of it
and then um then this this past June she
started to do the celing juice and we
are now off what four
medications uh 2 100% and then and then
slivers of the last two my God we are
almost in we're almost home she almost
has a normal life that's incredible I'm
proud of you I'm proud of
you they very proud of truly both of you
Journey thank you okay you're an
inspiration to me okay and many
others what's going on Hi how are you
nice to meet nice to meet you how are
you guys is your daughter yes where did
you guys come from course I feel like I
know you because I've known you talk
about you every day really yes Anthony
William that medical medium what a pain
in the butt he is what a troublemaker he
is literally just be like he says this
he we know she's talking about you oh
bless your heart it's almost like they
joke my oldest daughter especially will
say we know Mom medical medium says
medical medium we know it's
everything because I'm thankful for
everything you've done for people and
everything I think that's the biggest
gift of all for thank you for coming
here and thank you for putting up with
Mom with the medical medium stuff okay
it's honestly like I like hearing it and
I really take it into consideration
everything she said I've done aming when
I had weird red stuff all over me and it
went away just from that Inc no one else
can help me so 16 oz 32 oz 32 love the
advance you're 32 too the advance
amazing you guys blow me away okay you
want to get a
picture here we'll step right up here
okay it good
amazing amazing I'm proud of both you
guys and I hope you enjoyed tonight yes
thank you hi what's going on thank you
so much for all the hope and all the he
I like this Medallion and I love I love
this necklace thank you appreciate
you're so much to you andc and can I ask
you an unusual question unusual yeah
yeah you talk you talked about psychic
attacks right and so I would I would
love if you could tell I'm going to do a
whole thing on that coming up pretty
soon I've been working on something
about that and I don't know if that fits
with curses where I come from people
believe in that and it causes so much
fear so I don't know if that exists if
it doesn't what exists curses curses
curses curs curses and
hexes um you know uh spirit of
compassion has told me that those aren't
things that really hold but there's
other things that cause trouble and I
think I have to start doing more about
that so just look out that would be
awesome
thank you
[Music]
and I mean I've used the only time I've
ever used the word curse is is saying
how since I was four years old I was
cursed with s so making me do health
information for others for the rest of
my life but it's not a curse it's not a
curse oh good
to Blessings oh my God I know how are
you hey Catherine how you guys how are
you guys so good to see you how is this
is this the guy that's on medical medium
stuff right I can't believe it are you
65 6
64 oh my God anthon oh my gosh it's so
good to meet you reason we all he
ushered Us in he ushered us into ER 20
vitamins a day dimery he gave me the
book for my birthday really and it sat
beside my bed I'm like wait a minute how
long ago uh 2016 2016 you gave the book
to Catherine well I interested to her
and they gave it to Catherine okay for
my birthday I said why would I read this
on so I let it sit there you guys blow
me away and then I read it and it was
shocking I stayed up all night reading
it like I know you endorsed my books I
know your endorsement is in the medical
medium books which I treasure so you
know good to see you guys I'm so glad
you guys are here you want to get a
picture together or what amazing so good
to see you thanks for coming man hey
let's get a picture right here yeah I'm
going to you know I've got a great app
Anthony yeah take it you really do
editing why am I getting
nervous this you're never going to look
so good as you look in one of my
pictures Okay who wants to take this
yeah right
here right here okay which wait call we
need you next
a you good all right
smile my God you guys thank you than for
having us thank you okay okay only if
you guys want one sure you sure are you
kidding I've heard that before yeah
yeah exactly you know how it works for
sure I I love you guys so glad you're
here so you're looking so good I can't
believe it you really are thank you
thank you you look amazing you guys look
amazing seriously okay took my I take
your of vitamins twice a day now oh my
god really yeah oh yeah good job good
job thank you I worry about her okay so
I want you to do the best Stu my go no
we're on it all right I'll see you guys
we'll see you guys hey what's going
on what's
happening mom and daughter oh my God I'm
her oh talk to me talk to me well you
know what I'm so happy this will be the
third time I got to see you this year
yeah and and I I can't thank you enough
you know you know your commitment
wanting to come and see me okay it means
the world to me it does cuz you don't
have to you could just see me once or
something but you but you came again
thank you it warms my heart been coming
been watching you since
2014 think got 2014
2014 and brains saver brain saved I I
wouldn't even drive anywhere I drove
here today by myself no one understands
that unless no they don't they don't get
the driving thing being able to drive
again in your life it means everything
in so many ways do you want to step up
closer I sure awesome awesome
than you when you get when you get too
sick to drive and you can't go anywhere
and you lose that freedom you bought you
bought Hing to my thank you thank you
for all that you're doing okay
so Hi how are you Hi can I sign that ni
to see you yes thank you so excited to
try the new
menu how are you good how are you doing
thank you thank you yeah I wanted to see
if you have any messages for
me
um you know it's okay that you take
Sometimes some breaks on some things
that's okay all right but but try to you
know the things that you feel are the
best and they're they make you feel the
best cuz that's you've told others that
this makes you feel better yeah use
those consistently okay okay thank you
let's get a picture
perfect thank you thank you for coming I
hope you enjoy the food right how we
doing nice to meet you nice to meet you
I'm just missing the overshirt or we'd
be matching I know I know I love the
black t-shirts they're my favorite you
know yeah thank you for coming do you
want to get a pick Let's Do It Let's Do
It All
Right amazing are you going to get some
good food tonight you got it all your uh
Creations good stuff thank you my
brother it means the world all
right anony so nice to meet you how are
you look at this guy I know right look
at this guy he's the one that got Frank
H Frank yep love that name thank you for
he got me into you he found your book
and he said you got her into the
information yeah and now I do the
information I'm trying to keep up with
her cuz she's 20 years younger than I am
well well you know that's good that's
good you guys are you know you guys can
keep each other healthy you're doing the
information I'm so proud of you guys no
we really Greatful for you oh let's get
a picture together super grateful okay
okay oh this
camera
[Music]
okay incredible thank you for coming
enjoy the food thank you for the support
and Cafe Gratitude here for giving
support
amazing hey how are you Kathleen good to
see you so nice to see you nice to see
you too yeah it's been so good to be
with you the last couple events oh my
God thank you for coming oh my God I
wouldn't be anywhere else oh cool cool
cool next one I do I hope you're there
for sure all right absolutely well
thanks you want to get a picture I would
love to I just want to thank you for
everything that you do for us oh thank
you thank you really thank you so much
for trying my best I mean you're kill
you're [__] EXC my friends you're
killing it I know lot of obstacles that
aren't fair in the world for sure but
you know we're weaving through them we
see you though we know thank you thank
you so thank you yeah from the bottom of
my heart champion of yours yeah here
step up here okay
great incredible I hope you enjoy the
food oh how could I not yay thanks a
lot hey what's going on good how are you
what's happening thank you for
everything you're welcome we're so happy
to meet you happy to have you guys here
seriously have you tried the food yet
have you been to town been here before
um the food is fantastic but we're
excited to try the food that you know is
being partnered up with you amazing
thank you for the support supporting
Cafe Gratitude what they've done with
this food they've taken the food and
made it so good I'm addicted in a good
way thank you for coming let's get a
picture appreciate it step up here
amazing thank you guys enjoy get a good
seat
doome hey What's happen y thank you how
you doing good thank you for being the
anchor and shining the light for all of
us trying I'm for you I'm honored you're
here and I love you and I just my heart
just pours out out so well I'm I'm on
your side okay and thank you for the
support do you want to get a picture
love
to thank you for coming we're getting
ready to move you are our house numbers
has us he wants us to look for see what
comes see what comes they come in a way
for a good reason okay don't want to
force it to see what happens
okay you got a book for me honor yes
honor is mine honor it really is mine
thank you so I want to tell you about an
experience that I had coming into your
information uh and Egypt and and abided
Egypt yes and Temple Temple stud the
first which is built on top of a much
more Ancient Temple of Syrian and I was
there with friends during Co and we had
a meditation the temple was empty and we
were allowed you're not allowed to main
the temples but it was empty and I put
my hands against the wall and I
Disappeared whoa and what was in front
of me was this large L on fire and I the
it wasn't a voice that I heard but it
was information I received from within
me after that experience was this
information I was going to receive it
from a woman of my wife that I hadn't
met yet let's get a photo that's
incredible after that experience that's
your wife right there my wife oh my God
come over here let's take I wondering
what that L was if Spirit has any idea
what that L was this camera got you up
okay got you thank you right here here
we go two more thank you thank you man
appreciate it yeah right this way sir
you know you take the L and you move it
around and you look for an answer don't
see it as an L okay remember
that hey what's going on what's
Happening thank you for coming thank you
it's good to good to see you I have well
you yeah I have a question which is is
so I do the work that I do which is not
fulfilling and I'm working for darkness
and to support my mm lifestyle and so
how do I
shift out of that
work and what is the work I do events so
I do meeting planning and events and
you're trying to shift out of that yeah
I don't want to work for pharmaceutical
Banking and
Telecommunications you just just don't
fight it there's probably some positives
out of it that there don't fight it and
then when the timing is right it comes
together okay okay let's let's um let's
get a picture for you all right
y thank you for everything you do thank
you for coming okay you know I
appreciate you I love
you one with everybody oneck with all
three all
three miss the picture okay let's go
let's go you
ready oh you guys we love you
man my son says thank
you tell your son and said grandaughter
oh send my blessings in love okay thank
you brother God
bless what's going on how are you North
Face huh yeah I know just like you right
good to you so much thank you for your
compassion and all of your love and
everything that you do it means the
world to me and I don't know where I'd
be without you thank you for coming here
let's get a picture thank you for that
it's in my heart truly
I I appreciate your support okay thank
you than Spirit have any messages for me
you're doing a lot of things not just
one thing you're doing a bunch of things
and that's what sfc loves
okay hi hey D you got a book yeah Dawn
yeah thank you so much you're welcome
everything going okay yeah you happy to
be here yeah it's it was a little
stressful getting here but I'm here it
happens yeah it happens thank you for
coming let's get a picture
okay oh
yes are you going to enjoy the food oh
yeah I was here for lunch it was so good
my God that makes me so happy hi Anthony
hi what's this oh I met you at the book
is this your guy yeah Joseph this is
this is Sarah and then this book is my
mom I bought this um I ordered this from
Taiwan this is so cool CU she can only
read Chinese so then I have to order
this one for her here no I know I know I
know sorry about that sorry about that
no no I know it goes the other way I
know not my first
rodeo thank you so much Sarah's
evangelized everything uh about what
you're doing to her family she's got so
many people that have have been affected
by that's amazing that's amazing thank
you I didn't fold it right though okay
think you guys want a picture definitely
thank you you want to get in the
middle you guys ready
yeah oh wait step forward a little bit
good thank you amazing thank you guys
thank you so much thank you for coming
okay thank you
Joseph
hey what's going on good to see you
coolest soul I can't believe you think
so okay I'm honored 30 seconds we get so
in 20-some years I like went full circle
back to like where it all started with
eating clean like the vegan Delian
college and um had a kidney transplant
because I was misdiagnosed at 4 weeks
old so at 25 I did the paranal dialysis
we had nonetheless my brother saved my
life 17 years ago and um because of you
my blood is cleaner and my skin is I
told you the last time in Culver that
you saved my skin so thank you I'm
really embarrassed people hear us but
yeah they do hear us right now and I get
embarrassed too okay cuz I'll say
something like I need something to drink
yes and then I forget okay here step
forward I'm proud of you for all that
you're doing and everything you've been
through and you're fighting forward okay
yes sir it means the world I love that
you're you're working hard on your
healing process thank you so
much thank you for coming you connected
the dots for me cuz you know go crazy
when you're like it's this it's that
matter this matter it matters it's
critical yeah thank you blessings to you
blessings hey I'm Iris OT oh nice
finally I tell my name I want to just
like everybody else want to thank you
for your dedication and you know
everything you're doing for us
information it doesn't make it any less
meaningless okay no it's any less
meaningful okay love everything it means
everything yes I love the podcast I love
especially the little music to my ears
okay you're singing the Anthony William
you know Anthem that you love the
podcast cuz I put so much into that
podcast so thank you and we feel it
thank you for bringing the community
together do you like the poems at the
end the prophecies from Spirit of
compassion yes yeah those I knew it is
from those are all from so yes I know
thank you so much
much thank you so much let's
your hey
hi nice to meet you oh my
God I'm glad you're here thank you have
you tried the food yet yes I I come here
all the you do you come here all the
time are you going to come here all the
time to get the the medical
medium okay thank you that means the
world to me I want to I want I want the
um Cafe Gratitude to have those there
for people they need them there for
people it's it's a different level of
healing food so thank you for support
the support you want to stand up here
yes are you feeling a little better
you're not crying here Step Up forward
forward
here right there that's
awesome amazing I'm so happy you're here
right this way I'll see you later right
this
way good to see you that's my wife there
that you're all she talks about oh my
God incredible incredible yeah she's
been on an incredible journey and uh uh
she probably can't express it right now
she's been doing your program for about
7 years that's a long time yeah yeah and
it's really changed her life and you're
watching her do this and you're you're
seeing it you're trying to do a little
for yourself yeah participating myself
you're like okay I'll go do this I'll do
this yeah I try to keep up with her
you're doing some celery juice at all oh
yeah yeah I love it love juice okay what
happens when you stop it you're like you
can't live without it yeah that's I
crave it yeah and crave it mhm do the
lemon juice been doing the lemon juice
I'm proud of you I'm proud of you all
right spectacular thank you I truly
appreciate it welcome
hi hello lovely to meet you good to see
you nice to meet you to meet you
um you you have given me
hope that matters that matters greatly
yes yes it's so important hope is
everything yeah I'm actually going to
create an app to help all those people
that are struggling to implement your
protocol into their busy lives you know
what it's just doing good work doing
God's work is all that counts okay do
you want to get a photo I'd love one
thank thank you for coming you going to
have some good
[Laughter]
food what's going on how are you what's
happening
healing oh my God it's such an honor to
that's that's a very um serious title
you are the Godfather of healing okay
well I'm honored I'm honored thank you
for
everything um gosh this is this is
surreal thank you for coming thank you I
don't think I could uphold that standard
of god father of feeling but I will try
my best to to get there okay right thank
you so much thank you for coming do you
want to get a picture yes
yes two more
all right have you tried the food yet
not yet okay it's going to be good you
it's going to be incredible all
right hey pleasure to meet you nice to
meet you too how are you I'm good um I'm
here to support my sister she's been
following a regimen for about four years
now really can you tell where I said hi
yeah well you just shook her hand that
was her that was her oh my God amazing
she you know she really um is really
into your work and she's been following
you around for quite some time now and
you've made it a dramatic difference in
her you know health and wellbeing so
thank you for that so wonderful Wonder
life thank you for supporting her yeah
that's what counts that's what matters
let's get a photo yes please here step
forward
here thank you fantastic can you send
her a message yes just tell her that
hydration a little bit just a little bit
more okay aome
welcome Hey to meet you I'm Angel it's
good to see you good good just want to
say thank you I used to drink about like
a handle OFA a week for like four years
and like Dr nesbet yeah like Dr nesb
right um quit 6 months few days ago so
okay yeah you
quit you quit 6 months ago or a few days
ago 6 months ago 6 months ago yeah so so
a few days ago was 6 months yeah what a
marker what a landmark I so proud of you
I can't even tell you all all your all
your information is incredible so thank
you let's get a listen it's the best
news I ever heard okay thank
you right
okay know that I'm proud of you thank
you stay on track excited to be here
yeah amazing you made a commitment a
good commitment okay my
brother welcome
hey how are you I'm good how are you
good to see you yeah you too thank you
for coming yeah thanks for having me did
you travel far uh an hour nice yeah do
you ever come here at all have you come
here before um I have I I I've been here
few years ago but when you had your new
items I came within the past week thank
you thank you for coming it's so good I
just don't even know what to say and I
appreciate you giving support phot want
to get a photo yeah how long you been
doing medical medium want to step
forward a little bit um since maybe end
of
2017 are you kidding me yeah no it's a
long time
[Music]
um since 2017 yeah I mean I I've fallen
off a little bit sometime that's okay
but you started then mhm I'm really
blown away yeah I'm really proud of you
yeah I I I really love the information
I'm so grateful for you I'm grateful for
you doing it okay seriously I hope you
enjoy tonight thank
you hi hey nice to meet you staying warm
didn't yep good good thank you for
coming thank you I'm so excited I'm like
speechless um I started doing uh
following in
2019 and when I was really following
very strict my blood work was like
perfect I started doing it for anxiety
and but it's been a long process so
takes time but you're doing it yeah do
you want to get a picture
yeah I appreciate you coming tonight
thank you keep on working on it I will I
will thank you so much how's it going
hey how you doing good I'm I'm her
juicer I'm here a supportive partner
that's what I am amazing that's great
thank you for coming you want to get a
pick sure why not let's do it why not
right
yeah thanks thanks for coming nice
meeting you
too you take one with both of them oh
wait hold on we got to do it quick which
way which we got to do it quick just
quick Mike okay thank you thank
you appreciate
it I'm just going to walk on
take your time you're walking through
yes that's fine that's
fine CU I I don't really have anything
to contribute I'm just here with a
friend good good good thank you for
coming now oh you you are contributing
you're supporting thank
you
amazing hey hi Hi how are you hi I'm
excellent how are you how are you doing
so much better oh fantastic so much
better thanks for coming thank you want
to get you want to get a picture I would
like a picture come
on thank you you ever think about we
would be okay if you took a
break what did you say I said we would
be okay if you took a break oh I know I
know it's okay it's a long night we got
some good stuff coming so I'm good I'm
good and strong today okay yeah thank
you for coming welcome hi my gosh how
are you I'm so grateful I'm grateful for
you oh my gosh I wish I had flowers to
give you like I'm honestly so grateful
that you're out there and you share all
your information and it's not an easy
existence I know I read about it so I'm
so grateful thank you for reading the
information thank you for reading the
books do you want to get a picture oh
sure thank
you I don't
thank you for coming I hope you enjoy
the food oh my
gosh hi what's going on who's this I'm
Jamie Jamie and this is my daughter
Amber Amber nice to meet you awesome
yeah how are you guys doing good nervous
nervous though no need to be nervous
we're only on 10 cameras maybe even more
oh my gosh but yeah just thank you for
everything Anthony I'm nervous don't
worry I'm always nervous from
meeting new people thank you for coming
though people I really appreciate it are
you guys are you excited about the food
so excited okay cool cuz I am let's get
a
picture
okay
awesome thank you for coming you guys I
really appreciate the support thank you
Amber
what's going on how are you nice to meet
you to see you I know I know third event
that I've come to thank you for coming I
made a potato wrap for the first time
and it was delicious oh my God amazing I
loved it loved it well thank you for
coming back again years on S years on
celery ju 7 years wao it's a long time
good that's amazing I've been seeing
some good improvements well don't stop
don't stop I'm trying to feel my face
keep it going yep keep it going you want
to get a picture
here step forward
here thank you for coming I hope you
enjoy the
food you doing how's this guy right here
Matt nice to meet you Matt nice to meet
you you want to get a picture yeah let's
get a picture I'm just with my wife I I
can
[Laughter]
tell thank you for coming thank you for
the support hey I know you I know I know
good to see you I like your medallion
thank you Sophie from Sweden oh my God
thank you for thank you for coming it's
so great to be here it take a long long
flight long flight y I did I did and um
I just want to say I'm an engineer but
I've studied to be a massage therapist
and I help people and they're so
grateful and I see like they come in
they need the help and then when I'm
done it's like they're they feel so much
better and I know how great it feels and
I can just imagine how you must be
feeling when you help people it's
amazing you're doing you're doing
incredible God's work amazing God's work
keep up all the work thank let's get a
picture all right um I have a quick
question we're going to have to get a
photo all
right thank you I know you got a
question but we got wel thank you for
coming in hello oh my God good to see
you are we getting a picture come on
let's get a
picture you're amazing thank you can I
ask you something do you have a tip
where I should direct the light
too can you direct it to your stomach
okay okay okay good good I will do ITC
how are you good to see you thank you
for coming where did you uh come from
come
from fantastic I'm I've heard some
healing food here I'm excited wait did
you have it already I had it already
yeah good good you're having it tonight
too tonight it's going to be just as
special so excited well thank you for
coming let's get a picture
yeah great
more thank you thank you
welcome good to see you good to see you
again yeah I know I know thank you for
coming you want to get another pick yeah
let's go yeah let's do it all right
um how'd you like the food oh it's great
I've been having it every day it's
awesome best thing I ever heard thank
you for the support yeah you're welcome
yeah I actually got it for that reason I
was like I got to like sell out the the
items so you know they know it's like
yeah good stuff it's healing
really really healing yeah thank you my
brother you're welc I'll see you
yeah hi can I yeah it's such an honor to
meet you your information has absolutely
saved my life and I was trying to think
of what to say or do and so I wanted to
get well you just said it saved your
life and that hits me really hard you
know cuz I know that that's very serious
you know people say that well this saved
my life or that saved my life they're
just using it as a saying but this is
serious this is serious so so I I made
you something it's so silly don't laugh
at me but it's just like a little fun
thing to
remember why is this silly don't read it
out loud let's get a photo it's very
nice okay it is far from silly thank
you thank you okay I'm going to hold on
to this s see if my type 1 diabetes is
reversible I'm sorry we have to keep
well you have to always keep strong and
keep doing what you need to do you can't
let it go meaning you can't let what
you're doing go very important okay very
important with with type one hi name is
Ana nice to see you nice to see you I'm
a dietitian so I love your passion and
you know the way you help people and
it's just like it strikes me like your
energy
thank you for coming I'm grateful you
came here all the way where did you come
from well I came from Studio City but I
was teaching nutrition still sometimes
people who live in the area they go out
less than somebody who flies across the
country so thank you for coming yeah and
I I love what you do it's just do we
want to get a picture this way yes yes
sorry just got to get the pen out of
my good had a pen in my front pocket
yeah what kind of pen this camera
two
more thank you for coming appreciate so
much
your hey nice to seeet nice to meet you
too thank you for last time I saw you
and you um signed my book you said x-ray
as I was pulling it away and put X on my
book and I don't know why do you
remember I don't remember but Spirit of
compassion um
did I say x-ray yeah you said x-ray like
that and put it
X maybe when you see your doctor or or
you know when you or your practitioner
you just tell them that you know that's
what I I did at the time but s so was
doing a message of some kind but um I'm
glad you're here okay I'm so glad too we
get a
picture ready
thank you for
coming amazing take
care oh thank
you hey how are you again um I know I'm
probably not supposed to ask you a bunch
of questions but I have severe chemical
sensitivities and I don't know what I'm
doing wrong and you went into the book
and you found the chemical sensitivity
section okay I feel like I'm missing
something like there's something I'm not
doing
right there's a lot of information there
but remember you have to read that part
where it says there's these toxins that
are floating
around and getting rid of them over time
that means you need to keep
diligent chemical sensitivities heals it
heals and goes away say that it goes
away and it heals okay do we ever see
our dogs again that that went to heaven
already do we ever see our dogs again
that went to heaven already we we see
our dogs when we
here
more okay do it
there I'll talk about that tonight okay
I will about seeing our dogs when we
leave here thank you oh my God hey
finally good to see you to see you
finally finally many years how many
years now um since 2019 begin 2019 we
start drinking celer using that's a long
time 2019 is a long time yeah and I've
never never missed a day never missed a
day of drinking celery juice yes oh my
God I'm so proud of you and heavy metal
talk smoody so my whole family you've
been having us um like having my parents
to here from all the sickness that they
have by COC can you send my blessings of
course I absolutely would let's get a
picture thank you so
much thank you for coming tonight we got
one here
yeah amazing so good to finally meet you
well enjoy the food good to see you good
to meet you
Al how's it going I got a little note
for you coule questions is that all
right Fus
mhm what does this name
mean we'll get some answers for you
don't wor
okay how patient do you think you are I
can be really really patient okay good
good okay it's going to take a
while good that that's good there's a
reason for that okay it's good stuff
it's only good
stuff heyas Anthony nice to see you
again nice always nice to see you wow
how are you good good good very happy
very excited yeah I am very excited
spectacular event here in Venice
California I mean come on that's I get
to see you I get to see everybody means
the world this means the world I I'm a
little bit nervous I have a little poet
for you to say something to you okay um
I get to inspire get inspired maybe my
English is got good enough out of the
ashes we rise in new with wisdom light
and sky so blue inside fall Noble bous
trustworthy and wise Together We Stand
where hope Never Dies who wrote this I
get
inspired I get inspired from from it and
uh I was thinking it's a good thing it's
a very special
poem very special okay and this is for
for you may maybe if you have lat is
this for me yes you can read
right okay BL your heart bias you sure
you want me to have this yes okay
yes the photo okay okay that's
good oh yeah sorry about Anon is is okay
when we when we point like with the
finger in the C okay come for oh yeah
thank
you hey nice to see you nice to see you
it was so nice meeting you the other
night we got a last minute ticket this
is incredible I'm glad you're here want
to get a picture another
picture incredible thank you for coming
enjoy the food
this is there's a lot to say though okay
we don't have that much time this is
like 10 minutes 20
minutes really yeah these questions are
bigger than you think much bigger one
though at least very big questions here
let's get a
picture I love you Anthony
you know that
right the the heaven name starts okay
with the heaven name starts with the
letter
n right this
way good to see
you good to see you again I know we've
only got a minute but I didn't really
get the chance to say it the other night
um just to express my gratitude and
appreciation for you and all that you've
done don't want to cry so I'll keep it
short but um you know from the moment
that the information the books literally
landed on my doorstep I mean mind blown
all on its own just divinely landed
there and how did you trust how did you
trust it was the
information and I know so many people in
the community can relate just reading
those words it's like that knowing
right and everything
and still blows my mind to think that is
just hanging around it blows my mind too
on a daily um and I mean I've talked
about it a little bit on social media
but it's it's really personal to me but
when I flipped the back and I saw your
photo I just connected and I just felt
like I knew you and I do have a kind of
understanding of what it is but like
your your essence was there and I could
feel it in the photo and I it felt like
I knew you and from that moment I just
knew like this is my purpose this is my
mission too and your mission is my
mission and I I just want you to know
I've got your back thank you thank you
means the world that you have my back
seriously can't thank you
enough smiling it is thank you for
having my back seriously truly the end
we're going to do Michael wants to do a
group photo with you cuz we're all Ming
not right now not right now you guys not
right now we'll get one though okay okay
okay maybe a little later thank you so
much have a good
night is that
it how's my thing
here all right it was just showing on
camera hello hey good to see you what a
pleasure thank you honor thank you for
the inspiration thank you for coming
yeah I appreciate that you were really a
Pioneer with um putting out channeled
medical texts yeah
I'm honored it's a strong word pioneer
thank you yeah means the world coming
from you okay yeah it's it's um where
I'm I'm I'm riding the wave with you
I'll take that I'm rid support let's get
a picture for
real may I put my arm around you of
course thank you so much I have a gift
if you want to receive it it's um a book
that I wrote that has you featured in it
do you do you have the book here I do I
do you have to give it to Joel if you
can
okay I'll trade it for thank this way
this way man I'm giving something
okay very pleasure to meet you thank you
so much for everything that you do nice
to meet you very nice to meet you is
this your guy right here one more time
my husband your husband amazing amazing
nice to meet you it's an honor thank you
for coming yeah of course thank you for
holding this and for having this place
for everybody yeah uh if I mean it
wouldn't be fun if if no one came and
you guys came where did you come from oh
we live in Studio City so we live here
yeah but still I keep on saying this
it's harder sometimes to leave Studio
City to come here than it is to come
from a plane on another state okay
sometimes thank you for coming okay
trust me I I I appreciate it I got a lot
of
respect great
two
more thank you guys oh
great thank you so much thank you thank
you I think it was on
video one more time okay you ready
yeah come in the Middle come in the
midle no this is
thank you
[Laughter]
okay hello hey are you nice to meet you
nice to meet you how are you Isaac hey
Isaac nice to meet you nice to meet you
too it's an honor thank you guys where
did you guys how far did you travel oh
just like 10 minutes away from here 7
minutes away amazing thank you for
coming do you eat here often we eat it
uh before but you know we've been
keeping it for now so thank you thank
you well let's get a picture yeah sure
[Music]
thank you guys enjoy the food please
thank you Isaac thank you you're a good
man what's going on thank you um did to
try the food oh it was
great my friends want to know uh what
determines whether someone's going to be
left-handed or
right-handed well it it it all depends
you know because uh it's more than just
what
neuroscientists theorize sure so it's
really about the supernatural it's about
God it's about The Ether that determines
it in the end's get very interesting I
love it thank
you amazing thank you for coming enjoy
than
you hey hi nice to see
you so excited to try the food really oh
my
God I'm excited to have dinner tonight
myself oh I'm nice and hungry so thank
you for coming do you want to take a
photo yes please here step right here
the like at this camera in this part
here right straight
ahead two
more amazing and let's get one here is
that your phone
yes amazing thank you for coming right
this way ma'am thank
you how you doing how you doing man
strong handshake right here handshake
thank you man thanks for coming problem
is there is there anything so needs me
to
know just keep on working hard okay um
don't get distracted if you get
distracted it's fine be lightart about
it but just keep on stay persistent okay
and cons and consistent okay brother
thank
you all right getting a little smile
there that's awesome thank you thank you
for
coming taking one quick second hold on
one
sec need a
drink e
[Applause]
epic congratulations this is Monumental
um years into my journey after
miraculously healing a lot of symptoms I
had an epic setback where I couldn't
properly apply her tools okay and what
helped get that happens thank you yeah
thank you even just affirming that what
helped get me out of that was
recognizing that I was under attack from
negative entities and negative energy
and when you it's just so helpful when
you affirm let's get a photo it's um
there's a lot of snares and tiger traps
and um a lot of negative crap out there
all right here we
[Music]
go and even lots of lies and things and
all kinds of stuff that throws somebody
off their healing process and they get
tricked or something you it's it yeah it
can be a real Twisted world thank you
for like staying with it staying with
the information healing that's all that
counts is you and your healing you and
your body okay that's you and and your
life is means everything and that's what
counts not all the [__] out there
okay thank you thank you
welcome hey hey nice to see you so nice
to meet you thank you for coming yeah I
flew in from mon gr wa that's amazing I
know Paris and I made both flights so
wow well I'm honored I can't believe
you're here have you tried the foods yet
well only tonight I'm here because of
the foods no I haven't I haven't tasted
yet okay but
yours it's my daughter who got me to
know about you oh my God she couldn't
come she has two babies at home and can
you tell her I I thank her yes that I
thank her for getting you here I know
she said you have to come so I did okay
that's incredible we have all your books
and I do the liver Clans I did four
times last year aot and my arms felt
like they were alive all oh my God I
love that let's get a picture
yes thank you for coming thank you see
you inside I'll see you inside I'll be
there thank you so hi those are really
cool boots thank you so much thank you
good to see you thank you for saving my
son's and ni life I I tried protocol at
2 months of pregnancy and um I was today
was my official uh due date and I gave
birth 13 days ago everybody keeps
telling are you going to tell your story
yes yes I you you
did it's going to inspire other people
this is so important yes because
postpartum is a very dangerous place but
I can tell you that you know whoever's
been trying to you know do negative
connotations onto the community it's not
it's not real it's not real a lot of
government sectors have been trying to
call me delusional for even partaking
like yes this helps so much my heart
there are so many people in the medical
M community and so many people worldwide
that have healed this and have had these
beautiful things happen I'm a two-time
heart attack Survivor that had these
heart attacks because of masses growing
that doctors did not want to partake and
help me with the protocol helped so much
and I only did it once thank you thank
you for doing all that you're doing
let's get a picture thank you so much
here step forward here oh thank you
thank
you two more thank you thank you I hope
you enjoy the food soome hey hi hi so
nice to see you nice to see you too
thank you for coming you're welcome the
last time we got a chance to speak was
about 12 years ago um we spoke on the
phone thank you for coming oh you've
been such an inspiration in my life and
and I follow your information and anyone
I meet I try to get them on all the
protocols my God 12 years ago yeah 2012
yeah that was the last time I spoke with
you yeah um summer summer July summer I
knew it I knew it yeah yeah I have a
very good memory this is amazing so it
was summer July
2012 yeah
um when we had the convers ation you
were
relieved that's it Spirit of compassion
says then when when they had the when we
had that talk 12 years ago you were
relieved yeah thank you for coming back
here you're welcome I brought you a
little gift I know the other day you
mentioned you like passion flowers so I
brought you this is very kind oh you're
welome here's Joel let's get a photo
here step right up here all
right thank you for coming
it means the world to
me Health with
Liz you got a book why do you have a
book so you can sign it it's the first
one it's an original copy here okay yeah
and this is for you this is a note for
you I'm just so
Greatful I'm just getting
emotional thank what's that a note it's
a
note it's just a long message come on I
can't say everything it's
just I thought you had the snow blank
trying to get I do
but you have to do everything you can to
try to let Spirit compassion
say yeah see and help
see I just it's just so you notice
there's a couple of notes people have
given me and I said there's too much
here one of the notes I said there's too
much here but there wasn't I just can't
read
it an hour ago an hour ago I can read it
not anymore oh some oh
yes I I honestly have like no words and
that's why I wrote the not yeah all
right right here
okay
okay step up here where right
there I'm going to see you later yes can
I give you another hug of
course the best
welcome hello hello hello I know you are
Seb oh thank you
um I've been to the last three events s
same s good to see
you um yeah we we healed uh debilitating
mental illness both of us I know I've
seen your post okay I
know you want me to sign this yes please
and sorry we're like all nervous right
now we're all nervous like right now we
um we met at the last event at the the
light blast and we like manifest each
other are you serious you know how
insanely that is it is cool right like
we both wanted mm partners and like
we're like literally like super similar
it's insane we pray to the angel of
relationships too all the Angels that's
incredible thank you it's really is you
know I really appreciate your support
you know that you two okay truly all
right wait I have a question Also let's
get a photo oh yeah Arwin Arwin Flames
real I might talk about that at some
point how about that because that would
be good okay thank you thank you thank
you get some good food okay oh we got to
get a
picture all right good good that's great
two more let's raise that up a little
bit there you
go thank you Sebastian thank
you what's going
on
um who's this this Steve Steve remember
okay so oh my God I don't know if you
recognize me Erica zier 144 yeah you
know it's me I W you I know I even blind
we're start calling you Tommy we want
you to know that snow blindness comes
after enough readings I know we want you
to know that our our um our faith in you
and and in so and in your mission and in
this information is absolute and we we I
hope that you always know that we're
walking with you every day thank you
support means the world and um you know
we're eternally At Your Service we work
for God and we're at your service means
the world sorry sorry I came so late way
darkness no no no no guys know I care
let's get a picture okay absolutely
there's your mark oh um I need to not
have my
phone oh sorry right catching your shirt
[Music]
yep taller amazing
the best I'll see you
guys is that it all right so so Mike you
want to get a
photo is it you and me just finished so
now we're going to head and enjoy the
fabulous four course medical medium
dinner let's check it
out amazing bring him in here bring him
in here come on
Jay right here it
is two this way here we
go all right man
[Applause]
than
ready e
po
you like
[Music]
she has to know why
[Applause]
very
is so good
[Music]
a
you
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
so
[Applause]
C
need
you
how many
ingredients
for for
is for
[Applause]
here
anyone love
[Applause]
it
got for
[Applause]
rot everything up
[Music]
by
for for
need a
be moving
[Applause]
got the
live here we go
[Applause]
[Music]
this first
[Applause]
[Music]
here we go you guys enjoying the
food it's it really
good you got the Nori Sushi Nori rolls I
see
that right the kelp
noodles amazing
[Applause]
woo all right all right you
got that's what the food does that's
what it
does that's exactly what
happens this is wonderful you guys
spacular night I can't thank you enough
I just have to thank everybody you guys
were busy thank you me okay saying that
I saved your life even though it was so
who saved your life you know and
thanking me for all the work that I've
done but I just have to thank you
sincerely thank you you know I know a
lot of people say thank you every day
and they're thankful for things but I
really am I am it's what keeps me going
each day it's why I wake up in the
morning it's you know it's why I stay
till 3:00 in the morning
working which isn't a good idea don't do
it it's why I eat so fast and stand up
in the kitchen and shove the food down
sometimes because I want to make sure I
get what I can get done because you guys
you guys are there you're there for me I
want to be there for you I'm fighting
for that every day and uh I see you guys
really are enjoying the food this is
amazing and you're comfortable right
you're comfortable yeah this restaurant
and I've said this before but has deep
meaning to me when I first walked into
this restaurant I walked into this one
right here all right my mind was blown
my mind was blown and spirit of
compassion told me there was a soul in
this restaurant it has a soul and I
haven't experienced that and I've been
in a lot of restaurants throughout the
years and I didn't experience that but
in here I did I never forgot it ever and
to think that years later over a decade
well over a decade that I'm actually
standing here right now talking to you
guys I mean come on right mind blown it
blows my mind big time it does how you
guys doing outside you guys doing okay
out there okay it's a cool night right
in California nice and cool instead of
124 like it was in
September you guys remember for the ice
packs yeah yeah well listen I want to
introduce you guys to somebody to two
special people okay uh Patrick hoskis
okay he is the COO of Cafe Gratitude so
here he is right here I want to
introduce him
and and I want to introduce Drew Ellis
okay now
these these two individuals these
special human beings here on planet
Earth made this happen they were totally
on board which is mindblowing all on its
own right and I said it before medical
medium recipes are amazing you guys like
medical medium recipes
right and that doesn't touch this it
doesn't touch what Drew did when you
take an expert sh
like Drew okay and the and and a
Visionary a Visionary same with Patrick
another Visionary and you actually take
the medical medum recipes this is what
you get in here it's it's why it's my
home I hope you guys come back someday I
hope so because you'll catch me in here
all right because I'm going to be coming
in here a lot I'll be maybe I'll find a
table somewhere in the corner you can
say hi to me if you feel like it or or
I'll just be like a fixture you just go
walk by me all right but anyway um Drew
C can I give you the floor for a second
is that okay sure um what was it like
what was it like when you first put
these dishes together what were you
thinking were you like that aw this
needs work right this needs work no
definitely that's not what I was
thinking but uh what I what I was
thinking is that you know as a as a chef
my job is to create food that will bring
in all kinds of people right and so it
was an interesting project to to use the
protocols of this of this you know way
of eating this this methodology and
incorporated into the food in a way that
not only would your community be
interested in in eating this food but
also the Cafe Gratitude community and
and people who are new to both
communities so that was the inspiration
to really sort of like H how can I make
this appealing to both sides of the
spectrum
so that is I really appreciate it we
appreciate it you guys right
and I actually I have another invitation
to everybody as well for for those of
you who know Cafe Gratitude uh we we
started in 2004 uh it was created by
Matthew and tery anglehart and what they
did at one point was decided that they
wanted to create a board game that
brought our attention to abundance and
gratitude so it was called the abounding
river board game and they created it and
then they decided why don't we create a
little raw food restaurant where people
can come and play that game and so
literally the the board game was the
tables and people would come in and it
was sort of like a Trivial Pursuit game
where you were ask you know certain
things about your life and about your
past and uh out of that evolved Cafe
Gratitude and our question of the day
which most of you may well some of you
may know about and I invite you to ask
each other the question of the day which
today is what in your life is unfold is
perfectly unfolding is unfolding
perfectly What in in your life is
unfolding perfectly so I have a couple
of answers to that question in my own
head but I will give it back to you
thank you so much for everything you've
done with us it's been wonderful I'm
honored I'm honored and that
question you know every single person
that heals using the medical medium
information that's unfolding perfectly
for them for me to get out of chronic
illness it really really speaks to me
you just drew honestly that's very
special just hearing that because it
really it in me it just ignites the the
sensations and the feelings of when
someone starts to heal how better to
unfold
something so that's that's beautiful
truly is right it's not an accident it's
not an accident and and it's not an
accident for all of us to be together
right now here in Cafe Gratitude right
now this day this hour that's not an
accident
Pat um Patrick Patrick's you know when I
met Patrick you know and and we were on
that Zoom together and we were talking
his passion for wanting to help his
passion for wanting us to put this
together was so strong I got off that
call and I was just saying it over and
over to my team I was like that Patrick
like he's got like this powerful
intention we can do this and then you
got on there was like aw aw yeah let's
I'm going to do this I'm going to do
this with it we're going to work on this
anyway I love you guys for it I had to
say it again because it's that special
to me just thank you thank you from all
of
us so so where are we are we on the
third course you guys what happened are
we on the third
all right all right I'm excited for you
I'm going to come back in a little while
just eat eat eat okay relax get to know
each other too how many of you guys are
meeting people that you didn't expect to
meet right here really here too amazing
are you guys meeting new friends then
creating new
friendships
[Laughter]
whoa that's powerful that is a blessing
that alone is worth coming right okay
okay that is just incredible that's
wonderful all right you guys I'll let
you eat I'll come back in a little while
all right and I'll see
you guys you're
amazing you got a little baby over
here for
[Applause]
I
that
[Music]
good
for e
spe
[Applause]
watch
e e
than
[Applause]
spe
[Music]
e for
[Applause]
spe
want
[Applause]
to
long it
[Applause]
know
[Music]
e
[Applause]
for
e
e e
[Music]
friend e
the
[Applause]
e
e for
[Music]
I know I know
know
[Applause]
e
[Music]
[Applause]
e
e for
[Applause]
[Music]
where e
[Applause]
of
[Music]
y
[Applause]
e
for
for for
a
go
[Music]
for for
tell e
[Applause]
your
got
some
[Applause]
don't turn
[Music]
hey guys we're back on the red carpet
with aw and we have just been having a
blast these past few nights aw I do have
to ask you why is medical medium it's
not a one-size fits-all can you talk
about that a bit Yeah in the health
world there's a lot of one siiz fits-all
that's how it works if someone believes
in one thing it's really restricted in
so many ways medical medium information
you could come in and you can can keep
all these Foods in there that you love
and do these and you can just take one
thing and start one thing only and
you're in it you're doing it and you can
customize and you can't customize in all
the other health Arenas but that keeps
the healing aspect down low you know so
what happens in the health world is
because it's one size fits all and all
these different Trends and diets and all
that and they make it look like it's not
one size pit all but it is and when you
scratch the surface sure you get one out
of a 100 people that start healing and
they Harald that as it's the Holy Grail
how about getting 99 out of 100 better
fast how about getting 100 people healed
a th000 people healed a million people
healed and it takes something that's not
on size fits all to heal a million
people like in the medical media
movement it takes it takes a lot of
different aspects different things in
order for that to happen and one is you
got to be able to customize you got to
be able to take the information to your
doctor and ask questions and have them
look at it because it's complex it's
medical information that's Advanced so
people can just take it to someone if
they want and they can customize it they
can read it they can use it in the way
they need to it's for every everybody
and that's why that many people heal
Millions heal on medical medium fact
just fact and that's the street cred
that's the record that's the track
record and so but you can't find that
anywhere else you just can't it doesn't
exist but what they do though when one
person gets a little better because
they've gotten rid of processed foods or
something and they start getting that
sluggishness out of their way they drop
some pounds it's heralded is the
greatest thing on the planet try getting
somebody who's in a wheelchair with
multiple sclerosis who has been to a 100
doctors and who's been in a wheelchair
for 20 years try getting them out of
that wheelchair walking and driving
again and healing and that's medical
medium information yeah and it really
truly is incredible the stories we're
hearing this over the past few nights
have just been incredible what is it
about medical medium food that's
different from other healthy food well a
lot of things are labeled healthy food
and over the years all the this garbage
was in so-called healthy food medical M
was Advanced information called the
shots on natural flavors being toxic
called the shot on organic flavoring
organic natural flavoring being toxic
any kind of flavoring is toxic and so
that alone is huge and there's been
copycats now they're like look out for
natural flavors now but it was done way
before with medical medium information
all these years years and it's that kind
of thing it's like the citric acid it's
like the yeast extract it's the yeast
it's all this other stuff that people
don't realize I'm just naming a couple
of things right now but it's about
taking it to a different level of
healing cleaner food Pure Food that's
just one powerful aspect of medical
medium yeah so many powerful aspects
really of medical medium but what are
your favorite top 10 medical medium
tools
it's a tough
one it is it could be as simple as
B12 simple as B12 and how to use it like
the medical medium shock therapies
that's one of my favorite favorite out
of the tools right there is the medical
medium shock therapies so that's one
right there like the propolis shock
therapy like the B12 like the zinc shock
therapy these tools alone are
lifechanging golden seal shock therapy
lifechanging for people like life or
death stuff like UTI that are killing
someone where they're literally on the
verge of sepsis and it's like and
they're doing the medical medium golden
seal shock therapies and they're getting
their life back nothing exists like this
out there in the health world nothing it
just doesn't exist and so the tools you
got the 28 day cleanse you got the 369
Advance you got the um you know heavy
metal Det detox cleanse you I mean
there's so many things you can use the
top 10 tools tough one heavy metal detox
you know smoothie celery juice still to
this day changing lives you heard people
tonight where the celery juice is just
it changed their lives right but you
know you have to just be open to it and
you have to be able to not be blind and
you have to be able to see it and
understand it and when you do your life
changes and those top 10 tools and with
the medical information top 100 tools
your life can change yeah it is so
incredible what is it when you say
medical medium is for all walks of life
can you talk a little bit more about
that to you people get stuck in their
belief systems they get wrapped up into
this belief system right and they're in
it and they can't break it they can't
leave it they're stuck it's like all
walks of Li of life in belief systems
Right medical medium is not this belief
system it's all these tools you can
bring into your life so whatever life
you're walking whatever your life you're
living whoever you are wherever you are
on the planet it doesn't matter you can
bring these in and there isn't this
crazy like set of rules that stops that
like the other belief systems that
medical medium is not and so it's these
tools you can bring in and change your
life with it's for everybody and anybody
and the other you know the other the
diets out there and the trends and
things like that they have so many
different restrictions it's not about
like for all walks of life it's just for
somebody coming in they're stuck they're
locked in this box and that's the way it
is here it's not it's for everybody
doing anything come on in try one tool I
challenge you your life starts to change
yeah yeah it's truly incredible the
stories we've been hearing are just
unbelievable really truly unbelievable
and it's so great that people are able
to travel now able to come out here and
eat this amazing food this evening lime
disease is a big one Li the lime disease
trap for all these decades tens of
thousands of hundreds of thousands of
women lost their lives because of bad
treatments for Lyme disease because they
didn't understand Lyme disease the
industries didn't understand the labs
didn't understand all the games played
with people all the different hidden
dirty secrets in the Lyme disease
movement medical medium broke that wide
open
people with lime disease and
neurological lime recovering getting
their lives back that doesn't exist
anywhere else yeah thank you so much aw
you truly are such an amazing human uh
the work you do changing lives all
around the world you just see it here
with the community It's amazing And
thank you for having me be part of this
thank you you're welcome yes now we're
going to go back inside and check out
the food yeah yeah
[Applause]
h for
spe
spe e
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
re
for e
[Applause]
[Music]
spe e
[Applause]
EX
the
[Applause]
e
[Music]
for
e
[Applause]
for e
[Music]
[Applause]
better
[Music]
e
[Applause]
e for
[Music]
[Applause]
spe e
like
[Applause]
[Music]
want
[Applause]
[Music]
IM
you
[Applause]
walk for
[Music]
[Applause]
you
you e
[Music]
[Applause]
spe
for
[Applause]
e
e for
[Applause]
spe
e
[Applause]
for
for e
[Applause]
it's
don't
e for
[Applause]
other people
us
[Applause]
it's kind of
off for
[Music]
hello
everyone uh we just want to take a
moment I hope everyone is having a
beautiful night I see you're on to the
smoothies already how are they
tasting amazing amazing well we have uh
someone that would like to share
something special with us this evening
so I'm going to hand the microphone
over dang
[Applause]
M
sh sorry I speak in German and um my
friend Fabian translate for all of you
we um
we are together in this world and we are
going the same way together and before I
met you I thought there is no one here
on this planet who is able to love me
and can love me
you showed me that it's different he
showed me that there is someone who can
love me he showed me that there is the
possibility to experience that
and there's no one I can imagine to go
this way
with she said yes
w
congratulations I don't I don't want to
take up too much of your moment what an
incredible moment that you shared with
everyone wow I've seen this couple at
other other medical medium events just
so beautiful you both just radiate love
and I just want to say thank you for
that we and congratul we wish you a life
of happiness love and lots of celery
juice as well abundance yes yeah
[Applause]
thank you so
much thank you for all for um for for
this and um to having this time to do
this um and sorry for my English
um but it was for my for me the right
time to to ask Julia and it's um for us
amazing to be here to be with you with
Anthony and to do this thank you thank
you
thank
you I think we should toast with the I
am precious
[Laughter]
now next pleas
yes thank
you what a moment beautiful
keep
e
e e
all right I think we can do
this
hey good to see you guys
[Applause]
you ready for a little
talk you can have eyes and they can see
fine
right and everything looks
good but yet there could be a fog and
that fog is what a lot of you guys have
been through which is the health
movement and the medical system system
too not forget that there's some fog in
there and you got good eyes you can see
but all these things are
there and they become this thick
fog all the different Trends all of it
everything from what
charcoal
colostrum list goes on right I can name
off a hundred things
but we'll just talk about some other
things too but it becomes like this fog
that gets in the way and maybe that's no
big deal for someone who feels
fine maybe no big deal at all for
somebody who just maybe needs to drop a
couple of
pounds maybe feel less
sluggish but when you're somebody that's
been really sick and really struggled
for a long time
30 years 20 years 5 years 6 months 6
months can be a long
time that
fog can seem death
defying it could
seem
depressing something that holds you
back you got eyes and you can see and
you could see fine but that fog can
really get in the way over time and
maybe you guys experience this
so when you're chronically sick and
you've struggled for a while in your
life it becomes like doors that end up
closing on
you it becomes a lot of confusion it's
easy to get
lost and I was told about that when I
was young and I was a
kid was told about that from Spirit of
compassion because all I wanted to do
was just go fishing in a pond ride my b
icle hop on my
skateboard that's all I wanted to do
also go in nature too as
well but Spirit of compassion would say
well we have bigger things to do we have
more important things to do there's a
lot of people out there that need
something and you know when you're six
seven years old 8 years old that becomes
a strange sound strange sound in your
ear cuz it really doesn't make sense
like what do people need what does it
matter and spirit of compassion told me
that someday there's going to be a lot
of people out there they're going to be
very sick they're going to be lost
they're going to be in a fog and you're
going to have to help them see
differently you have to help them see
things that actually can change their
lives move them out of that Darkness out
of that fog into the light of healing I
heard that when I was seven eight years
old and it was the most foreign strange
words I've ever could imagin to hear at
7 years
old it took a little while to care
because I didn't want to
care I cared about animals I cared about
birds with a broken wing I cared about
frogs with a broken
leg I cared about
caterpillars
dragonflies I would get so sad when a
dragonfly seemed weak and something was
wrong I would try to give it water and
revive
it and what happens along the way when
you're young like that and you're
hearing this information you want to
kind of avoid it but Spirit of
compassion said you have to care with
everything you have you have to care and
so I did everything I could to reach
deep when I was young and spirit of
compassion said the same way you care
about animals and the same way you care
about dogs and cats and birds and
turtles you have to care about people so
it's 7 years old I was like okay okay
I'm getting the hang of this I have to
care about people I have to see what's
going on and I wasn't
sick and I say it all the time unless
you've been sick and walk in someone 's
shoes will you ever know what it feels
like being that I wasn't sick that was
the next Hill to climb for me because
Spirit of compassion said somehow
someway you have to know what it feels
like you're going to have to experience
it in your Consciousness in some way
you're going to have to make that
connection to someone suffering just
because you're not there and you haven't
suffered like that
physically at a young age doesn't mean
you can't connect and make that
connection I remember seeing a wounded
turtle that was hit by a car it was
still alive when I was young I did
everything I could to save it I couldn't
save it was too injured shell was just
fractured it was weak and weakening fast
but I did everything I could and I beg
Spirit of compassion to send down light
and I sent that light with Spirit of
compassion into that turtle through me
and also to the turtle
direct just like the light blast and we
kept that turtle alive for as long as we
could as long as we could a lot longer
than it ever would have because it
should have passed probably within a
half an hour and it was alive for
weeks but that Turtle still passed away
because it was run over by a car so
badly but that was the moment right
there when I was like okay I'm awakened
I'm awakened we have to save people we
have to keep them alive we have to
recover them we have to bring them back
no matter what happens we need to do
that and at 7 years old I made the
connection and that's when I was
reborn I wasn't the same person as I was
when I was 4 years old or 5 years old or
one it was a rebirthing for for me to
make the connection to somebody who is
suffering and struggling but that was
that level now that I had to meet up to
which means I had to now live with that
that means that all through my days it's
all I thought about it took over my mind
my Consciousness and every time I had a
hard time with it about suffering in
people suffering as Spirit of compassion
was telling me this person has brain fog
and the term brain fog didn't
exist didn't
exist this person has neurological Lyme
disease did not
exist this person has this this person
has that it didn't exist hearing these
words hearing what was wrong with people
then connecting that to the suffering
and remembering about that turtle that
was suffering and making that connection
probably one of the most difficult
things in my
life but I had to get over these humps
and I had to live with it I would go out
into the woods when I was younger
alone I would sit out there and fall
asleep on the ground next to a little
campfire some rocks I would have there
that got really hot with the fire around
it and I would every time I heard some
twig snap or break I would say the
spirit of compassion
Sasquatch Spirit of as would say no no
Sasquatch a frog a
toad but I would be in nature and I had
to be there to decompress at a young age
to lift off that pain and suffering in
the moments because I was taking it on I
took it on at a young age people's pain
and suffering and it would fester and I
had to learn how to cycle it through
learn how to understand it learn how to
process it and guess what nobody
[Music]
cared nobody
cared my parents did but nobody in the
world cared they don't care about the
chronically ill and I learned that at a
young age nobody cared about the
chronically sick oh my God if you've
been sick for 30 years or 30 years ago
you know they care now because it's
clicks and likes and all that [__]
and then sell whatever you're going to
sell to the chronically sick because
boom cha-ching cha-ching the industry
changed completely
now but back then nobody even cared
about anything with the chronic Leo so
here I was young a child okay I care I
feel it I understand it nobody
cares and then I hear this
voice that's teaching me all these
different things things about why people
are sick
and and then the connection about
suffering and struggling and then
realizing just like I heard tonight
someone's driving now who couldn't drive
before that simple little thing how
important that is losing that freedom to
drive losing the freedom to even talk so
many people have been
there and then connect to that
understanding that my job all these
years has been you have to know what
that's like in some way you have to
understand it it can't be just words
from Spirit of compassion I have to
connect with it and that's what drives
me that's how I get up in the morning
and that's what drives me every single
day my life has passed by like this like
that because the spirit of compassion
all I've heard is a bunch of scrambled
eggs going into my ear about every
illness and every symptom and every
disease and everything else and it's
made my life kind of go by like this but
guess
what it was worth
it how many people
[Applause]
healed how many people healed how many
people recovered throughout the years
the fact that we're in here in Cafe
Gratitude in La blows my mind all on its
own I can't even believe it can't
believe
it you know I've talked about three
steps up you guys have heard that from
me probably broken record there he goes
three steps up two steps back right what
does it even mean right you ever think
about that you guys know what it means
though right you're moving forward
you're moving forward then you're kicked
back a little bit scared
[__] scared [__] you get kick backed a
little bit and then but but you're
further than you were you're further
than you were with your symptoms how
powerful is
that the healing process is exactly
that
it's a few steps forward one step back a
few steps forward two steps back that's
how it works when you heal even if it
doesn't feel that way sometimes you are
still healing you are still healing
I think one of the problems in the
Natural Health world right now to this
day right this second is they still
don't know why anybody's sick I hear it
every day out there this person knows
this this expert knows this this person
knows this this professional knows this
but at the same time none of them know
why anybody was sick what happened when
you found out why you were sick did
anybody in here find out why you were
sick
ever find out
why when you find out why you became
sick it's half the battle I talk about
that the other half is now just doing
the right tools and moving forward right
and and doing that and
healing the world of chronic illness in
the world of natural health is
still still in the Dark Ages
still in the Dark
Ages and when you find any kind of
resistance out there towards medical
medium information like
censorship and
social not a lot of comment here not a
lot of comment here getting kicked off
of here whatever it is means you're in
the right place and you're doing the
right
[Music]
thing because we're Advan ened
information is what we
are it's not what people think it's the
opposite of what's happening out there
it's the advanced
information is what it is and that's why
sometimes it can feel like my God am I
the only one doing this medical medium
stuff oh my God why is everybody on my
ass about it how come people are saying
why are you eating that way why are you
doing this why are you doing
that but it's Advanced it's a ahead of
its time it still is it's Timeless it's
in your hands you have it and you know
what's going to really piss you guys off
down the
road you guys are going to be like I was
doing that already I already
knew it's going to piss you
off especially when little tidbits are
being poached left and
right you already knew you're already
doing it
every
time you bump into a
wall and you think Justice isn't there
or you're not being heard God hears God
knows how many of you guys have had dogs
and cats that have passed
away how many many of you got dogs and
cats
now
someone back there on the red carpet
talked about that are we going to see
our dogs are we going to see our cats
are we going to see our pets when we
leave here 100 years from now 80 years
from now whenever it is and yes we are
they're going to be
waiting now I can say that not as a
psychic that's just saying it because
people want to hear it or
something Spirit of compassion told me
that years
ago that when you leave here your pets
are there to greet
you there's so much more than the
[__] down here on planet stress and
planet
Earth when you have this Advanced
information and you can move forward and
heal
and live a good
life it doesn't matter if someone really
doesn't understand it yet or if someone
doesn't respect it yet or if someone
thinks whatever some medium guy whatever
it is it doesn't matter there's bigger
things going on there's angels watching
over you I've had angels watching over
me you
guys I've had angels watching over
me I remember being in some tricky times
in my life and Three Angels
were by my
bedside and I know they're by yours
too I do there's many times I shouldn't
have even
survived been through some things in my
life but I'm here because of
angels cuz God was looking out because
the Angels were
there and I'm still here and I'm
standing here with you guys it's
mind-blowing I just want to say that
I don't say enough about the people who
look after loved ones that are really
sick I know there's some good people and
family members that are looking after
loved ones care so much they do
understand they do understand what it's
like they see the suffering they
understand it I I do want to acknowledge
that by the way I know I say all the
time it's like you don't know or
understand unless you walked in
somebody's shoes but there are some
people and family members that take care
of their other family members and they
care and they feel it they feel the pain
and they do understand I want to
acknowledge that by the way you
guys and maybe you know somebody maybe
you're somebody right now that
understands
that I was talking about the other day
yesterday I think it was and spirit of
compassion was talking about time and
how time works
[Music]
and how we're up against the restraints
of time and how we're under the law of
time and the rule the rule of time and
we're always faced with that all the
time there's a couple things I didn't
talk about though in that
moment is that any day you lost
here on this Earth because you lost it
to having to take care of your yourself
having to fight for your life having to
tend to your health or someone else
every day and every hour you lost comes
back to
you an S so told me that years
ago because the time you lost is noted
and
calculated it's added up by the angels
and by Supernatural
forces because the time you lost was of
the holiest time the holiest hours hours
of your suffering hours of you're
struggling hours of you taking people
who are taking care of people who are
sick hours of feeling like maybe you're
hopeless and you don't have the right
healing information no one understands
you you're not validated hours of all
those hours are protected by
God and they're placed aside and they're
gifted back to you at some point either
in this lifetime or when you leave this
lifetime gift it back to you in some way
shape or form or given to a loved one
either way that time is not
lost you bank
it because struggling in suffering is of
the noblest it's of the most holy it
has it is the most
important part of
existence it's not a throwaway it's not
a loss it's a gain and what happens is
when you're chronically sick and you've
suffered and struggled you're gaining
not losing critical to know Spirit of
compassion has told me that and wanted
me to tell you that tonight
it becomes a
vault of struggle of
Vault of everything you've been
through and it becomes the gold and the
Diamonds and the jewels of your
life it's not the diamond that you see
at the jewelry store it's much bigger
and greater than that that your
suffering is much bigger than that it's
the Holy
Grail it is the true true treasure is
your struggles and your suffering and
everything you've gone through it's your
true
treasure and it's
vaulted and it's
banked and it's there for you with all
the hours you've struggled all the
minutes you've suffered the moments that
you may know somebody that was on their
hands and knees praying to God wondering
how the hell am I going to heal how am I
going to get my life back how am I going
to go back to work how am I going to
live all those minutes are all protected
are all sealed up and vaulted for you
safe nobody can mess with it nobody can
touch it no matter what you've been
through it's your
legacy they're your
Jewels they're your Soul's Jewels
they're there for you when you leave
here they're even there for you here
now and they'll pop up when they pop up
when God and the angels say it's time
and you need them nothing is lost all is
gained from everything you've done every
single intention you put into healing
yourself is banked and
protected under the right of
God if you don't believe in God then
under the right of of a Creator under
the right of the
universe the universe is all you believe
in that's perfect it's fine nothing
wrong with
that and it's there for
you tonight we're going to do a light
blast and
[Applause]
and it's going to be a big
one I was sitting on the bench in the
back over there
relaxing talking to Spirit of
compassion telling s so I've had a lot
of readings tonight a lot of information
came through can you just give me a few
seconds because this light blast I know
is going to be really powerful really
big it's worth it for me to be laying on
the bench afterwards for a few minutes
way worth it wouldn't trade it in for
the
world tonight's light blast is going to
be similar to last night where you can
split the light if you need to some of
you probably remember that you can split
the light send some of the light to
somebody else
send some of the light to an
animal send some of the light to anybody
you want to and then keep the other side
also you don't have to do that the light
that's coming down tonight similar to
the light that came down last night and
it holds within you for a longer time
but more than that you'll be able to
possess it hold on to it and touch
somebody and some of that light's going
to enter
them you touch them on the top of the
head or on the forehead it's a great
place to do so the shoulders fine as
well but everybody's going to be glowing
when you leave here
tonight I'm just waiting right now for
so why can't you time this
right we're just about
ready so on the count of three we'll
take a deep
breath and then we'll release is
everybody
ready
wonderful one 2 three deep breath
in and then release
now
remember it's not a
contest the deepest breath doesn't
win could be shallow it could be light
breath a light one not a heavy
breath it's not a breathing
exercise count of three deep breath in
then release one 2 three deep breath
in and then release
we're just going to do the first one now
SSC says we're ready to roll and that's
not exactly what s so
said I'm a translator of s
so I try to talk a little hip but I'm
not but the words from SSC sound very
odd and it's
a very strange
way of
talking on the count of three we're
going to do a deep breath and we're
going to hold it I'm going to say light
as SSC sending that light what part of
your body do you want it directed
into I have to make sure you guys know
that is it your heart is it your brain
are you dealing with some kind of brain
issue of some kind emotional issue of
any kind do you do you want it right on
top of your head to your brain do you
want it in your
thyroid I noticed there were some
thyroid
nodules that came through the line
tonight do you want it
there do you want it on your
pancreas that's a spot too think about
it okay get
ready now we're ready
and the count of
three deep breath and hold it one 2 3
deep breath in hold it light light light
light
release uh 50 people 60 people that are
blocked get ready we're going to do it
again on the count of three one 2 3 deep
breath in hold it light light light
light
release that just cleared up a good 20
of
them some of you going to see the the
light really bright
tonight on the count of three we're
going to do another quick one one 2 3
deep breath in hold it light light light
release
how many of you seeing some light you
see it you see it you see it deep breath
in and out just one one breath going in
and out on the count of three one 2 3
deep breath in and then
release this one's going to be more
supercharged SSC says let's
go count of three 1 2 three deep breath
in hold it light light light light
release we have a few more people to
clear through who's blocked here
somewhere like
abdominal you got it right there okay
and you got it not this
time not this
time count of three one two three deep
breath in hold it light light light
light
release and we got one last one to go
there's one person
here I'm just walking around with s
so this is going to be full power get
ready and count of three
one 2 three deep breath
in light light light light light
release you guys are
glowing you guys are
glowing
[Applause]
success what's going to happen next
couple of
days you're going to have some strange
dreams I had one last night was really
strange a dog that passed away in my
life many years ago showed up in the
dream I was walking down a dirt
road was walking by a house there was a
woman on the front porch
playing with a
dog I walked in front of that front lawn
in that
porch and it was a dog that passed away
in my life decades
ago
profound I can't tell you what I felt
like woke
up and that was what happened with me
with the light blast last night
there's going to be a lot of things
happening like that in the coming weeks
and your healing is going to continue
it's going to be ignited and continue
and be stronger than it ever has been
after this life last I'm trying to
prepare you
because as you're healing you're going
to be like why am I
healing why am I getting such a
boost why do I feel better this is four
steps up
well you know
why we have an engagement tonight I
heard in Cafe
Gratitude congratulations on getting
engaged Julia
Thorston it's beautiful truly
beautiful I can't wait to watch the
replay on that
I think by now you guys all
know that you're very special
people but you really
are you have the most compassion out of
any community in the health world I know
that sounds a
little harsh or tough or a stretch but
it's true true it's true anybody in the
medical medium communities know they
know the
difference and they know the people that
they're communicating with and the
people they're
around always remember that there's
support out there and there's somebody
that
understands always remember
that back 35 years when I was doing
consultations back 30 years ago and 25
years ago when I was doing
consultations it wasn't like this it
wasn't this huge massive
Community I think somebody tonight that
was on the red carpet said they had a
consultation with me 12 or 14 years ago
or
something I thank them for coming and
being here
and she knew that what happened in that
consultation that talk with
me really
helped helped move her
forward there's a community now we got
to be proud of
it remember that when
the world makes you feel alone or you're
in it alone cuz you're
not keep that in your your heart and
soul anyway I love you guys
[Applause]
[Music]
I want to I want to thank Cafe Gratitude
I want to thank the staff here the chef
the
cooks the Sue
chefs the all the staff the
owners I want to thank
everybody I do and I want to go outside
because I didn't go outside before I
want to say hi to you guys out there for
a second as
well
hey all right heading out here for a
little bit just for a second here you
guys I missed you last
time you hanging out you hanging out
okay out here you got the heaters wow
that's
nice it feels good out
[Music]
[Applause]
here
incredible food was good amazing amazing
Christian food was
good all right all right that's what I
love to hear proud of all you guys
you're welcome you're welcome I can't
wait to
[Music]
eat I just I just can't stop at one you
know serving of nor you
know so I'll have to sit down and and
tank a lot of food you guys I love you
enjoy the rest of the night
okay and you have my deep respect please
know that by the way you have my deep
deep respect truly all right and I'll
say this last thing and I mean it I
don't take any of you for granted your
support your healing process your
struggles what you went through your
suffering all of it I don't take it for
granted please know that I care deeply I
love you guys and I'll see you
soon love you guys too I'm meline and
these gorgeous ones below and then this
is our son Noah oh hi Noah
Elana it is so lovely to meet you all
how are you all connected here um we we
actually met through the medical medium
community in the last few months um in
Southern
California wow that's incredible for the
kids to have some other medical medium
friends yes yes what made you want to
come out this evening into Cafe
Gratitude medical medium pop-up dinner
um I think it was just an amazing
opportunity to for a more intimate
environment to get to meet Anthony and
to get to connect with more of our
community as well and what are you most
excited about this evening uh to be able
to thank Anthony for changing our lives
changing our kids lives they're both
complete medical medium babies and
anytime we get together it's just so
Soul
filled you said you met through the
medical medium Community how did that
happen was it online Instagram how did
you how did you make that initial
connection yeah so there was um it's
actually another set of our friends but
um there was a very big California
Meetup Network
and then we were invited we happened to
be in California and got invited and
that's where we got to meet mine and
your daughter Finley and that was
January of this year but since then
we've met up a lot of times including
this one that's beautiful there's
something about connecting with the
medical medium community and that's what
I think even the last few nights we just
seeing how strong it is how beautiful
how uplifting it is for everyone to
connect and get together it's very
special yeah absolutely and it's been a
beautiful Journey like we we started
medical medium in 2019 so it's been
almost 6 years we're just reflecting on
that and you know our daughter was 6
months old when we first started and you
know we were at a place in our life
where we were exhausted we were burnt
out we were like struggling for some
health challenges and we came across
celery juice and then found medical
medium we did a 28 day cleanse and we
never looked back since then it's been
pretty special and our daughter's always
been always been a a big fan of animals
and she what she can tell us she can
tell us what she would share about
animals yeah um I told my family that
animals are my friends and I shouldn't
and they shouldn't yes oh are her
friends yes yeah that's beautiful do you
have any animals at
home I have caterpillar butterflies I'm
breing oh wow we're growing butterflies
yeah that's beautiful so at home how do
you how do you like the celery juice
you've tried the celery juice you do the
Smoothie as
well start our morning um with lemon
water with maple syrup and then I wait
15 minutes until CES and then again
H and is it beautiful that you've made
this friendship through the medical
medium
Community yeah yeah and what do you
think do you like doing the celery juice
as
well you like do it with your
friends and you're holding some
beautiful uh you've got uh drawings
there and also a little note is this for
aw yes
you would you like to read it or is it
something personal is it okay to read on
on camera okay it say hello medical
medium I love the green smoothie I like
Maple and my lemon water I have heals so
much thank you love Ella a this my mom
wrote this for me you know you guys have
awesome parents because I wish I was
doing the medical medium at at 6 years
old that's really cool can would you
like to read yours on camera you don't
know how to would
you and finle says good morning medical
medium I like my smoothie the green one
I love your mm pizza thank you love a 4
and a half wow wow and you have one too
here would you like to read it for you
you want someone else to read it for you
would you I read it oh she's doing such
a good job isn't she you proud of your
sister yeah
yeah it say hi medical medium what is
your favorite food I like the potato
with avocado Mas St with lettuce
scooping up I like your red glasses
thank you you love no eight four wow wow
can I have some high fives by the way
awesome awesome you're awesome too there
there's some strong high fives there I
think it's all powered by all that
beautiful food that you're eating how
have you healed as you know a family
some of your symptoms and conditions
that you had you know health problems
before doing the medical meeting
protocol yeah I think for me like I I
suffered from adrenal fatigue and and
burnout and it was uh it really
transformational to have uh the celery
juice in my life and and what it's done
for my energy levels and for my healing
alysa's had some pretty incredible
healing too of course I'm very grateful
to have a partner that does medical
medium with me um I've healed severe
lupus and my daughter had neonatal lupus
that we both healed together within a
year of doing medical medium um and I
healed it more with just a healing foods
versus supplements which was a really
fun thing to watch um and then our son
um has an eye condition called Dwayne
and that's healing as well with medical
medium and his prescription has gone
from plus 4.5 to plus two that's huge
yes yes and what about you how what
benefits have you found from doing the
medical medium protocol so I found
medical medium uh in 2021 and I was
super desperate I had all the kinds of
neurological problems adrenal fatigue my
family was tired of me saying I don't
feel well I don't feel well what's going
on with my health so I went Doctor
shopping doctor to doctor trying to
figure out what was going on um MRI came
back clean we couldn't fig figure out
anything and then I went to a naturopath
who did a viral panel and said okay well
you have epine bar um and the only thing
that will heal that is celery juice and
didn't connect to the medical medium um
but I had to do my own research and my
mom had actually read the first book and
she brought it to me and I put that book
down on the table that night and I
cracked it open I said I'm starting
tomorrow morning and I did and it was
February 2nd of
2021 and um this journey has been
miraculous ulous truly I mean I started
just because I wanted to feel better I
didn't know I was going to have the best
life ever because of it um so it's truly
incredible I've met the best friends um
I love my life I love my family I've my
whole family has reconnected over this
and I truly feel like what had started
as just healing my illness blossomed
into this fruitful Beautiful Life wow
that's incredible so your family does
the protocols
and it's brought you together a lot yeah
and I think that it just healed old
emotional wounds yeah so the soul like
all of the um emotional healing as well
like sometimes we think about the
physical and that's what we what we
really want to heal right the symptoms
but then we don't realize that it can be
connected to to the
emotional interesting talking to
everyone over these past few nights a
lot of people are saying it's very Soul
healing like you're saying as well yes
oh well I I don't want to keep you too
long cuz I think the kids want to go do
their mate and grade we should let them
do that wild blueberry cake here too
this is an mm recipe mm recipes they
love there
which yeah I love it do you make that
the wild blueberry well we're actually
very fortunate we have a medical meeting
manyu as well that for us so we found a
a community within the medical medium
that is so great amazing well thank you
so much it's so nice to meet
you thank you so much for talking to us
enjoy your evening and have a beautiful
dinner thank you so much Dad thank you
wow what an amazing evening and that
light blast was so powerful we are now
back outside on the red carpet though
and I'm joined with two of the dinner
guests this evening what was your name
again my name is bat yes and Kashi so
nice to meet you what was your
experience like with that life blast oh
it was very um I felt refreshed pretty
much I I kind of was like uh too much I
had so much food and I I felt myself a
little bit heavy but now I feel like I
think I have one hour drive and I can
I'm not going to fall asleep for sure so
I feel pretty light and pretty um
energized energized I love that yes and
what about you I think I start feeling a
little relaxed and I definitely can feel
that I'm lighter now yeah the last time
when I get it in Calabasas actually it
it was amazing I had beautiful dreams
like and I'm hoping this time is going
to be same yeah yeah now we've also got
a talk about the food what was your
experience like with the food did you
love it in there uh food was amazing we
had it at lunch we came here at 2: p.m.
well actually 1:00 p.m. and and then
because they were about to close at 1:30
so we had to catch and then we did try
that medical medium uh special menu and
the food was um I was um very surprised
and it was just easy eatable you know
and it was just like you know and I felt
so light anyways after having so much
food I could take a walk to the beach
and I didn't feel tired so it was nice
yeah MH did you enjoy having lunch and
dinner here yeah definitely you know
especially when you're are not cooking
it because cooking food is also takes a
lot of time and having this going out
and having a like medical medium healthy
food it's the best thing I could ever
dream of yeah yeah incredible and you
guys are somewhat locals from the OC
area so you can come back again yeah
definitely yep definitely I'm pretty
sure we're going to do it a lot like
maybe celebrating some like any holidays
here right that's such a good idea what
was your favorite dish uh I did like the
the sushi mhm and since it doesn't have
any fish any like a meat and it it just
tastes like sushi so it was with the
Wasabi and then the side yeah it was
very nice I liked it very much what was
your favorite dish yeah I like the sushi
as well and the second favorite is the
I'm trustworthy I guess the fajitas was
yeah and was the guacamole was the best
oh yeah it's incredible I finally had uh
the kelp noodles the papaya salad oh my
gosh it's so good I loved it yeah I'm
Noble one was also um it had a nice
potato and it was nice dressing it was
very delicious yeah yeah do you think
that Cafe Gratitude having these medical
medium uh dishes on the menu will help
people's healing Journey make it a
little bit easier for them and more
enjoyable I believe so I wish they had
more uh options specifically medical
medium yeah cuz I only saw like a five
or four and it's still already a good
start and I feel like in the future
maybe uh once they will see more people
are ordering them they're going to add
more options so definitely I'm excited
for this yeah yes what about you yeah I
think having it in the in the menu it's
already a big thing because a lot of
people who doesn't know about the
information they can see and try it and
maybe find it out like you know and I
believe that it's going to like the cafe
gred is the one of the first like places
have this menu I hope in the future
maybe the other places going to like do
the same and I hope the information
going to be even more spread it around
you know yeah yeah did you enjoy
connecting with the community tonight oh
definitely yeah we we had a wonderful
party in our table
so we just enjoyed we shared all our
experiences how you know how they some
people was I think uh someone was in our
table she was uh on and off with medical
medum for over 10 years we only only two
years so and we already can see it's
life changing experiences happening it's
just uh unbelievable yeah yeah would you
like to share a little bit of your
healing Journey since using medical
medium oh yeah so as I said it's been a
couple of years since we've been U
primarily focused mm medical medium um
diets and then uh and thank you thanks
to my wife actually I discovered mm and
then she's been very encouraging us to
stick into it believe in it I initially
was a little bit skeptical because it
felt like maybe it's another some kind
of you know like someone just said and
then she's just following someone else
and then I just like okay let me give it
a try as well and I right away started
feeling well I have healed um in general
uh per year I get sick like at least two
three times I used to get sick so since
I switched to Medical medium uh type of
feeding myself I I feel myself great I
haven't been sick for 2 years and it's
very incredible cuz I'm 37 years old for
the last like 30 something years I
remember I've been always a year at
least couple of times get flu or some
kind of coldness and then my wife uh she
healed so many uh health issues and then
also my mother
she had a chronic asthma issues she was
heavy on medic medicine and then uh now
she no longer takes any medicine only on
medical medium and she is already
getting much better she doesn't have any
more like a chronic illness more like a
seasonal little bit but we're working on
it so it's getting much better wow so
you introduced the whole family to the
medical medium information yeah I guess
so I did so I uh I found medical medium
information because of my own health
issues and I think my husband was seeing
how better I'm getting by using medical
medium because before whatever I did uh
whatever doctors I FL p i I couldn't
help myself anyhow so uh yeah he he
actually I I'm grateful that he catched
it right away you know of course he was
skeptical he was just taking whatever
food I'm giving to him and I think first
like um year and a half he was doing
just the morning detox and my husband
was uh addicted to caffeine and stuff
and he had the anges actually and with
the celery juice like it's actually uh
helps people to like count down I guess
like he's getting very understanding and
calm yeah and um yeah so me um I think I
get rid of over 30 plus symptoms yeah
wow yeah in 2022 actually I had some uh
issues and I went to one of the like
modern places to get the IV therapies
and and I was unfortunate that I got
poisoned with the heavy metals because
they they injected like five different
medications at that time and I think it
didn't work well with me yeah after
right after the IV therapy I start
having like very heavy symptoms of
poisoning with the heavy metals and
depression and panic attacks was the one
of them yeah and I remember then when I
started drinking celeres like on day
four I felt so much better my anxiety
start getting better and it was like
Miracle because it worked for me like
from the first day so I knew that this
was the
information yeah well that's incredible
and now you're here going out to dinner
at Cafe Gratitude connecting with the
community that's so amazing I just want
to thank you for your time for sharing
those stories I have to get to a other
people that are here as well but I
really appreciate it appreciate you
sharing thank you so much enjoy those
smoothies you're going to love them yes
yeah if you go this way and then we'll
bring our next guest
hi what is your name my name is Maddie
so nice to meet you you too yeah now
what did you think of the evening oh it
was lifechanging yeah it was such a an
amazing opportunity to connect with
other people um celebrate you know the
man that kind of brought us together um
as well as just the healing that we've
all done so uh I don't think I'll ever
forget it what was it like meeting a in
person gosh um you know I think a lot of
people have said this but
um he really is just so compassionate
and grounding and cares for people I
think at every level of his being um and
even in just the small inter
interactions I've had or the
interactions I've heard him have with
others uh that's just kind of the the
sentiment that I get and uh it was just
it was incredible I loved it yes and the
food this evening oh my gosh what did
you think of the food oh it's it smelled
amazing it looked so good um I I love
just how creative they got with the
meals um I think it's such a treat being
able to see these options available for
people um at such a an amazing level so
uh I loved it and I love that it's
accessible to all now do you have a
favorite dish um I didn't get to try too
many um but I the one that I did try was
the smoothie and that popped off that
was amazing this smoothie really is
delicious what was your experience like
during the LIF lost yeah so I've done um
I've been following medical medum for 8
years so throughout my time um I've gone
to every event this year in California
and then also so I've done like virtual
light blast and things things of that
sort and I feel like this
was the most powerful one that I've been
able to do um to where like I feel like
I could see the light and feel the light
um and so I just I feel grateful that I
I got to do it so yeah uh do you think
Cafe Gratitude having these menu options
available the medical medium dishes will
help people's healing Journey make it
easier and more enjoyable for them oh
absolutely and it reminds me of
something that Anthony Williams says
where you know we only have so many
meals in this lifetime and I think you
know in any of those heals if meals if
we can bring that healing into it it's
so important every everyone counts and
so being able to have a place where
people can go and and enjoy meal with
their loved ones um at such an
accessible way uh it's it's a
GameChanger so how has the medical
medium information helped you heal yeah
so um like I mentioned I've been doing
this for eight years and I came on to
his information because I had a lot of
severe mental health issues um you know
I'd wake up and feel just severely
depressed and anxious but not really be
able to pinpoint why I felt that way it
wasn't like an outside factor or
anything and and I just um I remember I
was going through a heartbreak you know
as we all do breakups girl you know and
I'm in the bookstore and I'm soul
searching and I I I actually look on my
phone and I'm like what are the top
books right now in this space and I make
eye contact with the first book with the
lungs and I'm like that's so interesting
that it looks like that and I look up
from my phone and I make direct eye
contact with the book and so I kind of
took it as a sign I was like okay let me
take it and just immediately I resonated
with it and um with time I've been able
to incorporate so many of the healing
protocols um to the point where I really
feel like I've moved forward in feeling
more mentally resilient um and just have
a more positive compassionate out look
on life and I think if anyone has
struggled with like a mental health
issue like that's so invaluable
especially if it's been your day today
and and there's so much freedom in that
and so I I feel like the trajectory of
my life has changed so I I feel so
grateful wow that's incredible thank you
so much for talking to us I really
appreciate your time tonight yeah thank
you so much have a lovely evening yes
hello how are you I'm good and what is
your name my name is Terry so nice to
meet you did you enjoy the evening
tonight oh it's fantastic yeah really
really fun yeah what did you think of
the food the food was was really really
good um just amazing to see that sort of
a range of flavors in in a medical
medium type meal I'm used to things
being quite a bit more basic and rustic
in what I cook you know so uh it was
quite it was quite good um the first few
dishes were you know really clean and uh
um and just really cleansing and you
could feel that and then to me the L the
latter the last dishes but the last
couple dishes you know they were a
little richer and and filling so I I
enjoyed it yeah do you have a favorite
dish favorite dish I think they're
all they're they're just different you
know it's sort of like picking a
favorite child or something like that
you know um I mean you know the
the the sushi was was very very clean
and it just sort of went down very
nicely cleanly on the pallet um of the
I'm not a chef okay so I might be
completely bungling words on this um uh
what came after that it was
um the kelp yes the kelp that also was
very clean it had a nice it was kind of
crunchy and nice and tasty and then we
had uh the the was it
the the I am Noble they had a bowl and
the fajitas oh yeah the bowl and the
fajitas yeah the fajitas those were also
clean but just a little bit richer and
nice and the and the um uh
the the the little oh the tortillas
tortillas yes those were fantastic those
were really great they were so amazing
what what was your experience like
meeting
aw um
very I mean very moving very moving
experience
um uh let's see I
asked my wife wanted to give him
something cuz my wife's kind of a nerd
and likes to do research and such and um
wanted him to look at some of the
research that she did and so she wrote
something up and I gave and that and I
thanked him for some of his podcasts
that he's done actually the telegrams on
on angels that I found particularly
meaningful for me uh because for me
I I I used to pray um like actually
starting around the age of five until
around 20 and then I started getting
kind of confused a little bit about what
I should be praying to because it seemed
like there are people from all sorts of
religions that have deep
meaningful uh thoughts about what they
believe and I didn't feel like those
people were any less or more valid valid
than the belief system that I was at the
time following and so I kind of stayed
on the sidelines for a long time until I
heard that the couple telegrams he had
and somehow it that clicked for me on on
angels and praying to the angels and
then so I started resuming that again
and it's been a long long Hiatus when I
really kind of stopped or felt very
insecure about it so
um so yeah those are some of the things
I mentioned and I think I mentioned to
him if he had any idea or if SOC said
anything special and he said he was just
he was just very I was Floyd he was just
very very
nice about communicating what SOC had
said
he's um something that I
was you know a smart guy and you know
keep doing things I honestly don't
remember it was a moment you have to
watch the live stream back and get that
you know that's right yeah exactly I
would have to watch it again to know for
sure cuz I could say now and then I'd
watch the live stream and say wait he
said that you know that's actually what
happened in the M yeah yes exactly it
can be a bit of a blow yeah yeah and
what has your medical medium Journey
been like would you like to share a bit
of that with the community watching um
sure I mean my medical medium Journey
has been mostly just sort of watching my
wife who's the canary in the coal mine
for me because whenever Anthony speaks
of ailments basically she's kind of felt
them all you know it doesn't matter what
you know at some point she has felt any
one of those number of ailments
and um and I've seen how helpful it's
been for her because she's done we've
done so many different other things and
tried so many different other things so
um at first that was the main thing and
then because I saw the benefit to her I
started doing some of those things like
the lime water and the celery juice and
the heavy metal detox smoothie and
eating eating cleaner and um you know
and then gradually find tuning in and
getting more knowledgeable about what to
do and but finally toward the toward the
end I I had a full mouth reconstruction
done by my brother who was a
dentist is a dentist and um but I kept
losing caps anyway um cuz he would cap
my teeth and they kept coming out anyway
I lost a bunch of them and
um as as a result you know I I would was
I saw a few other dentists who said that
it they didn't see any reason that it
would stop unless I did something more
aggressive and so or do something
different because they were just they
still kept coming out and so I decided
to finally adopt some of the protocols
and that those finally worked so um
those have been really really helpful um
I would hardly say I'm out of the woods
and I you know I'm hopefully not um you
know going to make make a two steps
backward move on you know cuz he talks
about the three steps forward two two
steps back so um uh that's been really
helpful that's kind of been the main
thing oh that's incredible well where's
your wife this evening is she with you
here or is she watching from harm or
she's watching from home she she um has
a tendency to need to eat very very low
fat and she was concerned whether the
dishes would be sufficiently low fat for
her and so um she decided rather than
take somebody's spot she would just stay
home wow can we say hello to her before
you go hello Vicki yeah hi well I'll let
you go thank you so much for your time
really appreciate you you're going to
talk to the next person now
hello hello oh hello again yes so we got
to get your reaction on the evening how
was the food oh amazing loved it yeah
what were your favorite dishes for me
was the sushi and the burrito bow
um yeah the food was amazing everything
was so good but I think probably the
sushi yeah but the sushi I ate so many
of them yeah Sushi was incredible what
was we spoke to you before meeting aw so
what was your experience like meeting aw
this evening oh my God it was amazing it
was just like a light and such a happy
moment it just felt amazing yeah what
about
you same here is it was amazing just
being so close to him it's just I don't
know something like the um energy in the
room everything it was you know I I
can't even words cannot describe it's
just amazing yeah wow wow and I've got
to ask you what was the experience like
with the light Blast for you both oh my
God uh this was the most uh intense time
at Culver City I felt it but this is I
just I get always numb in the hand and
tingling in the feet and then I always
feel released I wonder if anyone else
feel like relaxed I always feel anxious
before and I feel lighter it's amazing
it's wow what about you yeah this one
was really I I really felt it yeah my
hands um they're still numb from the
light blast it's just yeah this one was
a really strong one yeah well I'm so
glad we got to quickly talk to you again
after your meal it was so nice to meet
you this evening enjoy that smoothie I
will this was delicious already sampled
day my mom finished it
already yes good stuff well thank you so
much for stopping by bye we've got
another couple to talk to hello come and
have a stand here I'm Danielle daniielle
Wendy nice to meet you I'm Danielle nice
to meet you I see you've got the book
there I do yeah yes is that the first
one you bought no this is like maybe
maybe the 30th one that I bought I give
them all away so oh isn't that beautiful
that you give them away you help people
Hil that's what this community is all
about right it is it totally is we we
had PE a person buy us tickets here
tonight from Germany we never well we
did meet her in this
second uh get together in Calabasas but
yeah it's the only way we could get here
was have someone in Europe buy us two
tickets cuz we couldn't give them here
in the United States oh that's
incredible incredible well what did you
think of the evening then oh it was
fantastic from the start to the finish
everything was just magical yeah the
life what about the food as well food
was delicious if we could replicate what
they did here at home I'm never going to
eat out again or ever be tempted to eat
out ever again that's the key right yeah
no it's just so delicious the food did
you have a favorite dish from this
evening um I like the sushi yeah the
sushi was Dynamite is it Sushi all the
way yeah hands down hands
down and what was your experience like
meeting aw this evening
he just warms my heart yeah it's just
like Father Figure you know the the warm
cozy cuddly bear that wants to just hold
you and keep you feeling safe and um the
light so if if I can imagine what it
would be like to walk with Jesus Christ
on Earth it would be this cuz I you know
we're standing next to Anthony it's a
different feeling like it was to have
the Divine technology of God like right
behind his ear and we're here and able
to hear messages from Spirit is quite
incredible yeah quite incredible yeah
quite incredible what did you feel when
the light Bloss was happening this
evening um I shared it m so uh we have a
family pet that's my sons and they've
been like Pals and he's got a little
cough and he's the older dog so just
knowing that the you know this light was
being shared with not just family
members but with the pets and and and
just Joy yeah
peace well I you know I felt it really
in my I directed to my brain and I could
feel it trickling down through my face
like tingling down through my face and
so uh and I also shared it with my son
and his his girlfriend just had surgery
today and so you know sending them some
light and hopefully that helps the
healing process yeah so that's beautiful
how did you first discover medical
medium I have always loved health and
seeking had gone through some things in
my life and um it just appeared
angelically I believe you know it's just
like it's just there and I was intrigued
and so so I started to look into it
little by little and then just kind of
evolved started doing celery juice and
hmds now we have a routine where every
morning we get up and we do the the the
protocol straight on through so it's
been beautiful yeah what benefits have
you found the benefits I found were just
the skin the skin healing and clearing
up and uh sinuses was the big thing for
me I had sinus issues bad sinus issues
and those issues are now gone I can ask
I remember actually the day that I was
able to taste food again which was quite
profound spiritual experience like
losing taste is just like I didn't like
that at all yeah it takes a vital part
of life away from us flavor of life and
I got that back from the information
celery juice hmds every morning texures
every morning
yeah and then trying to stay fat free
and that's the big challenge for for us
moving forward is staying fat free so
I'm really give it a shot I'm so glad
that you got your taste back so that you
can enjoy this beautiful evening it was
so beautiful tonight and it was it was
it was gorgeous I wish there was a
little I'm trying to figure out how they
made these uh these dishes here I can
really figure that out we we we got
something going there cuz we need this
like a Cafe Gratitude on the East Coast
yeah like Wilmington North Carolina
please happy gratitude come to
Wilmington cuz they would be very
successful there I know they would be
well maybe this is the start of
something else to come let's put that
out there oh for sure good abolutely and
so it is well thank you so much for
talking to us we're going to wrap up the
live stream I'll let you head out over
here but thank you have a beautiful rest
of your evening wow what a magical four
nights Cafe Gratitude medical medium
popup dinner collaboration we're here in
Venice this evening uh we just had such
an incredible time so many beautiful
people came by to talk to us and we so
courageous and kind to share their
stories with us uh thank you so much
thank you for having me here I hope you
all enjoyed that watching this at home
uh that's the end of our live stream
thank you so much