hello
yeah this is fly you flying wall
where are you you're a fly too
where's your where's your wall you don't
have a wall
you're a fly in a tent where
where in a homeless place really
well what are they eating there nothing
someone got a candy bar and someone gave
somebody a milkshake
a week ago really well that was generous
well i'm a flying wall here and they got
plenty to eat but they're complaining
they keep on saying that potatoes are
boring
uh-huh they're doing the mono cleanse
and they said they hate bananas
what you're homeless person oh
they would like bananas do you think
they would do good with whole
bunches of bananas and lots of potatoes
they would would they be happy oh they
would huh
would they complain about their kidney
problems because
the person i'm watching right now got
kidney disease starting
and they got kidney disease from eating
meat and lots of eggs
yep and the only banana they ate was a
banana split
because i watched them eat a banana
split and now
they're all complaining uh-huh that
they're afraid to eat a banana for the
mono cleanse
uh-huh oh i watched them eat chocolate
for months
yeah they lots of chocolate lots of meat
lots of eggs uh-huh even some candy
what's your person doing in the tent
well you just flew to another tent
what did they eat oh they they haven't
had really anything they've been going
into dumpsters
they're dumpster diving they had a piece
of pizza last week huh
well i got people here they yeah
i got a lot of complainers i don't know
this mono cleanse i'm hearing about
uh yeah lots of complainers uh-huh
okay well all right okay i
i gotta go i gotta go
well the phone's ringing again
go fly on the wall uh-huh yeah i'm in a
house right now
i'm on the wall uh-huh i'm in the
bathroom
yeah i slipped into the bathroom with
the person
yeah i'm on the i'm on the bathroom
mirror right now
and they're on the toilet uh-huh
yeah they say that the uh-huh
they say that the banana or the potatoes
given them
problems with their bathroom but i've
been a fly flying the wall in this house
for a long time and they always have
bathroom problems
yeah and they said they're getting
bloated from the potato but
they're always getting bloated i've been
a fly here for months
uh-huh yeah i'm in the bathroom now hold
on the person's going to bathroom i want
to listen
yep sounds about normal
i'm hearing lots of squirts and lots of
bubbles
when i'm hearing splashes in the toilet
uh-huh
yeah it sounds like the normal thing and
now they're holding their stomach
because something's hurting in their
stomach i
don't think it was the banana they ate
because i've been watching this on and
off for months
yeah they have all kinds of things they
eat and they're always in the toilet
uh-huh all right all right i gotta go i
gotta go
okay all right bye
day three the mono cleanse challenge
yeah let's go hey guys i'm happy to be
here
doing the mono cleanse challenge we're
day three
do you have your homework
have you been doing your homework
if you don't have the book i feel bad
for you
okay we're live right now live on
youtube live on facebook live on tick
tock live on clubhouse
all right make sure you have your
homework take advantage
the 51 off amazon.com us blah blah blah
amazon.com us blah blah blah 51
off beca i i say it so many times
but it's it's it's an opportunity
to make sure that you got this
incredible medical textbook so you know
how to do these things so you could do
the mono cleanse
so you could do the heavy metal detox
cleanse when you want so you can do the
anti-bug cleanse you could do the 369
the tools are here and then learn about
things to take and do
to help you with your condition it's
a legendary book at this point out there
saving lives take advantage of it
good to see you guys happy to be be in
the
mono cleanse so what are you guys doing
on the mono cleanse who chose what did
you guys pick the papaya did you pick
the banana
are you doing your celery juice how did
you like the lettuce
we're gonna talk about transitioning
transitioning two if you want to stop
the mono cleanse
or if you're starting the mono cleanse
today maybe you'll start today
and you'll do the next three days and i
won't be doing the cleanse with you but
we'll do the next three days maybe i'll
do it anyway
and this is such a great thing you know
what happens is we
take for granted the amount of
crap we shovel down the chute
we take for granted the amount of fast
foods
fried foods all the chocolate the coffee
we take for granted all this stuff we
take for meaning we take for granted
that we're just
we're just doing we're doing all the
vegan pizzas and we're doing the fake
cheese and the vegan cheese and we're
doing all the soy products and then
we're doing
all the almond milk and we're just do
we're eating whatever we want
and then when we get sick and we get
sick
it's like well what was it what happened
i don't get it everything was going okay
everything was going fine everything was
okay but now i'm sick
now i'm sick all really censored bad on
facebook today
and you know and this is how it works
you know good to see you guys coming on
and what happens is if you go hungry for
a little bit
and you start to do something really
good for your body
and you're doing your bananas and you're
doing
almost lost these bananas you almost hit
the ground you're doing your bananas
you're doing your papayas you're doing
your lettuce
and you start getting hungry and then
you're whoa this banana tastes good whoa
this papaya tastes good
whoa and then your taste
buds start to do some healing
and what does that mean your taste buds
start to realign what does that mean
your taste buds start to do some healing
what does that exactly mean you guys
that means your cranial nerves are
starting to realign
and heal the mono cleanse
helps to realign cranial nerves think
about that
you know how powerful that is we blow
out our cranial nerves
with over senses over sensing over
sensitivity
eating this and that all this flavor
boom boom boom boom boom
and we blow out some of our cranial
nerves we blow it out with caffeine
we're blowing out our cranial nerves
that way
and we're realigning cranial nerves
that control all the different senses
right and the taste buds and everything
so
really this is really in a great
opportunity a great opportunity to do
some good healing
and to move your body forward okay and
the mono cleanse is a wonderful thing
because you're removing
you're removing poison but still eating
removing poison and still eating you're
getting rid of insulin resistance
and still eating everybody doesn't know
it
but their insulin resistant jacked
up bad they're like insulin resistance
everybody walking around is an insulin
resistance
okay you go into a place where there's a
crowd of people
just everybody's boinked out with
insulin resistance
everybody's got the insulin resistance
their pancreas is on overload
pushing out insulin left and right
because they have so much
fat inside their blood you can't get
sugar in your cells
sugar that you need in your cells
because you die
without the sugar did you know that you
can't live without glucose did you guys
know that
you know that you know what's funny
i talked to somebody the other day right
okay
old friend who's a doctor right have
been talked to in
25 years and they're like aw
i got a patient who is doing this
this this carnivore diet thing
and i'm like and they're and they're
saying and
i said what's in the diet tell me what's
in the diet this is really important
what's in the diet is um all the meat
of course and then what's interesting
what's in the diet is also like honey
they put honey in the carnivore diet now
they're putting honey in there
guess why because you go
that's why there's honey in the keto
diets now
there wasn't hot honey wasn't in the
keto diet did you know that you guys
honey wasn't in the keto diet okay honey
honey wasn't in there
nor were some berries nor were some uh
avocado wasn't even in there right
nuts and seeds weren't in the keto diet
but they're putting all the sugar in
nuts and seeds have sugar in it not just
fat but there's a little sugar in it
avocado's not just fat there's a little
sugar in it right
they're putting all the stuff in there
because you
can't you can't live on a keto diet
a real keto diet where you go into
ketosis you'll die
yeah you don't believe me people have
died who adhered to it to the
tooth and nail the people who didn't die
binged
on carbs and then went back on their
keto diet for a week and then binged on
carbs then went on a keto diet for a
week and binge on carbs they had to
binge on carbs back
20 years ago the reason why they had to
binge on carbs because if they didn't
get sugar they would actually lose their
mind and just start going down hole in a
rabbit hole right
and so keto diet changed it's not just
meat
and a non-starchy vegetable or just meat
alone it now
changed into put all the sugar in it but
keep it the keto name how stupid is that
because you can't go into ketosis
the point is is that your brain runs on
glucose
but everybody's got the insulin
resistance everybody in keto diet land
has insulin resistance i'm sorry they
all have insulin resistance even if it's
not measurable
to a degree yet because your a1c isn't
jacked up yet
they still got the insulin resistance we
walk around with all this insulin
resistance
that's what we do you guys if you're
doing the mono cleanse
you just got rid of insulin resistance
bomb gone boom gone
gone that's what happens you lose your
insulin resistance
and when you lose your insulin
resistance your body has a chance to
heal
and when you get the fat out of your
blood for a few days your body starts to
heal you start to cleanse
that's what happens health is good to
see it
you know you start to cleanse on tick
tock when you get rid of those
fats for a little bit you start to
cleanse
because you're not even battling insulin
resistance anymore
here's what we do here's what we do on
planet earth we kill our pancreases
that's what we do
we're taught even with healthy
professional healthy diet people out
there
we're taught to destroy our pancreases
kill our livers
we just do it slower because you get off
of processed foods you get off of fast
foods you get off a junk food so you're
slowing down your kill
process that's what's happening
and then you're working out you're
working out to counter
the junk you're eating or you're working
out to counter the healthy foods you're
eating that still
fill the fat that's giving you insulin
resistance foods that are still killing
you
diets that are still killing you you're
you're working those diets off
you're doing your exercising right
you're keeping that death
death level slower
but what happens you guys is in the end
you're still battling all the fat
because everybody's trying to fat
themselves of death
they become the fat yourself the death
robot you know like no
families off their death robot that
let's help to death myself the death
robot
fat fat that's good for you need fat
need omegas need fat need fat
hey i read an article fat fat fat you
need fat um healthy healthy article
you need fat you need fat so we're just
trained to do the fat thing and pat
ourselves to death
and that's what we're trying to do but
you guys if you're doing
the mono cleanse that robot's hard to do
i got to tell you
it's hard to do because it's a it's a
ride listen
it's hard to do because the robot is so
so real and it's kind of heartbreaking
i do it in a joking way but it's hard to
do because it's heartbreaking
because you got a whole bunch of people
out there losing things losing their
pancreases over time
getting diabetes a1c starts going up
there they're getting chronic illness
things are going wrong
losing their kidneys losing their hearts
getting strokes and heart attacks down
the road because they're fatting
themselves of death so when i do that
robot on that i'm like thinking about it
well it's sad
here's the thing right so the bottom
line is okay is that
when you're doing the amount of cleanse
you're cleaning up the mess
and that's what's good about it so you
guys got your textbook i hope you got it
hope you started reading it hope you
learned about it
we're day three of the mono cleanse
challenge we're gonna talk about
transitioning
gwen says i love that on the mono
cleanse potatoes and lettuce
i am healing and detoxing without losing
my energy amazing
amazing exactly
exactly you guys elizabeth seriously
though i can smell
fresh air it has a scent
i didn't appreciate smelling but now i
do because
what happens is the minute you get rid
of all that over sensitized stuff
right for a few days
the minute you get rid of the vinegars
the minute you get rid
of all that crazy you know vinegar the
vinegar on all your even your vegan hot
dogs the vinegar on all there
all your chocolate right all your
chocolate all your coffee
and caffeine all your different vinegar
and sugars that no one even realizes is
on all the different foods out there
right that's a sushi
i'm just grabbing whatever i can even
when you get rid of all that
salt right and
you you get rid of all that salt you
know
you realign your cranial nerves guess
what your cranial nerves are you guys
guess what they are vagus nerves
how about that right trigeminal nerve
facial nerve right your nerves
the cranial nerves get realigned and all
of a sudden
things start getting better and things
start getting better
and that's a key the only i got to tell
you
to that last comment about smelling
fresh air
we're at a place right now in the world
where the chemical companies have
brainwashed
most of the human beings on this planet
to spray and use their chemicals
daily perfumes cologne scented candles
air fresheners aftershaves
scented products detergents and fabric
softeners
have dangerous chemicals fill the
dangerous chemicals from dangerous
chemical factories
and they have taken over you can't go to
a beach without smelling everybody's
crap coming off of them
there is no smelling fresh air you got
to find a place nobody's around to smell
it
and you're lucky if it's not blowing out
of somebody's dryer somewhere it's we're
at a point
now where they're they're trying to take
out people by by doing the chemical
thing to such a degree they found a way
to make sure all the products have it
they found a way to kill the environment
through this process of fragrances
no one's talking about it as the only
one talking about it for years
still pretty much the only one talking
about unless someone's you know heard
the medical medium podcast at apple
podcast on fragrances
but we're we're at a place now where
clothes that are that you want to order
and buy
or something you go into a store there's
it's everything saturated with air
fresheners and scented candles
everybody's got it all over them when
they they eat everybody who thinks
they're healthy
too it's like oh i'm so into the
environment
i'm so into like you know sustainability
and environment and health food and
i'm into this and that and oh i'm just
gonna write my camp light my
scented candles with my friends and i'm
just gonna
do my air fresheners and spray more
perfume all over me and
not that the perfume ever went anywhere
that you sprayed a month ago it doesn't
go anywhere
you spray perfume on you a month ago
it's on you the same
it's on you the same it's like you smell
like that for the rest of your life
unless you clean the stuff out of your
life the point is the chemical companies
found a way to get into people through
all their chemicals
and it's polluting the environment
polluting people aging them fast
making their liver sick making them
viral
because it's so poisonous and you guys
got if you guys got a chance you guys
start writing to close companies you
should start writing to
other companies saying stop poisoning us
with these chemicals there's no reason
for this
anyway the point is is that we're up
against a lot
and the mono cleanse diet is gives you a
chance to cleanse while you still have
energy
you realign your cranial senses yeah
you're going to sit you're going to
smell those chemicals out there because
they're
entrenched everywhere but at least
you're getting healthier no matter
what's power of it
what i love about the mono cleanse is
the insulin resistance goes away
i love that you can cleanse you know
while you're eating
i love that it heals helps to heal
digestive problems
how cool is this georgiana good to see
you
anthony with what should we uh color
our hair with um well okay
my hair yesterday and i am not okay and
i think it's because of it
so look here hair coloring hair coloring
i'm hoping people come out some really
natural hair coloring
i'm hoping that happens i think there
are more natural ones
can try to find them or not scented it's
just the toxic
the toxic ones real conventional hair
coloring companies
those are yet those are really really
rough okay those are really hard
and you know and so and
and that's the thing is when we go into
hair places you got all the clones and
fragrances you got all that stuff too
and the hair products are so entrenched
with chemicals
but looking for a natural hair dye
is the way to go for sure if you're
doing hair care coloring right natural
hair dye's the way to go
and i'm hoping better ones keep on
coming out the standard conventional
hair color hair coloring dye is
definitely really
harsh whoa so yeah i totally get it it's
like it's why cleansing is so important
there's some things we
we we get we get into right it's of
course
walk out your front door and get into
something that's why we're doing like
the mono cleanse it's why we're taking
care of
ourselves that's why we're on day three
to get the stuff out of us build up
build to make us
stronger too all these things matter
you know so i got steamed potatoes in
front of me right here these are piping
hot
which are really nice nice piping hot
steamed potatoes
i got papayas in front of me i got
bananas in front of me i got this
beautiful lettuce i don't know what kind
of lettuce you guys have been getting
but i found this
i've been really lucky with this lettuce
look at this and this is a butter leaf
the kind that's
it's like it's like so good it's so good
right
i got asparagus over here too i got
green beans over here i got
um brussels sprouts over here okay
because you know i told you there's
there's other options there's like the
steamed squash option and you can do
some asparagus with it or some brussels
sprouts how cool is that
i got the pea option which is really
great i made the pea hummus you guys
know that i've been making the pea
hummus i might
might crack one crack into one you never
know uh today we'll see
get rid of the coffee cup right now for
that
so i want to talk about transitioning
get that
off our plate good to see you guys
tic-tac good to see you guys on facebook
youtube good to see you guys on
clubhouse
okay so
what happens is not trying to be harsh
not trying to be tough it's not not
doing
not trying to be mean but we we
really get spoiled with our foods we do
we do
and i get it it's a hard world we we
lean on our foods
i totally understand and it makes sense
no shaming no judgment
not judging anyone i know how hard life
is
okay had my fair share okay
and i know life's not easy i'm just
letting everybody know right here
okay and at the same time right
same time that's why i don't judge
anybody for what they eat
never did never judged anybody for what
they
for what they eat or anything like that
you know and
and there's a reason for that i've known
people people have walked into my office
throughout the years
you know when i used to see people by
the thousands people would walk into the
office
and they'd be eating whatever they've
eaten whatever
and and i never was like
oh that's bad how stupid are you
how silly are you never ever ever
because it's not easy because there's a
lot of reasons first of all we're taught
not to eat the right things
second of all the world is set up to
just mess
us up it's rigged in a way
to keep us sick so our institutions when
we're raised in school and we're going
into school
it just doesn't teach us how to eat
right i mean all of it we're just we
come out of this right and it's
generations of this
and uh thumbs up on this video marissa
thanks for telling everybody you're the
best and
so we're in this we're in this place in
time now
too where we're dealing with the same
thing it's life's not
life's not easy so we're gonna eat a
whole bunch of things
emotionally too we go through a lot of
hardships go through a lot of struggles
broken relationships broken friend
relationships
broken you know broken marriages uh
loss of life loss of loved ones um you
know hard times like we go through all
the stuff and food
is what we run to right we tend to run
to and this is why i really like the
mono cleanse
because you weren't put on michelle
miller
to see you weren't put on a juice
cleanse
right a juice cleanse okay that's you
know
you know it wasn't something like that
the mono cleanse is designed
so you can function live your life eat
food
and still move yourself forward
and it could be done long term
now i mean i i've talked to another
doctor friend the other day that's had a
patient now on for two years straight on
the potato and
butter leaf lettuce and the celery juice
to heal
all these conditions going on and the
person the patient said
it's been a godsend because
they were able to eat food they need
have their energy sustain their muscles
um eventually get to exercising because
they had that strength
and this is this is amazing amazing and
they tried everything else before
so what i love about the monofins is
just just all these reasons right
and if you just came on here you're new
or you're just the first time you're
you know you're checking this out on
both tick tock or facebook youtube
check out the last bunch of lives with
just three three days of the mind eating
plans
so i'm gonna make some lemon water
really quick we're gonna talk about
transitioning today
i'm gonna head there right i'm gonna
move these potatoes over here i'm gonna
move this papaya
somewhere and
i'm gonna just crack some lemon water
right jenny the mono eating cleanse is
perfect to include in a busy life
it saves time love it
wow that's really cool really really
cool
dig it dig it so
at the lemon water that's done 16 to 32
ounces
let's talk about the fluids during the
mono cleanse you could do like a liter
of water throughout the day you can add
coconut water into it too
you can break it up to coconut water and
water you can do straight coconut water
throughout the day if you really wanted
to
that's what you have don't do pink
coconut water don't do red water
red coconut water it's the scam that's
the scam out there one thing you'll get
from medical medium
is i'm not trying to do that thing where
whoa don't want to step on the coconut
water people's toes
because you're screwing people over with
the red pink coconut water telling them
it's the best stuff
what a lie i i don't want to step on
their toes
i don't want to step on everybody else's
toes you know caffeine people or the
chocolate people because everybody's
doing the plant medicine or the
ayahuasca people or the ionizer people
like
you know what i mean it's like i gotta
have your back
i noticed that everybody in health they
either the health like the
say the the people in health that are
the so-called pros
that we're supposed to all listen to and
health out there right i noticed either
they're completely ignorant of of the
right information
right they're saturated with the
misinformation that they have
or they just don't want to step on toes
when they do learn the right information
for medical medium and they don't want
to step on toast because they don't want
to
they don't want to rock their friends
you know their relationships they have
in the industry it's like
dude are we watching the back for the
chronic leo
the people who need it the most are we
playing games
are we playing games and using the
chronicle
as pawns in a big chess game because
that's what i'm seeing out there
if chronicle are used as pawns in the
chess game sell them some left in
supplements
tell them it's oxalates try to sell them
this tell them you know hey
do this and this tell them like it's
just your pawns like that's what they're
trying to do they just like
pawns in their chess game while they
build their empires everybody's building
their empires and using the chronicle
because that's how it's done right
everybody's building empires and using
the chronicle to do it
without like really looking out for
their best interest and
it's critical to look out for the best
interest and one of those best interests
is
don't do the pink and red coconut water
back to that don't do the pink and red
coconut water
i mean it's bad coconut water i know all
about coconut water
everything about it okay so
it's old it's oxidizing it's not better
for you
anyway do the coconut water if you want
one of liquids during the day
you could do regular water you could do
your lemon water you could do lemon
water all day we got that covered
right let's cover more liquid to go into
celery
juice namina
says this mono cleanse taught me to
appreciate all the variety we have a
normal and medical medium diet
not everything now everything is amazing
what a lesson
incredible exactly because the medical
medium
diets if we want to call it that right
they got all kinds of powerful foods
look at life-changing foods look at
little rescue
look at cleanse the heel there's 75
recipes anybody coming on that doesn't
have this you want to get
you do get it free at the library if you
try to find it that way amazon.com us 51
off okay i'll give you the broken record
thing again
amy day three mono eating cleanse
bananas papayas and lettuce
whoa you're doing bananas papayas unless
you're doing both the combo of that
combo
blown away thank you for your
life-saving information anthony
amy proud of you okay and um
even lost a few pounds whoa
blown away i bought the book and love it
cool on tick tock oh awesome
incredible so yeah there's a
huge variety of foods that's the whole
thing huge variety of foods the medical
medium information do 369 advance
do 369 original cleanse simplified
cleanse do the 28 day cleanse
right you can do like there's so many
things you can do
and the foods are really really but
we're doing the mono cleanse
it's a powerhouse it realigns you
and gets you in a great place um
let's talk about transition let's just
run a little bit over the rest of what
we're doing for stuff we got
we got the lemon water we're covering
the fluid aspect right
you're drinking water do a liter water a
day you're drinking your lemon water you
can sip your lemon water all day long
do your lemon water at night too okay
celery juice
really important i got to tell you let's
get to that
now let's do some celery juice i want to
grab the juicer
i want to juice some celery and then
we're going to talk about transitioning
in a little bit so i hope you guys stick
around for that because that's important
um excited about the transitioning
factor
and what we can talk about with that
right
and by the way you guys i'm honored to
have you in my kitchen
okay and it's it really is a great thing
to have you guys in my kitchen
when i was four years old and spirit of
compassion reached out to me
via talking to me
um i didn't realize that i would be in a
kitchen
many decades later
with a computer screen with computer
screens in front of me
with you guys there like i wasn't
thinking that was gonna happen
[Music]
[Applause]
if you're already having a health
condition like you went into the mono
eating cleanse wanting to fix the health
condition in one
shot okay remember the mono
like say ibs or anything like that the
mono cleanse in three days
may fix it for one person but not
another
everybody has a different level of
pathogens and toxins
takes time to heal that's why people do
the model cleanse for weeks
take breaks sometimes they do it longer
the medical medium cleanser little book
explains all of this question the
questions are all answered
guys should have this if you if you
don't make sure you check that out
[Music]
i was asked to write the books
it was asked because the waiting list to
see me
became impossible to ever
penetrate on any level so
i was begged to write the books 2014
i was like i gotta get this medical
medium book done
so you want the books when you can get a
chance
austin aw you literally saved my life
thank you for everything you do healed
my acid reflux
and i've had it for five years austin by
the way good to see you
honored you're here my brother
[Music]
and a little disclaimer for you guys if
you don't like my jokes or
the fly on the wall or the robot or
anything else i do
or the dogs that it bring on just read
the books
read the books you can get aw the
medical textbook version of aw where
there's no jokes
or sarcasm and you can get the
jokes of sarcasm involved with the
information here on the
but my acid reflux is gone too
whoa on tip top
[Music]
i'm running some so by the way there's a
juicer sale on this juicer
if you don't have a juicer and you're
and you're eventually looking for one
gift 24 says love the jokes keep them
that's funny this is the mm-900 hds by
the way
this is the omega juicers.com
megajuicers.com the celery model
mm-900 hds cuts the celery
cost in half for me it's incredible
jay says mm i have such a hard time with
all the sugar i'm not a sweet girl
the banana cleanses too much i want to
swap for potatoes kind of after one day
yeah of course you could swap for
potatoes yeah totally totally
[Music]
definitely
i also want you to be a detective
your own detective and
kind of go back in your history a little
bit and see that maybe you were doing
stuff that was sweet but didn't know it
was sweet
i'm not saying you were on any of this
that i'm about to say but it's for
anybody that's listening
did you do any alcohol right
because that's the methyl sugar it's
really sweet did you do any chocolate
this chocolate's always got sugar in it
for the most part right
[Music]
did you do any pizza that's really sweet
but what happens is did you do any pasta
did you do any ice cream
[Music]
did you do any you might not you might
feel the bananas are too sweet but i'm
just wondering have you done any of
those
now if you're
thinking why is he saying this
because when you add fat to those sugars
like a chocolate bar that has fat and
sugar or ice cream that has fat and
sugar
or pasta that's got fat and sugar or
pizza that's got fat and sugar you can't
tell you're
doing the sweets you can't tell
you're loaded with fat in there right
but when you do the banana by itself
you're like whoa that's sweet whoa
that's because it's not laced in fact
when you do the banana and lettuce
itself
just a little detective forensic talk
[Music]
you guys are okay with that we're on the
third day of the challenge
it's about introducing um you to the
mono eating
so you can do it long term if you want
to do a long term
short term here's what's incredible get
this you guys
just check this out right you know how
to use this
what if you get food poisoning down the
road what if you get food poisoning down
the road
and you survive it right and
and you can't eat jack for like
weeks anything you eat your stomach goes
sour because you're trying to recover
from food poisoning happens all the time
to people okay right because people are
out in the restaurants
and you got the mono cleanse
as a reference to help you out
what if you fat yourself to death to
such a point you blow your pancreas out
so what if you're at a friend's house
you eat one slice too much pizza and for
some reason there was so much oil on
that pizza like there usually is
that your pinkers finally said you know
what i can't do this anymore and you get
pancreatitis
you got the mono cleanse reference
what if you're somebody that gets their
liver sick you get the fatty liver and
you're just getting so sick and finally
you get a fatty liver diagnosis by your
doctor your a1c through the roof
you got the mono cleanse to reference
the mono cleanse right
what if you're somebody that ends up
with an ulcer because you've got some
bacteria eaten away at your
stomach you've got some bacteria you've
got h pylori eating away at your
duodenum you get an ulcer you go get
your
you get your endoscopy and they're like
you got an ulcer mrs brown
and you're like oh my god oh my god you
got the mono cleanse
reference what if you're someone that
boom you get this mild stroke happen you
don't know it's a
you don't know it's a tran trans uh tran
exchemic attack you don't know it's a
mild stroke
and all of a sudden you don't get nerve
signals to your gut and you got
gastroparesis you got the mono cleanse
to reference
this is the mm-900 hds i told you it's
20 off right now at omegajuicers.com
medjusters.com but it's the mm-900 hds
if you're interested
so worth it because the pulp comes out
dry it's dry
for god's sake which means the juices in
here
saves you so much money what if you what
if you're addicted to food to such a
degree
you can't break the food addiction you
just can't break it
and you need to reset your taste buds to
try to break it you got the mono cleanse
reference
i've been doing the mono cleanse with
you guys it's given me extra energy so
now i'm like flying off the handle
christina i've been through everything
you said anthony the mono diet has
really helped me so much
incredible
incredible incredible
cindy i love that juicer i love that
juicer best juicer ever had hands down
best juicer such a great juicer
incredible juicing our celery
now with the omega mm-900 hds excellent
juicer
right there on tick-tock amazing what's
the mono diet
wait someone just asked what's the mono
diet
uh i want to sit down i got to sit down
oh my god i'm just going to sit down
ah dear lord god
help me down here uh re-watch the
youtube lives if you can on tic-tac
please we want to re-watch the lives and
i'm not going to give you the fast-paced
one
i did that on one of the youtubes that
was crazy when i did the fast-paced one
where i did supersonic quick speed
and was a robot telling everything that
was in it that was that almost
short-circuited me that was so intense
the robot almost got short-circuited
um anyway all right come on
get the book aha you're right
the mono cleanses in here tick tock tick
tock person on tick tock by the way
person on tick tock thank you for being
here
get it for you the library if you want
okay try to get it free at the library
if you can't you at least you know
amazon.com is 51
off on this book which i honestly think
that's an angelic thing
i think an angel made amazon
price the book under what the book cost
the print
51 off i've never seen that happen like
that for such a medical textbook like
this
so every time i'm talking to a friend
i'm like i know an angel
is keeping that book at 16.99 on amazon
because
i have no control over pricing
can you show can you tell us how to
steam potatoes tock good question let me
strain this real quick 16 to 32 ounces
of celery juice i would do 32 ounces of
celery juice for sure and i would
consider doing more than that
on the mono cleanse you can do it at the
end of the day as well
if anybody is new to this okay
celery juice cooking with rebecca says
yes so much energy i have been
cleaning my house top to bottom and
guess
what this is getting cleaned out
from top to bottom this is getting
cleaned out
this is getting cleaned out this liver
is getting cleaned out too
so here you are you're cleaning your
house i gotta put this away
hey what's this oh i gotta put this away
hey what's this meanwhile this is being
cleaned out
right here right there
susan doesn't the publisher set the
price
not on amazon publisher doesn't set the
price on amazon no
no no amazon can keep that book really
high priced
and like i said i believe angelic powers
have intervened to keep the book at that
off right now and uh which 16
costs more to print that book 75 recipes
it's
500 600 pages it's unbelievable chris
what are you doing you seem fine to me
just talking about potatoes for a couple
of seconds how about that i think that's
a good idea how do you steam potatoes
okay you can get a pot right with one of
those baskets
stainless steel pot with a basket
that you can do it that way stainless
steel pot with a basket
got water on the bottom and the basket
on top
put your potatoes there that's one way
you can do it right another way is you
can buy a steamer
right and i might have a steamer on
medicalmedium.com
the kitchen section on the uh
products page right i don't own the
steamer i don't want the steamer seamer
company it's there
as a directory
so yeah what causes malaysia it causes
the sun spots it causes the sunspots and
all that
you wanna know what causes one of the
one things that cause it it's the
caffeine
keep that on keep on getting caffeine
caffeine chocolate
right and toxins all right
let's go you guys let's talk about this
a little bit more let's go into
transitioning now
so before i show you some other stuff
too at this point many of you guys have
done the
papaya or banana option or the banana
papaya option together
or the steamed potato option or the
steamed pea option right
many of you guys have tried that okay
now you're three days into this
maybe you just started today so then go
two more days after this we'll talk
about transitioning
and christina
says what's wrong with potatoes with
green spots or sprouts
well it's because the potatoes turning
into something different that's all
you just you know it's not not that
anything's terribly wrong with it it's
just that it wants to start growing
it wants to be put into the ground and
so you don't want to eat it when it
wants to do that the minute a potato
starts to change its mind and says you
know what i want to go into the ground
and start to grow
and become a potato plant you don't want
to eat it
okay because the sprouts and the leaves
it's a lot it's like that with a lot of
foods
a lot of foods not just potato it's like
that with a lot of foods there's
certain stages of foods that you eat
their stage at
right and that's how it works
don't eat a green potato don't eat a
potato that's sprouting
you don't and the same thing with sweet
taste there's times you don't eat sweet
potatoes don't eat a sweet potato when
they get all those rotten spots
because that's a sweet potato saying hey
i'm done they're sweet
sweet potatoes get when they when they
sit in the fridge too long they get
rotten spots but you can't see them they
become like pockets every single fruit
and vegetable
every single food on the planet the same
thing like meat right
don't eat brown meat the sad thing is
they stop they
they try to stop the meat from being
brown in the store and they cover the
meat with
an ammonia to keep the meat red
so the red is stored in the red no one
knows it but the meat in this door is
all red it's a
it's not supposed to be red because it's
already gone bad
monocle and potatoes are grounding if
if you need them to sleep too a lot of
people have sensitive central nervous
systems
and they can make you sleepy because
they're so grounding and relaxing so
they make you sleepy sometimes because
it helps the body heal it helps nerves
to heal potatoes actually
help nerves to heal you're getting
glucose to your nervous system
here's what happens the minute you take
out all the fat and you get rid of the
insulin resistance you guys
right now you've got ample glucose for
all your nerves
when you get ample glucose for all your
nerves
you're now you're now good your nerves
are being fed now healing starts to
happen you might get sleepy
your body might be like wow we can heal
let's take a little nap here
let's get ready and take a little nap
take a little nap
here we go and your body starts to heal
okay that's how it works a lot of people
are already dealing with fatigue but
they don't know it
because they're over stimulated they're
jacked up on caffeine they're jacked up
on adrenaline from eating too much fat
they're jacked up on stuff and because
people are so jacked up they don't know
it and they're really fatigued
underneath it all when you remove
all that it also shows that they
actually have fatigue
now let's say hey that's a window until
really what's happening and now i have
to heal
and then you can nap and rest so you can
heal
part of the healing process of when
you're doing like the mono cleanse or
anything it's part of the healing
process
it's important transitioning right
first things first to give you the first
thing about transitioning
first things first is you don't want to
start tanking crazy amounts
of crazy food that's just simplistic
it's in a nutshell that's one one thing
right there
you don't want to just get off the mono
diet
stop at your favorite vegan pizza place
and start tanking you just don't want to
do that
you know there's no reason to put your
body in a shock
right there's a transition section too
in cleanse the heel keep that in mind
remember that read that section
it's important okay and you also don't
want to tank on
a ton of fat and that's what this is by
the way
right but you don't want to take on a
ton of fat
so you don't want to come off the mono
cleanse and
you know and start diving into something
crazy you don't want to do that
you don't want to get up you don't want
to come off the mono cleanse
right and you know the whole bit
can you talk about healing from long
covet
let me grab my other book real quick
so
it's a new edition of medical medium so
long covet is that that whole long cover
thing
stems from medical medium information so
if you hear it out there it originates
from medical medium that's
that's uh fc bar
okay and what happens is that would have
epstein-barr comes back so when we get
knocked down by anything you get knocked
down by the flu you get knocked down by
flu related bugs you get knocked down
by food poisoning you get knocked down
by anything
okay then it reactivates epstein-barr
that's original medical medium
information
it reactivates simplex 1 epstein-barr
simplex 2 set of megavirus shingles
hhv-6h8v7
can reactivate any of them really so
you can look into that book if you
really want to know about that
so you don't want to come off the mono
cleanse and be like yeah
i'm going to start eating elizabeth
edwards says your info helped me
understand my sons that have autism and
adhd now i'm able to meet their needs
better nutritionally and they're
becoming passionate about eating healthy
and meeting
those glucose demands in healthy ways
that's incredible
i couldn't believe my eyes still trying
to get them to do the heavy metal detox
smoothie but i'm so proud
of how they're doing that is just
precious that is just precious truly
truly
truly so when we come off that mono
cleanse
you don't you don't want to dive into
chicken i mean it's not a great thing
just dive into chicken
if you're somebody that eats chicken
every day and you're doing the mono
cleanse and now you're without your
chicken
take it slow if you're gonna go back to
chicken take it really slow
that's one thing if you're somebody
who's vegan or plant-based
you're used to a vegan diet that has all
that all the fat in it because you're on
the you know the high-fat vegan diets
right
just hold off the vegan cheese and the
vegan burgers and the
vegan bean burgers with all the vegan
cheese and stuff like that don't
don't pound that stuff down coming off
the mono cleanse this is one of the most
important
one of the most important things to
understand really truly so
keep that in mind right there okay and
i just saw somebody on tick tock would
you say poor chicken
poor chicken yeah well let's see what
our friend has to say
here oh wait i don't have my friend here
i thought i had dr nesbit my chicken
friend with me right here but i don't
you never know i might be able to find
dr nesbit he's been busy with patience
lately
we'll see what he has to say on another
time possibly you never know
can you use watermelon yeah of course
you can you can come right off the
cleanse on watermelon
definitely you could break your cleanse
on watermelon you break your monocle and
then go on watermelon
look i'm into melon i'm into melon i'm
going to demonstrate a whole thing on
melons eventually i'll do a youtube
facebook whatever i'll do a whole thing
on melon
eventually too talk about like how i've
used melon for
for recoveries for people and everything
else and
all of that and watermelon's amazing
definitely you can do that you could
also mono cleanse on but keep that
celery juice in there
okay the mono cleansing that i've
shown you guys in this mono cleanse that
we're doing not
dr nesbitt is coming i think so we have
to see
what's happening there where dr
nesbitt's on his way here
dr nesbitt how you doing okay
dr nesbit is a chicken i want you guys
to know
darkness but it's actually doing you see
everybody on tik tok
right yeah you see what some people been
naughty
they have what do you mean
some people have been some people
some people here haven't done the mono
cleanse
huh dr nesbitt says that some people
here haven't done the mono cleanse
really well how do you know
you're a chicken a smart chicken
um dr nesbitt's here and
he says try not to dive into a big
roasted chicken
dr nesbitt you don't eat chicken when
you come off a model cleanse do you
he said he's had a bite
i don't think that's a good idea dr
nesbit um
what about for the vegans what do we do
should the vegans jump jump into a fake
chicken you know when you go to those
places or you go to the freezer section
in the in the stores
do we do like the fake chicken
is that good dr nesmet says it's poison
uh poison that's what dr nesbitt said
poison i said why i'm saying one
that's pretty funny dr nesbitt says that
the fake chickens have tons of msg
and gluten in them lots of msg so what
do we do how's everybody gonna
has everybody gonna come off the mono
cleanse you want them to drink
what you want them to drink a
giant jar of peanut butter what do you
mean you got peanut butter let me see
you went them on a giant giant jar of
peanut butter
dr nesbitt doesn't want you on peanut
butter he was just
joking no doubting a whole jar of peanut
butter when you're coming off the
monocle lens
dr nesbitt is there anybody to call
out there you want to say something on
the telephone no
no let's not do that anyway look
i'm going to let dr nesbit go back to
his patients
uh he's working on some very critical
sick
people so we're gonna get him back to
work
i'll see you later okay all right
what you don't want to do on the mono
cleanse is you don't want to
dive right into heavy fats radical fats
is what i call them
read the cleanse the heal i talk about
radical fats if you're vegan don't
don't jump into all that fake cheese all
the nut butters don't jump into all the
peanut butter
don't just dive into all that
fat right maybe if you're into avocados
you bring in some avocado you do that
you bring in your avocado salad at night
maybe you bring in some hummus if that's
something that you do
maybe you bring in that if you're
someone that's already been eating this
way and that's how you like it now i
recommend
okay i recommend keeping your fats low
no matter what you're doing
so if you're doing the an animal protein
based diet and that's what you like to
do
keep the animal proteins to once a day
maybe at the end of the day maybe every
other day
okay and make sure you do like the heavy
metal detox
movie if you're working on cleaning out
the metals make sure you're doing your
celery juice make sure you're doing your
fruit bowls
make sure you're doing you know liver
rescue smoothie make sure you're doing
things that are really good for you
right
have some melon in the morning do your
celery just do your lemon water celery
juice and do some melon do some honeydew
melon
do some cantaloupes do some watermelon
right do that and then
lunch time do your heavy metal detox
smoothie then later on do steamed cooked
vegetables steamed potatoes have a
potato salad
have a potato waffle for dinner just
don't dive
into the heavy fats off the running you
guys
don't dive into the nuts and seeds don't
be tanking in all the almonds and the
walnuts and if you do i'm still gonna
love you
still gonna love you not gonna judge you
still gonna love you
okay of course of course but that's what
i recommend
is not diving into too much of that
when i went off i leaned when i went off
i leaned into the list of mono foods
and started my heavy metal detox
smoothie great
incredible it's hard to see the handle
for some reason
on tick-tock it's for some reason on my
device it's all the way to the left
where i can't see the handle
sometimes it's crazy but i just read
that on tick-tock
um dr sherry green
good to see you
so that's the number one
recommendation the number one
recommendation
is not high diving into
the oil really important what you do
want to do
too what you also want to do is you want
to keep out the poisons
okay don't high dive into the caffeine
it's poison don't high dive into the
vinegar
poison okay don't high dive into
um you know fermented foods which isn't
good for you
i mean it's not the worst for you but it
doesn't help at the same
time i talked about that for a million
reasons and i won't go into the
fermented food thing right now
but it's something you just don't want
to just jump into when you're coming off
the mono cleanse
read what you need to know about the
supplement section two in the
supplements
chapter read the information in there
chapter 27
supplement chapter so all the stuff is
important okay guys
so let's keep on moving forward a little
bit
let me get the burger off the counter
all right it was nice of dr nesbit to
show up
what i like to do is a potato salad so i
like to take some leaves
when i'm doing the mono cleanse i like
to do potato salad i'm going to chop up
just make a little potato salad really
quick
right this is a little one i'm making
okay
grab another leaf
right make a little potato salad
grab a plate guys it's always great to
have you in the kitchen with me
now when you're on the mono cleanse by
the way when you do it again maybe
you're still just starting it now and
you're going into
your next couple days you can do a lot
of lettuce this is not a lot of lettuce
right here
you can do a lot of lettuce okay and
you don't want to just eat two leaves of
lettuce
you should eat more lettuce get the
mineral salts do the
that's the kind of balance you need
right and
now what i'm going to do is i'm going to
cut up some potato right here
and um
some potato wedges right
so what i'm doing is i'm making a potato
salad
real simplistic simplicity is so good
for healing
many times this is a great
so i'm hoping you guys did this a lot
right
made yourself
potato salad squeezing a little lemon on
it now
uh lemon seeds are going down in there i
want to get that lemon seed out but
that lemon seed went down went down
there
this is just one potato you can do more
than one potato right
you can do two potatoes three potatoes
four
he doesn't peel the potatoes i see that
on tick tock you can peel them if you
want
you boil the potato question mark on
tick-tock no don't boil the potatoes
when you boil potatoes the glucose in
the potato
goes into the broth now you
unless you're gonna have the soup and
you make a potato soup so you can try to
get that glucose back right
but when potatoes are boiled in water
and they're underneath
water potatoes are underneath water
the glucose from the potato leeches into
the water boils out of the potato and
leeches into the water now you got a
potato with very few calories in it
you need the calories you need the
glucose you need to be sustained
and then our brain runs on glucose so
we'll run into that a little bit what i
love about the
mono eating cleanse
your brain starts to die in five seconds
without glucose
in five seconds your brain tissue starts
to die
letting you know in 10 seconds your
brain is already dying
your brain is already dying in 10
seconds
your brain is already dying without
glucose just so you know
in 10 seconds it's already going bye-bye
keep that in mind that's how important
glucose is
so when you hear the rhetoric out there
your brain needs fat your brain needs
fat who hasn't been eaten
fat who hasn't been eating fat
for a hundred years tell me
who hasn't been eating fat every single
day
fish meat eggs chicken
nuts even avocado oils
olive oil who hasn't been eating fat
every day in their life
that's do you do you find that things
don't make sense out there or
or what i mean think about that one
because i'm i'm kind of i'm scratching
my head about that one you need fat
that's what you need uh the brain needs
fat um you need fat in order to heal you
need fat
for your hormones i mean are you kidding
that everybody's sick
and they're eating fat and they're
eating fat and they're eating fat i mean
am i right
just tell me if i'm wrong tell me if i'm
wrong go ahead just
put it on there you're wrong no one eats
fat
and and so but with your brain
you can take fat out of your diet your
brain will start to heal
i just want you to know this piece you
can take fat out of your diet
your brain starts to heal
brain inflammation starts to heal
you can't take sugar out of your diet
your brain starts to die because your
brain is mostly made out of sugar
news flash glycogen storage
and the brain tissue itself runs on
glucose
so why is everything twisted out there i
purposely think there's plants in
natural medicine
to purposely confuse the bear so people
stay
sick it's a game of chess like no one's
ever seen on our planet
you know why do you think they they're
removing supplements into ins and making
them forbidden to use why do you think
supplements are being removed away from
the people
and and going under the guise of now
prescription and stuff it's a game of
chess
to just to really torture people along
the way and alternative medicine
is a place where there's lots of plants
in there so that you stay confused
and if you're strong enough and you're
young enough and strong enough you can
stay confused and just
mess around while your acne comes back
and forth or some skin problems or
some fatigue and you can play the game
be like well i need fat or i need this
now i need collagen powder or i need
this and that and
you can play the game right and but
the minute you're really sick that's
when you know something's up and an
alternative medicine is a place where
there's so many pitfalls and so many
potholes
just like conventional medicine
isabel once i took the fats out adhd
immediately
started clearing up
the sky opened up
ah the sky
i mean is that incredible that's
incredible
incredible so that's that right there
that was a perfect
example of what we're talking about you
guys
make sure you have the book proud of you
proud proud proud
truly am seriously you guys and good to
see
all you on here bless your heart truly
okay
know that i care all right next month in
a little reminder
next month we're doing the medical
medium
heavy metal detox cleanse
in august i'm pumped we're going to have
some fun
we're going to do a little dance we're
going to have some fun
you guys going to ig going to turn tick
tock back on going to turn clump house
back
on go on instagram probably about 15
minutes could straighten up the set
a little bit and i'll see you guys there
love you guys greatly okay take care