this is day two
of the medical medium anti-bug cleanse
challenge do you have cleanse to heal
do you have the life-saving book turned
around so many lives people suffering
and struggling throughout the years
this is the book right here this is the
famous book and i say that because when
you get your life back and you recover
and you know how to heal and you can
live again the way you want to it is
that amazing of a book you guys have it
on sale amazon.com us
16.99 incredible it's 51
off i can't say how incredible that
really is and what that means it costs
more to print the book
get a free at the library if you can too
okay
get it free at the library so that's an
option we're doing the portabella stew
right there i'm going to start cooking
right now because it's a stew and i want
to get it started good to see you guys
we're live on telegram incredible
we're live on youtube facebook live on
tick tock good to see you guys coming on
and uh it's a special moment because
we're day two let's just get cooking a
little bit
let's start that because
it's going to actually take a couple of
minutes to get this stew a roll in and i
want to do that i'm going to put a
white onion right here you can use
yellow onion you can use
red onion i'm gonna get an onion in here
as we speak okay so we're doing that
[Music]
get
a nice little onion in here
i love onions
real healing food it's an herb
it's an herb still this day i hear
people say yeah no onion's a vegetable
and i'm like it is when was it a
vegetable really
because
i'm pretty sure
it's an herb
a herb
for sure so i'm getting some onion going
in the pot that's first right so are you
guys making this with me that's what i
wanted to ask you because i know that
many of you guys are like okay i'm gonna
do it with you and then some of you guys
are probably like no i'm not doing it
with you so all right let's get these
onions
going good to see you michelle l
good to see you guys coming on we're
tick tock we're telegram this is day day
two of the anti-book cleanse i got
something really important to tell you
too
i'm gonna be on rumble at 6 15
eastern
3 15 pacific
it's gonna be a rumble
zinger
okay
and
i hope you guys are there so let's put
some onion in there let's chop up some
celery too a couple celery sticks
let's do that
get a little celery in this
you can make this stuff small if you
want now in order to see me on rumble
exclusively because it's just going to
be rumble at 6 15 eastern 315 pacific to
see me on rumble exclusively you got to
make sure you go to rumble.com okay
forward slash medical medium lorraine l
i just saw you pop up seeing all you
guys pop up
yeah
yeah tail tail onion is an herb
onion is an herb but you can make it
small you can make it bigger hunks if
you want i'm doing smaller ones okay so
i hope you guys are okay with that right
this recipe is from cleanse the heel if
you guys just came on right now
make sure that you go to the library you
get a a copy free out of the library
where you get it 51 off amazon.com us
all right this is a life-saving book
when you see when a book actually has
the power and ability to turn somebody's
life around to get them out of suffering
it's a life-saving book and that doesn't
exist out there in the health book realm
so this is a book you want to have it's
51 off amazon we're doing anti-bug
cleansing here
there's a critical reason why we do the
anti-bug cleanse there's a very
important reason for that so we're going
to cover that i'm just cooking up these
onions
[Music]
good to see you
guys
paddy derby good to see you from
virginia
wow amazing
seeing you guys come up on tick tock
all right i'm just chopping up a little
bit of celery to get into the stew this
is the portabella
mushroom stew
love it
i actually eat this one a lot just so
you know
right
i eat this one a lot i don't know if you
guys do or
courtney good to see you
i see you left i see it courtney i see
you leave youtube
comments too i always read them
because if i don't respond in a comment
section in youtube or somewhere else or
whatever
just know that's not because it's not
that i didn't read them
right
it's just so i'm trying to finish up a
book right now and
i'm under massive stress that's why i
love doing the anti-bug cleanse right
now because i just love any medical
medium cleanse because of power they
have
and
i need that extra oomph
so
what i'm doing is sauteing this
celery and these onions right here right
now i'm gonna pop some mushrooms in i
think
let me pop some some shrooms in there
right got some mushrooms
i got some shrooms here
hey man
i got some shrooms here i just got them
out of a bag
once the concert's starting
soon
oh
whoa
hey man did you know that
because you know that
the aristocracies
do you know that they run
they run a space program no one's ever
seen before
did you know that
i got to get these mushrooms in there
these are portabellas
i made a promise i wasn't gonna fool
around today
i just can't keep it straight or serious
let's get these mushrooms in here
you guys good to see you
we're doing the anti-bug cleanse but i
want to get the stew going before i
start
throwing out the info
right
you can make your mushrooms bigger
pieces you can make your mushrooms
smaller pieces
do you man
do you you don't have to do it my way
here
right
you can just throw the mushroom right in
have whole mushrooms in there
this is the portobello stew just throw
whole mushrooms in there
why not that's okay
no one's no one's like
hey
it's not mandated
you can throw mushrooms in there
there's no one telling you what to do in
your home
you still got some freedoms left
so just do do what you want to do
be you
right
medical medium information isn't
mandated okay
you can you can choose to do it you can
choose not to do it right you can you
can do what you want the medical medium
information
all right
so i got some portobello mushrooms in
here i got some
celery i got some onion all right i
might throw another mushroom in here if
you guys are okay with that
let's throw another one in here
we'll throw one
more love it love it
i'm going to pop some you know what i'm
going to pop a broth in here this is
this broth right here you guys you guys
just arrived we're doing the end time
we're going to get the anti buglets
this is the healing broth right here
popping that baby in
that's a liver rescue healing broth
right there this is the medical medium
anti anti-bug cleanse challenge i just
want to get this stuff in here i want to
get this this stew cook in right
i'm going to pop some potatoes in here
are you guys okay about that
right
i'm cutting them small
now i'm not having them really big in
this i'm cutting up nice small pieces
right
let's get those in there
nice small pieces look at that
i'm gonna pop some garlic in here i'm
gonna pop some carrots in here okay
and i'm chopping up some potato right
now we're making the potato
portobello mushroom stew
boom
let's get that in here
you guys i really appreciate you being
here and i know you guys are busy i know
you got a lot going on i know many of
you don't feel good
i know many of you don't feel good i
know many of you are trying you know
you're fighting
to just get your life back on track
you're working hard on your healing
process the fact that you spend time
with me means a lot to me i don't take
it for granted one bit telegram you guys
on there i don't take you for granted
one bit if you're gonna chill out with
me if you're gonna hang out in my
kitchen
if we're gonna talk you know shop if
we're gonna
you know whatever we're gonna do just
know i don't take it for granted like i
really appreciate it i know you guys got
a lot going on same with you guys on
youtube too guys give me a thumbs up if
you ever feel like it if you if you're
the platformer you know has that ability
to give me a thumbs up
you know if you like if you like it if
you like it
if you don't like medical medium
give me a thumbs up
doing some carrot right now
okay
so we got some carrots
what i like to do with carrots is what
i'm gonna do is i'm gonna cut it this
way let me get the back of the carrot
off
i don't like the carrot top right the
carrot top cause a lot of times you'll
see the carrot top gets green
around the edges because when they grow
carrots the carrot sticks up
out of the ground a little bit and it
gets that green color and i don't like
that that part you shouldn't eat with
carrots
right so i like just cutting the top off
a touch if you guys are all right with
that all right i like splitting the
carrot
just like this you see
like doing this
right just splitting them down the
center right
and
there we go and then what i do
is i'll take all the carrots together
i'll put them all together like this
right and i'll do this right
and just cut through them
so and i'll make the carrot pieces small
enough
you can make them big you can have big
hunky carrots in there it's fine
you want big hunky carrots in there
that's fine let me get the carrots in
we're making the stew now
nice
just got to throw some garlic in there
you guys
let me throw some garlic in there
if you guys just came on austin good to
see you
trying to catch the comments as they're
going up
right
so if you guys just came on we're doing
the anti-bug cleanse right
what day are we on anti-bug plants
right what day what day are we on
we're on two
that's what day we're on
okay
and
i'm going to talk about why it's
important
we're doing the anti-bug cleanse like
why
why do it
why do it at all
like why why bother
there's a reason
a really good reason okay so hang in
there
anna says you're an amazing cook i don't
know about that
i don't know about that
you're just watching me bumble lina it
every second is what you're doing
you don't know it but i'm making
mistakes left and right no i'm just
kidding
all right
good to see you too so let's pop in some
fresh herbs in there okay so i'm gonna
put a little thyme in there you guys
okay with that
pop a little bit of time here's what i
do you could do different ways you could
just throw it in the pot like this and
then take it back out right
but you can also do this
you can strip it look
you can strip the time all the leaves
you can do that that's perfectly fine
let's see how i'm stripping the leaves
right here on the time
okay
look at that
i'll do a little bit more
because thyme is such an incredible herb
this is this is an anti-bug herb right
here oh boy this is an entire bug right
there keep that in mind some rosemary
how about that anti-bug
anti-bug
listen i know everybody's into essential
oils i want to talk about that for a
minute too there's something i just i i
don't think i've said enough about
essential oils that
that people should kind of be a little
aware of
talk about that too i'm like you know
what i'm gonna save that for rumble if
you guys exclusively i'm gonna be on
rumble later okay at 3 15
eastern
sorry 3 15 pacific 6 15
right
i think i'm going to save that tidbit
about essential oils
i think i'm going to say you know i know
there's other things i'm going to talk
about on on rumbletime but i think i'm
going to save that tidbit uh for then so
i'm going to put
a tablespoon here of tomato paste in
here i'm also going to chop up
this the um
the herbs but i'm going to put a tomat a
tablespoon of tomato paste in here
fantastic
boom
there's no salt in that
two
no citric acid in that too
these the bio nature tomato paste
so what i'm doing is chopping up the
rosemary and the thyme right that's what
i'm doing i like it chopped up sometimes
i don't like just throwing it in
guys just give me a second i want to get
this
nice and small
all right let's get that in
boom got it in
i think we're looking good
let's get it cooking and let's get
talking
are you guys making this too some of you
guys making this too
love it
boom
lid is on
worth day two
of the medical medium anti-bug cleanse
challenge do you have a book it's a
reminder april taft good to see you do
you guys have a book
it's a reminder
because it's critical okay if anybody
has a symptom a condition and they don't
want to live with it forever if they
have a symptom condition or something in
their way this is a book you might want
to have at home in your hands it's 51
off amazon.com us okay and it's
you can walk in the library too just
walk in the library get it for free
perfectly fine we're doing the
portabello
mushroom stew
and it's even fat free there's no fat in
there there's no fat in that meal
okay
so 16 ounces of celery juice who's doing
the 16 ounces of celery juice
just curious
who's got that going on
16 ounces of celery juice
that's important right
doing a little bit of celery juice now
so why are we doing the anti-bug cleanse
why are we bothering with the anti-bug
plant so please don't
everybody has bugs
now
you get your first symptom
you get your first symptom right
maybe fatigue
maybe you're more achy and painy than
usual
maybe
a little bit more tired than normal
maybe you got a little rash on the skin
starting
maybe you get your first
bladder infection or uti
maybe you get some ringing in the ears
maybe
you get some eye floaters going on
eye floaters
maybe you see some black spots in your
eyes
maybe you're dizzy
maybe you feel off balance
right maybe your feet hurt
maybe your neck hurts
maybe your teeth hurt but you don't know
why
right
maybe you feel
just something or a lot of things
okay
now what do we do
what do we do
we call the doctor
then we have to drive to the doctor or
travel to the doctor
right
now we have to call the doctor or travel
to the doctor
gotta wait in the waiting room with all
the other sick people who have the flu
or the plague
now we have to risk that
we don't feel good
now we gotta get some blood work
so get your arm out and get the needle
stuck in
and this
might not be the only rodeo
you might be going to the doctor for the
next 10 years you might be going to the
doctor for the next 20 years you might
be going to different doctors now you're
adding now you're at a
chinese medicine doctor
now you're at a nutritionist now you're
at an rd now you're at a functional
doctor now you're at a naturopathic
doctor now you're at a chiropractor
now you're spending money
now you're getting recommended for
medications
and guess what
guess who did it to you
something that's trying to own you
and it's a bug
all those problems
are caused
by bugs
so why bother doing the anti-bug cleanse
why bother
who cares
no one needs to do the anti-bug cleanse
let's just fill hospitals and doctors
offices
let's get another severe unexplained
panic attack
let's get more migraines
let's get some more diagnosis in the
reproductive system
let's get endometriosis
let's get all these problems
okay
and
the bugs are causing it
why do
the anti-bug cleanse
because bugs are running people's lives
it's running your life it changes your
schedule it does more than that it
dominates your brain it takes over your
mind the bugs take over your mind if you
guys just got here i hope you watch this
from the beginning because i just showed
you how to make this stew and it's
cooking and i can't wait to eat it i'm
actually really hungry today
really hungry today
all right we made some celery juice
gianna says got blood drawn recently and
made sure the phlebotomist only drew
quarter vials only
yeah
your info has protected so many of us
i would like to do a dance for that i'm
so happy but i'm not gonna do the dance
but of course i'm gonna say i'm at your
service
i am at your service
definitely because i want to help so
badly you just spared yourself
70 milliliters 100 milliliters 150
milliliters 180 milliliters you just
spared yourself without you didn't lose
your immune system you told them quarter
vials and you didn't lose your immune
system you know what's messed up
medical medium is the only person
talking about this on the entire planet
not one doctor not one practitioner not
one healer not one youtube doctor not
one podcast doctor not one single
anybody on the planet has brought this
to anyone's attention just spirit of
compassion to protect you and you
protected yourself
you know
if you cut yourself really bad they'd be
worried about you they'd be worried how
much blood you're losing because they
don't want you to go into shock but they
don't care if they take 28 vials from
you and you go into shock for a week
they don't care
crazy anyway listen i'm really really
proud of you i can't even tell you i
really am
let me just drop this juicer down for a
second
listen to the blood draw podcast when
you guys can you guys on telegram i mean
if you can't i know you've heard the
podcast probably
everybody everybody tell everybody
because people forget
please if you if you guys can do if you
can do this for me tell everybody you
know comment on every post comment on
everybody's post comment wherever and
just tell everybody right you should
listen to the blood draw podcast medical
mean podcast at apple podcast the blood
draw podcast because here's what happens
i can't tell you how many people have
died early with their neurological lyme
with their ms with their fibromyalgia
yes fibromyalgia and they die early
lupus and die early severe fatigue and
die early
reproductive problems and die early i
can't tell you how many people have lost
their life
because they lost their immune system
from too much blood being drawn and they
died and lost their life they got and
the sicker you get the more they draw
it's a death trap
back to the antibody cleanse oh wait a
minute which reminds me why are you at
the doctor's office why are you getting
quarter vials well you need quarter
balls why are they trying to pull more
than quarter vials and pull all that
blood from you why are you at the
doctor's office
because the bugs are making you sick
we're doing the anti-bug cleanse i got
some celery juice right here
by the way you guys i listen you should
wait for the juicer sale okay because
i'm sure they're going to come up with
another sale for the mm-900
and
that's insane i want to show you
something okay
more than 32 ounces of celery juice
right here right look at that okay i
want to show you this
this is dry
that's dry
that's the only pulp i got this time out
of that juicer on my fingers
and it's dry and look at it now i know
there's a food shortage stuff being
talked about i know food prices are
going up and stuff like that right
that's why but just wait for the sale of
the mm-900 i just wait for the sale of
the mm-900 the juicer i just used i'm
just telling you guys
and
because they're gonna have a sale and
i'm telling people more than ever about
this juicer because the amount of money
they can save with their food and
juicing
is it's unbelievable compared to
unmatched to any juicer
that's dry to the bone it's this little
bit of pulp that's how much juice i got
but i just wanted to tell you guys
because because i know that people
someone asked me they said the other day
i don't know if it was yesterday a
couple of comments said when is the
juicer sale gonna be it's coming up i'm
sure it's like the beginning of november
or something like that because you guys
know i work with the mega right
i'm walking around here aimlessly here
we go
so i got the stew cooking
let me just make sure all's well
yeah i'm pumped about that still
smells so good
those mushrooms
all right so i'm gonna actually
i'm straining the celery juice just
letting you know
doing a little bit of a celery juice
strain
because you don't want to not strain it
you want to strain it it's important
okay
really important to strain it
right so i'm moving this over
if you guys don't mind because this is
allowed on the cleanse i want to tell
you what's allowed on the cleanse don't
add anything to your celery just make
sure it's just celery juice don't lemon
no water no anything like that
this is allowed on the cleanse right
here
a big glass of ale no it's not a glass
of ale this is
spicy hot apple juice the medical medium
recipe my god
it's so good
the problem though there's a problem
though with me with drinking this for
some reason
and
we're all starting to notice this
that the more i have the spicy hot apple
juice
the more silly things seem to come out
of my mouth
um
you can sip coconut water or two if you
want during this cleanse right you can
do lemon water do a liter of lemon water
or 32 ounces minimum of lemon water i
like having a big thing like this and
i'm sipping it all day
i'm doing the spicy hot apple apple
juice right now
recipes in the medical medium book
cleanse the heel back to this again you
guys the book saving lives the info is
in the data is in the street cred is
happening the book's been going around
the world now for over a year and it's
turning lives around and
that doesn't happen with health books
not like this
make sure you have this amazon.com 51
off get it free at the library the
anti-bug cleanses one thing out of many
in here
so
the problem is is this little guy
right
sits inside everybody
hhv-6 hhv-7
hhv-8
which is not a good one at all to have
right simplex one simplex two shingles
cytomegalovirus hhv 10 through 16
undiscovered right
all the different viruses that people
walk around with and then the bacteria
struck the cactus
you don't think you have strep in your
system what about the strep throat you
had years ago in college
what about i never went to college by
the way but
so my friends did and yeah they always
got the strep throat and they'd be
calling me up like i got nowhere sore
throat
was where you're partying all night
and then you know strep throat right
that's one thing right there
mono
people have mono that's the epstein bar
right but people think i don't have
strep well then uti's bladder infections
overactive bladder how about that so
overactive bladder utis bladder
infections chronic sinusitis acne
i repeat acne is streptococcus in your
lymphatic
system
acne is streptococcus
in your lymphatic system
if you have acne
you have streptococcus in your liver and
lymphatic system and the real place it's
in is in your liver and then it ends up
feeding up into the lymphatic system
that's the streptococcus and then when
your cycle comes out medical medium
information when your cycle comes out
when your cycle's happening menstruation
is occurring for women your immune
system drops
eighty percent of your immune system
goes to your reproductive system and
then the acne breaks out
because you can't contain your immune
system can't contain the streptococcus
so now your your acne is breaking out
right
okay what i love about the anti-bug
cleanse
it's not hormones what a crock of crap
that is
unbelievable
the one thing about conventional
medicine is it brainwashes alternative
medicine you think alternative medicine
is different than conventional medicine
when it really isn't
the difference is you know yeah they use
different treatments that's the
difference right
but rea and it's one of the differences
but the problem is the whole
trickery pattern that happened from
conventional medicine was to blame women
for their hormones for everything
anything that happened was their
hormones you got anxiety at your
hormones
if you got depression at your hormones
if you got fatigue get your hormones
if you got acne it's your hormones
everything was blamed on hormones this
was a pattern this was a pattern
conventional medicine did to women was
blame everything on their hormones and
what it did in the 1950s is it turned
this thing into it where then all of a
sudden
all the men in the 1950s were like it's
your hormones it's your hormones honey
honey it's your hormones
stop it stop acting crazy honey stop
acting nuts
your anxiety is your hormones the doctor
said it's your hormones honey your
depression is your hormones
that's what happened that was the 1950s
right alternative medicine
i'll turn the medicine
it's like it's like it it is it's just
basically an echo of conventional
medicine in so many ways right here's
one example you talk to an alternative
functional medicine doctor and you say
well wait a minute
a doctor it what's what's the is
the shingles chicken pox and the
alternative doctor will be like
functional doctor bill uh yes um the
chickenpox virus is the shingles no it's
not it's two different viruses they echo
everything from conventional medicine
everything's echoed from it you think
alternative medicine is just something
completely different
sure
and then when you go to alternative
doctors in the clinics in the medical
prestigious medical clinics that you
know the ones that are conventional the
ones right you go to alternative doctors
and i'll say you go to alternative
doctors at the mayo clinic you go to
alter alternative doctors at the
cleveland clinic you could alter an
alternative doc doctors see your side
night whatever you go whatever you go
those all turn doctors they're playing
by rules
um
we can't do that for you sir or ma'am
nope we're under yep we're under the
rules here
yeah we're alternative physicians
but we're under the rules
you think you got an alternative they're
the alternative sections there i know
because i know doctors in all those
clinics
and i know alternative doctors in all
those clinics
and so they're under rules
rules
you know what i mean
and that and that's another thing too so
what happens is people think altered
medicine's alternative it's like yeah a
little bit it is a little bit but it
became one
it's become one
sean
shimon says that one never made sense to
me how can one virus turn into another
virus how can all those smart doctors be
buying that i'll tell you why it doesn't
mean they're smart
doesn't mean they're smart
the one thing i've learned throughout
all these years and that's coming from
an uneducated person right here okay
the only reason why these books are
written is because spirit of compassion
gives me every word if spirit of
compassion didn't give me every word you
wouldn't see a medical medium book i'm
not a highly educated person
but i'm street smart
i'm street smart
you can be the smartest
person
academic-wise go through medical school
and be the most dumbest ass the dumbest
ass you ever met out there
and that's one of the reasons
so when you go you lose your common
sense there's no common sense left so
you can be this brilliant physician and
still think
shingles is the chickenpox virus when
they're two separate viruses
the only reason why medical medium
information has saved the lives more
lives with chronic illness around the
world than any other any other
any other modality any other belief
system out there because the medical
medium is in a belief system
it doesn't it doesn't segregate
like it doesn't segregate and say oh you
can't do medical medium eating animal
protein no this is just veganism or
we're we're animal protein you can't be
a vegan medical medium information is
not occult but the colts out there
they're they're they're locked in
they're locked in those colts you gotta
buy into those colts and you get locked
into those colts right those are the
colts that's why you don't heal you
don't heal in colts you can't heal in
any of those colds because when you even
if you are healing a little you get
screwed up and go backwards and go down
the drain you can't heal in a cult
medical medium information worldwide has
healed more people in chronic illness
than history history today no one can
match it because it's free from cults
and it's free
and the cause of chronic illness that
that medical media put out there such as
epstein-barr and the reactivated
epstein-barr all that information that
got out there and how shingles works and
the cause of it how there's over 30
varieties of shingles and all these
things all this information these broken
barriers turn people's lives around you
guys we're doing the anti-bug cleanse
it's over 60 varieties of that steam bar
and growing
you're somebody here's how it works
somebody with an epstein-barr
right
and then you pick up another epstein bar
two epstein bars inside the body
can create a new epstein bar that new
epstein bar then you pass to someone
else
that new epstein bar is different than
the other epstein bars
that's how it can happen too
so i just made some celery juice
one of the greatest tools
of all time happening right there big
part of people healing i'm cooking
portobello stew i'm really digging it
they didn't know they didn't even know
epstein barker reactivate they thought
you had mono and it disappeared forever
that's it they didn't know epstein barr
caused the neurological symptom
they didn't know epstein-barr caused
hashimoto's thyroiditis multiple
sclerosis lupus fibromyalgia
chronic fatigue syndrome me chronic
fatigue syndrome they didn't know they
didn't know it caused tinnitus ringing
in the air vertigo they didn't know yeah
this is an interesting one and i thought
look i saw someone make a comment of
this about this and it's so true right
in the medical medium feed
is
now i have an answer
for why i have vertigo
they told me it was crystals
in the ear
crystals in the air right in the ear
crystals in your ears right
but the person was 20 years old
you can't get crystals in the ear at 20.
you get them when you're in your 50s
60s up and 70s
and that doesn't cause
vertigo crystals in the ear do not cause
vertigo vertigo is caused by
epstein-barr inflaming the vagus nerve
and here you've got a 20 year old that's
waking up to it through medical medium
information and waking up to it saying
wait a minute i'm 20 years old
i crystals in the air don't even exist
in a 20 year old
by the way long haul covet that's
medical medium information as far as
epstein-barr reactivating and being
long-haul covet because kova knocks down
the immune system then the obscene bar
reactivates that's published first by
medical medium it's medical medium info
you're hearing it out there from podcast
doctors they're spineless they stole it
they took it they poached it they're
using it they're pretending it didn't
come from here when it was published
here first she goes to show you
integrity
there's a war on in podcast land
the doctors and podcasts are trying
everything they can
to get paid millions of dollars by
advertisers spending millions of dollars
in ads and wanting to be um wanting to
be famous in their podcast it has
nothing to do with people getting better
they act like it is but it's not has
nothing to do with that
elena says i used to work in
neurological clinic
the amount of bs that they tell patients
is insane
quote that's amazing it's an amazing
quote because it's it's not only true i
know i not only witnessed it out there
myself between all the contacts and all
the physicians i know and i've talked to
throughout the years that is so solidly
true
guys we're doing the anti-bug cleanse
and i'm making the stew
and i'm pumped up about this because
it's really good smells so good
it smells so good
what i just want to run by the
announcement real quick if you guys just
came on here okay so at 6 15 eastern i'm
gonna be on rumble exclusively
just so you know and that's 3 15
pacific time
time wise i'm gonna be on a rumble
exclusive i hope you guys all come
in and chill out and we're gonna it's at
rumble.com forward slash medical medium
right
good to see you guys on tick tock by the
way
we see we got a few people on there
and good to see you guys on telegram
just letting you guys know telegram and
rumble are gonna probably gonna be more
of the future
home for medical medium i want you to
kind of keep that in mind sign up to my
newsletter so you can know where i go or
where i am sign up to the medical medium
newsletter go to medicalmedium.com
sign up to the medical medium newsletter
tell other people to sign up to the
medical medium newsletter too please so
you know because i'm going to be at me
we
rumble and telegram a lot
in the future
you just go where you're appreciated
you go where you're appreciated
right
so many nurses and doctors go up it went
up
so many nurses and doctors go into
medicine as idealists and want to heal
the world
yeah
cold white spring good to see you
cold white spring i feel the same way
i do
all right you guys
so we're doing the stew
okay i think we're okay i think we're
okay
where am i
tara appleman good to see you bless your
heart amazing person amazing human being
absolutely amazing human being
they don't make them like you
doing the anti-bug cleanse
[Music]
um this is day two the anti-bug cleanse
just a reminder anybody coming on do you
have a copy
i mean i know there's some people out
there like i don't have a copy of it ah
do i really have to read a book
it's a book you can hand to somebody and
save their life
it's a book you can give to a family
member
i talk about the levels in here for the
anti-bug cleanse let's go in there now
medical medium books are not just a
business card because that's what books
are in health their business card
they're just to start your career off so
you can um get the word out on whatever
it is you're selling
medical media books were were created to
just turn lives around and heal people
and save lives
that was that was the main reason
because there was something
interesting about medical media books
and what it was was unique information
never before seen in holistic medicine
or conventional medicine unique
information
unique
original
let's go into the anti-bug cleanse
here we are we're going into the
different levels what level are you guys
at are you at level one eggs dairy
gluten soft drinks telegram you hear
that message by the way you guys if you
guys haven't subscribed to to my
telegram
okay t dot m e
forward slash medical medium that's
telegram if you haven't subscribed
please go and do that because i'm doing
private audio messages
private audio messages i talked about on
telegram on the private audio message
today i'm talking about the egg shortage
that's happening right now it's going to
get pretty crazy the egg shortage is
getting crazier and crazier and the egg
shortage
is happening out there right big
and
this doesn't mean go buy a chicken it
doesn't mean go buy a whole bunch of
chickens and start a chicken coop that's
not what it means this is your chance to
break away from eggs because eggs feed
the bugs that keep you sick so here's a
chance you can actually break away
because there's going to be an egg
shortage
there already is
right
there's an egg shortage
so if you stay away from eggs dairy
products milk cheese butter gluten soft
drinks boom level one out the door
level one out the door
if you want to take it to level two
get rid of pork it's a little piggy here
got a little piggy
get rid of pork get rid of tuna
right
people think
like sushi is healthy but all i see with
sushi
is that right there
that's all i see with sushi
okay
but this but with vinegar
so mercury with vinegar so i'm not just
going to have mercury i'm going to have
mercury and vinegar
so healthy
anybody coming on here vinegar is not
healthy at all it's something you don't
want to
do so stew is definitely a stew
there's no question so what i'm doing is
turning down the heat
that baby looks good
okay
pork is a blood thickener so here's the
rules
the anti-bug cleanse is really awesome
you get away from bug fuel
you get away from blood thickeners
right
you get away from
dehydrators of the body and you get away
from toxin contributors
so we're on day two what level did you
pick right
and what i love about taking out pork is
you you open up the doors for more
oxygen inside your blood because pork
swallows up the oxygen and takes it away
level three
soy and lamb
industrial oils palm oil canola oil corn
oil safflower oil soybean oil
fish all fish except for salmon trout
and sardines
it's level three level four everything i
just said
plus vinegar including apple cider
vinegar fermented foods including
kombucha tea coconut amino acids
including that
caffeine including coffee matcha
chocolate
that's level four can we go to level
five
right
all the above
plus all grains except for millet and
oats
and then we get all oils out olive oil
all the healthy oils olive oil walnut
oil sesame oil avocado oil we get rid of
all the oils
okay i love how the vegan doctors think
that like
sunflower oil sunflower seeds is like
the reason why the whole world's sick
the whole world's sick because of
sunflower oil and sunflower seeds
really
i'm scratching my head on that one
because i got friends that never ate a
sunflower seed in their life
and they're so sick
a lot of the vegan doctors come out with
a new thing every other minute
food science dictates that it's not a
mega
it's not omega-6s that are good for you
now it's omega-3s it's a we're all sick
the whole world is sick because of
omega-6 it's because of sunflower seeds
so you're sick in bed right now on
mattress island with your lupus because
of sunflower seeds do you understand how
ironically stupid the whole thing is how
every time the vegan doctors even speak
it's almost embarrassing like i can't
handle it
every time the vegan doctors speak out
there it's like holy are you sitti
oh my god here we go again what is he
saying
what is he saying what is dr saying
michelle l haha every other minute
something else exactly
the reason why the whole world is sick
is because of potatoes
because i'm scratching my head on that
francisca my doctors says my anemia is
due to veganism frustrating
unbelievable
so now the vegan doctors believe the
whole world is sick
because of sunflower seeds
how many sunflower seeds have you eaten
in your lifetime
so your your multiple sclerosis ms right
ms your lupus your fibromyalgia your rna
your hashimoto's thyroiditis your eczema
psoriasis from sunflower seeds says the
the vegan doctors
my god but no they'll just come out with
another stupid book
and another
and they'll put a million dollars behind
it with the pr company
and they'll sell crap
and they'll send everybody down the
wrong direction and no one stops it
because you can't it's a train that
takes you to hell
and i love this a doctor is going to
tell you so your doctor says my anemia
is due to veganism when literally
there are
millions tens of millions of people that
eat animal protein that are anemic
so i'm scratching my head on that
there's tens of millions of people women
that are anemic that eat animal protein
but for some reason you're you're you're
anemias because of
does that doctor have any idea it's
epstein-barr course night is there no
medical medium information and that
epstein bar creates anemia because it
eats iron there's a lot of varieties of
ebv that eat iron
all right so we're level five plus bonus
we'll talk about the bonuses so we're
level five here you don't have to be
level five you don't even have to do the
anti-bug cleanse i just love having you
here it's fun
so
level five
all grains we take out we leave millet
we live oats in right we leave oats and
we take the healthier oils out we take
the oils out
and then for bonus
we cut out salt baby we cut out
seasonings not fresh herbs and spices
that are single but the bad seasoning
mixes that have all the msg and other
garbage in them right we avoid fats all
together you avoid your nuts and seeds
and your avocados and your oils you
avoid all the fats and if you're an
animal protein person you avoid all the
animal proteins too right you avoid it
all
also
remove alcohol
natural artificial flavors now i got to
get rid of my ale i can't believe it i'm
on level five now this is spice hot
apple juice
you really need in order to understand
that too you need to get the book
because you need to read the
troublemakers chapter
get rid of alcohol artificial flavors
nutritional yeast
citric wait a minute i got to get rid of
my nutritional yeast
crap
by the way nutritional yeast has msg in
it
it's got fake b12 in it
okay that they add to it
you know you know why they add stuff to
nutritional yeast did you guys know why
it's the same way they add
uh they fortify white bread
they enrich
white bread
and white rice
right
they enrich
white rice flour and white bread
right wheat flour that's been stripped
of everything
they fortify
yeast is not a food for human
consumption
so they fortify it
and then they get you addicted to that
glutamic acid
and then you stay sick and you never
heal completely
because you're trapped in this
alternative medicine hell right here
which is nutritional yeast
nutritional east that's the bonus let's
let's have some uh
let's have some stew
they get a bowl
let me get the top off the pot
all right so i'm gonna i'm gonna get the
stew out right now
all right this is so good
i can't even tell you guys
let's get the my finger out there
someone
burn it off because this is one piping
hot
stew right now
there we go
wow that's incredible
what i'm gonna do is i'm gonna pop some
parsley on here so let me
throw
that baby here for a moment let's get
some fresh parsley right on top
guys hang on okay
just wanna
now you can put bigger pieces of parsley
on there if you want
right
i'm gonna do smaller pieces
okay boom i'm gonna pop a little bit of
fresh parsley on top
look at that i like a lot of parsley so
after
you know after we're done here what i'm
gonna do is probably put even some more
on
i just love that
that is the portabella stew right there
you guys fat free you don't clog up your
veins and arteries with any kind of fat
at all
right
you don't
rob the oxygen out of your blood
you got a chance to heal your liver kill
off bugs and starve your bugs
right
so it's really good taking the twig off
the top
a little bit of a twig on there
that's incredible right you guys
make sure they're on rumble don't miss
it
because i'm going to be on rumble
at 6 15 eastern 3 15 pacific
if you're overseas or somewhere else do
the math make sure you're there unless
it's like four in the morning and you
need to be sleeping
god would go to bed if you need to be
sleeping
if you're having a problem getting on
rumble because it's a brand new live
stream situation they got going there
refresh refresh
okay
and
you know lemon bomb love you're gonna be
there
no way
so
and you can also press top video up
there press play on top video up there
you'll see it
you guys i'm going to
instagram i'm going to turn telegram
back on because i love you guys
i'm going to turn tick-tock back on i
love you guys too
so i'm going to telegram
ig
tick-tock all at one time and after
we're done there we're gonna have some
fun there after we're done there i'm
gonna be on the rumble exclusively
so
all right
you guys know i care and thank you for
being here on day two of the anti-bug
cleanse and make sure
make sure
you someday have this right here
as
something that you can keep
and learn how to protect yourself okay
you guys check out the blood the blood
draw podcast too everybody should listen
to that later on tonight or tomorrow
critical that you get reminded on how to
protect yourself because you'll get
snagged you'll be at a doctor's office
and you'll kind of forget but not really
have enough that info and data and
you'll be
kind of a little worried me being a
little sheepish because you're just a
little scared and they draw your life's
blood out of you and then you get sicker
medical mean podcasted apple podcast
that's where you listen to the
uncensored version all right you guys
love you
i'll see you in a little bit