[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
mold
talking about mold
ready mold on this
got some mold on here
[Music]
good old mold
day five Medical Main brain shot therapy
challenge
[Music]
I'm excited you guys
let's talk about it
try holding your breath that long
dear Lord
I had to give it up I actually had to
finally give up so we are on it right
now day five medical medium brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge I'm excited
about it let's go into a little bit
let's get going
mold exposure
mold exposure shots
the exposure shots but the mold exposure
forewarning man
telling you right now I've had the mold
exposure shot before
it's not the tastiest shot you be the
judge of it that's all I can tell you
right now you be the judge of that shot
and the taste of that shot
because that shot
doesn't taste sweet
doesn't taste yummy
it's not the best tasting shot
but that shot is rigged and it's it
levels you out and I'm excited about it
because it is a mold exposure shot
yeah and it's intense it's intense
but sometimes you need the intense stuff
you're gonna battle the mold exposure
really important so mold exposure
all right
when to use the mold exposure shot you
ready for this guy's visiting or living
in a moldy house or building if you're
visiting a moldy building you don't know
it's moldy maybe you're at the dentist
office there's mold everywhere maybe
you're somewhere else maybe maybe you're
at the veterinarian clinic maybe you're
somewhere else maybe you're in the store
or whatever it is buildings mold
exposure how about this one
working in a moldy office or other
workspace so if you're working in a
workspace
that there's mold exposure right now
this one
inhaling mold breathing it in right
breathing in that mold
okay inhaling mold off another person's
clothing it's like give somebody a hug
and they're they're in a moldy house and
you're like how you doing you're giving
them a hug
right and they're getting it all over
all over you it's a moldy shirt
I think your shirt's moldy
oh my god I think I'm wearing a moldy
shirt right now so if you got mold
exposure shot if you're up against any
of that consuming water contaminated
with mildew or mold spores or eating
moldy food and moldy food isn't the
worst problem unless it's moldy meat
that's another story some moldy food
moldy Dairy which is mold moldy meat
right mold right
these are just some of the examples
right here if you if you're worried
about mold exposure in general that's
another reason and if you're not worried
at all you don't have to do the shot but
here's the thing the medical medium
brain shots do things for us that even
break the boundaries
you take the shot for one thing and it
can do wonders in all kinds of different
ways so even if you're like well I don't
know if I'm up against mold right now
but let me try this mold exposure shot
you'd be surprised be surprised indeed
all right let's move through this a
little bit okay
so now we're gonna go
to my next little spot right here
medical medium brain shot therapy are
you guys new are you new to this new to
medical leave information did you just
hop on here and you're like where am I
the whole bit we're doing brain saver
this is the brand saver book spring
saver protocols right there these are
two very large books packed with
information
front and back packed and jammed just
letting you know so if you get a chance
check out the brain saver books
amazon.com us 40 off Karen Churchill
said last shot must have cleared stuff
I have chronic fatigue syndrome but
after the shot was the Energizer Bunny
incredible but that's the power of these
shots they're Miracles is what they are
they're powerful they're Miracles it's
what we needed I begged SOC to keep on
giving me incredible information these
books are packed with this kind of
information the healing Let The Healing
begin Let The Healing happen so we're in
the brain saver books if you don't know
what's going on and you've got here
okay King said medical media mold
exposure was strong I want to see
Anthony's face when he drinks it this is
what it will be it'll be you're ready
the mold exposure shot I'm gonna drink
it
that's what it's gonna be
I have a feeling
because I know because I did the mold
exposure shot before and that's what
happened to me but maybe you're like
you're not like that maybe maybe not so
maybe you're less dramatic and you're
that's not going to happen to you you're
just gonna make up a face right but
that's what I did and maybe you're just
gonna make a face and drink them all the
exposure shot you're gonna drink and
you're just like
you know he saw that movie Elf right do
you remember that movie Elf right I
remember when elf was in the department
store and that lady was like fruit spray
anybody fruit spray and he goes I love
fruit spray and it was a perfume it was
a perfume and so she took that perfume
bottle and she sprayed it in his mouth
and he went no no no no that's where
right that's what this is gonna be like
the mold exposure shot or you might like
it you might be somebody that actually
likes it
that's the other thing too so think
about that
all right so medical mean brain shot
therapy offers instant relief
instant relief it absorbs deep into the
blood vessels in your mouth
Nobody Knows the combinations comes from
above
nobody ever knew and ever will never
know
unless they get it here that if you take
fennel bulb
radish
basil oregano Rosemary and ginger and
you put them together in the order and
you juice it
and you run it through your juicer and
nobody knows the power that's there
against mold exposure comes from above
and if you get a chance 20 off BM M 1500
right here so the Omega mm 1500 you guys
know I'm working with them now
something has something sad has happened
in the medical medium Community there's
been a lot of advertising from the
Sharks a lot of heavy money lenders
behind it pushing
other juicers people buy the juicers
they don't squeeze as much juice out and
then you have to buy double the produce
and the juicer doesn't pay for itself
this is the mm 1500 20 off it pays for
itself it has the compression it
actually squeezes the crap out of the
juice you use less produce you save
money the money goes back into your bank
and then you can buy more produce
it eventually pays for itself the juicer
that's my experience and that's other
people's experiences but there's some
juicers that are tricky they'll say
things like oh for large amounts of
juicing that's silly it's all the same
you're still juicing it all and it still
ends up in the same place it's a scam
the other scam is you know this juicer
works this way this way but they don't
get it it's a lot of metal in those
juicers that's one problem the other
problem is all the juice escapes nobody
gets it you have to run a lot more
produce in it I don't want to be the
juicer guy screaming about a juicer
every 10 minutes but when I go quiet and
I don't talk about the juicer for a long
time the Sharks come in and they take
advantage of people and they rip them
off and that's what's happened so what I
recommend
is since that's the route somebody's
gonna go if you're looking to save money
you're looking to buy less produce for
what you need to do and your juices then
look into the mm 1500 or 900 save up
whatever it's 20 off wait for the sales
when they come on whenever they do
that's my recommendation and I haven't
talked about the juicer forever and
that's what happened I can't be
everywhere at all times and I can
literally I'm trying to get the books
written trying to get this information
to you in the minute I like let one
thing drop for a little while people get
screwed over and it's the saddest thing
I've ever seen it's just as I don't even
know what to say so medical medium brain
shots absorb quickly into the blood
vessels and they rush to the brain
rush to the brain
that is what they do you experience it
for me for you it could be the first
shot I mean the first sip of the shot
for me it's the second sip every time
it's always the second sip for me so
when I'm doing the shot of course you
could send your shot down in one shot
like that boom you got it down there but
what I do is I sip the shot so I'm like
sip the first Sip and then I do the
second Sip Sip and boom it hits that's
for me is when it's starting to hit and
you like you'll probably feel it too on
the second shot
Allah Monica says I love my Omega Juicer
incredible I do too Sherry says love my
mega right I do too and so anyway when
it comes down to the brain shot
therapies they absorb quickly in the
mouth and it's incredible okay these
specially formulated shots have the
ability to reset and rewire the brain
so what the shots do
like the obsessive shifter shot betrayal
and broken trust shot
okay all the different shots what they
do is they help to reset and rewire the
brain the emotional sensors of the brain
is one place they help to reset and
rewire the emotional center of the brain
since one place now our brain gets
injured by toxins poisons junk garbage
pathogens metals
emotional hurt our brain can get injured
physically from all that the neurons can
get burned up so what the brain shot
therapies do is they rewire and reset
the brain they help to rewire and reset
the brain which is incredible people are
always asking me about it you sir right
they're you know they're always asking
me to they're like what kind of juicer
what kind of juice or whatever and so
the name of the juicer if you're if
you're you know the in the description
you'll see it in the bio bio you'll see
that the juicer mm-1500 or mm-900 see a
mega juicer mm1500
mm-900 20 off right now if you want to
know and here's the thing
you get dry pulp you guys you guys you
get dry pulp I'll show you today
and people are asking the comments I saw
that too you you when the dry pulp comes
out you squeeze everything out of that
produce
and you're saving money you're cutting
your costs for me it cuts it in half
almost cuts it completely in half for me
that's what it's done so it's like I buy
less of everything that juicer pays for
itself it's like incredible that's why
that company is why I've endorsed that
company fully endorsed them the heck
yeah I will
you know and so it's important to know
so the mold exposure shot
okay is really potent and you're gonna
feel it you're gonna you're gonna feel
okay here's a question Angie says do the
ingredients contain binders to fully
remove the mold from the cellular level
my functional medicine doctor needs us
on good binders too charcoal Etc
charcoals charcoal doesn't remove things
and that's the misinformation out there
and
no disrespect to the functional medicine
doctor
if you read the brain saver books
you'll learn what charcoal does
it suffocates the lining of the
intestinal tract not allowing nutrients
to pass if you're on charcoal long term
long term
you'll get so nutrient deficient your
hair will fall out everything will go
wrong in a year or two and it'll be a
nightmare I talk about it in the books
charcoal is madness the heavy metal
detox smoothies in the books
really cleans up the intestinal tract
and crosses the blood-brain barrier
getting Metals out but also cleans up
things that shouldn't be in the
intestinal tract and on a cellular level
powerful cleanses right here in these
books but the point I'm trying to say is
charcoal is a mishap it started in
conventional medicine
and then it went to alternative medicine
because alternative medicine didn't know
how to break away from conventional
medicine on that one
so people who are all alternative
they get wrapped up with old
conventional medicine standards charcoal
was an old conventional medicine Theory
of possibly trying to remove something
from the intestinal tract with no
science behind it that shows it
got to be careful with the charcoal
thing I'm just being straight up if you
take charcoal on a regular basis because
you think you're cleaning something up
no disrespect for any practitioners or
doctors or anybody well you think you're
cleaning something up with charcoal
what happens is the charcoal sticks to
the lining of the intestinal tract for
weeks suffocating good bacteria and
suffocating the cells of the intestinal
lining so nutrients don't easily pass
through into your hepatic portal vein up
the highway to your liver and no one
realizes this and it's sad
I just want it you know but listen do
what your doctor says if your doctor
says charcoal do what your doctor says
I'm not telling you to go against your
doctor's wishes or your functional
medicine doctor's wishes if your
functional medicine doctor says do
charcoal you do what your doctor says
I'm just telling you from what I tell
doctors out there and what I've what
I've you know learned through the
information that I have
so let's
let's I think we had plenty of talks
about the charcoal
I'm gonna be a podcast doctor and talk
about charcoals supplementation of my
podcast I'm gonna invite a guest on I'm
gonna invite a functional medicine
doctor out there I was gonna save
everybody being charcoal
I'm also gonna have a glass of wine I
have a glass of wine right here
this glass of wine I got from I got this
from the valley fifty two thousand
dollars a glass of glass perfectly right
price
hmm
it's glass of Wine's delicious
tastes like apple juice
um
Kirsten says I have to tell you I have
never felt as good as I do now in years
this has truly been life-changing for me
incredible Kirsten that's what I want it
to be that's what I live for that's what
I was born for that's why I received the
messages at age four about all this
that's why I was given that the gift
that actually here a voice which is
really a gift for you guys it's not a
gift for me it's a pain in my butt but
it's a gift for you guys to have this
information it's why I'm hated so much
too
I'm hated so much
but yet but yet the books are the the
most selling Health books in the world
eight years running now but yet I'm
hated because people just don't like
knowing where I get the information it
drives them insane
I take up real estate in so many
people's heads out there that hate me I
just take up all the real estate in
their minds in their heads they don't
understand how all the new information
can constantly keep on pouring out from
over here
and they poach it whenever they can and
they try to step on my face while
they're doing it but either way the
point is is I'm here to be at your
service and At Your Service I need you
to heal because I need you to heal as
many people that can heal until I can't
be here anymore on this planet and I'm
leaving this place and then today I'm
leaving this place
and I'm on my last breath
I'm gonna say I did everything I can to
get that many people healed and the
books will live on and keep on healing
people before I sign off
all right we gotta keep on going you
guys
we're talking about brain shot therapy
if you guys just got here some medical
me and brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge we're doing the mold exposure
shot I got the mold exposure ingredients
we already talked about the mm 1500
mm-900 and what it does and how it saves
money and everything else 20 off we're
going into the book now we're in brain
safer do you
do use right here brain saver protocols
brain saver
let's move into this oh by the way if
you just got here and you don't even
know what any of this is and you're just
like what the hell is going on
medicalmedium.com
by the way which we're enhancing every
single day we're making that
medicalmedium.com a place where you can
find everything and anything and it's
free free
it's free
can you believe it
all free go to medicalme.com download
sign up to the brain shot challenge we
have five days left and download your
free pdf with your grocery store list
shopping list and all that stuff
you ready guys I'm reading out a brain
saver for a couple of minutes are you
with me virtually every human being on
the planet experiences at least one
symptom at this point
foreign
every person on this planet experiences
at least one symptom at this point is
that good is that normal is that
supposed to happen it's not supposed to
happen
every single person on this planet every
single football player every single
tennis player every single soccer player
every single Olympian actor your athlete
every single actor actress every single
person on this planet from royalty
all the way down to Common Folk
every single person on this planet
experiences One symptom at this point in
time in our history right now and if you
say if you've talked to somebody and
like I don't have anything wrong with me
I beg to differ I guarantee you they got
something whether it's a scratchy throat
that they're not remembering or talking
about that they get periodically whether
it's a little low energy at different
times whether it's a UTI periodically
that they fail to tell you they had last
year whatever it is they get one symptom
they have it and they're living with it
one condition or whatever
we're at a place where chronic illness
is growing comments I tried the
fragrance shot headache disappeared
incredible Francis incredible
you can't get that in alternative
medicine it doesn't exist what you
experienced with that doesn't exist
medical medium books give people results
heals long-term chronic illnesses we
know that gets people out of wheelchairs
recovers people from mattress Island and
then you got the brain shot therapies
and people are getting instant results
like Spirit of compassion told me they
would and I couldn't wait for you guys
to get this information
we're at a place where chronic illness
is growing at rates we've never seen
before in our history
there are different levels from very
mild to devastatingly severe you see it
out there people who are twitching and
spasming and they're just like losing it
they're just they're they're tortured
they're suffering there's people with
all kinds of conditions right now
there's The Not So Sick group you know
the not not so sick group is you got
some symptoms you go to your functional
medicine doctor he tells you you got
sibo you got this you got that that's
the not so sick group you get a little
bit of a little bit of energy problems
you're going to your naturopath and they
say you got an adrenal issue you're
going to your other doctor but you're
still living your life drinking your
coffee doing whatever you want eating
what you want exercising That's The Not
So Sick group
there's The Not So Sick group those who
are experiencing symptoms like I'm
talking about
and still functioning that's a not so
sick group you guys they're working
they're being productive they're
exercising they're playing all day they
have all their Privileges and they're
getting all their self-care 24 7. That's
The Not So Sick group right
those who are frightfully ill those for
whom each day is about surviving is
another group
which was all for medical medium
information to heal and help all these
decades the group that really was
suffering that's a big deal
this increase in sickness like never
before is only going to keep developing
so are we evolving in the right
direction
so are we moving forward or backwards
are our physical bodies any different
than they were in ancient Rome 2500
years ago I'm reading brain saver you
guys
he came on here and we're in the medical
medium brain shot therapy class which is
really incredible
and if you believe that we evolved since
then we are evolving faster than what's
evolving around us no we're not because
we're sicker than ever before in our
history and that's the whole point check
this out talk about the immune system
because we're talking about mold
exposure shots today and I said mold
can trigger things it can lower the
immune system and saying that for 35
plus years it lowers the immune system
there's no way humankind could
physically evolve faster than any of
these forces against us that's why we're
all getting sick so we're having the
medals and we're having the chemical
exposure and we got the fragrances the
perfumes colognes air freshener scented
candles the detergents we got all that
nanotechnology that's in chemicals we
got the pesticides herbicides fungicides
we got all that junk being sprayed all
over us on our Lawns around our
buildings and apartment buildings and on
our highways we got stuff flying out of
the air we got mosquito spray being
dumped on us did you guys know that
every single town in the U.S is getting
dumped on by mosquito spray lethal spray
just coming out of helicopters and
drones and landing on everybody is that
nice and that's what they do but yet the
mosquitoes are still here hmm
it's kind of funny too because they also
genetically modify mosquitoes and they
let them out by the trillions so they
have a mosquito Factory does this make a
lot of sense they have a mosquito
Factory and they're letting out
trillions of mosquitoes that they breed
and then they're using you know
our money to make sure that they dump
lots of mosquito spray on every single
town and city in this country and around
the world huh but let's keep on breeding
and letting out trillions of mosquitoes
and then keep on dumping spray does that
sound like a great place
so we're up against all this stuff our
immune systems weren't made to put up
with all this BS doesn't say that in the
book put up with all this BS assist put
up with all these chemicals
either the number of varieties
are the outright quantity of these
chemicals including everything we talked
about with like radiation and everything
every time something foreign enters into
our body we're reading out a brain saver
enters into our body
our immune system has to gobble it up
and Gobble it up and Gobble it up
so our immune system the white blood
cell here has to eat it up so we're an
expo we're exposed to some type of mold
right because I got a moldy rag right
here
my robot wasn't happy about the moly rag
did you see that the robot was not happy
robot was very put off by The Moldy rag
so like this mold spot here that I have
when we get mold in us and it goes in
our body our white blood cells have to
eat it up
so our white blood cells have to go and
Gobble it all up whatever that mold went
to whatever it is
and it has to just eat it up and Gobble
it all up
Maria why did they create GMOs
mosquitoes
maybe to create the need for trillions
of gallons of mosquito spray on every
single town and city in the world
do you see what see how it works
who's creating those ketos uh mosquitoes
are created and they're dumping all the
stuff on you see how it works
so there isn't any real mold on this
towel I don't want anybody to be upset
there's no mold it's a Juice Spot it's a
green juice spot from juicing and it's
on this toggle so the towel is clean it
doesn't have any mold on it I know
somebody was upset see there's there it
is the green spot right there
smells like green juice
because I was making a shot this morning
okay you guys
so here we are your immune cells have to
gobble up any mold and any mold exposure
just like that so we need to know that's
how it works
and
let's go into it just a little bit if
you guys got a second I feel it I feel
that our halftime or half time is coming
up any second so I want to get this
information going oh
yeah my immune cell's falling apart
they weren't designed to fight off
engineered viruses either they weren't
designed to fight off chemicals but our
immune cells have to fight off
everything it has no choice it wasn't
designed to fight off radiation but it
has no choice but to fight it off and it
wasn't dissolved it wasn't sorry
designed to fight off certain varieties
of mold but yet it has to fight it off
so our immune cells have to go up
against so much that we're up against
all the time
so how long your blood cells can last
like this one that's Fallen apart on me
right now
it's up against all that mold and
everything how long a blood cell can
last
depends on how toxic a substance is and
how strong your immune system is so when
your white blood cell gobbles up a mold
Spore
or anything
it eventually dies or can die on the
spot and explode so then mold can become
a trigger
because as mold is knocking down our
immune system
something else inside of us can rise up
any kind of pathogens any other kind of
problems and then we kind of get
triggered we can get sick
depending on what kind of mold depending
on how strong your immune system is
depending on what else your body is
being protected by with your immune
system what else is happening inside
your body all of this matters and are
you on a lot of caffeine it could be
somebody that's like drinking a lot of
caffeine then that lowers the immune
system you could be somebody that's
eating a lot of chocolate that lowers
the immune system
you know what's crazy
uh the chocolate dealers the drug
dealers
they'll tell you that chocolate's great
for you they'll throw up they'll throw
out any science they can at you to tell
you that chocolate's great for you the
drug dealers right
but what you don't realize is chocolate
knocks down the immune system it hinders
the immune system knocks it down that's
why if you just if you eat too much of
it and just you're just gonna be like on
this like crazy cacao high right your
immune system is getting trashed when
you go on that crazy cacao ride it
knocks down the immunity the immune
cells
somebody compromised by all these
different pathogens chemicals and
everything else that's out there gets
all of a sudden exposed to mold it makes
it even harder and it makes it difficult
but then somebody else
that doesn't have any pathogens or other
compromises they expose to the same mold
they get exposed to the same variety
mold somebody else in the same house was
exposed to they may not get affected
some people get affected more than
others
mold is a mystery like that all depends
on what's happening in the person's body
[Music]
foreign
let's get moving on here we go
somebody said then why does your body
ask for so much more chocolate or so
much for chocolate why does our body ask
for chocolate
do you guys know the answer to that can
you guys answer that question for the
person
why does the body crave chocolate if
chocolate lowers the immune system you
guys got the answer right
you don't need me for that answer
I mean we know that those are short
halftime Robinson said a smiley face
that's a short halftime that was really
short
because someone said I saw that it never
asks because of the caffeine addiction
Michelle L got it
you guys want to do the robot with me
let's hit the halftime
let's do it you guys want to do a good
one we'll do it right in your house you
guys are doing it
if you're if you can't stand up or
something you got to sit down just do it
sitting down
yeah
let's start
[Music]
awesome
foreign
did you do the robot
okay
so what happens is yeah
it's about our immune system so mold
can eat up did you guys hold your breath
except because I hold my breath while
you're the robot the whole time
anyway maybe I should change that up
start breathing
when I'm doing the robot
but you can't stay super still if you do
that it's good like you're breathing
like I'm a robot that's alive I'm
breathing while I'm working
okay
Aubry says studies show when craving
sweets it means you're lacking in
essential nutrients really do those same
studies know why anybody's sick
to the same studies know why everybody's
got lupus Hashimoto's multiple sclerosis
or anything else
they need to read the caffeine chapter
in the brain saver books so you know
so when you're craving a chocolate bar
you're not craving something sweet
you're craving the caffeine the high
that's what you're craving a chocolate
bar you're craving all that caffeine
breaks down the immune system that's
what I was talking about before you read
the caffeine section in the brain saver
books
so the thing is with studies so studies
show
when creating sweets it means you're
lacking essential nutrients right
but studies don't know why anybody is
sick so it's it's a tough call there
you can be sick for 30 years and read
that study along with thousands of other
studies and stay sick for 30 more years
you can be sick for 60 years 70 years
your whole life's sick
with 10 different diagnoses labels a
hundred symptoms
and then you'll get the study shows why
you're craving sweets or the study shows
caffeine's good for you or the study
shows that now coffee is good for you or
the study shows that antioxidants are
good for you something or some whatever
it is
it doesn't it's not enough so you can't
it's like how do you trust the study
when they don't have one answer to why
anybody's sick it's really painful when
you think about it and then you don't
know how the study works and I talk
about that in medical medium books
Melissa said thank you for the trauma
loss brain shot just in time for my
mother-in-law's passing oh so sorry to
hear that it really does help I've been
a friend of mine had something happen to
them and I I recommended the trauma loss
brain shot too and it gave them some
peace as well so I'm happy to hear that
uh what I what I recommend is you use it
a lot
you use it a lot so you do it more than
once and I was telling a friend of mine
you do the trauma shock loss uh you know
shot you do it more than once
Robin said did you did the dream shot
last night
and wow what a beautiful meaningful
dream I had incredible
I I have a personal connection with the
dream shot
I love that one I was doing that one
when Spirit of compassion gave me this
information and I was getting it all
down for the books
I was I wasn't getting a lot of sleep I
was trying to get with the book
deadlines done trying to get the books
done and I only got like a half an hour
sleep
a one-hour sleep some days and I was
just pushing and pushing and pushing so
when I would get like a one or two hour
chance to sleep
I would take that dream shot down
and then
oh my God the dreams I had within that
one hour that two hour it was like
unbelievable what was happening it was
incredible I mean it was revelational it
was just on just incredible so all right
so you're talking about the immune
system we're talking about the mold
exposure how our immune system has to
gobble up the mold has to eat it up
right and how our immune cells they
weaken but we're up against so many
other things as I was talking about
earlier I know we gave you guys the
mosquito spray talk and everything else
and I didn't even give you the Sea Trail
talk too all the sea Trails right the
stuff pouring down on us all the sea
trails
okay the letter c the letter c not s e a
the letter c for anyone just coming on
right now we're day five the medical
meaning brain shot therapy challenge
we're doing the mold exposure shot you
can sign up free at medicalmedium.com
get your downloads your free pdf your
grocery store list
and we're on day five
so what you see in front of me are a
bunch of ingredients I'll talk about
that for a little bit
we got some radishes here
let's get them up here so you can see
them better radishes if you guys can see
me here we've got fennel bulb right here
we have basil
all of it's fresh
we have oregano
which is incredible
got that one out of my garden we got
rosemary
as well
we have ginger
so these are the five ingredients
lupus free with celery 333
says all the shots make me feel I'm
sorry all the shots make me sleep
soundly I love them regardless of taste
you're a brave person some of these
taste pretty rough and that's incredible
Kim Miller says I feel my nervous system
regulating and my vagus nerve healing
already with the shots incredible my
heart beat felt so normal last night I
felt so good this is what I wanted
this is what I was promised
when I was taking the information down
for the brain shot therapy for the books
from Spirit of compassion
I was promised you guys would get some
healing done
from these brain shots
that's what I was told that's what I was
promised
I don't like broken promises
I don't like being told something that's
not going to happen and and it does in
when SOC tells me
like The Meta like the medical medium
heavy metal detox cleanses are going to
get the metals out they do and they have
I I know people I know doctors
that are seeing results in their
patients that's unreal by using the
medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanses right now out of the brain
saver books so
when it came down to the brain shot
therapy like and SOC was telling me
and I was writing it down how they give
instant relief and I was writing that
down and then how they absorb in the
mouth that I was writing that down
and then how the brain shots are
systematically synergistically put
together
and because of their combination they
can do this certain thing I was just
like oh my God this is incredible
instant results is what I want it to
happen and that's what was promised of
me promise to me many many will have
instant results and some will be getting
relief
that they noticed a little bit later so
that's another thing with the brain shot
therapy so here's how it works
many people are going to get instant
results I will tell you this you will
feel something instantly no matter what
the results can come later through the
progression of the cleanse 10 day 20 day
or 30 day the results can come later to
how many you do a day it says it in the
book all the details are in here the
results can come
even later and sneak up on you but
you'll get you'll feel something
instantly within like for me it's second
sift every single time for you it might
be after you had the shot and you sat
there for five minutes but each person
you're gonna get so you're gonna feel
something
Susan said I slept so soundly last night
and feel rested for the first time in a
long time since starting brain shots
last week that's exactly what I'm
talking about you're getting results
and it's a week later and you're getting
results
Esther says I hated cilantro before I
did the heavy metal detox movie and now
I actually like it that's incredible
used to gag drinking it because I would
juice it separate from the smoothie
now I put more in to get the taste that
means your metals are dropping
your chemical load is dropping
I talk about that in the books Esther
did you see it in here I talk about it
in the book right here it's in the brain
saver books I go into detail about how
it works with cilantro and how you can
hate the taste to begin with be totally
repulsed by it and then you start to
heal and get the metals and chemicals
out
but doing the heavy metal detox smoothie
or cleanse and then what happens is all
of a sudden you like the cilantro and it
gets better and it gets better and it
gets better how incredible
so much good information to talk about
let's talk about this now
let's go
we're in the medical medium brain shot
therapy cleanses right here
we're an entry level
but can I say something if you guys are
okay with this
Enlightenment is not about being
all-knowing Enlightenment is the freedom
to be at peace before you have because
you have full control over what resides
inside of you
and inside your brain since we don't
have control about whatever resides out
there because that's what happens you
guys I'm on page 516 for the moment
we don't have full control of the
outside world
Enlightenment is having full
cover your your body that's a big part
of enlightenment
so when you use your free will
to work on your healing Enlightenment is
there
that's what enlightenment really is it's
your free will saying I am going to work
on my healing process
I am going to do something for my health
that can turn it around
I'm going to work on my brain I'm going
to use my own brain to heal my own brain
that's Enlightenment right there I'm
going to take my free will my intentions
I'm going to direct it to healing myself
with powerful information from above
so I can heal
that's enlightenment
I'm going to take control over my
healing process I'm going to take
control over my health no one's going to
Own Me No One's Gonna own my soul
I am my own person my own soul that's
empowerment that's enlightenment
I did not do anything wrong to get sick
it's not my fault I'm not a bad person
that's Enlightenment when you realize
that I am working on my healing I'm
doing my full free will into it I'm
using my intentions
that's enlightenment
what's incredible about the brain shot
therapy is it enhances your
clearantvoyant skills that are deep down
your gifts that are deep down in there
enhances your intuitive Powers your
psychic powers your telepathic Powers
everybody has it or some or all and it
enhances all those over time
These Are Spiritual cleanses not just
physical so let's go into it we're in
the entry level right here so I'm on
page 520
we're in the brain shot therapy cleanse
entry level right there
what does it say
add these steps to your normal eating
routine so if you guys have a normal
eating routine whether it's a medical
media meeting routine maybe you're
somebody that came here and you're like
well I'm on this other eat better diet
out here
and
you can still bring in your brain shot
but keep in mind there's a scale
you might be bringing in the brain shot
and it's helping you to battle
your caffeine addiction
your apple cider vinegar addiction that
you don't know you even have
right
you're really really high fat diet
whatever it is that you're doing
your bad supplements like charcoal and
whatever chlorella and whatever else
you're doing that's actually bad for you
and then you're doing the brain shot
therapy so now you're about your brain
shot therapy is actually not only trying
to give you instant relief but it's
battling all this other stuff that's not
good for you
Jeanette says I'm buying these books as
gifts for everyone for Christmas yes
amazon.com I think they're 40 off right
now at Amazon us
so somebody said Tammy says I've done
the four day brain shots and this is the
first Monday in years I'm not feeling
brain dead at work
that's absolutely incredible
so it's two books if you're buying them
for gifts just so you know there's the
brain saver brain saver protocols be
prepared they're heavy
they had to be split in two books their
one book publisher could not put it out
there it'd be a 10 pound book
see celery healing says I've been taking
the energy shot and feeling my energy
come back
that is miraculous stuff that's Miracle
stuff
that's what all this is
and I'm not naive like I was naive when
I was younger about something else say
Sophie's healing said that this shots
are true miracles
I was naive when I was younger I thought
everybody once you have the answers the
whole world will just have parades over
it you know and celebrate but that's not
how the world works it's an evil world
see um Brenda says instant starting
instantly started laughing after the
portrayal and broken trust shot and had
the biggest smile that I've had in years
incredible
that's amazing
all after an emotional blow after work
my God that's incredible so you had this
laugh attack
from that shot all after a really hard
day at work with an emotional blow so as
I was saying before you guys I was
really naive when I was younger I
thought that since I was hearing this in
incredible voice that was giving me
Advanced Medical information about how
to heal and about how the world works
and everything else I thought for sure
that the whole world would just want
what's here but I learned that's not how
the world works the world is crafted to
condition people and brainwash people
and confuse people so they can't always
get the answers so I realize now I'm not
naive about it there's a lot of people
that are never gonna
get these books in their hands billions
of people in the world and they're just
not going to experience this and it's so
sad I just I have to live with it
so we're at let's go to page 4 49.
we're in the exposure shots you guys and
we're doing the mold exposure so if you
just got here medical medium brain shot
therapy right
we're in the cleanse challenge we're on
day five we're doing the mold exposure
shot now I'm in exposure shots here I'm
talking about this area these brain
shots can be administered before an
exposure if you know you're going to a
friend's house and you're concerned
about a little mold at your friend's
house take this shot
during an exposure too like you're
living in a situation where you got mold
around you just get the stuff out and do
the mold mold shots
the mold exposure shot
Tyra says the shots hit me about two
days after I take them and I hear that a
lot by people too it can happen a couple
days you feel nothing at first then by
day two dramatic change agitation gone
and attention span increased that's when
they're working on a deeper level that's
when they're that's incredible and
that's how it works
Melissa said I thought the mold exposure
shot would hurt my stomach because of
all the Rosemary indeed there's a lot of
Rosemary but it didn't hurt at all it
was strong but I still liked it God
bless you that you like the shot I'm
probably not gonna like mine because I
had one before and I went
because it's strong
mold exposure shot let's hit it
here we are you guys so let's start
making the mold exposure shot but I'll
talk about it for a quick second as well
you're visiting somebody who's living in
a moldy house or building you're working
in a workspace that's moldy you're
inhaling mold off of another person's
clothing say you had a bunch of wet Rags
that were sitting somewhere in the
corner of your house you didn't know
about it and I don't know we're on the
front porch or wherever you're living
and you smell the mold and you can take
the shot and do it
hope for healing said I feel immediate
results incredible I get hit with a
feeling no matter what when I'm taking
the second sip sometimes the first sip
so let's go into it let's start working
on it
let's get the juicer out
so once again the mm-1500 20 off
find if you have a juicer already it's
not going to squeeze out as much juice
as this one will I've tried them all
they don't so keep in mind when you buy
less produce or you juice less produce
or you buy produce and you get more
juice you save money it's money back in
the bank the one thing I said since the
beginning of the mm-900 and the mm-1500
is it pays for itself
I haven't talked about the g-shirt in a
long time and because of that the juicer
sharks all came into the medical meme
Community sold people bum juicers in my
opinion because they're juicers that
don't squeeze out that much juice and
they're all gimmicky it's sad but true
and the rising cost of food
the whole point is the reason why I
backed up and endorsed this user was
because of the rising cost of food
because they figured out a way to create
more compression
to make sure that we squeeze more out of
stuff twenty percent off mm-1500 but
it's not all omegas it's just the
mm-1500 900 but I want people to know
because I feel bad and then I feel
guilty
so I need the guilt and shame shifter
you know basically and that's what I was
thinking about I was like after the 10
day
after the 10-day um
challenge I'm gonna do the guilt and
shame shifter for me because I feel
guilty I wasn't screaming from the
rooftops about the juicer every 10
minutes you know like it's hard it's it
makes me feel like when people get taken
advantage of by sharks it's it's a hard
one for me
okay we're on the mold exposure shot
let's go let's fire it up
I'm excited
all right here we go half cup
tightly packed basil
[Music]
nice
got my basil here
so tightly packed basil half cup
let's knock some in
[Music]
credible
half cup tightly packed oregano
why am I screaming the juicers like so
quiet I could whisper and you guys will
hear it
half cup a tightly packed oregano
nice
one strong juice
you want to knock the hell out of mold
support your immune system build your
immune system up against mold
yeah okay so
half inch
of a piece of Ginger let's see actually
we'll do
Rosemary next that's the one sorry sorry
you guys all right two sprigs of fresh
Rosemary so we got the Rosemary right
here
that's a that's a big sprig
I'm gonna send it down
let's put another sprig in there
crazy not actually incredible I mean I'm
Blown Away
half piece half inch of Ginger so let me
just get that pop that ginger in there
strong
two radishes
if you got a huge radish right like a
huge radish you guys
you probably just need one radish
I got two like radishes here
foreign
bulb of fennel now depending on your
size of your fennel here's a bulb right
here
I'm going to cut the bottom of the bulb
I know you guys can't see dry pulp by
the way dry pulp that means the juice is
being squeezed like for real
you won't see that with those Sharky
juicers out there they're not called
Sharky they're called something else all
right let's go with a
let's chop up this
mobile fennel right here you guys
let's get it in here
incredible
put a little bit more of that fennel in
there
all right
[Music]
we got it
okay this is like dust I just want to
show you this this is like dust in here
it's so dry
it's incredible that's where you're
saving money
I don't even know what to say
that's insane
here it goes
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
here's my mold exposure shot do you guys
have yours ready did you do that with me
because I'm getting ready
[Applause]
all the mold that we're up against in
the world different kinds of mold
everywhere not just molds molding or
shower and in our bathrooms there's mold
everywhere it's falling out of the sky
it's in the sea Trails there's mold
coming out of there there's mold
everywhere stores places shops we walk
into our dentist office
there's mold in bathrooms and public
bathrooms there's mold exposure all over
the place it's the medical medium mold
exposure shot I'm going to take the
first sip
[Music]
this one's hitting me in the first step
not the second sip usually it hits me in
the second zip
oh man
that's the second Sip and it's hitting
me
oh my God
that's incredible
because
I've always been spiritually connected
to what goes in my body
since I was young
it's part of that connection with spirit
and compassion
and I can see my immune cells
through the ability of what Spirit of
compassion has given me since I was a
child
and I can see my immune system
loving this mold exposure shot right
here
the compounds synergistically combined
in just the right way is doing something
for my immune system that's never
happened
oh my God it's incredible it doesn't
taste that bad
[Music]
bartender give me another
for real
you guys have you guys tried this brain
shot
I can't tell you it's making me feel so
good it's incredible what did you feel
what results have you experienced can
you guys post about it do reels about it
whatever
share stories about it and tag at
Medical medium also hashtag medical
medium
okay and remember we're doing the entry
level cleanse 50 ounces of water minimum
a day don't do the water now like I'm
not gonna drink a big glass of water
right now I don't want to do that give
it 15 to 30 minutes before you eat
anything big or heavy or drink water
Carrie Pearson said can we triple the
ingredients if we are making it for
three people or do we need to make the
shots individually you can do that you
can triple it if it's for three people
you can you can do that incredible you
guys
oh my God amazing amazing I just saw an
incredible comment on on Instagram but
it went up really quick it had something
to do with Twitches I think your
Twitches are getting better
you guys I have to tell you something
really just blown away by what you're
doing for your healing process how
you're taking initiative how you guys
Empower yourselves how you take the
information and use it how you guys
become your own experts that right there
is incredible and mind-blowing
Darcy Lee said this shot surprised the
hell out of me super healing and I feel
so much better
incredible absolutely incredible amazing
I'm so proud of all of you guys you
don't even know you know for real
tomorrow is day six of the medical
medium brain shot therapy challenge we
are making the burnout stabilizer the
burn out stabilizer tomorrow day six if
you haven't signed up go to medical
medium.com and sign up please
medicalmedium.com sign up get your free
pdf download your grocery store list all
of it know what tools and whatever you
might need all of it
because we are 10 days into this free
medical medium brain shot Challenge free
I could have guessed I could have done
what everybody keeps on telling me to do
take this challenge somewhere make
everybody pay for it and we do a big
course about it and all that and
everybody's got to pay a whole bunch of
money I can't do that to you guys can't
daily emails with so much details
sharing different people's experiences
with the brain shots check that out sign
up to my email list my newsletter list
the whole bit
and a quick message to Austin Austin
there are two couples that fight in your
vicinity around your neighborhood and
area just so you know one couple fights
more on Sunday the other couples fight
more on any day just for the record yes
whether you lied or not lied or whatever
you did I'm telling you right now there
are two couples that fight in your
vicinity and that's how it works and one
threatens to call the cops on the other
they live a few streets down letting you
guys know anyway I'm happy about what
you guys are doing we're going in 15
minutes live on Dr nesbit's Tick Tock
account and Instagram account so Dr
nesbitt's Instagram account and Dr
nesbitt's uh Tick Tock account and 15
minutes Dr Nesbitt wants to make a mold
shot he says he's gonna try it I'm gonna
help him make it because we know Dr
Nesbitt isn't totally capable even
though he's a brain surgeon I'll see you
guys hopefully in a little bit
yep the 1500 is awesome it not only
looks awesome it's incredible I just
want to show you guys anybody so they
know
because I know that here's what's crazy
about it the Sharks out there pushing
juicers on the medical meme community
that that are totally ripping them off
they say all these things that actually
like oh here's this what does but that's
a joke look at this
that's dry pulp
it's dust in my hands right here
dust in my hands that means the juice
was squeezed out that means you used
half the ingredients you would have used
in any other juicer that means this mm
1500 is going to save people lots of
money and pay for itself you can't say
that about juicers out there
but I have to tell you because of what
has happened and it's so sad to see
people getting ripped off I love you
guys I'll see you in 15 minutes robot
let's do it
foreign
[Music]
robot he's afraid of mold
robots afraid of mold
but he's not afraid no more
he's not afraid of mold no more
[Music]
love you guys
see you in like 15 minutes if you want
to see Dr Nesbitt