I've always wanted to do when we do that
the best of our ability but we need
something in people's hands like a
resource of some kind that can help what
happens is PTSD is a huge one when
someone goes through trauma shock or
loss
anything like that betrayal broken trust
whatever it is
PTSD can happen it can happen actually
really fast it can happen in days can
happen in weeks can happen in years but
it does happen and what I love about the
stabilizer trauma shock and loss
stabilizer is it has a punch to it to
help rewire the brain so that's what
we're doing today you guys
trauma shock and loss stabilizer for day
12 of the medical medium brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge
what happens is to rewire the brain it
takes more than just
mental counseling therapy right it takes
more than that because when we go
through trauma shock or loss
something physical happens to the brain
and that's something that people don't
realize out there science of research
doesn't know this
so when we go through an experience a
difficult experience
physically we get injured
not just emotionally so it's not just
soul and emotion and spiritual and
mental and mental health it's physical
and what happens is when there's a
physical injury that happens in the
brain from trauma shock or loss
we end up in a situation
where we have symptoms because of it
and then those symptoms are seen as if
the person is just emotionally unstable
so say the person goes and sees a
psychiatrist because they've been
through trauma shock or loss
psychiatrist is going to be like oh this
person's unstable
really no this person has an actual
physical injury inside the brain
because of the trauma shotgun laws
and then yes
emotional symptoms can arise from it you
guys good to see you I'm actually
excited can I read a little bit
I'm gonna go to page 76 but first of all
let me just show you right here we're
making the trauma shocking loss
stabilizer
today
so I'm excited about this here it is
have you tried this one this is a brain
shot therapy that's really powerful
really special really works I'm going to
talk about how it does that too in a
little while and what it packs as a
punch to help rewire our brain Jennifer
Cockrell says I'm remembering to give
the video a like thumbs up every day
please do that if you can thank you for
do that's really special really nice
we're day 12 of the medical medium brain
shot
therapy cleanse challenge you can still
sign up we have eight more days to go
but remember when you sign up you don't
have to pull out your credit card you
don't have to pull out your debit card
it's free and that's what it is and this
challenge has all been free it's a
20-day challenge you can join now if you
join now you're doing an eight day
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge if
you join now for free
so go to medicalneem.com and you'll see
you can download your grocery shopping
list and everything else
all right so let's go to page 76 you
guys would love to read a little bit to
you if that's okay
the Heat of the Moment paid 76 of brain
saver
as we go through life we come across
difficult situations
betrayal
have you experienced betrayal in your
life I know I have
loss The Experience lost in your life I
know I have
heartbreak
yes
loneliness yes confrontation
all of us experience these one way or
another
somehow or some way
we get emotionally hurt have you been
emotionally hurt
I know I have I've been emotionally hurt
we get emotionally hurt
and the physical aspect of this goes
wholly ignored so what I was saying
before is when we get emotionally hurt
there's a physical aspect there's a
physical injury
something happens to us physically
but that's never understood totally
ignored holy ignored
we need to address the physical core
strength of our brain
so that no matter what we're
experiencing emotionally like someone
harming someone else emotionally
or what we're thinking
that intercourse strength of our brain
can survive emotional injuries
that's the part that people don't
realize
that we need a strong brain
so what medical mean information does is
it helps to support
people's brains to make them stronger
because
we're not in control of other people's
free will
other people on this planet have their
own free will and it doesn't stop them
from harming someone
you can still get emotional injuries
losses and hardships
we can't control all that in this world
but what we can control
is the atmosphere of our brain
and what we can control is the
environment inside our brain
we can control that we may not be able
to control the hard-hitting punches we
get emotionally
betrayal broken trust loss
trauma
mental abuse we may not have control
in receiving any or all of that
but we may be able to control
the environment inside the brain to make
us stronger to be a shield
for all of that
the physical aspect of this goes wholly
ignored we need to address the physical
core strength of our brain so that no
matter what we're experiencing
emotionally or what we're thinking that
inner core strength of our brain can
survive emotional injuries
when we have a loss or betrayal
God knows right we've all had those
our physical brain
can become injured
especially if our brain doesn't have
what it needs and that's what I love
about the trauma shock and loss
stabilizer it offers something for the
internal workings of the brain the
physical brain
part of what injures the brain is not
the broken trust itself
someone breaks the trust
and we're hurt and we feel that hurt
that hurt is deep
we're on page 76 someone just asked a
brain saver
I'll show you do you have this book
this is the brain saver book
part of what injures the brain is not
the broken trust itself right has anyone
broken trust
in your life
it's the fire that occurs
when an event like this happens
when trust is broken it's not the broken
trust itself that's injuring the brain
it's the fire that blows up inside of
the brain
that creates the injury from that broken
trust
that fire is the heating up of the brain
an intense electrical Heat
someone had it right 200 years ago when
they noticed that a friend needed to
blow off steam
someone had something right 300 years
ago when they called another person
hot-headed
not that someone needs to seem angry or
irate on the surface for the brain to
heat up someone
sometimes when not showing emotion the
fire inside the brain Burns hotter than
ever
you could be lying in bed hurt by
betrayal how many people do you know
that were lying in bed hurt by betrayal
you're lying in bed you're hurt by
betrayal you wake up in the morning
you're hurt by betrayal
betrayal's a tough one
I can't tell you how many knives I've
had to pull out of my back
myself
throughout my life it's like oh hold on
you guys hold on
hold on you guys
let's pull out another knife out of my
back
you could be lying in bed hurt by
betrayal wake up in the morning hurt by
betrayal not expressing a word not even
talking just thinking
feeling and remembering it
you can be hurt
by betrayal without realizing it and
you're lyingly or upset while the fire
burned really bright inside your brain
and overheating occurred you may not
have noticed that because it's hard to
know but the brain goes on fire when
we're betrayal and maybe you can't
identify that that's what it is but
that's what it is
because publicly medical research and
science publicly known medical research
in science
no only a tiny tiny fraction about the
brain in this day and age
this brain heating can't be measured
your brain heating up from betrayal
can't be measured your brain heating up
from trauma or loss or mental abuse
can't be measured science doesn't have a
way to measure it they don't even know
what's happening
if by some miraculous chance the Earth
is still alive one thousand years from
now
and not a dead rock floating along
we still won't know everything about the
human brain
if this Earth is still alive a thousand
years from now and not a dead rock with
no human beings on it or wildlife
that would be a miracle all on its own
Bonafide miracle for sure
miraculous miracle
but if this Earth was to still be here a
thousand years from now and not a dead
Rock annihilated by nuclear waste
annihilated by sea trails
annihilated by GMO food
if this Earth is still alive
a thousand years from now
medical research and science still won't
know everything about the brain
no matter how advanced science gets
because there's a sole aspect of the
brain that science will never understand
and it's intertwined with the rest of
our brain and science will never have
those answers
ever
even if this Earth is still
alive and breathing and the Earthly
mother is alive
even though the overheating of our
physical brains can't be weighed or
measured
it is just as real as the burn you get
from touching a hot stove
it's as real as spilling hot coffee in
your lap the heating of the brain it's
as real as walking barefoot across a
scalding parking lot to get to the beach
if you ever had that experience
this heating of the brain occurs
instantly when we experience an
emotional challenge of any kind it could
happen at any moment in someone's life
where a burning sensation we can't
understand mental Agony inside our brain
is what it amounts to
an IG Starlet says oh my God
mind-blowing
a heating occurs in the brain
that heating you may not feel like the
hot Touch of a stove but a mental Agony
is what you're feeling from the heating
of that brain
and what you're going through
emotionally
it can happen in a minute in someone's
life
it even happens when people are merely
frustrated with whatever situation is
before them have you ever been
frustrated I just frustrated
frustrated about anything or everything
we get heating inside the brain our
brain gets hot inside just from
frustration alone
the fire in our brain can burn at
different heat levels no matter
the level it burns and it can't be
measured by medical research and Science
and never will be
if you've ever heard of the phenomenon
of spontaneous self-combustion
have you ever heard of that phenomenon
it's actually related to this electrical
Heat
for those that don't know what that is
spontaneous self-combustion it's when
someone's just standing there and
everything's fine or sitting in the
rocking chair or sitting on their front
porch and all of a sudden internally
there's a fire that starts a physical
fire and it starts to burn all through
their organs until literally they're
nothing but Ash and their their shoes
are left
as if it was the Wicked Witch of the
West on The Wizard of Oz
we're one of the wicked witches
I forget I haven't seen a movie in very
long time
if you've ever heard of the phenomena on
spontaneous combustion self-combustion
it's actually related to this electrical
heat science research doesn't know this
so there's no citation in here because
science of research doesn't know this
information this is medical medium
information of what causes self
combustion
Reiki with Daria I've always felt the
overheating Sensation that I described
to doctors but never had anyone speak to
it
surprise surprise surprise Spirit of
compassion always surprises us all the
time
with just Advanced information
it blows my mind all the time just so
you know I'm just I get mind blown just
like anybody else who reads these books
and
learns this information
so we're talking about spontaneous
self-combustion
it's actually related to this electrical
heat science research doesn't know this
when there's a specific when there's a
very specific recipe inside someone's
body creating elevated ammonia levels in
the bloodstream
people walk around with ammonia gas
it's a ghost like gas that floats
through their bones
and drives through their bloodstream and
organs
when there's a very specific recipe
inside someone's body creating elevated
ammonia levels in the bloodstream a
spark off the brain's electrical grid
can cause combustion
keep in mind you need a lot going wrong
for spontaneous self-combustion so I
don't want anybody in fear about that
because you need a serious recipe
in order for spontaneous self-combustion
to to occur
to begin with
the stage is set from one putrified
proteins rotting inside the intestinal
tract and other sources of fermentation
in the blood from weak digestion and
Foods fermenting inside the gut all of
which adds to the ammonia in the
bloodstream two
chronic dehydration
meaning never enough water in the
bloodstream and three high blood fat
levels from a high fat diet then if
there's also continual overheating of
the brain from a maxed out electrical
grid due to brain betrayer toxins and a
lack of electrolytes trace minerals and
glucose the grid can spark and catch the
ammonia
alcohol consumption increases someone's
chances of self-combustion as does
smoking anything
Deborah McVeigh more mind-blowing
information
brain heat can also be an aspect of
someone feeling like Madness is taking
over so before I go into that I want to
talk about the self-combustion a little
bit
it's a rare phenomenon but if the recipe
is just right in a person
that ammonia that's in their bloodstream
that gas can ignite
and when it ignites the person Burns
internally from the inside out
brain heat can also be an aspect of
someone feeling like Madness is taking
over
where you almost can't stand it anymore
or stand yourself like Madness is taking
over your mind you're upset with
yourself or you're upset with something
or you're upset with someone else and it
feels as if Madness is taking over
so many people doubt themselves when
they're going through an emotional
experience do you doubt yourself when
you go through an emotional experience
they ask am I going crazy did you ever
ask yourself am I going crazy
did that ever come to your mind at all
did you ever ask yourself that ever at
any point in time
am I going crazy
you're not going crazy
they're experiencing intense heating of
brain tissue in an emotional center of
the brain eventually reaching all areas
of the brain at some point this is often
heightened by toxic heavy metals which
everybody has in their brains and other
chemical poisons present in the brain's
emotional Center so inside their
emotional Center they can have the
metals and other toxins and other
chemicals all in there that shouldn't be
in there
stress loss trauma and betrayal burn hot
Trail is one of the hottest burners
someone cheats on you that's one of the
hottest burn
someone doesn't understand you and they
make a decision without your permission
that affects your life that burns real
hot
loss feeling like
we can't get back something we lost
whether it's a loved one a person a
thing a place something we lost that
burns really hot inside our brain
stress loss trauma and betrayal burn hot
and we're not just talking about one
angry spell a year which still Burns hot
we're talking about everyday
frustrations too
for example driving to work in traffic
when you're late
slow down or stuck in a light causes the
brain to heat up even the slightest bit
it still causes it to heat up having a
difficult conversation can cause the
brain to heat up
participating in a virtual meeting can
cause the brain to heat up and that's
what's happening so many people are in
Virtual meetings these days their brain
heats up from just being in a virtual
meeting
because video calls often involve an
additional form of stress
whether from spotty internet connections
that cause delays participants talking
over one another or because we tend to
raise our voice increase facial
expressions or emphasize body language
when we feel the format isn't allowing
us to project our message can even raise
the brain's heat I'm just giving
examples of how the brain's heat can be
raised
Brad Danielson says what chapter is this
word page 77 or in the emotional brain
chapter of brain saver thank you for
asking
the brain heat of life's challenges is
harder on the chronically ill
I want to emphasize that a little bit
if you have a symptom or you're on
mattress island or you're struggling the
heat the brain heat does affect us more
if we're chronically sick if we're
struggling with a symptom or condition
if we're struggling with any kind of
diagnosis or any symptoms that are
holding us back
if we are fatigue we don't feel good
body aches and pains if we have brain
fog the brain heat does increase
the brain heat of life's challenges is
harder on The Chronic Leo science
research doesn't even know this
Nicholas Russell says where the heck
else can you get this kind of info
nowhere
I'm honored to be the messenger of this
information from Spirit of compassion
on IG there's no other place that you
can get this awesome amazing info
that's Hemi Hemi mom on IG
but you guys know what happens
bits and pieces are stolen all the time
never cited back we see it over here all
day long out there
from all kinds of you know gurus and
health professionals just taking the
info Non-Stop
it's happened to me for decades but it's
happening more than ever
and I'm just a dirty Secret
a dirty Secret at this point
for so many to get the information from
it's crazy
and all that does is cheat people out
who need the information so they can
heal and have a chance to save their
life
the brain heat of life's challenges is
harder on The Chronic allele because
they're often stuck in bed and people
don't realize when someone's chronically
ill and they're stuck in bed
how
it's Amplified
no one understands that when you're
actually illing you're actually not well
and you have to be couch bound or bed
bound a lot
you can't play the reindeer games that
everybody wants to play
that everybody's out there playing
you're really trying to reserve you're
trying to get better you're trying to
heal and when we go up against emotional
hardships or emotional struggles when
we're trying to heal and we're bed bound
the brain Heats even more intense and
people don't know this or realize this
the chronically ill or anybody who's
sick and struggling
they have more than just their symptom
to contend with it's not easy at all so
when betrayal happens when you're
chronically sick or any kind of hardship
or loss it's even more of a difficult
situation that's why they chronically
he'll have it so difficult
they're too fatigued to walk it off
you know what I hear from people know
what I hear from influencers out there
too
they're like well when my anxiety is up
I just hop on the treadmill and I run
for an hour
what about somebody who's a mattress
Island chronically ill and sick
and
and they're not at that industry
indestructible moment in their life
and they're bedridden or having problems
or
they're struggling in other ways severe
fatigue they can't just run off their
anxiety they can't just go and run for
an hour run off their anxiety and have
it all just go away
because they're often stuck in bed
they're too fatigued to walk it off
they're too fatigued to go exercise
singing sweetie says this makes so much
sense as to why my healing is taking so
long and it does it takes longer because
of that but it's okay it's okay but it
does take longer because of that
foreign
there's still plenty of Hope to recover
and get better it just takes a little
longer for so many people because of
this
they're too fatigued to walk it off and
just go exercise they're too fatigued to
distract themselves and run around and
do appointments all day and self-care
appointments all day and go out to lunch
at a busy restaurant and everything else
they can't just shake it off it's not
easy to shake off when you're
chronically sick plus if you have PTSD
if you're chronically sick what if you
got
lots of PTSD and OCD because you've been
sick too long sick for a long time
you've been to too many doctors too many
experiences with family and friends that
haven't been positive you've been
struggling looking for answers
if you just can't shake it off
a lot of people run from their stress
that's what people do they run from
their stress they make appointments if
they have the resources they go and do
self-care all day long they go and do
this they go out with their friends they
go out for lunches they run away from
their stress they can burn off the
adrenaline also called epinephrine
created by mild Stress and Anxiety by
keeping busy with activities all day
long
and wearing themselves out
so that the thoughts don't keep cycling
they get to run it off so the thoughts
don't recycle over and over again their
stress doesn't recycle they're out there
doing this doing that they're doing
whatever they're just they're staying
ahead of it right because they can
the Divine loaf says
and then Health gurus and influencers
just say you just don't have the right
mindset
foreign
do they ever say that and boy does that
get my goat
totally
people who are chronically ill don't
have the option
when you're stuck on your mattress
Island
you can get caught up in your headspace
no one understands this
unless you've gone through it
when you're stuck on mattress Island you
can get caught up in your head space
with your brain fire burning hotter
it's like adding insult to injury
because you're already dealing with the
physical challenges that have isolated
you in the first place in your life and
have you stuck in bed
you guys just so you know we're in brain
saver I'm now on page 78.
and kind of just walking you through
some of the information in here
brain heat can even burn on a different
level
with a different kind of heat when
everything is good and happy
that's because when we're having fun the
brain still runs hot the difference is
that the brain's cooling mechanisms
which we'll explore later are usually
enough to temper that type of heat
that said it's the reason why people
with chronic illness can find that
experiencing a little happiness is hard
on them I know people throughout the
years that were so sick that even
experiencing happiness was a lot
that was hard on them
even experiencing Joy was hard on them
because they were so sick
they had so many different nervous
system conditions the brain fog all
kinds of OCD all kinds of issues they're
suffering they're struggling and then
they get told some good news
and it's hard to even take in the good
news it's like it's it's hard because
it's it's intense even a little bit of
brain heat on good news is hard for
someone who's chronically ill
it's why those who are very ill in the
hospital can't have too many visitors
wishing them well on a birthday it
generates way too much heat in the brain
that's why someone in the hospital
really really sick you gotta walk in
quiet and everybody's walking in quiet
and they're trying not to say anything
and then when two family members are
arguing why the person's in bed in the
hospital sick someone else says hey wait
a minute we might not want to have an
argument right now why Grandma's sitting
in the bed
are laying in the bed in the hospital
or anybody not even Grandma whatever
Andrea says did anybody
got the name of the book please brain
what
brain saver and brain saver protocols
that's one book they're just splitting
after two over 600 page Bibles right
here I'm on page 76 78 lost that one 78
a brain saver
foreign
so let's go a little bit more and this
is really cool good information right
here
I've known people who say oh whoa this
is really good too
even when we're not ill the brain heat
that happens generates can be exhausting
I've known people who say they love
every part of putting together a dinner
party and have an amazing time talking
all night and then feel completely wiped
out and exhausted the next day if you
ask them if they wanted to do it all
over again the next day they would feel
reluctant they put on a big dinner party
they're not sick they worked really hard
they entertained 50 people came rolling
into their house
right they had a huge dinner party
that's because the brain ran hot from
all the fun you can get burnt out from
too much fun there are people in the
world who have the means to play all
they want they're loaded with cash they
can play and do anything they can go
anywhere they want and they end up
needing vacations from their vacations
I know a lot of wealthy people
out there in the world
personally I know a lot of wealthy
people out there
and what I find
from the wealthy people that I know out
there in the world
is that they vacation a lot
like a lot
they're traveling all around the world
they're on boats they're on yachts
they're on planes constantly
traveling overseas
they're here they're there they're
skiing down here they're up here now
they're in Aspen now they're in Germany
though whatever they're in Switzerland I
know a lot of wealthy people and they
play a lot
but they have to take vacations after
they play a lot their lives their lives
are almost permanently vacationed
because they're playing so much because
they have the wealth to do it
that they need to take vacations
constantly
I usually say to me aw why don't you
take a vacation and I'm too busy working
I haven't taken a vacation ever
I'm too busy working
and they're always like I don't
understand that I don't understand that
I go don't worry you take another
vacation
because that's what people do right
they need vacations from their vacations
from their vacations from their
vacations
or they need chill time for days
afterwards a chance to do nothing at all
and increase self-care protocols lots of
massages lots of massages to recover for
many of the excitement from their
vacations they need massages when they
come home from their vacations
they had a fabulous trip which was
intended to be self-care to begin with
in the first place no matter who you are
and how lucky you are in life you still
have to protect your brain is what I'm
saying even from people who are having
fun all the time still have to protect
their brain
on IG
see Visa Hill says the fact that he's
not charging us for this info should
tell people that he's the real deal and
really cares about helping others can I
just add something to that
can I add this the medical meeting
podcast in apple podcast doesn't have
commercials or advertisers
and it's a top podcast in the world of
Health
and it's the only one with no
advertisers or advertisements on it or
commercials
that means it's a free podcast to listen
to free from the burden of your ear
having to be sold stuff all the time
when you go listen to a podcast
and it makes me no money because I don't
have advertisers in front of my podcast
I could charge thousands per person
for like a huge program or something
like that to hand out this unique
information I can box up all the books
keep it away from the world I could put
subscription fees all over my website I
can't tell you I have a top website in
the world
people hit that website I mean people
are on that website because it's free
information it's incredible information
but I don't put paywalls up
I don't want to meddle I don't want a
medal well here I do want a metal it's
this metal right here do you have brain
saver protocols you can get free at the
library
I don't want a metal for it I just want
people to heal
go to medicalme.com check out the
website so much information on there
it's it's actually incredible it's an
incredible resource go on the newsletter
too the newsletter we we like do all
kinds of cool stuff the light blast is
free
I did a free light blast
and I'm happy to do so
but you need to be on the newsletter
and I'm not complaining or anything but
all this stuff running a website like
that
and the amount of team that you need and
the amount of costs are insane and I put
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
upon thousand upon thousands of dollars
into it all
blah blah blah
so I want to talk a little bit more
about
um
the solution here isn't to stop yourself
from having emotions we don't have total
control over that anyway we can make
what feels to be a lot of progress
emotionally with conquering demons we
can move mountains in our emotional
state and that does not mean we will
stop having emotions I don't care what
anybody says
they're still going to have emotions
I don't care what Guru says they control
their emotions they're still going to
have emotions
no one on this planet
is emotionless
no one
life is not a definitive mapped out
journey we know that our life is not
somebody else's life
yet if you look at the lives of others
they can seem to have a good run of it
for a little while and when we can think
they have life figured out slowly
their best life moments in public
behind the scenes they're running into
emotional quicksand so I'm not reading
this so great right here I'm bouncing
around what I'm trying to say is people
can seem like they got their
together totally together everything
solid as a rock but behind the scenes
they're running into emotional quicksand
more than we know you can see it on IG
you can see it in Social everywhere
people they have a different thing going
on for the public eye right influencers
have a different thing going on behind
the scenes their life's a mess
you scratch the surface
and it's pretty bad
but what they show
on social all the time is a different
picture
but what's behind it all isn't really
what's happening
in front
what you don't know that's happening is
behind the scenes they're in another bad
relationship you wouldn't know they're
not going to talk about that part on IG
or social
they're not going to talk about that on
YouTube that they're in another bad
relationship
they're going to keep that quiet in the
back
or they're experiencing another friend
betrayal they're not they're going to
keep that quiet in the back too and when
they're doing their thing on social
another career Downer and they're not
going to talk about that on social but
they're going to make it look like on
social debt their career is booming and
incredible
but you scratch a surface underneath it
all their career isn't booming actually
they make it look like it's booming on
social they make it look like the
relationship's going great on social but
behind the scenes there's problems and
they're going through a lot of emotional
turmoil
they feel like they're drowning again
stuck at a bad Halloween party again
falling off the horse again emotionally
poisoned again we just don't know it
you don't know it
some people do go for a little while
without being challenged
it's true without too much turmoil
sometimes many years before a big
divorce happens or a big life upset
happens before they get trapped in
emotional quicksand again
others have shorter stints of what feels
like emotional freedom and progress
either way eventually adversity comes
adversity comes it just does Christina
Brad says I feel so validated on YouTube
and adversity becomes your greatest
adversary if we don't know what is
happening inside our emotional brains
in any moment of time if we don't have
our brain protected
the heating that can occur can set us
back these setbacks can feel very
confusing when we believe we're taking
the right steps to our emotional and
physical health little did we know these
steps might not have been the most
appropriate to sustain itself during an
emotional storm no matter how many
meditations someone has done or what
they've conquered emotionally if they're
not taking care of their brain and
dealing with their brain heat correctly
they're not protecting their brain so
what I'm saying is
we have to protect our brain because
we're not going to be able to stop a lot
of hardships that come our way or other
things because other people have their
own free will when you're in a
relationship the other person has their
own free will
they're not beholden to you even though
it seems like it's like that
they still have their own free will
another person in another relationship
they have their own free will and what
that means is
something could go wrong at some point
foreign
we can't get worn down by the little ups
and downs and challenges thrown our way
we can get worn down by the larger
challenges that come along every so many
years whatever life brings whenever it
brings them our brains burn hot
being prepared ahead of time is the
ultimate defense and protection for our
brain and that's what the brain saver
books are about and that's what medical
medium information is about protecting
the brain where the soul is just
protecting us
it allows us to preserve persevere
through any kind of emotional hit or
pain or even overwhelming joy we
experience
when it comes down to it being aware of
our emotional brains is not about
avoiding life's ups and downs because
whether we like it or not something does
happen it happens to me it happens to
everybody we all have something that
makes us emotional
it's about learning how to cool the
brain and keep it
safe and from being scorched
guys the information is just incredible
here
Cold Light spring says I feel stronger
with the brain shots we're doing the
trauma shock and loss stabilizer today
this is day 12 medic mean brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge I'm excited
about this you guys what you see is some
ingredients in front of me we've got
apples we've got spinach and we got
cherries which I'm excited about those
are frozen cherries that defrost it
and we're going to make the trauma shock
and loss stabilizer very excited
meditation isn't going to stop someone
else
from dying
getting caught in an accident
it's not going to stop a breakup
it's not going to stop what happens
physically to the brain when we have
betrayal
because the brain has to be able to
withstand the Heat
foreign
books have a lot of meditations in them
I mean medical being podcasts at Apple
podcast incredible meditations from
Spirit of compassion that help rewire
the brain
but we still have to protect our brain
so when it gets hot
that it has enough Reserves
so that's something to keep in mind
there are physical things we need to do
for our brain the right amount of
glucose the right amount of Trace
mineral salts all of that
and
medical meme information is about how we
can actually fortify
restore and actually keep the brain
strong
Mark crossy says your information is
restoring my health Anthony
Adam
says I did the one yesterday when I got
some difficult financial news
it helped me so much these shots work
like magic thank you so much aw and sfc
love you so much
how and why does the brain even heat up
what does the what does the heat do bad
or good
well the bad is that the heat kills
brain cells and we all know that we
don't want to lose brain cells at a
rapid Pace the cleaner the brain cell is
the greater ability for the brain cell
to stay alive under Heat
it takes hotter and more sustained heat
levels to destroy brain cells when the
brain cell is clean okay so what that
means right here
is if our brain is filled with toxins
and chemicals and metals and too much of
that the brain cells get hotter the
brain gets hotter that means the brain
cells die easier that's why someone with
Alzheimer's their brain is dying why is
their brain dying because they have a
high level of toxic heavy metals in
their brain that's mm info
because the person with Alzheimer's has
toxic heavy metals in the brain causing
their their Alzheimer's the brain gets
hotter and hotter more brain cells die
faster and faster to the point where
brain tissue dies and then the person
with Alzheimer's can't catch up they
can't get past it they can't beat it
the cleaner the brain cell is the
greater ability for the brain cell to
stay alive under heat that's why it's
critical to clean the brain cells and
that's what we're talking about
it takes hotter and more sustained heat
levels to destroy a brain cell when it's
clean when a brain cell is dirty filled
with everyday toxins and toxic heavy
metals the brain cell heats up more
quickly and stays hot longer so what
happens is like somebody with
Alzheimer's or dementia is just one
example
the brain has so much toxic matter in it
that when the brain heats up it stays
hot longer Burns and kills brain cells
longer
more toxins make the brain cell more
conductive to heat plus toxins coat the
brain cells inner cell membranes not
allowing heat to escape if a brain cell
doesn't die the heat can render the
dirty brain cell out of service
people walk around with brain cells that
are where the light is out
the light is out in the brain cell
it's out of service the brain cell does
not respond with electricity
electricity inside the brain it's out
the lights are out
a clean brain cell can release heat more
easily through its cell wall a dirty one
can
that said extended heating over a period
of time can still render clean brain
cells temporarily disabled too if we're
up against a lot of problems forcing it
to Slumber into dormancy which happens
to a lot of people
many times when someone is under extreme
stress or emotional distress that
opportunity for brain cells to restore
doesn't come it's why someone who's
going through a difficult relationship
with constant fighting or emotional
abuse May reach out to an old friend for
help saying it feels like what I'm going
through is killing me
when someone's going through emotional
torment emotional abuse a difficult
situation a difficult relationship
and they tell a friend
often what they say is
this is killing me
this relationship is killing me this
arguing and fighting is killing me I'm
dying
because what they feel like they're
going through is killing them
that they feel like they're dying these
messages aren't just about a soul injury
someone experiencing from a cycle of
abuse or a roller coaster ride painful
relationship of ups and downs this
person is experiencing brain cells
themselves shutting down brain cells
actually shutting down going into
dormancy with some brain cells even
dying
brain cell dormancy and death aren't all
that happens when the brain heats up
there's also a diminishing of beneficial
brain chemicals like neurotransmitter
chemicals hormones including the
hundreds of thousands of important brain
functioning chemicals that surge through
our brain and remain undiscovered and
undocumented by research in science
Health with Liz what's up a debut in
spirit I I felt so seen when I read this
chapter
I used to suffer from that brain heat
due to metals and other toxins that I
suffered so much from it I couldn't even
find peace at the beach
that's a powerful comment Liz and I have
to just say something about that
where like you guys what Liz is saying
is so powerful and one of the things
that's really powerful about it is that
she couldn't find peace at the beach
that means when she went out of her
house
to try to have some type of peace and
joy and then went to a beach to sit
there
she was in agony
and other people don't understand this
out there I mean maybe you guys because
you might experience that but what's
happening here is that other people in
the world who have an experience that
don't know what that is they don't know
they think that you should be on the
beach no matter what and you're fine you
look fine everything should be good but
instead like
being on the beach and still suffering
when you're supposed to be having fun
right
it's just really difficult educating
myself says that's why we're all
brainwashed
I think that's what I saw life coaching
nurse Kim said these brain shots feel
like they're really cool to my brain
these chemicals get utilized burned up
so what I'm saying here in in brain
saver is that
the good stuff in our brain gets used up
and burned up really fast
when we're up against betrayal anything
relationships difficult situations if
our brain is dirty filled with metals
and toxins all of it
and IG I have been totally there Liz I
am better after four years of mm Earth
humor said that
and then M Campbell said happens to me
in the beach as well
Carol says I experienced that too
then there are some brain chemicals that
are there for other reasons of your
well-being and when the brain gets hot
these special types of chemicals make it
hotter for example the chemical
compounds of the brain involved with
passion and creativity
someone has a lot of passion and a lot
of creativity and their brain is filled
with a lot of toxins and poisons
whoa the brain can just burn
these are invaluable brain chemicals
the ones that are behind creativity and
passion that can help us create and get
inspired express ourselves but when
we're suffering and we're sick with
chronic illness we feel like we're dead
inside
when we're suffering we're sick with
chronic illness our passion and our
creativity gets hindered
that's what it feels like for a lot of
people this electrical grid of our brain
should not be controlled when it comes
to creativity so these chemicals run
hotter and our brain ignites and lights
up because that's something special that
we have inside
and explores the benefit of our growth
this knowledge also explains what's
behind creative blocks when we feel we
have a block what does this create a
block I have why am I stuck
because of all the toxins
blocking
our creativity interfering with the
creativity chemicals that are good but
right now yes it's true it doesn't
matter where you are in fact it's even
worse when you're somewhere nice and
still feel bad exactly Lorraine
by the way on YouTube comment Lorraine
you left a comment and you put a a time
time stamp on yesterday's YouTube was
pretty funny and I hit the time stamp to
see what part you were talking about
it was a part where I was cracking up
about stuff
I thought that was actually funny
Elvis lives had a rough rough month my
creativity songwriting passion went away
you were so right Anthony
foreign offering relief is more than
just trying to offer someone emotional
comfort
if someone even has that privilege or
opportunity to receive solace
many people don't have someone reaching
out and offering comfort
they feel they're in it alone
so many people feel like they're in it
alone and that they don't have a lot of
people reaching out to them or anybody
reaching out to them to offer them
Solace or Comfort they feel like they're
just in it alone
and even if someone does reach out a
hand and tells them that everything is
going to be okay
doesn't mean they're going to feel that
comfort
on Rumble
see
JK says I can relate I hurt everywhere I
go
I go this all explains a lot
if I butcher any of your comments just
just forgive me
or if I butcher any of your handles just
forgive me
I'm not a scholar
SOC
has the information on messenger
I try to message the best I can
over here verbally doesn't mean they're
going to feel the Comfort even when
they're getting Comfort they can still
feel like they're alone
when we're in the fire of hurt
betrayal and anger and distress were in
the thick of it
we've been let down our brain may be so
physically compromised by the heat of
emotional fire that we're not able to
see through it with our own eyes
can't even see through the smoke it's
hard
here's a part that's really important
you're not a bad person
if we break robot status and express
emotions such as anger frustration or
pain we can feel that we come across as
weak
the self-help out there tends to lean on
the side let's change you as a person
maybe you have some faults
that we're allowing maybe you have some
faults that are causing these emotions
to happen we can make you a better
person to self-help out there always
folks focuses on you're really a bad
person and we're going to make you a
better person
since science research doesn't know
what's wrong with you and no one else
knows what's wrong with you you
obviously have just some mental problems
so you need to work on yourself because
you're the fault you're the faulty
person you're a bad person so let's
change you as a person
since you're so bad as a person
we can make you a better person this
type of self-help tends to point out
your flaws and imply you're a bad person
everybody's got flaws I got flaws
everybody does
even if it doesn't imply you're a bad
person it's an approach it's an approach
that about learning not to react
learning to think logically learning to
meditate to control your emotions
because you can't control the outside
world so you can control yourself this
still doesn't address what's physically
wrong
self-improvement
blames us
as if we're the bad person or the faulty
person we just don't know how to control
it
but really
no one realized it realizes it in the
self-improvement world
that there's really something going on
we've been really hurt and it happened
physically not just emotionally
and we're struggling
and we're not a bad person it's not your
fault you didn't even cause your problem
you were hurt
so why am I being blamed
for not handling it right
any approach that says you're the
problem can knock a person down slightly
injure them on top of what they're
already going through in that hard time
so here you are you're hurt emotionally
physically
you've been through hell and back and
then someone tells you you're not
handling it right you're the problem
it can make them feel like they can't
handle their emotions you can't handle
their emotions
it can even make them feel like they're
creating their emotional reactions
you're creating your emotional reactions
what's never part of the self what's
never part of this self-help equation is
telling people that there are toxic
substances in their brain they've been
poisoned physically
on a physical level that's interfering
with their fire
they've been hurt this should be the
main headline
incredible information you guys
let's make the
I I could I could go into this all day
seriously so this is the trauma shock
and loss stabilizer right here brain
saver that's what we're gonna make
Sue Thorne says use this shot when my 15
year old dog who was so special to me it
was incredible how this shot worked
Breezy Bree says when I lost my
childhood pet I felt like I couldn't
live on
then I tried the moon meditation and
immediately brought me back
the moon meditation if you guys don't
know about it it's that medical meme
podcast at Apple podcast
the free meditation it's there
dream healing says I've made this
yet yes it really works I went through a
lot of trauma for years after having a
shot I felt so much joy like never
before
so we're doing the trauma shock and law
stabilizer and Ingrid says the shot
helped me with my loss of my 13 year old
dog
the loss of a pet is just so much
Debbie says on IG a few weeks ago was
the one year anniversary diversity sorry
one year anniversary of my oldest son's
death
I have been doing this shot often
God bless you going through so much
and IG Health with Hannah says
here with Anna says brain shot therapy
is helping me big time with my Botox
illness also
it doesn't just heal that specific
symptom or exposure it goes beyond
from the botulism injuries
accounts bookkeeper said this
information is so life-changing and I
love this shot I do it often simple and
comforting
Tara Appleman this is one of my favorite
brain shots yeah it's one of my favorite
ones too
trauma shock and loss stabilizer this
shot is supportive too for any kind of
emotional upset emotional challenge or
emotional stress consider using it when
you're given challenging news or you
receive any emotional blows
big sister helping Kitty says I could
probably live on this shop all the hurt
I've lived through
use a shot if you're dealing with any
kind of emotional upheaval
use this shot if you lost a loved one or
a pet
what you guys are doing
use a shot if you experience any kind of
loss
use a shot if you've been diagnosed with
a chronic illness or you learn something
challenging about your health Michelle
Grace says on YouTube I am so grateful
for all the brain shots I really need
this one especially been through lots of
pain in my life and this in this TS and
L brain shot
really works been using a lot lately
sleeping better Incredible use this
brain shot if you've been diagnosed with
a chronic illness or you learned
something challenging about your health
use the spring shot if a local if local
or world events are affecting your life
use this shot if you're going through
some kind of emotional turmoil within
your family or difficult friendships
M on YouTube I had so much anger anger
shots helped me tremendously I have lots
of frustration yes I get upset I've been
betrayed myself
on a daily basis
so I need this shot big time
people think I don't need this shot
but I do
[Music]
robot
some people like the robots some people
don't like the robot I can't make
everybody happy
but I try
Western Shambhala says such perfect
timing in neighborhood friend died last
night ah thank you Anthony
no that's definitely good timing I'm so
sorry by the way I'm so sorry
Tamara cover says I suffered loss
recently I used lemon balm and the
trauma law stabilizer felt calm
supportive I also used chaga for adrenal
support thank you aw lemon bar lemon
balm I don't have my lemon balm right
here and I always usually do
I have it over here
where is my lemon balm
and looking
where is it
ah got it
got it I just rummaged through my pantry
for my lemon balm right there
I
live on lemon balm not only do I do the
trauma shotgun law stabilizer but I live
on the lemon balm this is critical for
me in my life I'm just saying it is a
commentive
for real accommodative that's the
vimergy one I can't say that for any
lemon balm supplement out there it's too
much junk and garbage in all of them and
the quality's not there but that's the
Bemidji one you guys know I endorsed
them and I am proud to say I have and I
will say it again and again anyway the
lemon balm is just amazing
all right let's go
all right
now how do we make this half cup fresh
thawed cherries go in
foreign
there's a lemon balm shock therapy in
brain saver protocols
okay
[Music]
lemon balm shock therapy in the brain
saver protocols by the way
I just gave doc a doctor friend some
advice about because the doctor friend
asked me about the lemon balm and how to
use it with patience and I said it
curves the brain heat that's what I was
telling a doctor friend anyway
all right so I'm going to drop some
cherries down in here if you guys don't
mind
incredible now half cup
so good
these are frozen cherries by the way I
defrosted them
okay one cup tightly packed spinach next
drop some spinach in here I got spinach
on both sides of the cherries there
let's go
oh I love this Trace mineral salts in
the spinach are really incredible too
coupled with
the glucose from the cherries
so one cup tightly packed spinach so I
still got a little bit more to go
there we are
there
let's get some apple going next you guys
half an apple
nice Apple
I'm gonna cut the Apple in half now
nice I'm gonna drop some apple pieces in
here
I'm excited about
boom
so what I love about the trauma shock
and loss stabilizer is it happens to
tastes good and I can't say that for
every one of these brain shots because
Spirit of compassion wasn't thinking
about making the brain shot taste good
good sort of compassion wanted the brain
shot to actually work
that was the key and if for some reason
the right synergistic combination
happened also taste good at the same
time then fantastic
that would be incredible
and I happen to like this one because it
tastes good and that's what I love about
it
so
here we go I'm just moving it through my
screen a little bit
turn that off
aha
nice
all right
let's go
come on come on
[Music]
where's my shot glass
terrible bartenders that work here
worst bartenders ever that work here the
heck is my shot glass
it was my fault
I am the one that forgot to bring my
shot glass
foreign
do I have any hardship of course I do
I am a human being like everyone else
I have my trauma shocking lost
stabilized right here
I'm excited
you guys don't mind I'm going to take a
sick
why does this taste so good in this one
so good
synergistically combined
no one would know besides the research
doesn't know that if you put these three
ingredients together in just the right
quantities of what it does to rewire the
brain that information comes from above
that's why these work it's why the brain
shot therapies have profound profound
effects
so good send it down
oh
[Music]
tender
give me another one
[Music]
bartender
where are you bartender
give me another one
coming right up Mr William
I'm gonna give you one more
thank you
so good
bartender give me another for sure that
was so so good
really really good now
relationships
can be very difficult heat up the brain
a lot for so many people you know
and that happens to a lot of people in
relationships
and relationships aren't easy
[Music]
I'm just sitting down relaxing a little
bit because
kind of just feeling the effects
[Music]
guys know who came here to visit today
on this trauma shock and loss
and
someone else is here too if you guys
don't mind I'm introducing Beatrice
uh rise
9899 on IG says that shot is so calming
and grounding and comforting
Dr Nesbitt
um says that they've been having some
relationship problems again Beatrice
has been very upset
with Dr Nesbitt
ra says that
she's getting a lot of mental abuse from
Dr Nesbitt lately because
of all his bad habits
uh Beatrice
so yeah anyway Dr Nesbitt
um leaves the TV on all night long
and Beatrice can't sleep
because the television is on all night
long Dr Nesbitt that's not a good idea
that's not helping anything Dr Nesbitt
um brings his bloody scrubs into the
house and Beatrice was making a salad
for Dr Nesbitt
yeah Beatrice is making a sound for Dr
Nesbitt and Dr Nesbitt got somebody's
blood
in the salad when he was taking off his
scrubs
Dr Nesbitt said it was
it's true it was blood from a surgery he
was doing
be interested and appreciate the blood
on her salad so she had to make a whole
new salad
and when she made the whole new salad Dr
Nesbitt chose not to eat it he went
straight to his whiskey and did not have
a salad
Dr Nesbitt says his Beatrice makes his
brain heat get real gets really bad
and Beatrice doesn't appreciate that
Elizabeth says his brain he got so bad
from Beatrice that his brain almost
exploded he said
and that is not a good thing to say Dr
Nesbitt how dare you say that about
Beatrice
Mitra said
it's not true Dr nesbit's the one that
causes all the trouble in the
relationships
uh that the relationship issues they
have
Dr Nesbitt said
now when Beatrice nags him
he feels like
he the only thing that cools down his
brain is an extra shot of whiskey at
night
I don't know what to do about these two
I really can't I can't help them what
does Donnie the donkey say
oh
oh Beatrice is pissed off about
something her brain Heats Rising right
now Beatrice says that Donnie the donkey
picks up Dr Nesbitt
and takes them out to the bars at night
so Donnie the donkey is really the
Troublemaker takes Dr Nesbitt out
drinking Dr Nesbit said only on Saturday
night
Beatrice said
that that was a Saturday night that they
had a planned
date night
Beatrice and Dr Nesbitt had a date night
that Saturday night Donnie the donkey
came and picked up Nesbit and they went
out drinking well all right you guys
tomorrow by the way
is day 13. we have seven more days just
letting you know you guys can you give
me a chance Dr Nesbit saying bye to
everybody and Beatrice is saying goodbye
too
th saying bye okay look you guys want to
go all right that's fine crispy
perspective says commercial and sales
pitch noises totally cause brain heat
for me truly appreciate you going above
and beyond to keep the shells and sharks
out tons of respect for how you do what
you do thank you very crispy perspective
Dr Nesbit is
Darkness says he likes your comment very
good comment Dr Nesbit yeah Dr Nesbit
said big Pharma takes all his doctors
out for a steak dinner
and
he goes out and the pharmaceutical reps
sit there and try to sell all his
colleagues lots of drugs
have you tried this brain shot I know
you guys have I just have to say that
please post your real stories and posts
and tag at Medical medium and hashtag
medical medium so I could see them
what did you feel what was your
experience
Jackie B says thanks for doing these
lives
Beatrice says that
she's never invited to any of the
functions
at the medical clinic that they have
and Dr Nesbitt says because the
pharmaceutical
uh reps have to sell them lots of drugs
so they just go out and have a big steak
dinner and talk about the drugs they're
going to purchase from the
pharmaceutical companies right yeah
you can still sign up for the challenge
download your free
grocery shopping list at
medicalmedium.com we still have
seven more days ago and you can watch
the 12 days that we just did eight days
to go
and you can watch the 12 days we did
uh do I have my numbers right
after Nesbit just get it straight
okay
all right you guys
I mean I know it's a
Beatrice
Beatrice is
sitting here she feels very not
represented properly here on Dr Nesbitt
is always the star so okay you guys you
guys want to go
all right they want to go low on IG
Sophie Nordstrom yes this is this shot
feels calming it calmed me down
I actually feel calm and feel good
I feel so calm with the shots
I do too Dr Nesbit
Dr Nesbitt no these are different shots
these are different shots doctors
yes yes these are different ones these
are brain shots and they're healthy
shots these are different shots Dr
Nesbitt
don't talk about those shots here please
whatever you doctors
no don't talk about those shots here
I have enough problems Dr Nesbitt yeah
yeah okay yeah no I know I know what
shots you're talking about
yeah no these are these are brain shots
these are you know the little
yeah
just be careful
don't get me in trouble
Dr nesbit's a doctor he can talk about
anything he wants
lumus free celery 333 the shots make me
sleep well
says it makes her sleep well too
okay you guys
I need some lemon balm
for later
Dr nesbit's gonna have lemon balm later
too
all right you guys