today we're talking about chemicals
we're talking about sea trails
um
we're also talking in code
major code today
big topic today
we're also in day four with day in four
day four day five which stays at six day
three we got 20 days ahead of us we're
day four of the medical medium brain
shot therapy
cleanse challenge I got brain saver here
we're gonna be talking about some sea
trails and some chemical stuff
it's going to be a really interesting
talk I hope you guys hang out for it
you see a bunch of ingredients here
because we're going to be making
the sea Trails
exposure shot
but you might be thinking I'm not
exposed to Sea Trails
so you think
but everybody is everybody is on this
planet is exposed to the Sea Trails I
can promise you that mark my words
everybody's exposed to the seashells but
we're talking and remember we're talking
some kind of code but we're gonna be
reading about sea trails in this brain
saver book
so we got to be you know cool about that
what you see right here is some lemons
you see some kale really actually nice
kale too like whoa that's really nice
kale
and then we got some asparagus right
there we got some brussels sprouts some
brussels sprouts don't look that good
because I had to peel them back and peel
them back they were like in some bad
shape
I got some chives and a little bit of
green onions scallions which you'll use
I got some cilantro
and I got some celery right here
so those are my ingredients I got my
shot glasses right here this is day four
of the medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge that's a mouthful say
that three times in a row really fast
anyway you guys coming on because we're
gonna be talking about some serious
chemical crap and it's gonna be really
fun so I want everybody to come on or
whoever's coming on because we're going
to talk about this
because I want to drop a few bombs
c h e m I'm gonna do some cheerleading
stuff right
give me a c give me an H give me an e
give me an m
give me a t give me an R give me an a i
l s
foreign
does AI know what does it spell
all right
stop messing around
we got we got some work to do okay all
right
we're here we're talking about chemicals
on the brain man chemicals
we're talking about some serious crap
and I'm not kidding about this all right
let me just start reading forget this
start reading I'll read anything
add a brain saver
I'm gonna just start on page 220 let's
go in there for a little bit
when we speak of chemicals we are
speaking of any kind of chemical created
by the chemical industry
whether we know that chemical exists
inside a product or not
chemical companies are Exempted for the
most part
from full disclosure in labeling
they have free reign in the creation and
use of their chemicals because they
produce so many different chemicals for
so many different Industries they got
free reign
this is just interesting in general but
wait do you guys hear about sea trails
wait do you hear about that
this is a fun day
there's no proper regulatory system
designed to monitor Safeguard calculate
and keep track chemicals
it would take rebuilding the entire
chemical industry and Beyond
so what did that just say that just said
that
chemical industry
worldwide has full reign
create whatever they want
without really being cataloged properly
or monitored or understood
thousand check this out this is really
cool thousands of chemicals are churned
out daily
thousands of new chemicals are churned
out daily by the way
so they get thrown into extremely large
categories instead of individually
tested for safety so so many chemicals
are turned out at once then instead of
each chemical
being tested for safety
they just throw them in batches
you can have 10 000 chemicals in one
category and have that category deemed
safe by an authority think about that
right there
we got to be in code today man
there's nobody talks about that stuff
but I can't help it you can have 10 000
chemicals in one category and have that
category deemed safe by an authority
think about this beretti ten thousand
individual chemicals that were never
tested
the effects on human nature and nature
nature
wildlife
more than 5 000 of them are
life-threatening in large dosages while
the other four thousand plus chemicals
may not cause immediate obvious health
effects within the first decade of use
yet with continual exposure will
contribute to diseases symptoms and
conditions as the years
tick by
there's such a vast array of chemicals
in production for these domestic Invader
products
thousands upon thousands of chemicals
once these chemicals enter our body
through our nose through our mouth
through our lungs right or skin
they can saturate any aspect of the
brain whether deep in the inner core of
the brain stem or
just in any lobe
inside the hemispheres or the cerebral
cortex
some domestic Invaders are petrochemical
derived when they settle into the brain
domestic Invader products often end up
deeper in the brain's grooves than other
petrochemicals domestic Invader
chemicals are created to have radio
sorry radical absorption abilities and
the brain is vulnerable and easy to
invade so I'm just talking about how our
brain can saturate get saturated by a
tremendous amount of chemicals so the
chemical industry creates thousands upon
thousands upon thousands of chemicals
constantly
but each chemical itself is never tested
as far as any kind of damages on
Wildlife or human nature
and but what they do is they batch the
chemicals so chem the chemical industry
batches the chemicals purposely
so they don't have to go through any
kind of regulatory system right
say batcho
I mean that's crazy
different chemicals do different things
there's no wall up that stops certain
chemicals from entering any part of the
brain they go past the blood-brain
barrier oh no no medical medium you
don't know anything about the brain
the blood-brain barrier stops everything
from going in it
it's a barrier medical medium I can't
tell you how many times I heard that
the blood-brain barrier it stops
everything bad from getting into your
brain
so you don't know anything medical
medium
this raises one of the foundational
problems those chemicals these chemicals
aren't brain tested so none of these
chemicals are brain tested they're not
they don't take a human being they used
to by the way they used to do this but
they didn't really look at the brand
back in the 1920s they used to
like experiment
on humans
and they would just have a ton of deadly
chemicals dropped on their head
and inhaled and on their skin and see
what happens then
Sophie Nordstrom says yet each
individual chemical is constantly tested
on animals in every country
I know that chemicals are tested on
animals but not each individual chemical
it's impossible
so that's something to know we're
talking about
millions of chemicals Millions created
each year by chemical companies chemical
Industries right around the world and
known a fraction of those very small
amount are tested on animals and they do
test on animals out there in the world
the diffraction
the chemical company's chemical
Industries are really the ones that are
testing chemicals on animals it's
product companies that did a lot of the
testing on animals
and so they don't even know from their
tests what's really happening in the
long term anyway when they do test on
animals
yes there's been a lot of tests on
animals and still is
in the industries in many of the
industries that aren't even chemical
based in their testing on animals we
know that right
horrific and horrifying all of it
this raises one of the foundational
problems these chemicals aren't brain
tested it's not like the chemical
industry knows what these chemicals can
do inside the human brain or how they
can penetrate the human brain so nobody
knows how these chemicals actually
penetrate the human brain there's no
Authority overlooking this either by the
way
I mean that's insane if the chemical
doesn't burn the hair off your arm
then it goes to the next stage of
testing for use no one's monitoring any
of these chemicals entering the brain
with current medical tools it's not even
possible to monitor the full scope of
these chemicals effects on the brain we
can't just cut open someone's brain
remove a portion and look for these
chemicals so the industry's ultimate
protection is that they're creating
chemicals which affects the brain and
can't be measured or monitored so keep
this in mind
and I'm on page 221 we're just reading a
little bit about chemicals before we
move on with this topic but keep in mind
they can't even test on human brains you
can't even test on a human brain because
you have to cut the person's brain open
to look inside and even if you cut the
person's brain open to look inside
you're still not going to see the
chemicals
so this is completely experimental on
the planet what the chemical industry
does
meanwhile chemical industry domestic
Invaders can create immune system
weaknesses that allow brain diseases to
take root feed viruses and fuel the
creation of tumors these domestic
Invaders also contain traces of toxic
heavy metals and you know by now what
those can do to your brain If You're
Reading brain saver and brain saver
protocols
and experiment on humankind
it's no if you guys just got on here
we're talking about sea trails
sea Trails sea trails
and we're making the Sea Trail exposure
shot and we're day four of the medical
meme Branch out therapy
cleanse challenge it's no secret that we
encounter and use these products all the
time there's a lot of products out there
that are saturated and dangerous
chemicals people don't even realize
Danielle says thank you for doing these
challenges and lives for free for free I
am at your service
happy to be here
brain shot therapy challenge is free yes
and sign up at medicalmedium.com
and get your free shopping list where is
it it's under this brain right here sign
up for your free shopping list right
here go to medicalmean.com so you can
get the emails and everything else about
the challenge and all kinds of other
details plus you find your grocery list
and then you see what shots we're going
to do and you can choose your own shops
you don't have to do the shots that I
have chosen here
it's no secret that we encounter and use
these products all the time what's
hidden is what their ingredients do to
us humankind is one big chemical
industry experiment right now
how many dangerous chemicals can a
person sop up in their lifetime before
it becomes apparent that it's hindering
their health and well-being and even
injuring them
it's almost like a joke or a prank
how far can the chemical industry push
the envelope before it's blatantly
obvious
the key to chemical industry domestic
Warfare is to slip every day items
through the door and never have the
finger pointed at whatever evil is
slipping through that door it's the
ultimate Con on humankind
that's incredible
it's unbelievable right
right
Danielle says you're the best changed my
life and my kids incredible
I'm so glad you're here
Lorena L tried the pathogen exposure
shot today really liked it garlic also
added wow
all right you guys we're going to move
on we're gonna read a little bit more I
want to go to the next part okay so
right now
and I am looking for the next part
I think uh
look for page two
come on let's get through this
oh yeah
foreign
so let's read a little bit here in this
next part you guys if you want to know
where I am
because I don't know where I am right
now where am I
I am in the brain saver book
okay we're gonna be making the sea
Trails exposure shot but I'm talking
about sea Trails a little bit
there are 100
thousands of chemicals used in our
Industries every day
they're put in our food
they're put in our cleaning supplies
they're used in every thing that's
manufactured many of these chemicals
are so toxic that if the human body were
dipped into a vat of these chemicals it
would be a very quick death
under storage containers these chemicals
carry the death warning
the death warning on these storage
containers of these chemicals
a skull and crossbones
and every single chemical that's
manufactured for industrial use equals
thousands upon thousands of gallons of
waste check that out every single
chemical and there's hundreds and
hundreds of thousands of them every
single chemical used for industrial use
leaves by product
that people have no idea to the level
what page Melvin Knight asks on YouTube
page 234
page 234 the paragraph starts
at there are hundreds of thousands of
chemicals used
in our Industries
so check this out every single chemical
that's manufactured for industrial use
equals this is insane thousands upon
thousands of gallons of waste
from the chemicals Inception to the
chemicals released in the marketplace
thousands upon thousands of byproduct
gallons the amount of byproduct that
results from perfecting that one
chemical far surpasses anyone's
imagination
millions of gallons can be produced of
byproduct waste as they're perfecting
one single chemical for industrial use
but you guys know where I'm going right
you guys know where I'm heading do you
guys know the inside info right here of
like to where I'm heading for real like
the inside
right info
you guys you guys get it right
in the old days Industries
just dumped chemical waste right into
rivers
in the old days
it was dumped into rivers right
you know that
the chemical industry just dumped it
into rivers in the old days you hear
what I'm going now
in the old days
mm6123 on IG they say sea Trails cause
Morgellons
they're actually
repeating medical medium information
that was put out there years ago
and you're repeating it back to Medical
medium which is always like a trip for
me
it's always I plant seeds over the
decades and when the seeds come back
it's always like a trip
that is soc's information
all right so ready
in the old days Industries just dumped
chemical waste right into rivers we know
that right into oceans we know that
right chemicals were just dumped into
oceans
the old days you guys hear what I'm
saying though the old days not today the
old days
and chemicals were dumped in and on the
land right in the old days in and on the
land
the chemical industry cannot dump into
our lakes in waterways and oceans to the
same degree anymore
by the way I put out a sea Trails
podcast a few years ago
get ready for this point right here
seriously
this is like this is on freaking
believable
in the old days all the chemicals were
dumped into the rivers the ocean the
land right and lakes
but the chemical industry is producing
more chemicals now than they ever did
before the chemical industry is
producing more than ever before in our
history
there's billions of more people on the
planet now there's that much more
industry now
there's that much byproduct produced by
all the chemical Industries
but yet it's not in the Lakes it's not
being dumped in the ocean anymore it's
not picked up there wouldn't be an ocean
left because there's that much chemical
created do you guys see where I'm
heading you guys know what I'm talking
about right
it can't be dumped in a river anymore it
would end the river's life if it was
dumped in a river it would destroy an
entire River now there's that much
chemical being produced the industry is
producing but in the old days there was
not a lot of chemical being produced in
the old days and it was just dumped
straight into rivers until finally they
said they knew they had to stop
let's see
the chemical industry cannot leach into
our land to the same degree anymore
with more chemicals being produced than
ever before where does all the chemical
waste go can you answer that question
for me can you guys answer the question
for me that should be the number one
question on the planet Earth right now
everybody says oh environment
environment environment climate climate
environment environment everybody's like
gotta save the oceans everybody's like
gotta save the oceans gotta Save the
Fish that's what everybody's saying
gotta save the bees the bees they're
gonna die the bees environment
the number one question that should be
asked
where does all the chemical waste go
if it's not being dumped inside or on
the land and it's not being dumped in
the rivers anymore and it's not being
dumped in the ocean anymore and it's not
being dumped in The Lakes anymore
but yet there's more chemical waste
created now than ever before in history
with the most chemicals made in
byproduct made ever before in history
then where does the chemical go is there
a genius out there that knows that
and by the way people that knows the
chemical Industries having anything to
do with sea Trails until a couple years
ago when I released the original piece
of information nobody knew in the
chemtrail world
try to say as fast as possible and hopes
that it blips by
by the way happy birthday Michelle L
Michelle L happy birthday because I know
it's your birthday today
it's a blessing to have you on this
planet it's a blessing to have you in
the medical immune community
truly
with more chemicals being produced than
ever before in history where does all
the chemical waste go
there's too much chemical byproduct and
no place to store it and release it
you can't store the chemical byproduct
the industry is producing billions of
gallons across the world the planet but
there's no place to store it they can't
dump it into the river so where does it
go
it can't be recycled
it's not like a plastic bottle you threw
in the recycle bin
and so this is the chemical industry
since the chemical industry cannot
dispose of their wasted the ways they
once did which was the rivers the Lakes
and the land and the ocean
now chemicals are being
I don't know they're just out there you
guys who want to do do you guys play
with paper planes at all
you guys ever make paper planes
anyway
[Laughter]
foreign
anyway
sea trails are composed of very top of
every toxin possible that the chemical
industry creates this includes toxic
heavy metals such as mercury and copper
it also includes old outdated Antiquated
chemical storage bins that have been
backlogged in storage for decades
chemical waste that has sat in tanks for
60 70
and 50 years I don't know why I want the
080 or even 100 years
It's a combination of chemicals both old
and new being placed in
[Music]
and dumped
it's just a theory
doesn't mean any of it's true I'm just
having fun
you know it's crazy right now because
everybody's worried about this planet
they're worried about the Earth they're
worried about the environment they're
worried about whatever climate they're
worried about all this stuff and
literally
one of the most diabolical situations
that can ever exist in in any history
anywhere
on this planet in any time frame is
happening now and it's like the craziest
thing when you think about it right so
everybody is just exposed so it's fear
of compassion did was because we can't
avoid this exposure it's not
avoidable the exposure
right
because we can't avoid it we have to
protect yourself so empowerment occurs
right it's important to empower
ourselves and our families and our
children and everything else
so
and you got like you got all the
different concerns about the environment
but this brain shot therapy is here to
help that's the whole point because we
can't avoid exposure it's not possible
unless you don't want to go outside if
you don't want to go outside but that's
the thing inside too we're exposed
because the air outside is the air we
breathe inside inevitably or you would
just
lose oxygen inside your home
wherever you live so everything that we
breathe in inside our home is air that's
coming inevitably from outside so we do
get we do get exposed so we're all
exposed
the entire planet is exposed right
everybody on the planet so it's not
about being afraid
and just so you know to make things
clear because there's a billion of
questions if you have questions you can
see in detail about what I'm talking
about in brain saver if you don't have
the brand saver book you won't have
those details because I can't drop all
the details over here
foreign
it's not the passage your commercial
flights you know
that a bunch of people are flying on
that's not what it is but their details
are in here which are really interesting
really interesting to know but the point
is is we don't have control
over like this exposure nobody does but
you have control to be aware and then
do something about it if there's
something available and the whole point
of what Spirit of compassion did was
Spirit compassion
want it to have something available
there was a synergistic combination
that works just right
for overall that type of aerosol
right so what Spirit of compassion said
it takes a little bit of celery a little
bit of cilantro a little bit of of
chives a little bit of Brussels
a little bit of asparagus a little bit
of kale and a little bit of lemon it's
that exact chemical combination meaning
food chemical meaning phytochemical
compounds in food that exact combination
that has an ability to help us Purge
to help us Purge
a well-rounded amount of aerosol you see
the difference right there because it's
released in an aerosol fashion
so it takes a certain combination to
help with this
to actually help the body Purge
chemical warfare that's in an aerosol
form
so Spirit of compassion wanted to offer
something because
there's there's nothing we can do about
the exposure there's nothing anybody's
going to do about the exposure
it's just
the way it works
but we can do something to empower
ourselves and protect ourselves very
interesting
we live in a world where we're being
taught to Fear the Future of our climate
at the same time there's a terrifying
reality that's being ignored
which is the unprecedented high level of
dangerous chemical contamination and
saturation being released
within our sight onto our children
I can't keep on reading too much of this
though there's too many hot spots in it
let's just figure this out we'll do some
other stuff we'll actually do the shot
and everything else I'm excited let me
see if there's something else I can try
to I'm trying to pick and choose what I
could read out here
oh here's the part that's really cool
an IG
clean up your diet that's your handle
that's cool I've heard people saying it
would cost a fortune the fly planes just
to dump that how should I respond to
that
you gotta definitely read
this because I talk about how that
happens and why and all that
and just so you know
it's easy and can be done
did you ever hear about thousands of
birds falling out of the sky you guys
ever hear that with thousands of birds
are falling in this guy like thousands
like ten thousands an entire migration
down on the ground right
that's from a migration of birds
I know it's not like you know it would
be migration sparrows or migration right
Robin's a migration of like
so that's from a migration of birds
running into a very thick patch
running
from a very thick Pack patch right
butter
being poisoned in the sky and falling to
their death it happens all over the
planet in places you can't see we only
recognize it when it happens you guys
we only recognize it
when it happens in it where it's in a
visible place like in a city a village a
town on the streets in the Town Center
you don't see it when the patch they the
birds hit happens in the woods somewhere
in the mountains just so so much wastage
Spirit of compassion told me that there
isn't going to be Birds someday and this
is the reason
check this out right
algae blooms and chemical clusters in
oceans and lakes are from
that as well
causing schools of choked out fish and
other sea life to wash up on the shore
and people don't realize it it's from
that
I don't know I just thought it was a fun
topic that's all to talk about
and I thought I would put the Sea Trail
exposure shot into the mix of the 20 day
um brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
because we're so exposed so I just
thought it would be a great idea
but they'll just tell you it's all your
genes and your body attacking itself is
what they'll tell you out there like
it's all your genes and maybe it's all
the birds genes too
millions and millions of birds falling
to their death
it's all the birds genes now right
sorry let's
let's get into it
it's not the pathogens and toxins it's
not the pathogens going around and the
toxins that we're up against no it's not
that it's our genes
but the part I think that bugs me the
most
I think one of the parts that like
really gets on my nerves like the most
when I really think about it
is
the fact that
we know what's happening
and everybody who has power in the world
knows it's happening
but it just keeps on happening
but yet we're supposed to worry about
other things
right Sarah says doesn't the Bible talk
about the ocean turning red yes it does
indeed
yeah and the red tide
all right come on let's lighten it up
let's move on let's make the shot
lighten things up a little bit
so what we're doing is we're protecting
our brain
from these chemicals now you don't have
to do this shot every single day but
it's a great shot to do periodically
like I'll do it for a couple of days
then I'll wait after a while do it for
another couple of days it's just an
incredible option
listen
I don't want anybody to be like worried
or upset right because we have the tools
and we have the power in our own lives
we can take care of ourselves right we
can do things we can we can get medals
out we can do heavy metal detox
protocols right we can do incredible
tools we can do celery juice we have so
many options to take care of ourselves
and clean it up in our own bodies and
own minds and that's the incredible part
about it all
and I didn't even talk about the scary
stuff about it so I hope people aren't
upset
if you want the scary stuff
read the brain saver book
or go to Medical medium podcast to Apple
podcast and listen to the episode the
episode was a couple of years ago
okay so I really like this shot
I'm not a big fan of the taste of the
shot the taste of the shots not so bad
some of these shots they're hard to get
down because they're not designed for
flavors they're not designed for your
flavor palette they're not designed for
that that's not what it's about right
honestly I wouldn't you know what if you
have air fresheners pumping in your
house
that can be worse because it's directly
directly in your face every second so
what I recommend if you want to be
empowered on any of the chemical warfare
you take out your air fresheners and you
throw them out you pull them out of the
walls and get them from under the sinks
and you throw them out first things
first is the air fresheners that is one
of the domestic chemical warfares of our
time right the other thing is right you
gotta be careful about cleaning products
another thing too is detergents
right with all those scented stuff all
the fragrances all the scents I've been
telling talking about this for years I
remember three years ago three and a
half years ago I think it almost four
years ago now I was talking about how
bad perfume colognes air fresheners and
scented candles were and then then
literally a bunch of people try to
cancel me
because
they thought it was the stupidest thing
to be talking about when there was
something else going on in the world and
they were like why is this guy talking
about air fresheners and scented candles
and they were trying to like rip me down
over that and I'm still gonna talk about
it and now you hear people talking about
it now you'll see an influence out there
yeah don't don't work don't do the
fragrances oh where did you get that
info
when you stop using a lot of the super
toxic chemical products right and you
stop buying those chemicals with all
those fragrances that they're selling
out there
they produce less of them
so yes the power is in our hands to stop
the industry
from possibly creating more chemicals
The Big Industry Giants in the world on
the planet so it's true you know that's
one way that could really hurt the
chemical industry if people
stop buying everything
that sent it like that air fresheners
fragrances chemicals perfumes clones all
that stuff has stuff in it bad chemicals
right and because of that they'll
produce less
but the air fresheners and their
fragrances the bad chemical stuff has
gotten so much more toxic than it ever
was before 10 years ago and ever was
before 20 years ago so we're up against
chemicals now that are so toxic in all
the fragrances it's like nothing
anybody's ever seen so the chemical
industry is creating fragrances that are
so horrific at this point and yeah
people stop using them and stop
purchasing them you better believe they
don't produce them anymore
they're creating chemical sense and
fragrances that actually stick around
forever
A Thousand Years could go by in a home
that's been doused
by a tremendous amount of fragrance
if it preserved a thousand years later
and they opened up that home A Thousand
Years Later you would smell that
chemical
you're creating chemicals that won't go
away but what you can do is you can stop
taking in the new stuff like you can
pull it out of your walls throw out the
candles that are scented get it out so
you're not constantly bringing more and
more more
meanwhile the scream about climate
change meanwhile no one's talking about
fragrances
chemical Industries producing trillions
of gallons of wasted chemicals that are
just waste
they're not talking about dryer sheets
they're not talking about any of that
they're not talking about sea trails
should not talk about nothing
all right let's make the shot
Muhammad said guys listen to me I have
followed the medical medium diet and I
am healing from Vitiligo it works it
really does what I what I really love
about the medical medium information for
Vitiligo is it's the only information
that's how Vitiligo in anyone
for years and years and years now
don't worry the media the media won't
cover that the media won't talk about
reversing a Vitiligo with medical medium
information which is like a miracle they
won't cover that but instead they'll
just do hip pieces after hit pieces
whatever or some other smack will be
talked about me but yet Vitiligo can't
be healed they can't be healed out there
but yet it can
like mm info is reversing it in so many
people like I I see it out there
it's really special
God bless you by the way
all right
I'm gonna put some kale in here quarter
cup of tightly packed kale
but I just want to talk about it it
starts with frozen wild blueberries I
don't have Frozen wild blueberries today
so I have wild blueberry juice today is
what I have so I'm gonna use that so you
can have the option of using different
wild blueberry
um you know sources so I'm just saying
put wild blueberries the key for this
one a regular blueberry won't do it so a
regular regular confident blueberry does
not have enough anthocyanin to or
phytochemical compounds to mix in with
all these others to make something
happen Nano chemicals are really really
tiny these are Nano chemicals we're
talking about septo chemicals the acto
chemicals they're so tiny it's insane
that's what kind of chemicals we're even
talking about
so yeah so wild blueberries the one of
choice not the cultivated blueberry with
the big the big bluebird
Brett Winters where does the nanotech in
the sky come from
Fred wouldn't you did you just come in
we're talking about it
oh maybe you're saying where does it you
know where it comes from up in the sky
you're wondering where it comes from
it's chemicals
right and byproduct for the waste I was
talking about from the industries
if that was your question all right so
on the wild blueberry front that's
that's key but I'm gonna add the wild
blueberry juice after right but if you
have your wild blueberries like frozen
wild boobers you can use that now and
dump them in the first so I'm giving you
a chance to do that
the next one would be kale so a quarter
cup technically packed kale so I'm gonna
drop some kale in here
nice
it's not a quarter cup though
if that was tightly packed that would
that would definitely be probably a
little over a quarter cup on that one
right there but yeah
quarter lemon peel let me get a lemon
I get a lemon right here first of all
I'm gonna peel it back if you don't mind
I was supposed to probably do that
earlier but
so I'm peeling the lemon you don't have
to peel it perfectly but this is the
next thing by the way this is the MN
1500 it's on sale right now the mm-900
is on sale too you guys know I work with
the magnets incredible products
I call them the medicine machine they
save people money because they squeeze
more juice out of stuff
and they can handle real juicing
medical medium Community juices like no
other community in the world like it's
it's unbelievable
to the degree
quarter lemon going down in there
half cup tightly packed cilantro
everybody
let's get that in there
tightly packed that's going to do it
there that's incredible
quarter cup tightly packed chives I got
scallions and chives right here you can
use either or
if you have chives just use chives but
I'm using a combination so I can show
you guys in case you guys are like maybe
someone's freaking out they're like I
don't have chives I only have scallions
foreign
brussels sprouts now these brussels
sprouts are so tiny I had to peel them
back so I'm probably gonna put four in
here
because
they really equal four or five of these
will equal two good sized ones right
there we go
this has a high compression which is
incredible this stuff is coming out dry
that's what you want with the juicer and
then the mn1500 does that
in 900. two raw medium stocks
of asparagus send you on through these
are little ones so I'm gonna add
I mean these are really small
these are Spears
you can call them Spears
I'm gonna add those in
half a stalk of celery is next
we'll use this this is actually a short
one and it's kind of tight and broken
it's a celery stalk
here we go
that's my shot right there
amazing
I'm excited
I'm letting it just trickle out a little
bit more
and then I'm adding a little bit of
blueberry juice in the end of mine
because you might have added the wild
blueberries the Frozen wild blueberry
ones right beforehand
I'm adding a little after
incredible
I got a little screen here let's not
knock over the blueberry juice
amazing
okay then I'm gonna add a little bit of
blueberry juice to here too
just a little bit
that is the chemtrail exposure shot
right there
okay
the music we didn't do a half time
what was I thinking
maybe we could do the robot down
half time
this is it you have your shot did you do
yours already
[Music]
what's incredible about this okay is
that no one would know that it's a
combination of phytochemical compounds
that are grown on this Earth we have
medicine now think about this
please think about this one point from
Spirit of compassion if we have the
ability to create chemical warfare
domestic chemical warfare chemicals from
the chemical industry on this planet
that destroys life and the environment
in which we live it if we have that
ability as human beings to create
dangerous concoctions of chemicals then
surely if it comes from this planet that
means the chemicals that are dangerous
and lethal and problematic if they come
from this planet then surely we have
something from this planet that can help
us
and it's the food that's grown on this
planet has mystery mystery
powers
to help us
phytochemical compounds
when they're mixed together
just like chemicals dangerous chemicals
in science
have an effect
and so in food when these phytochemical
compounds
are actually mingling with each other
they ignite and something occurs fear of
compassion
has brought this information here so we
can help protect ourselves
so in a specific way when these
ingredients come together
[Music]
synergistically the combinations that
nobody knows about
from above we have a way to protect
ourselves
and this is the medical media brain shot
therapy
this one's hitting me now like right now
right when that first sip went down
is my favorite shot of all the shots
c h e m I'm I'm a Cheerleader today
c-h-e-m-t-r-a-i-l-s did I spell it right
what did I say sea tails
this is incredible you guys
c-h-e-m-t-r-a-i-l-s
all right wait a minute
come on pull it together why does this
happen to me after I take the shots
every time or something happens
okay
see give me a z
all right all right give me a c give me
an H give me an e give me an m
yeah give me a tea
give me an R give me a give me an I give
me an L give me an s
and that's why you guys know this is
information that comes from above
because how the hell can I do eight
incredible volume as medical books with
Advanced information when I can't even
spell
you guys to see trails expose your shot
medical mean brain shot therapy it's my
favorite one
my body is receiving it and accepting it
receiving it
and accepting it
Trinity you're laughing
I see you laughing there
all right well that was incredible you
guys
everything and we missed out on the
robot but tomorrow we're going to do the
robot okay don't worry tomorrow we're
doing it we can do it tomorrow it's just
I don't know if we're supposed to do the
robot when we're talking about like sea
trails and Ocean's dying right check out
medical medium podcasts at Apple podcast
but here's the thing you guys ready
check out the podcast episode I was just
interviewed on
right
so the heal podcast Kelly Noonan Gore's
dear friend of mine right did you listen
to her episode with me in it yet did you
hear the episode so please check it out
it's the heel podcast there's links out
there right you should find the link
but the heel podcast and I just did the
episode she just released it yesterday
Kelly Noonan course just released the
episode yesterday she's the heel
documentary genius
and dear friend of mine she just
released it I posted the links please
listen to that episode because as normal
per normal per usual I'm talking on
there
because I just can't help myself
okay oh and make sure you have both
books
foreign
us
right amazon.com us and their discounted
so we're using Amazon discounts medical
medium books which is actually a godsend
in my opinion it's the one thing I can
say about them is the fact that they do
that and they make them affordable for
people who are in need
which is incredible go to the library
get them for free if you don't want to
pay the 22 or whatever they are
and you guys how was
your experience with the brain shot
therapy challenge can you please post
about it can you please put some reels
out or some stories or uh post about it
if you can how did you feel what did you
feel when you did the sea Trails
exposure shot what did you feel
I mean and you might want to do sea
Trails you might want to do sea trails
or maybe spell it like k e m Trails
maybe do something like that Kem trails
right
khem maybe k-h-e-m that would probably
be better
please share your stories your posts but
tag at Medical medium and hashtag
medical meme so I can see it you have to
do both so I can see it so I can repost
and share and all that other stuff but
how did you feel after this shot are you
feeling like I'm feeling
because what happened is this is
battling any exposure
it's incredible I feel good from it are
you feeling good from this one
seaweed hero good to see you
you're always drop in some good Rhymes
some good riddles you always try seaweed
hero you're always dropping some good
lyrics some song lyrics man you're
always dropping those two on YouTube in
the comment section I'm always reading
those
she would hear I always read your um
Ron's riddles and music lyrics All the
Time
when you're uh commenting on my YouTube
channel
this was so good
give me more
bartender
give me another
please
all right you guys
[Music]
wait
here's the robot song
and for some reason this
this sea Trails exposure shot is giving
me power
my robot's insane now
[Music]
you guys incredible
about time Lorena
Melvin Knight
download your shopping list
okay whatever you do
download your shopping list okay
[Music]
medicalme.com
free free free free
you guys call me crazy but there's 16
more days of this
I hope
I'm still standing afterwards but I will
be because we're doing the brain shot
therapy
so I will be standing
16 more days of this
okay
16 more days
wait we have a guest
I don't know how
somebody wants to do the robot with me
but they're getting dressed
someone said they just got out of the
shower and they're getting dressed
they want to do the robot
[Music]
Dr nesbitt's doing the robot
Dr Elizabeth I didn't know you can dance
Dr Nesbit that's really not a great
dance
Dr Desmond is a board-certified
psychiatrist and a board certified
surgeon and he wants to show his moves
uh oh
we were naked underneath Dr Nesbitt
Dr Nesbitt was naked underneath and I
hope that was okay because
I just saw Dr nesbitt's chicken skin
all right you guys
I'll see you tomorrow