Millet lettuce patty burgers right there
this is going to be incredible right out
of brain saver protocols we're talking
also about the
agenda with Daylight Savings Time
daylight savings agenda going to talk
about that too plus we're going to get
into cutting boards a little bit got a
cutting board right here is it big
enough we're going to get into this too
is there bacteria on your cutting board
is there mold on your cutting board how
do you take care of your cutting board
what do you do what's the secret
everybody's slathering oil on their
cutting board some people slather Crisco
on their cutting board some people
slather pork fat on their cutting board
some people put olive oil on their
cutting board some people are pretty
smart they think and they're putting
avocado oil on their cutting board and
some people even go a little bit further
and they're like over here at our
household we put hemp seed oil on our
cutting board here cuz we really got our
stuff together together cuz we know so
much we're going to talk about all that
is it right is it wrong what's the best
options do you even have a cutting board
if you don't and you decide to get one
someday you might want these tips and
this
information because I can promise you
this it's going to be really interesting
extremely interesting okay first of all
I just want to do a couple little things
before we go into daylight savings hell
this what I call it daylight savings
hell before I go into that little bit I
just want to see what I got here what is
what am I looking at I'm looking at some
potatoes because I'm going to be making
some crinkle cut fries with a little
crinkle knife right here I'm going to
make some crinkle
fries because I'm having Burgers going
to do the Millet burgers in this pot
right here I got some Millet piping
freaking hot right there in this pot you
can see it okay and then what I have
here is an assortment of leafy greens
leafy greens a term I did did not hear
before medical medium information didn't
hear it the hygienic Health movement
they didn't talk about leafy greens the
most they ever said was Roma lettuce
going all the way back the raw folks
they didn't talk about leafy greens the
raw folks were just eating lettuce and
the health movement in general didn't
talk about leafy greens and leafy herbal
greens like herb greens didn't talk
about that either but we did something
in the health realm Spirit of compassion
and I and the medical medium team
helping we got the word out there about
leafy
greens yes we got the word out there and
now you hear it in the strangest places
friend of mine said they saw a
commercial a TV commercial was like one
of the fast food restaurants and the guy
on there was like we have leafy greens
with our chicken and our burgers and I
was like don't want to hear it I don't
want to hear it because first of all
it's ridiculous because it's a term it's
a medical medium ter term and it's
important to know that because it brings
you back to the importance of leafing
grein like all about it and why and
everything around it and how it's so
important those details are critical
remember the details matter with all of
it it's not that I want a plug for every
single thing mm info did no I mean that
would be nice to get people back to the
start right but most importantly it's
about the chronically ill and then and
they're actually bumping into walls and
they're looking for help and theyve seen
10 doctors and they've done a ton of
antibiotic treatments they've done a ton
of this and a ton of that and they've
tried everything and they've been in
oxygen Chambers they like buy oxygen
Chambers and they're in oxygen you know
therapy and they're just laying in there
for hours upon hours you know thinking
the oxygen chamber is going to like just
fix them and next thing you know it
they're dipping in the cold bathtubs
covered in ice and they're doing that
and next thing you know it they're
trying something else and it's endless
endless endless and they try this
supplement that supplement this Elixir
that elixir and they stay sick and when
they find medical medum information
something happens you guys know have you
been around from the first book that was
released something magical happens you
actually find out why you're sick like
really find out why you're sick and how
to heal and then you're on your journey
and then you're healing and you're
moving forward and it matters but today
we're talking about cutting boards we're
going to be talking about cutting boards
today I hope you have your cutting board
ready do you have your putting board in
front of you right now we're going to be
making the Millet Burgers too beef
burgers we going making greasy beef
burgers bow Vine burgers with the juices
from the animal grease all grease
dripping out of the meat and the blood
all cooked up in the burger we're not
going to do those we're doing there's
nothing wrong if someone actually eats
meat half the medical mem Community I
think are meat eaters um of course
because we are not discriminatory to
animal protein and you can can actually
heal while doing animal pro protein but
you have to know how to do it and you
can actually heal if you're vegan you
just have to know how to do it and you
can heal if you're pescatarian just need
to know how to do it you can heal if
you're vegetarian and doing medical
medium you just need to know how to do
it and then you can do it so let's do it
all right so moving on moving on okay
good good good
call all right to start with I just want
to make sure my Millet is ready so I
want to get a closeup on this if I can
I'm going to put the pot right down here
here we are that's the Millet right
there I'm going to take my wooden spoon
and I'm just going to mix it up and make
sure it's done it's done it's looking
good okay I just wanted to do that first
going to make sure it's nice and ready I
just cooked it let's talk about Daylight
Savings
Time have you ever been in a situation
where Daylight Savings Time happens and
you feel worn down from it
now I know if many of you guys know
medical mum information going back I've
talked about it first in the health
realm it wasn't considered a health
issue so mm info brought D daylight
savings to town as far as in The Chronic
Leo and health department and health
issues other than that it wasn't talked
about except for other reasons like the
economy so why was Daylight savings put
together one of the biggest reasons was
economics economy it was to benefit the
economy the bottom line the dollar and
that's why daylight savings came to town
but is that the real reason because
remember this there's always some
Sinister evil plot behind a lot of the
big mainstream things going on now I'm
not saying everything mainstream has an
evil plot behind it but believe me most
everything in mainstream does have an
evil plot and there are things in the
alternative stream that have evil plots
too along with it but this one here
daylight savings is on another level of
evil one of the reasons why they do
daylight savings is to make your life
miserable yes now the powers that be on
this planet the
illumination on this planet they think
every way possible they think in any way
possible how can they make human life on
this planet more difficult a bigger
struggle much more of a hard time
obstacles pitfalls
traps tiger
snares and so one of those is let's
change the time around let's do that on
people we'll have them running on the
hamster wheel we'll have them tripping
over themselves you might think well how
does it really hurt us you know when the
time change comes everything should be
fine I'm okay just a little extra tired
when the time change
comes but it's more than that it throws
off people who are sensitive it throws
off people who are struggling and sick
it throws off people mentally
emotionally it's a trigger for people
who a bipolar trigger for people who
have depression anxiety OCD OCD is a big
one right there one thing that people
don't understand understand is when
daylight savings occurs when they change
the clock where they turn it back or
forward OCD and many people most people
they struggle they may not even
attribute it to that time change but it
can throw people with OCD into a major
Tail Spin one that can set them back for
months until the time gets changed again
and then after they've somehow
stabilized with their OCD even though
they're struggling and and other things
may trigger them comes along the time
change again and then somebody with OCD
boom they're now triggered again and
they're on that hamster wheel of OCD
hell because of the time change now you
may think well hey why would the
alumination be thinking about things
like this they do massive think tanks
with massive money behind it and
evildoers that do sit around and make
charts and power points on this very
stuff because they think about the
things that make our lives worse and
more miserable like for instance baby
formula baby formula with GMO corn oil
GMO soy in it the worst ingredients
you've ever seen in it baby formula you
would think the world would know by now
that they can make a better healthier
baby formula for moms that can't
breastfeed but no they won't and they
won't go there instead the baby formula
will be the worst crap there is there's
a reason for that this is what they want
same thing with daylight savings and I
could I could make a list of this stuff
going all the way back for years about
the things that they actually purposely
make the way they
do so that it causes more trouble or
harm or
difficulties so daylight savings so why
should that bother anybody overall if
you have some type of emotional
struggles whatever it is or you you got
some type of condition a mental
condition you're suffering and
struggling from anxiety depression
sadness depersonalization that's a big
one it throws off the neurons it
actually sends neurons in a tail spin so
the first thing that happens when the
time changes
forcibly is neurons start to heat up
when they heat up Metals start to cook
they start to oxidize faster they start
to move
around and what happens is our brain is
challenged so every time there's a time
change our brain becomes challenged and
do you think indigenous cultures going
all the way back you think the Native
Americans you think they had a time
change going on you think so so when
November 1 came
along in a Native American village make
sure you tell everybody across North
America
everybody that we're gonna change the
time we're gonna do
that it just doesn't happen it never
did but we do it here because as the
centuries have gone by and time has gone
by certain powers at be govern the
planet and we know that you know that if
you still don't know that then uh that's
a nice bubble you're in I'd like to
climb into that Bub bub with you and be
like yeah the world is perfect nothing's
going on this bubble's amazing give me
this bubble you're in I would love that
bubble but it's not really truly reality
of what's happening and daylight savings
is a prime
example prime example of how the world
works of how the hierarchy
works so when it comes down to Daylight
Savings time when it comes down to
spring ahead fall back and everything
else that they've termed it and coined
it it disturbs balance so it's geared
and created just to disturb the balance
of life and if you're somebody and it
really doesn't throw you much doesn't
throw you much but it does does throw
you much now Canary and the coal mine I
want to go into that a little bit so
what's a canary and a coal mine so you
got a
canary nice yellow canary right here and
it's in a cage in a
mine carved deep into the Rock Tunnel
deep into the Rock right when the air
and the oxygen the oxygen starts to
diminish the canary sings a different
tune and the miners hear it they hear a
canary struggling so the point is is you
don't want to wait until the canary
dies and falls to the bottom of the cage
you want to hear the canary sing a
different tune
you want to hear the canary say
something different so when the miners
were working it wasn't just about
checking the bird in the box or checking
the bird in the cage oh it's still alive
we're okay let's keep on mining let's
keep on mining right the bird's okay in
the cage they would pay detailed
attention to the canary cuz they didn't
have oxygen meters back then they
couldn't be like well the oxygen in this
cave we just dug
is actually diminishing it's at 15%
oxygen now it's at 14% oxygen now it's
on 12% oxygen now we're down at 8%
oxygen and we're struggling they didn't
have the
meters so they used the canary and when
the canary would actually sing a
different
tune it's the sound the voice of the
canary the chirp would alter and that's
the first thing you looked for what's
happening the last thing you wanted is
to just get down into that hole and look
into that cage and see a canary dead and
then realize you can't breathe and you
can't make it
back daylight savings
time is like sucking the oxygen out of
human life ever so
gently ever so
small ever so subtle but that's what it
does when you're 90 years old if you've
been blessed to make it to 90 and you're
in a nursing
home that time
change can determine life or death that
time change can get a worker who's
taking care of a 90-year-old in a
nursing home off their
game that time
change can get
a conductor of a
train with a bunch of passengers in it
off its game their game that time change
can get a pilot in the sky in a plane
off their
game it can change the way we feel the
way we think can make us more forgetful
in the
moment can make us more apprehensive can
make us less Discerning can make us too
Discerning can throw off our judgment
calls and so every time a time change
time changes and they don't measure this
cuz they don't want to measure this
science doesn't want to look at this
every time the time changes a bunch of
happens on this
planet a bunch of accidents happen a
bunch of moms driving their kids to
school
crash yeah all in different states in
different cities in different towns
because they're off their game maybe
maybe a mom didn't get their caffeine
and they're all groggy headed cuz
they're just sick every day maybe a mom
got too much caffeine maybe whatever
whatever it is or maybe a dad on a
construction
job because rushing to work cuz the time
change maybe somebody else maybe
somebody who was drunk all night all
jacked up they're usually used to
getting home at 4 in the morning they
time their alcohol consumption as they
leave the party or the bar or the club
and their time change throws something
off and now boom they're crashed with
somebody
else they shouldn't have been driving
drunk but either way they had their
system down while they were driving
drunk and now their systems thrown off
it's these subtleties I'm just talking
about all these different
subtleties you're not measuring it
science isn't measuring it no one's
measuring it but when it happens the
illumination Powers at be are measuring
it they know what's happening and they
know a storm occurs every time the
time changes they know it cuz people are
off their
game and they know the people that are
the most sensitive feel it the worst
like the canary and when we're talking
about the chronically ill and we're
talking about sick people we're talking
about
canaries people who they're
sensitive they they can't be that
indestructible 22y old that hasn't
really had a Health Challenge yet that's
working out every day and doing this and
doing that and drinking what they want
eating what they want running here going
here and then surfing here they can't be
like that right now in their Liv life
they're not at that State they're at a
place where they got ticks and Tremors
and vibrations through the body and
sleep problems and sleep apnea insomnia
all kinds of different mental issues too
depression anxiety OCD bipolar whatever
all the different things they got going
on and then you get old people that are
older Elders time change knocks them
hard it knocks grandpa and grandma and
great grandma and Great Grandpa hard and
the powers at be the hierarchy knows
this and understands this completely
understands this because that's the
whole nature of the deception and that's
part of the
evil that's it's not the greatest evil
in the world it's not the biggest evil
in the world but let me tell you it
changes when that time changes then
everything on the planet changes and
happens
and Calamity occurs happen stance
everywhere everywhere happen stance
happens here happen stance happens there
happen stance happens there and
goes wrong all around wherever they done
that time switch on people it throws
them
off people who can't see good and can't
drive at night end up driving in the
dark
now when they never drove at the dark in
the dark at that time of day when that
time changes and now they're driving in
the dark for the first time at that time
of day when they never did before
Calamity happens they're in an accident
on highway and somebody else gets
killed this is the stuff they Revel in
and love they love this destruction they
love injuries they love hardship they
love sickness and the thing is the time
change it worsens chronic illness it
worsens all the canaries and chronic
illness it starts to break them down a
little bit and then you got to recover
recoup and then the next one comes you
got to recover recoup and it's not like
daylight savings um The Wizard of
daylight savings in the sky isn't saying
make sure you drink extra celery juice
make sure you do your hmds make sure you
take care of yourself make sure you do
your spinach soup make sure you do your
aloe vera they're not telling you to do
that make sure you do your zinc make
sure you do more B12 to overcompensate
for the daylight savings time it's not
like this big pie in the sky and I in
the sky big brother and so forth up
there isn't telling you you should
probably be on Mor B12 when we change
the time on you and mess you up but they
don't cuz nobody cares it's a term I
know very well nobody
cares that's how it works in this
world Death By A Thousand Cuts is
something they love to do too it's all
packaged in the same thing you know
what's crazy is here we are you think
that people are looking out for the
chronical ill you think that's happening
now after all the work I've done for 35
years all all the work I'm sure a lot of
other people have done helping people
with chronic illness you think that the
message would be out there but no people
with chronic illness still get told
they're crazy still get cold told
they're lazy still get told there's
nothing wrong with them it's all in
their head that they're make believing
their symptoms conditions and their
diagnoses they're still being told all
this stuff then on top of
it
there's all the sand being thrown in
everybody's face there's all these
monkey wrenches being thrown in
everybody's
wheel and that's how it's done on this
planet but the daylight savings is
hierarchy kind of like April Fool's Day
on everybody that's how it works
it's there for reason and hopes that the
numbers rise every time they switch that
time fatalities rise yeah that's right
and with every
fatality there's a gain for illumination
with every sick person there's a
gain with every person that gets sicker
and sicker and a problem happens there's
a gain in a Reliance on the system and a
Reliance on the medical system that's
how it's built and daylight savings time
is all about helping to break the
medical system and when you help to
break the medical system things just
start falling apart everywhere and all
around and that's part of what the
illumination does and that's part of
daylight savings time let's go on The
Cutting Boards a little bit but we got
stuff to make though oh no pressure
pressure I got food to make but we I'm
going to get some fries going let's get
some fries crinkle cut fries all right
so what I'm going to do is I'm going to
take this huge potato right here this
huge rusted potato and I'm going to
start making some crinkle cut fries
these were just recently steamed they
weren't in the fridge but they're still
working out pretty good here so let me
just cut these up I'll show you guys too
what it looks like there we
go all right so I'm going to make a
bunch of these so just bear with me here
so what I'm doing is I'm making fries
cuz I like fries with my burger
you know what's incredible about these
Millet
Burgers they don't taste like you know
that like MSG and that gluten fake meat
stuff and even the fake meats that don't
have gluten in them still got all kinds
of hidden flavors in there natural
flavors and MSG in there and you don't
have to worry about that with these
Burgers but I like fries with these
Burgers so I'm going to pop some of
these on here right now just bear with
me these are that's going to be one big
fry right there nice
couple of these fries are going to be
really big I can see
already so we're making some crinkle
fries and then we're going to go into
cutting boards do you have your cutting
board in front of
you just curious if you
do all
right you have your cutting board in
front of you too we're going to talk
about that I think you're going to be
quite surprised about today's show cuz I
am at your service right here I'm going
to give you lots of tips that you may
not have have
heard about cutting
boards I think it's going to be fun it's
going to be exciting all right let's get
some get some of these fries
going now you might just want fries that
aren't crinkle cut but I like this
crinkle cut knife I could say crinkle a
thousand times crinkle cut crinkle cut I
just love for some reason I like the
sound of it I'm going to make some
crinkle fries see what I'm going to do
okay I'm using a steamed potato so let's
let's not get confused this is a steamed
potato it's already been cooked I'm
doing it so it's it's just it's faster
cuz you know I'm live right here okay
there we go
nice let's make some fries
here boom get these on the
plate I'm still
here and I think I'll bring this over a
little
bit
and it makes them crunchy on the outside
too when you do with steamed potatoes
they actually get crunchy on the
outside how cool is
that
yep all right let me just cut a few
more I hope you enjoyed my daylight
savings
talk
here we
go and I'm sure I'll be punished greatly
for
it with extra censorship with that
sauce I remember when my YouTube channel
was censored cuz it's still censored
even though you guys are on there some
of you I remember when it was cens
censored in I think it was
and yeah we were getting like 60,000
views really quick 880,000 views really
quick 100,000 views people were getting
notifications and then YouTube censored
our YouTube channel and then we're we're
we're lucky if somebody can find it
right now Mike Charles what's happening
man what what temp do you cook them at
when you're using steamed I cook him at
400 but you don't want to go too high
you don't want to go too low you know
375 to 4 and A4 if you go to 4 and a qu
you're going to be you know you might be
toasting those babies if you go to 4 and
a qu man good to see you by the way
Mike all
right thank
you do some crinkle business
here
all right and then Twitter was censored
years ago too so my Twitter channel was
censored long before Twitter was
actually censoring
people and then you know how Twitter
says they don't censor
anymore oh they haven't taken the
censorship off my
Twitter I don't know why why but here we
go all
right
there we
are and I think I'm going to put a
couple more
here so they're shadowed you know so so
uh that's
shadowed
okay I'm going to put some spices on
these let me just get these set up and
we're
good
nice these are steak fries I'm making
you
guys some of them break apart a little
bit but that's
okay all right going to move these
over you guys don't mind I'm just going
to kind of do a little sweeping on the
board here because I might do some demo
stuff on this board about cutting boards
all
right Jackie says I don't get
notifications anymore yeah on YouTube
yeah my YouTube was censored I think in
2020 or late
2019 I think we're getting like 6 7
800,000
views and 400,000 views 600,000 views
right we weren't running any ads we were
just getting views it wasn't censored
and then they censored us still sensor
on YouTube Paulette says twitch sends
notifications twitch does amazing twitch
twitch twitch
twitch I like that
one all right let's get these in throw a
little spice on them I'm going to do a
little paprika on here bring it
over
twitch I'm
twitching I like twitch it's amazing
you know when that platform came out I
thought it was Stitch and I was calling
it Stitch all the
time all right putting a little bit of
paprika on these fries are you guys okay
with that there we
go can't wait to talk about cutting
boards it's going to be really
fun okay um there we go I'm putting this
in all right we're in the oven
we got our Millet right here getting
ready for the Millet Burgers we're going
to do that in a little bit we're going
to talk about cutting boards we got the
crinkle fries in the oven Buzzy B says
yeah telegram informs and then I just
look it up it's incredible yeah that's
that's
amazing all right let's get into The
Cutting Board stuff see guys what do you
do with your cutting board how does it
work for
you how do like what have you been
taught about your cutting boards what's
happening there because and what do you
actually put on your cutting boards are
you a vegetarian are you plant-based are
you somebody that you're plant-based but
somebody else in your family is not
plant-based they're eating animal
products and their animal products are
going on The Cutting
Board and you're just like oh my God
there's chicken on my cutting board
you're freaking out is that happening
then you should have a separate cutting
board so I will say this to anybody
who's living in a house it's my first
tip is if you're living in a house with
somebody else that's actually cooking
chicken and they're cutting chicken up
and it's on The Cutting Board and all
that and they take a sponge and they
clean it all up and everything and you
come along and you now actually do stuff
on The Cutting Board you got some
lettuce on here or whatever it's like
Russian Roulette in the worst way so one
of the tips I have to offer which is
definitely have a separate cutting board
if it's at all possible or flip the
board and mark the board so board
flipping is my first tip of the day but
we're going to go into mold and bacteria
we're going to go into some other stuff
too we we ain't done with just flipping
the board that's not the only thing
we're going to talk
about all
right so say I'm cooking a chicken here
on this
board and I'm actually are cooking a
chicken preparing a chicken and I'm
cutting it up and it's raw and it's all
raw chicken on here
and you don't have another cutting board
in the house but somebody does that you
don't want to actually you know use that
board you want to learn how to flip the
board but you want to mark the board so
you want to make sure you put a
permanent marker somewhere on the edge
that points an arrow
down or points an arrow in a certain
direction that arrow pointing in a
certain direction will be your side of
the
board that's a really helpful thing to
do so when someone's done and you want
to make your food and someone actually
had raw meat on the board some type of
animal product or chicken on the board
you can flip it after they did it and
you got it I see someone talking about
peroxide and we're going to talk about
peroxide in the board peroxide ain't the
only
answer so that's one tip all on its own
if you have somebody in the family
that's actually using something deadly
like raw
chicken because raw chicken obviously
can kill a lot of people it has in the
past it just
does it's not an anti-chicken talk it's
just a fact anybody who loves chicken
and eats chicken they have to be careful
or they can get in trouble and they can
get really
sick so when it comes down to cutting
boards here's one tip that's very
important you don't want to get wetness
under your cutting board if your cutting
board sitting there on the counter and
it's a wood cutting board or any kind
would cuz that's what we're talking
about today you don't want it moist or
damp underneath the cutting board so
what you want to do on the counter with
your cutting board
is you want to take a dry
towel and you want to get the board off
the counter a little bit with the dry
towel so you got your board on a
towel what this does is if you have
drippage so you cut up tomato es you cut
up something wet something juicy you cut
up fruit apples you're cutting lemons
and then dripping or you're using water
on your board for some reason you're
cleaning it and the drips then roll down
go
down and they end up going under the
board they travel under the board and
mold starts to happen very quickly like
instantaneously mold will start to grow
underneath your cutting
board now mold does some weird stuff
mold can travel through
wood without it even looking like it can
mold doesn't just get down to say a
millimeter layer inside your cutting
board mold can travel through the board
how does it travel through the
board most everybody's cutting boards
are not one
piece they're glued
together cutting boards are multiple
pieces glued together that's the cutting
boards are now long gone are the days
where there was Old Oaks and old wood
old growth wood where you cut this one
piece and that's your cutting board this
one piece of
wood cutting boards are pieces put
together mold will travel without it
being
seen through each
slab right through the glue mold loves
glue the glue used for cutting
boards it actually can use glue to
travel and so even though that glue is
hard and that board is pressed
together mold can still grow through the
glue
and get deep into your board you might
be somebody that's like well only one
side of my board has mold I'm going to
flip the board over and a lot of people
do that I can't afford to get another
board right now so I'm going to flip the
board over and the moldy side of the
board is there I like that I like when
people do that that's a good thing you
can do you can flip your board and have
the
mold on the other
side eventually though the mold will
grow through the glue and you won't see
the mold on your other side your clean
side but it will be
there it'll
be within the glue itself through each
section of the
board another thing about mold and
cutting boards is there's people out
there that are mold
freaks they're making sure there's no
mold in their house there's no mold
under their kitchen counter sinks
there's no mold in their bathrooms
there's no mold in their
showers they got mold meters and the
mold meters are actually saying there's
no mold in their house but their board
is
moldy and they don't even know it they
have a moldy
board
now let's go into what we can lay on a
board what we can put on a board you're
thinking you got to oil up your
board first thing that happens when you
get a brand new cutting board is you're
probably told or you're probably
thinking that you got to oil up the
board
so you got to drop a little bit on there
so let's put a little on here right here
I'll show you two with a little close-up
maybe we could get but I'll put a little
bit
on put a lot more on there cuz people
put olive oil on their boards but I'm
not telling you to put olive oil on your
boards my boards stay dry and oil free
not because I'm afraid of olive oil I'm
not afraid of olive oil not because I'm
afraid of pemp oil not because I'm
afraid of walnut oil not because I'm
afraid of avocado oil not because I'm
afraid of coconut
oil when you put oil on your cutting
boards you're proliferating the bacteria
levels and you're proliferating the mold
levels so when you lay oil on your
boards you're
encapsulating mold and bacteria
in between the oil and the wood and then
the
bacteria stays alive and preserved
within the
oil and then
grows it grows it spawns couple of
things go on that bacteria has
oxygent that's on the surface of the air
and mixed in the oil when you rub it in
so you're rubbing oxygen into the board
oxygen doesn't necess necessarily stop
bacteria from growing that's how how it
works at
all in this situation you're rubbing the
oil base with the oxygen and you're
mixing it all up with the bacteria
you're shoving it down into the wood
fibers and bacteria is really
small and you think you got a nice clean
oily surface now and instead you got
bacteria growing inside your board
underneath the oil in the oil inside the
the wood fibers
in the wood pulp you have bacteria
growing I don't recommend
oiling or fattening up your
boards it's not a good idea you can't
kill bacteria well the oil will also go
deep down into the first or second layer
a good millimeter maybe even 2 millimet
of your board maybe even 3 mm of your
board and harbor and safe hold lots of
bacteria and mold
so you think you got a clean board I'm
going to rub the oil on here right there
you think you got a clean board you
think you're you oiled it up nice you
protected it oiled up your board and all
you did was create a playground and a
petri dish your board becomes a petri
dish for
bacteria viruses if they're
there if somebody cut their finger while
cooking and they got an epine bar
somebody cut their finger while they're
cooking and they got hsv1 2 someone cut
their finger and they got hhv7 whatever
it is it's in the board ceglar virus HPV
it's in the board because it's not going
to die it's going to sit in the board on
the board and the oil is going to
preserve it and keep it there for quite
a long
time and it might even procreate while
it's actually there bacteria will for
sure so I'm giving you this little
tidbit right here which is very
important and valuable which is don't
oil up your
boards don't grease them up oil them up
don't avocado oil them up don't walnut
oil them up don't cookon oil oil them up
don't sesame seed oil them up
don't don't oil them up and don't pork
fat them don't Crisco them don't stick
some other kind of oil don't vegetable
oil them either Lane says wow wow now I
realized I didn't have problems with
mold until properly oiled the
board oiling your
board will create a mold Fest and a
bacteria Fest in and on your board
eventually also possibly getting through
your
home
okay are you guys liking the tip so far
or no should I keep
going should I keep
going all right Right cleaning board
let's hit it you want your board dry you
want your board clean that's what you
want always have a sponge designated for
the board the sponge was in the toilet
and in the bathroom I accidentally
designated this one for the bathroom and
for the
toilet and uh but that's okay I'll
squeeze it out that's all right we'll
clean this board this sponge was in the
toilet clean in the toilet and the sink
their boogers in the sink that people
have and everything else and just all in
there and make sure you want to
designate a sponge specifically for your
cutting
boards that's your
sponge that sponge isn't for your
counters that sponge is not for your
counters really important tip you
guys you don't want that sponge for this
right you don't want this I'm going to
just do this here here I'm going to do
this I'm going to do
this oh yeah I got to get this clean I
don't want anybody seeing this dirty
here give a good wipe I got to get this
cutting board done now too let's do this
right here let's get the cutting
board yeah you see it everywhere you see
everybody doing it it's like yeah get
the counters this done this this this
let me do the sink over
here never do
that never
do that reminds me of people that like
they're so anal and OCD about something
a certain something and mean something
else it's just like
what do you ever run into that out there
there's people out there they're so anal
about something like so anal about
something like off the charts right but
then all of a sudden they got this going
on and they're doing this it's like
what I've seen people like don't dirty
up my car don't put a single thing on
the floor don't get sand in my car floor
don't get dust on my car what is that is
that a bag of chips don't get the grease
from the bag of chips on the
thing but I'm going to go pick up a
piece of gum off a sidewalk and they'll
just throw it in their mouth and chew it
up you don't think people do that no
they don't but they go and do other
things they go on to a kissing Fest
maybe they go into a kissing Fest where
they're kissing
people they got their mouth inside
somebody else's mouth they're exchanging
every single microb and bacteria and
virus and meanwhile you get in their car
they're screaming at you because you
actually touch your your feet to the
floor of the
car you want a designated sponge for
your cutting
board you just do all right let's go
into some cleaning of The Cutting
Board cleaning dry and
clean you want the wood dry now what
you'll see out there mainstream is no
the
wood will be ruined your cutting board
will be ruined you just bought a brand
new wooden cutting board and you're
going to keep it all dry like that where
it's dry how are you going to do that
you got to oil that board man you're
you're destroying your cutting board
you'll hear that out there that's the
mainstream
view
mainstream isn't always right you want
your board dry
to the bone of course it's going to be
wet when it's wet because you're using
your designated sponge and you're
cleaning it and everything and we're
going to go into that like what do you
use to clean your board so let's head
there too but first of all you want your
board dry no oil and you want it where
the board looks like it's starting to
bleach but you're not bleaching your
board with a bleach which takes me to
the another another level there what are
you cleaning your board
with you want something that's going to
clean your board but you want something
that's not
toxic you want something that can help
clean it but not toxic and the lemon
juice Theory it's a cute
one where you put lemon juice on the
board I've seen people do raw meat on
the board and then they squeeze lemon
afterwards and they wash it down with
lemon juice and they're like done that's
clean that's not
enough I just saw lemon on I with a
question lemon question it's not
enough you want nothing on here no food
no fruit no vegetable
juice no
oils nothing but water but you still
need to clean the board so here's one of
the tricks your board will end up
collecting things lots of different
things on top of your hardened food
different stuff and after you've taken
off the stuff that's loose you take off
all the stuff that's loose okay
after you do
that you want to get water on your
board you want water water becomes a
killer for microbes not a thriver check
this out nobody knows this stuff it's
it's all mm
info mm
info what is
it mm
info okay water
is an inhibitor why water swells the
wood it swells the
wood it swells it that swelling of the
wood brings out Bug Killers naturally in
the
tree so you want water on your board but
you don't want
oil what happens is the water on the
board is going to loosen up Harden food
Harden this juices from things that are
in there it's going to harden it's what
it's going to do is it's going to soften
up the wood and it's going to loosen up
the hardened things that are on your
board and then you take off the hardened
stuff you do your sponge
right you can get some more water on
here and get it on here but what happens
is the wood swells and the
antimicrobials come out of the wood
antimicrobial are naturally inside this
wood
forever you can have a cutting board
that's 30 years old 40 years old in your
family line and that wood will still
have antimicrobials in here forever
sitting in here but you can't access
them cuz you ain't got the key if you're
putting oil all over your board you'll
never access them it's never going to
happen you keep your boards wet with oil
you're never never going to access the
antimicrobials they're not going to come
out and
play when you keep that board dry and
clean and you put water in that board to
clean it what happens is and you leave
it even if it's for a couple of minutes
when you're cleaning a few minutes your
wood starts to swell when your wood
starts to swell the
antimicrobials are now leeching out
they're leeching out and they're killing
stuff naturally killing stuff so nothing
can live deep within the wood of the
board and harbor itself
there you get your board
clean take a hand
towel and dry it up
now now say that
wasn't say you're somebody you had raw
chicken on your board you had beef on
your board board you had raw fish on
your
board you want to clean it like this but
then you want to do something
else you want to bring
in the hydrogen
peroxide this one hasn't been opened yet
I'm going to open it I'm going to give
you a play bypl as I try to open
this
okay now we got
peroxide
peroxide won't
destroy the wood's ability to release
antimicrobials keep that in mind bleach
will you don't want to use bleach or
toxic cleaners especially bleach on top
of your
boards bleach will destroy your natural
anti microb Rials that lie within the
wood surface and deep within the wood of
the tree a tree will have a lifetime of
antimicrobials built into it that will
seep out right peroxide won't destroy
that so you put your peroxide on the
board you can take your sponge that's
designated for your board and you can
move that peroxide around your board
just like
this and you can start making sure you
kill that chicken salmonella that eoli
from the beef and
whatever you want to get that peroxide
on here just like I just did right there
okay give it some time Ivon says
unbelievable
information unbelievable
comment thank
you over here boom boom boom I like that
boom boom
boom I like it all right that's peroxide
on the board ready take a towel you
should watch this live a bunch of times
because it might go in one ear
right and might go out the other ear by
accident some of this stuff there's a
lot of info I just cleaned off the
proide but that's not all now get some
water on it
rinse out your sponge your designated
sponge rinse out your designated
sponge now take off the residue of the
peroxide with
water like
that
done done that's
it your wood will swell the
antimicrobials will come out strong used
a little bit of peroxide on there
amazing
Natasha says thank you so so so much for
this information wow wow wow
wow all
right so I want to go into a little bit
more of some other things say you do you
can't afford another cutting board you
don't have the money you don't have the
budget but your cutting board has mold
on it you can see the mold on it what
happens is that with a lot of people the
mold usually starts on the other side of
the board like this the back of the
board you have to have that towel
underneath your board because the juices
of whatever you're doing are going to
most likely end up soak falling down
here and soaking underneath the board in
the counter and it's going to sit there
and fester and it's going to soak itself
back into the board
right and you don't want to do that you
want to have that Bo that that towel and
then you want to change that towel every
like week or 4 days or 5 days you want
to change the towel flip it out get a
new towel down put your board down I got
to check the crinkle cut fries hold
on nice sprinkle cut fries are in the
works I might even pump this up a little
bit remember that question you had
before like what do you want your oven
at I said 375 to 4 and A4 I'm playing
with 4 and a qu right now I'm playing
with fire I got the crinkle cut fries
going in
there okay I'm trying to remember is
there anything else about the cutting
boards I want to tell you on this show I
think there can be there are a couple of
things okay oh yeah there
is
duh
okay when you oil your
boards you end up splintering your
wood last thing you need is splinters
you can't really see going in a family
member's throat and getting stuck in
there does it happen yeah it does ever
hear of somebody having a a something
going on with their
throat
right it can happen little splinters can
get in places we can swallow the wood
splinters they can get hung up and
jammed into the intestinal tract lining
for a year and just sit there the lining
and then the the intestinal tract just
calluses over it eventually and it
becomes a
pup in the intestinal
tract the point is the oilbased
surfaces eventually weaken the wood to
such a
point where it splinters so much easier
when you're cutting and chopping so keep
that in mind you'll end up splintering
without even seeing
it let's see here's a question over in
IG can you run it under the water in the
sink
two if the board is smaller or it's
better to just wait you can run it you
can run it under sink you can run it
under the sink if you can or want to
just make sure the other side of the
board is dry before you place the board
down on your counter on that towel on
your
counter here's something very important
about the cutting boards another tip I
think I should say is the reason why you
want to towel towel underneath your
board too you don't want your board
sliding so when you're cutting fruits
and vegetables and meat and poultry or
whatever you're cutting and chopping up
you don't want the board accidentally
moving on you and you cut your wrist cut
your hand cut your
finger so why I like the towel a nice
towel underneath the board that's one
thing that's really important too people
don't know
that your board's going to get less
damage by the way in last longer if you
don't oil it it's the opposite to what
they say so they say your board will
last forever if you oil it but your
board will actually weaken go moldy
become problematic become a bacterial
ridden
board and it'll start to wear out too
faster than it
should did you ever hear of a
tree that's in a
river
underwater and it's
petrified did you ever hear about a tree
that
and I wasn't even thinking of this like
so is giving me this right now you ever
you ever hear about a tree that falls
into a
lake and it's
underwater it's in the mud and the
water and it comes out of that Lake it's
petrified or it can be
used all the same as if it was cut down
literally the
1865 they cut cut it down it was logged
it got away it went down under the water
it it lost track with all the other logs
right and you pull that out do you guys
know how this stuff works with wood and
you pull that you can pull that oak tree
out of the freaking River and pl it and
cut
it
yeah it was
water it was in the
water not in the oil it wasn't in the
oil so why do I prefer wood over plastic
well plastic I don't like all the little
plastic
fibers they they peel off the board you
chop it up you got plastic little pieces
you can't see are everywhere and you
know the whole plastic thing I won't
give you guys a lecture on plastic you
can read the medical me books I have
lots of information about Plastics and
medical me
books right and when it comes down to
the plastic boards you'll have a higher
bacteria range Pro procreating on your
boards it's something you don't want I
prefer wood over plastic and even glass
now glass I don't like because you don't
know it but the glass
shards are flaking they're flaking so
here's what they do with glass so the
glass cutting boards is they put a layer
of plastic on your glass cutting board
you guys know that there's a layer of
plastic you can never see like Plexi
like plexiglass over your glass cutting
board over the glass you can't see it
that's supposed to give that coating for
you that chemical based coating while
you're cooking and chopping and you're
on your glass and all that eventually
you'll be eating all that
plexiglass plastic crap petroleum based
product that they laced on your glass
cutting board you'll be eating that with
your sandwiches you'll be eating out
with your food and then when that wears
off guess what you guys you'll be eating
glass chips not chips like the kind of
chip where you chip a glass and it's a
big chip and you see the chip fly or you
see you get cut on a little sharp chck
no when you use glass cutting boards you
won't see it but they actually temper
the glass so it doesn't shatter the same
so what happens is little micr flakes of
glass come off the glass cutting board
that you can't see it's wear and tear
that you can't see little tiny bits and
you eat it you eat it you long before
you won't even know it 10 years later
you might start seeing something weird
with your glass cutting board and you're
like I just ate all that stuff for
years Uma so
live all right those french fries are
are
cooking okay I think I can start making
food you guys there's more information
about cutting boards I can give you guys
and provide you guys there is we'll be
here all day that's okay that's okay I
wouldn't I'd rather be here all day than
anywhere else and that's a fact Jack I'm
going to put the cutting board
down all right as long as I'm
permitted
okay so I think what I'm going to do
while those french fries those crinkle
cut fries are kicking ass in the oven I
think what I'm going to do is I'm going
to start making I'm going to start
chopping up an onion that's going to go
inside this Millet first of all I'm
going to add some potato starch this is
potato flakes oilfree
oil flip free I'm going to add some of
these in
here recipe calls for a tablespoon or so
I'm going to mix this Millet in right
here with these
potato
flakes I'm going to chop up an
onion okay I'm going to crank up the
heat on this a little bit I'm going to
add a little touch of
water and I'm going to show you the
recipe in the book here little touch of
water in my Millet with the heat up says
that in the book I think and
then this is the recipe we're making
look at that check this out but it's
going to look a little different today
because I got an assortment of leafy
greens instead of iceberg lettuce I
couldn't find a good iceberg lettuce in
the store could not find one for the
life of me sometimes they're really
solid you just know you got a good one
right but then it wasn't there though it
just didn't happen so these are garden
stuff I have here all out of my garden
you guys you have the calls book you're
missing out if you don't have it you're
missing out I mean seriously you're
missing
out this is this is mindblowing it's not
just 100 recipes it's the heavy metal
detox cleanses it's like it's the
symptoms and conditions and protocols
this is a life-saving book right here
and we'll go down in history long after
I'm here as one of the most profound
healing books of all time mark my words
right here on this recording that's how
it will be
that's how incredible this book
is you think I'm saying it because it's
my book it's so's book and information
I'm just a messenger it's got a
companion book too okay so what I'm
doing is I'm mixing this in got a
companion book which is
mindblowing they're
Bibles all right so um I want to get
some onion in here chop up a little bit
of onion
let's do some chopping action let's
go all
right here we
go I'm doing good I'm doing good I'm
doing
good all right let's get some onion
chopped up it's going to go right in
here we're going to chop it up like
really good though like we're going to
mince it up pretty good
okay so I'm going to put it
here just do some kind of
like right I don't want big pieces in my
burgers this is going to go in
here and I don't want the onion cooked
to dep today I like it when it's also
like this one way got this let's get
this onion in here now let's get some
garlic in here what you see is a pot of
millet
Mill
it
nice let's get a garlic clove in here
recipe calls for one garlic
clove I'm guilty of putting in more many
times definitely guilty of putting more
than
one
definitely check those
fries let's be quick we got some crunch
on those fries we got some crunch on
those fries
[Music]
all right let's get a garlic clove going
I want to chop this up and throw this in
the Millet
nice I just don't want the paper there
we go let's do a little shopping action
here all right let's get that in
there
okay that garlic is not from my garden
that onion is not from my
garden but these greens are all the
greens here I I'll go through the greens
in a little while it's going to be
really fun I'm going to mix this up in
here I'm going to let that heat get in
here with the
onions okay bosia says over there on
YouTube aw your nails look so healthy
why thank
you only get a manicure and a
pedicure every week no I don't no I
don't I don't I
don't my nails look
healthy okay just mixing this up in
here okay I'm going to add some spices
in here too
Evelyn says is it true that when you cut
garlic wait 10 minutes before putting it
in your food so it can release all its
goodies if you like to do that that's
fine you can do that is it true
no fresher that garlic
is the fresher like right in that moment
right in that second you break that
paper
it's at its strongest always at its
strongest releasing all its goodies
instantly right off the
running all right let's get some spices
in here now to put a little bit of some
different spices here I'm going to put a
little bit of thyme oregano in
there let's get some Paprika in here
too little bit of that in there
too
all right let me show you here close up
what we
got take look guys what you'll see right
here is the Millet I'm moving it around
in here it's really hot I got some
sundried tomato in there I already put
in there I got some garlic I got some
onions I'm just going to give it a
little bit of a
mix okay I'm mixing up the Paprika in
there if you want something else in here
you can you can put hot pepper I might
even throw throw a Cayenne in here I
don't know if I should or not I got to
think about it I'd say no I won't do
that I won't
put okay just giving it a mix that's
nice and hot look at that that's a
milet okay
right I'm going to put a little bit more
of the potato starch this is a potato
flake add a little bit more these these
it burgers are going to be
insane
seriously all
right I just want to mix it up
nice here we
go get it back on the
pot give it a little bit couple
minutes we'll get everything
ready okay first thing I want to do
is I'm going to give it like about a
couple of seconds let me check those
crinkle Cuts I'm getting nervous
now no pressure don't want to burn those
fries now you guys are looking good
you're a little crispy man you're a
little crispy in some places yep all
right you're
done you're done
nice get you
out guys bear with me I'm over here by
the
oven not to
worry take a look at these crinkle Cuts
look at that that's
insane all
right take a
look you guys see that what you see
right
here is some Sear serious serious french
fry action I like fries with my Burgers
take a
look see this this is the way I like you
see this crunchy look got a little bit
of a little bit of a burn around the
edges but nice and crunchy let's just
see if we have oh yeah look at that
grilled Dude where's Bryce where the
heck is Bryce when you need him he would
go sick with this look at that after all
that weed Bryce smokes man he'd be like
Downing these things in a
second you guys know I don't smoke
weed I don't need weed I don't need
speed all
right
right that is so good all right so on
these french fries I'm going to leave
them on the pan a little bit for a few
minutes and I'm going to start making
the burgers I got to get them frying up
okay
pan is
hot put them down over here for a
second kind of move this over here all
right
okay let me get the
Millet in
here now this is some hot
Millet all
right guys do I do I look like I know
what I'm
doing all right let's get the pan back
on lately some this isign IG lately some
other doctors are doing cooking shows
too like they are copying Anthony they
do copy
Anthony they copy Anthony on so many
things you guys I can give you a list of
mile
long like a mile
long it's insane all right so check this
out I'm just letting this cool down for
a second but then again I can handle hot
temp like this is beaming boiling
scalding hot right here that's what this
is this is really
hot I think I can still do it so what
you do is put a little water on your
hands okay I'm going to grab some of
this so I'm going to make a big
burger right going to make a big burger
you guys see
this now what you want to do did you
ever do the Cho meat Burgers right so
many people love Cho me
meat they love the chop meat well this
is a millet Burger
H okay ready how's
that I'm getting it more
round there you go see
this there you go that's going on the
pan I'm going to do
three whoa that's a big one that's a
really big one there I don't know if it
should have been that big
but I can't help
it I'm wetting my hand again right I'm
going to move this over
okay this is this is freaking hot this
is even hot for me and I can handle like
heat on my hands I saw coming in like
the YouTube one time someone was
like they've never seen anything like it
all right I'm going to add a little bit
more to
that doesn't help that I have hot water
running out of
there but that's fine all
right see this is going in it's another
one get one
more
go all
right if you just got here got to watch
the show from the beginning that's all I
can tell
you if you just got here watch the show
from the beginning that's a smaller
Burger a little bit smaller going to
plop them one right there there
okay that's the mix let's get it over
here s right guys you're in the medical
M kitchen and we're
live that's how we do it we like to do
stuff
live ready get ready for the closeup on
the
pan get
ready see
him boom look at
that those are three Millet Burgers
right
there I got the heat cranked up not like
totally crazy I got the heat cranked up
these are
cooking I got my fries over there let's
start making
ketchup while these are
cooking so I got I I love this tomato
paste you guys know it's on my directory
check out my
directory go to medical.com check out
the
directory no I don't own the tomato
paste company the amount of crap I get
if I even just show anything it's crazy
I don't sell programs I don't sell this
I don't sell I'm not saying I'm not
going to do that someday but still I
don't sell this I don't have
subscription fees I don't do this this
this there no pay walls
everywhere no firewalls everywhere I
want The Chronic Leal to get all the
information free my podcast is no
advertising advertisements going on
where have like all those like you know
what I mean all those commercials on my
podcast I got none of that and on
YouTube the only reason why you see that
there is we had that we never had ads
running on our YouTube they did that
purposely to us and we purposely don't
collect the
money we purposely don't collect the
money we say we you know that we YouTube
we're like screw you I'm not even going
to take that
money all right cuz you're not even
supposed to have those those commercials
on my YouTube in the first
place so I'm not going to like take your
money it's principal on that man all
right let's
go so I'm going to make some ketchup and
I think I have some
ketchup
um stuff
here I'm going to get a ketchup Bowl
excuse
me
okay whenever you open any
jar any jar any glass jar whenever you
open make sure you hear that make sure
you press here make sure that pop is
down make sure that suctions there
here hear
that people buy stuff they don't
know Millet burgers are
cooking all right you guys we're doing
the ketchup right
now I'm just going to empty this in here
cuz I want a decent amount of
ketchup I like get extra
ketchup okay want a little bit of apple
juice in
here you can check out the recipe just
go to the medical medium protocols book
there get a little bit of apple juice in
there like
that
okay I might put a little touch more
cuz I got a lot of tomato
paste all right you can put a little
lemon in there if you want I'm going to
put a touch of
Lemon Back Spin touch a
lemon don't know why I have to do that
started when I was a
kid I'm going to have to do something
different over here with this okay I
don't want a lot of lemon in this one
but I'm putting
pretty much what the book says right
there all right onion
powder put a little bit of that in there
in the
ketchup okay garlic
powder really wasn't going to do that in
this ketchup but I will little garlic
powder don't want a lot all right pinch
of cayenne we can make this ketchup a
little hot I have a Cayenne around here
fresh cayenne let make this ketchup a
little
hot we're going to chop this up you guys
see
this we don't want it too hot though I
tend to make I tend to make stuff so hot
where I'm just like you know in that
crazy place of heat let's pop a little
bit there we go see
that rinse your hand of that cayenne
pepper please don't be rubbing your eye
and don't be in the
bathroom you might be somebody that's in
the bathroom screaming because you got
Cayenne yep you can put chili flakes in
there I went with fresh and then raw
honey can go in here but I'm keeping the
raw honey out because I like my Millet
Burger a lot of people like their
ketchup with a little sweet Edge I like
my ketchup a little Savory so I'm just
keeping the honey out not because I
don't like honey I love honey honey is
amazing I eat a lot of
honey that's some good ketchup that's
going to be really
good okay ketchup done let's take a look
at these Millet
Burgers aw's Bar and Grill can I take an
order
please what would you
like I thought I heard the phone ring
too thought I heard the phone
ring all
right God I heard the phone
ringing all right
here just let him cook you want to give
them a really
good you want to give him some time on
that pan you guys this this is where you
got to be careful you got to make sure
you you cook these
good that phone's
ringing hey de's bar
grill
yeah pork pork burgers yeah yep soldered
Pig Burgers yeah
huh pop no we only use pot belly
pigs you know the pets people don't
people buy the pot belly pig as a pet
all the kids love it in the
family and the pet is is like and then
it gets too
much and then the pot belly pig is
eating and eating and getting bigger and
fatter yeah and then they got no place
to put the pot belly pig so we put an ad
out on
Craigslist to ask everybody if they have
if they don't want their pot pot belly
pigs
anymore
yeah
so yeah that's what our burgers are made
out
of what Joe's Bar grill it's down the
street yeah you want their phone number
too
okay um it's it's I don't know what it
is just look it up okay
bye sry guys aw's bar grill gets a
little
busy it just
does come on Millet
Burgers all
right all right we're just making sure
sure we get these done right
here yeah they just got to get a little
hotter if you guys want a closeup I'll
show you a closeup right here
too real
quick that's the Miller
Burgers I got my French Fries over here
all
right they just need a few more minutes
but we're we're getting
there okay onig some people
believe of the sulfur of garlic and
onions cause bloating in gas is that
true the sulfur and garlic and onions do
not cause um bloating in gas
garlic kills a lot of yeast and
mold and a lot of unproductive
fungus garlic kills a lot of microbes
garlic kills bad
bacteria and when you send raw garlic
down and you're filled you're like
you're
overfilled or you got a pocket or two
maybe a pocket or two that you haven't
tapped into in inside your gut that
garlic is going
to Boom blow it up and all it takes is
one microbe
dying and that can give you some gas
just one microbe dying can give you
gas but it's not the sulfur that's
giving people
gas plus it's
hell like hot spicy
you name it too and that's that's a
whole another thing um I can go into
that in a second too so over here on IG
I got a sponsored ad the other day
trying to debunk info on celery juice
and
hmds
yeah yeah it's like it's really stupid
is what it is it's really dumb celery
juice is literally saving lives around
the planet the stores can't keep celery
juice or celery in stock anymore they
just can't they haven't been able to
there was a celery shortage around the
world roughly over 500 million people
are drinking it on the day on The
Daily
okay celery juice doesn't
make the scammers
money you can't make money off of celery
juice but you can make money off of
ripping apart celery juice and leading
them to something else you're
selling what you'll find is people
ripping down celery juice are usually
selling something what are they selling
products programs courses what are they
selling it's like praying on the
community that's people come in they
come in the
Sharks sometimes the sharks aren't baby
sharks sometimes the sharks are bigger
sharks and they come into the
community and they try to brain you
and that's what they do
and they do nothing but and
that's what they
do they come in like that those those
words are warranted for the situation
they come in for and they use money in
advertising and and what happens
is it's like I know people that would be
dead without celery juice out there I
know people who got their intestinal
tracks back to stabilization when they
were in the worst situations they were
on colostomy bags I know people people
that celery juice restored their gut so
they can digest a protein I know people
they got rid of their acne got rid of
this celery juice they acid reflux but
celery juice is all of a sudden bad you
can't make money off of celery
juice but you can make money off of
selling something you're selling but
talk about celery juice at the same
time just needs a couple more minutes
here a lot of these people also take the
medical medium original information at
the same time you guys and they mix it
up a little bit with their junk that
they're
selling they talk about binders or
whatever whatever they just try to mess
up people's heads and that's how it
works
yeah
all right just cooking these a little
bit longer what it is is I'm using this
burner instead of the burner here so I
might do that I actually might flip it
onto this burner so I can get equal heat
everywhere on
there so that's what I'm going to do I'm
going to flip this pan to the
stove make sure there's nothing on the
stove yeah we're
good there are millions of people around
the planet drinking s juice they needed
every single day it's
critical I mean critical for the
recovery
yeah including misinformation about
hmds which they wouldn't even know about
hmds anything anyway if it wasn't for
medical medium information with all the
Decades of putting heavy metal
information out there and toxic heavy
metal and toxic metal information out
there all right I'm going to flip this
onto
here guys I'm putting on the big pan
right here the big burner so I can
equally distribute it this this burner
is this big and I got three large
burgers in there this burner is big
small
yeah medical medum tools are saving
lives
and and it's just amazing but what what
happens is the big bigger sharks come in
or the smaller sharks actually smaller
sharks whatever the smaller sharks come
in and what they do is they'll rip apart
celery juice they'll mess up your head
making it you know your head could be
confused like oh my god really celery
juice is bad why because something that
was made up and not even true like
celery juice is bad what oh I need a
binder now oh celery
juice you know it's there to just screw
like screw your head
up all right
guys this Pan's doing good this Pan's
hot
one another one right
there
let that c a little bit
more just reading comments um hly says
healed my gastroparesis with celery
juice haven't thrown up in
months okay here you are
Haley you healed your your gastroparesis
with celery juice okay just imagine if
you like saw a bunch of bunch of like
misinformation about celery juice you
saw somebody out there that seems like
they have their crap together they're so
seasoned and they're sitting there
telling you how bad celery juice
is think about that right celery juice
healed your
gastroparesis and then you got people
coming into the medical mem Community
talking about how it's so bad for you
and it can cause problems but buy my
stuff here check out my stuff here check
out my my stuff
to sell right meanwhile if someone is
actually getting rid of their
gastroparesis heal their gastroparesis
or healed something or healed your sibo
or healed whatever it is that someone
might have so many people have different
problems are they each pylori or
whatever can you imagine just be like oh
yeah oh yeah celery juice must be bad
because look people are saying it's bad
out there they're running ads every
minute they're saying it's bad meanwhile
using all at the same time they're using
all my original medical medium
information about viruses and pathogens
and toxic heavy metals all in the same
all in the same talk yeah I
know all
right these are almost done I made these
babies big I put them on the little tiny
burner which I've never cooked these on
the little burner before that's three
big Millet Burgers I got it on the main
griddle we're almost
there
let's get a plate
out I love this
plate getting
ready you notice I'm quiet right now I'm
reading all of your comments right now
in between flipping
burgers nice I want to show you this
right here how great this is when it
gets like this nice take a look guys I
want to give you that close on this
pan take a look see that that's the way
you do it right there that's the way you
want it look at
that get them
toasty
okay I couldn't find celery yesterday at
two stories two
stores yeah this is
Stefan
yeah yes the sponsored ad was
marketed yep to another person stuff
yeah well that's what you know what
happens is what they'll do is they'll
they'll they're look the medical medum
community is unlike anything else out
there it doesn't you have to understand
you guys there's no Community out there
that exist exists like this community
there just isn't because there isn't a
community out there where that many
people healed or are healing like that
are really sick like chronically ill
that doesn't exist out
there and so because that doesn't exist
this is the prime location though
because the medical Med Community is a
large community and it's and it's
getting new people in all the time that
are kind of like scared sitting on
sitting on the fence they've been
through hell out there and they're just
starting to get their sea legs and
they're just starting to come around
where they're like you know they've been
through so much and then it's the
perfect place to shoot propaganda at
them to lead them astray so then they
get confused like I just started
drinking celery and now what I just
started drinking celery just and what's
going to happen to me now like
what it's
like well I got I'm I'm
um
so I'm I'm following this medical medium
guy
and I've been sick for like 5 years and
I've been through hell and back
and yeah I've been sick for a long time
and um anyway I'm on his I'm I'm on his
page right now I'm on medical means page
right now yeah I'm going through
Instagram oh celery juice is really
interesting the flavor it's like new to
me oh there's an ad celery juice is
really bad for you it doesn't work you
mean you're an authority this ad looks
very like you seem like you know what
you're talking about wait a minute
what what oh my God this is poison this
is poisonous celery juice I'm not even
going to take a chance I'm going to just
go right back to the same old crap and
maybe I'll look into what their crap
they're selling
[Music]
now
[Applause]
wonder why there's no celery
Emoji there used to
be uh-huh it used to be it was taken
down right around when we got
censored four years
ago all right
these are coming out
nice you guys this is what it's supposed
to look like thank you for hanging out
while I get this plated and done take a
look at this okay you see that on there
and I want to show you close on IG you
see Tik Tock how you guys doing right
see
that Tick
Tock you guys
see that's it right
there all right they're done we can
start
plating what kind of bun would you like
on your uh mil with on your Millet
Burger Lily homie says celery juice has
helped my baby and his eczema clear
we're going on our fifth
month so your baby's eczema is clearing
up because of celery
juice
but the
Sharks come in and they C is
bad all
right so I'm going to shut this pan off
I'm going to plate these
up what kind of bun would you like for
your burger now I have this beautiful
lettuce right here so I'm going to make
a few of
them I got this lettuce this is all
garden lettuce I'm going to make this
little lettuce bed here for the bottom
I'm going to take take off these
pieces funny thing is that
some da says on IG funny thing keeps
going up hold on we'll get that
comment it's like going up and then
doing this crazy thing funny thing is
that some doctors are trying to create a
community too haha they can keep trying
there won't be a community like medical
mediums amen
am
amen all right let's get these
going so I'm doing a lettuce little
lettuce bottom for this one and I'm
going to take a look you guys I'm going
to take one of these Millet burgers and
I'm going to Plate it in front of you
but I'm going to move it here like this
there you
go it's a tricky spot tricky
spot
okay I'm going to put a little ketchup
on top to
now little ketchup on
top look at
this you guys seeing
this the next one I'll put a little less
ketchup
on here I'll take a little bit off
here little too much on here let me take
a little there we
go let's get let's get some tomato
going got to cut this
tomato this is a beef steak a beef steak
tomato so I'm going to cut kind of thin
slices watch see watch
this I'm going to get some Thin slices
going look at
that here we go I think I'll get one
more out of this just for fun
okay let's get some tomato going on this
one let's just move everything over
there you go you
ready that
out tomato how many tomato slices would
you like I can put two I'm going to put
a third on here like that let's slice up
some
onion let's get an onion sliced up
now that onion is not for my
garden I grow onions they're just not
ready they had a hard time this year and
they're still dogging
it an
onion
problem all right here we go thin
slice I'm going to do thin slices of
onion you don't want it so thick and
bulky and crazy you want it thin see
what funny is okay so on YouTube what's
funny let's get some Thin slices here
what's funny is the woman in the ad
bashing CJ and hmds is married to
someone who shares the last name with
the doctor she's
promoting upside down smiley
faces
[Music]
all right let's pop some of this on
here I you guys I just say put the
lettuce on top I'm going to break this
little piece off the bottom not because
you don't eat that part you eat that
part but really I just want to Plate
this burger up all all nice right here
in front of you like that see that see
that burger let me just put it like
that look at that let's make another
another let's make another I'm going to
do this one with a collored green what
do you say about
that with a collared
green so what I'm going to do is cut the
collar green here like
this to about this
level I'm not throwing that
out that's the collar green I'm going to
pop it here I might even fold it in a
little
bit this is going to be the bottom
part let's get the
burger yeah what do you think Tik
Tock yep you guys
see try not to stick the pan on the all
right let's just
go that's insane right there you guys
seeing
this
you guys see
that you don't have to do ketchup on
this one I'm going to hold the ketchup
on this
one I'm going to do a ketchup list on
this one you know I want to change it up
each one cuz you don't know you know I
got family coming over you don't know
who's going to like someone might come
come over and be like I don't want
ketchup on mine you know how that
happens let's get some tomatoes on top
look at
that that is like
insane see
that see some onion oh yeah some fries
what am I doing totally screwing up here
and then you can take
this totally messing up
here okay a coll Leaf right there I'm
going to put it on top can you guys
see look at that is that the kind of bun
you
want
there we
go can't see the burger so easy though
presentation this is a festar Michelin
tire
restaurant okay all
right now we're going to go with some
fries on this
plate all
right
hold
on
worry got
it I'm
here
yep
look at these steak fries you
guys take a look at these steak fries
can you see
those I mean
right no
right look at these steak
fries do you guys like steak fries what
kind of fries do you guys
like McDonald's supplied us with these
french fries and just delivered them now
take a look at them they're making
McDonald's is making a new McDonald's
and Burger King they knocked on our door
and they wanted to contribute to the
live so they made these steak fries
there at McDonald's and they just
brought them over um
um I mean it's really nice of them
actually to do that to bring to bring
such beautiful French fries to us right
yeah like the head manager of all
McDonald's was at the door at Medical
medium just now and said look use our
new steak fries
W I'm just actually that was a
joke okay look at
that y over there on YouTube I've always
overlooked this recipe in the book but
this live made me want to do
it look at
that look at
that that's just crazy
[Music]
oh hold
on oo
[Music]
nice I
guess all right let's get some ketchup
in here okay SP with me this is for the
fries is this right
here
whoa okay let's let's let's plate this
up hey
guys I'm going to devour
these nice you guys probably can't see
this on the closeup there but it's it's
good it's good we're still doing it look
at the grill look at the grill marks on
these fries
like look at the grill marks on those I
got to show you look at that is that
insane look at the grill
marks
yep I hope Mrs Ferguson comes
downstairs and I hope she brings Mr
fergon because honestly they would
really like
this but Mr Fergenson he's always stuck
on the
toilet and
um
okay there we go set this up just
right
okay I'm going to fill this up right all
I want to show you
guys all right now I'm just giving you a
closeup IG
ticktock close
up all
right here we
go
all right I'm going to just fix this up
a little bit
here there we go it's a big collared
Leaf there you
go take a
look you guys I'm
hungry there we
go
okay
all
right you guys what do you think Tik
Tock take a look I'll flip it
around IG take a
look YouTube Take a Look Rumble take a
look
okay there you have it I'm going to dip
a fry in right
now m
mja
mja I'm going to take a bite onto a
burer are you guys okay with
that this one's
mine
M all
right take a look at this
burger
oh my God are you
kidding all right give me you guys a
little look on this look at that and
I'll do a little closeup with the
camera here it is that's the burger
right there you know restaurant quality
that's the Millet
Burger how does that look what do you
guys think that got ketchup all over my
face
that's what I'm talking about that's
what I'm talking
about well this looks better than all
the restaurant food on
YouTube thank
you you guys don't mind
right I'm sending this down I'm smashing
this
down oh crap darn it I
forgot I forgot that you have to do like
mindful chewing and mindful
eating I forgot I have to sit down I
have to
relax my mindfulness meditation coach
tells me all the
time I have to sit down I have to take
my time and I have to chew really slow
like
this
my mindful meditation code say
aw you swallow too fast 37 bytes per
bite 37 shoes per
bite one 2 three four 5 6 7 8 10 11 12
14 15
16 17 18 I can't make it it went down
the hatch I'm just kidding don't have a
mindfulness coach but this is how I
smashed out a Miller
burger oh man that's look
amazing hands down that's
incredible that's how I said one
down well if you guys don't mind I'm
going to have a
fry um this one looks good you ever pick
the fry you want
it all right guys
yes the lettuce is the bun all right
guys take care I'm going to eat thank
you for being here if you just got here
check out the show from the beginning
we'll cover a lot of cool stuff