healthy valve movements uh unhealthy
bowel movements we're going to talk
about that support intestinal tract gut
problems and we're not just going to be
having fun talking about proof we're
actually going to be talking about the
gut how it works a little bit too so
information that's really important to
know
so that's what i'm doing here right now
it's good to see you guys live on tick
tock live on rumble facebook youtube
live on telegram happy to be here you
guys follow click the follow button the
like button whatever you want to do if
you like this video we're going to have
some fun going to read some comments
i got some comments right here that are
really important too good ones and what
you'll see
a whole bunch of things set up right
here okay i get a whole bunch of stuff
you'll see the nut butters are here
you'll see the nuts are here you'll see
everything here you see chocolates here
chocolate
we got all kinds of stuff here at oil
everything else and so this is an
important life you would say well why is
this an important live about poop
because everybody
looks in the toilet after they go
very few people on the planet
don't look
behind them
after they've gone okay
everybody looks that's what they do they
get up and they look those down in there
like yeah looks pretty good
and so what happens is that
like poops everything to everybody for
so many reasons you know we don't talk
about it we don't want to talk about it
we're embarrassed to talk about it
at the same time every time you go to
your doctor physician your your health
care provider whatever it is they're
always asking questions people are
always concerned their stomach problems
everything else so it's kind of
important in so many different ways good
to see you guys coming on we're live
right now this is kind of part of the
poop-a-thon i promised you guys so this
is
an episode on poop so let's get started
okay so
what i love
okay
is
questions that are well that's not what
i learned in school aw hey that's not
what i learned
or that's not what i learned in training
or that's not what i was taught in the
medical field don't listen to this man
because he doesn't know anything
and you know that's i love when that
happens because i see that happen all
the time right it doesn't matter how
many people got better at medical mean
information doesn't matter the medical
medium information it's the first in
chronic illness to change the rules out
there where people are healing
rapidly all around the world that
doesn't matter not of that right just
know um you learn something about poop
that's misinformation you hold on to
that for the rest of your life and you
think you're you're solid
so the point is is that questions come
about and it's like okay
i always heard that when a poop floats
then you're in trouble a healthy poop
sinks
that's what people say a healthy poop
up unhealthy poop
floats right so that's what people are
trained to think or trained to know
but you got to think about i said this
before all the people dying
all the hospitals filled with very ill
people
okay and their poops all sink
there's people that are dying
only got a couple weeks to live
and their poops are sinking
so
it's not that the person's poop is
perfectly healthy and fine but they're
gonna die in two weeks
so they're unhealthy they're obviously
dying they're very ill
okay but their poop is healthy
everything about their poop is healthy
it sinks it's healthy you got to think
about that for a minute there right
understand what that means
and how it works okay sun moon love says
still hungry from your other life i
don't know if you're gonna be hungry
anymore because we're talking about poop
but it was really an incredible live so
anyway the amazon live you guys got to
catch it when you get the chance and you
can if you just so you know we did a
killer like game day prepared for you
know we did a seven layer dip and
buffalo wings and everything you guys
got gotta check out that amazon live
when you get a chance the link is in the
description link is in the profile so
it's like a super bowl meal i made so
and healthy too is cauliflower that's
incredible cauliflower bites buffalo
cauliflower bites you gotta check it out
so
so right now we're talking about
poop i'm glad you guys are coming on
good to see everybody all right so what
happens is the misinformation is really
rampant out there about poop
you can have people dying
sick
real sick all kinds of problems in their
intestinal tract all kinds of different
disorders different conditions and their
poop will sink
it'll sink
it will and that's what happens and
people don't realize this
michael scoots good to see people don't
realize this that that's what happens
and so you can what i talk to nurses all
through the years i've talked to doctors
and they'll tell you i know like i was
talking about this in amazon life friend
of mine is an emergency room doctor
right
and he's dealing with the sickest people
on the planet rolling in just rolling in
right deathly ill
their poop sinks
so now the person's sick
the person's dying
the person has organ failure but their
poops are
healthy does that make any sense to you
it doesn't make any sense that's the
whole point now think about this
millions of people
in the u.s alone over 275
million americans are sick
yes
275 million americans are sick you guys
with symptoms and conditions
some gravely sick some just moderately
sick
some partly sick and their poop all
sinks
i don't think
we can just confidently say
right
that if a poop sinks it's great and
that's what we've been taught you got to
think about that
275 million americans alone i'm not good
about worldwide
billions of people on the planet their
poop sinks
billions are sick with symptoms and
conditions so we have to we have to kind
of like take a look at that to begin
with and see how that works and nothing
makes sense holly's health says nothing
in the medical system makes sense true
very little does
so let's get into this a little bit so
here's the deal if your poop floats
that means you must have pancreatic
cancer that means you're not digesting
your fats
that means it must be all fat in your
poop right that's the misinformation so
that's the part that's the
misinformation
okay
right
so that's that part there is wait a
minute
if your poop floats you're sick
you're sick
it's interesting someone dying in the
hospital
organ failure and every other problem
right really sick on tons of medications
everything else their poop sinks to the
bottom of the toilet they're not sick
someone who doesn't exhibit one symptom
their poop floats all of a sudden
they're the one dying
think about that so that's why this
misinformation is so
basically
filled with so many different aspects of
it that we're going to cover and go
through that are just perplexing in so
many ways so let's go into that a little
bit guys so we're talking about poop i
want to grab a glass here with water
okay
so the misinformation out there is if
your poop floats
that means you're sick
very unhealthy unwell
you're not digesting your food right
and all the fat is floating to the
surface that's what we're taught right
there okay
but you got to remember
you're being taught that from
the industry both medical communities
both alternative and conventional that
don't know why anybody's sick and don't
know why anybody got sick
that's how it's always been that's why
people go to doctor to doctorate mystery
symptoms and they never find any answers
so we're taught that by those guys right
even functional medicine doctors we're
taught that by them that's great but
there are people that have been to a lot
of functional medicine doctors and still
didn't heal until they found mm info
and that's why functional medicine
doctors now use mm info but the point is
is let's go into how it works your stool
floating or stool sinking now i said the
healthiest stool
is a stool that's
mid-floating poop that's mid-floating
it's okay if your poop sinks if you're
eating really healthy and you're doing
you're working on your healing process
you've got a good diet and your poop
sinks that's okay
when you eventually get so healthy and
your liver heals and everything cleans
up your poop will start to float a
little bit your poop will start going
mid mid float like a mid float there's a
reason for that one reason is because
you're absorbing every last little bit
of fat
every last little bit of protein and
fats being utilized and absorbed and
when all your fat and your protein gets
utilized and absorbed you guys your
stool starts to mid float it starts to
take a little bit of elevation it starts
to float a little bit this is so
important to know right here
so
so we have to understand something when
you're
digestive system is so sharp your
liver's literally breaking down every
bit of that fat and it's going into your
bloodstream
right your stomach's breaking down every
bit of that protein breaking it down to
nothing
right
but what's going to be left in your
stool you guys
is fiber
fiber floats
fiber and pulp
will float so you have to know that it's
important to know
that will float
so let's take a banana right
a banana
is a lot of sugar like we know right
that's your sugar it's banana okay so
i'll put a piece of banana in here right
you'll see the banana float
your banana isn't an overt fat it
doesn't have a lot of protein in it it
doesn't have a lot of fat in it notice
it's floating
and pouring it out let's take a lemon
now all right
so let's take a lemon next let's do a
lemon slice right here okay a lemon
is pulp
fiber right
and your lemon's floating
see how it works
so that's your lemon
it's floating
okay
so what happens is
that there's no overt fat in here
so everybody keeps on saying well it's
fat that floats it's fat that floats
that's why you're sick it's fat that
floats it's that that's not true that's
not entirely true we're gonna go we're
gonna go through all of this okay
nature's gift said or that is made up of
mostly water and air not true
there's no air in a banana
so
you're wrong i'm sorry
there's no air in a banana
very important to know okay
there's no air
inside the lemon
there's no space for air and there's no
air inside of a lemon it is liquid pulp
fiber
pith
pectin
and all of that floats
very important to know right
so i know you don't like to be debunked
i get it you don't like to be debunked
no one likes to be debunked they don't
it's another reason why a lot of people
in the field of medicine don't like
medical medium because they hate being
debunked over and over and over again
they look like a fool and then they
don't know what to do and they're like
oh my god we've been wrong let's take a
cucumber slice now okay
so i got a cucumber slice in here
cucumber's floating
so i thought that means you're dying if
your stool floats so if you're somebody
that eats lots of fruits lots of
vegetables lots of leafy greens lots of
wild foods
and your stool floats
you're dying
does that make any sense
see
this is important information so i i i
would i would recommend re-watching this
live i really would because we're going
to cover this like
all through it right so let's go a
little bit more celery
there's no air in celery okay
it's no air and celery
celery's floating
right
see
there's no fat
in the celery there's no fat in the
cucumber there's no fat in the lemon
there's no fat in the banana it's not an
overt fat why is it all floating and
there's no gas in here
you guys
there is no gas in here
you can't say that a stool that floats
because it's made out of pith fiber
pectin
and pulp
you can't say that there's gas in there
that's not how it works fiber floats all
these things float you see how it works
your diet
when it's high in all of this you get a
mid-floating poop and a floating poop
and it's the healthiest poop you can
ever get and i'll tell you why
see
let's go into a little bit more on y and
everything so here we are
so right now if you guys just came on
here i'm going to read some questions
about poop we're part of the poop this
is part of the poopathon i've been
promising
i hope i can deliver there's lots of fun
stuff to talk about about poop so let's
go let's get into it a little bit so i
got another glass right here
all right
we all know chocolate's high in fat
if
fat is why your poop is floating because
you're not digesting any fat and you're
thinking oh well a sick poop is
undigested fat and that's just what the
way it goes let's take a look here
i'm gonna put some chocolate in here
the chocolate sinks to the bottom like a
rock just like your poop
just like your it just goes down to
the bottom
see how it works
when you eat a diet
with a chocolate bar in it it's going to
sink to the bottom
when you poo it out because your poop is
going to be filled with fat
and protein
when fat is in your poop it sinks to the
bottom of the toilet everybody has a
weak liver people dying in the hospital
have weak and dysfunctional livers
there's people dying in the hospital
with liver with liver um
failure
and they can't digest any of their fat
but their poop is stuck to the bottom of
the toilet
i know so
i talked to a lot of patients i talked
to a lot of doctors
and that happens you can have liver
failure and your poops all float to the
bottom of the toilet
so let's do some more different
chocolate here we got some chocolate
chips all these chocolate chips are
sinking to the bottom of the toilet
see
that's right
like that
that's how it goes so i'm dropping all
those chocolate chips down into the
bottom and there they are
right
let's do another little test too so
let's let's let's keep on testing we'll
have some more fun here right let's go
with some cashews right
dropping some cashews in here too
they're all going down
to the bottom they're all sinking
now cashews have air in them you have to
break the cashew open because they
actually have an air pocket like a
balloon
so if you put a whole cashew in it might
fall it might float but what happens you
need to know is that when you let the
air out because you'll see in the middle
of a cashew you have a pocket in there
it's hollow cashews are actually hollow
they're filled with air
it's important to know
so when you break the cashew in half
you'll notice they all sink
because
that's what fat does
it sinks
right that's the fat that everybody's
eating so let's go into a couple more
things let's do this
we're going to do some almonds too
almonds are sinking see
here's how it works everybody
if they all had their stools
analyzed right and profiles were done on
how much fat and proteins in their
stools
it would be loaded with lots of fat
that's why their poops are sinking it's
too the fats not being broken down or
digested this is an unhealthy sign this
means that people living their lives the
whole world is pooping and it's sinking
to the bottom of the toilet the whole
world's getting sick
and everybody's poop sinks because
everybody's poops are filled with
digestive problems they've digested
problems and their poops are filled with
undigested fat and protein see
so when you eat a whole bunch of almond
butter you're not breaking all the
almond butter down so what's happening
is your almond butter is being pooped
out and that puts the smear on the
toilet
that puts the smear
on the toilet
right in there in the basin right that's
that slimy smear
that's avocado that's chocolate that's
yes chocolate that's nut butter that's
tahini peanut butter that's all of that
is being smeared there if you're only on
bananas you're not going to get a smear
in the toilet
your poop will probably float if you're
only on banana after a while
daisy says not true i'm not sure who
she's saying not true to
but that's a daisy saying
so i have an egg right here
an egg
is high in fat this is why doctors for
many years said be cautious about eggs
because it'll bring you to a heart
attack
and then the egg industry pays for all
these you know new ads and new studies
and everything to try to get people to
start eating eggs again and so the whole
propaganda and everybody thinks eggs are
healthy and then you know against
sane advice that you eat too many eggs
yeah you'll get a buildup of fat inside
your heart and arteries
and cardiovascular system and you'll be
set up for a stroke heart attack or
whatever
yeah
right
so
there's a question right there daisy
says are you unhealthy and my poop my
poop is never sinking right
and i'm going to cover that
you can have gastritis and have a lot of
gas
and your poop can float from lots of gas
from a from a digestive system that's
also struggling
but
everybody in a hospital in every single
hospital in the united states and and
abroad or anywhere else right overseas
or whatever they're in the hospital
their poops are sinking they're sick as
dogs most those people and their poop is
sinking
i got an egg right here right i'ma drop
an egg in here
okay
so i just put an egg in this
that egg sunk to the bottom is what that
egg did
so people eat eggs every day
that egg is high in fat
and here's with something interesting
that egg has air in it too
and look how heavy
the fat is
and the protein is in that egg look how
heavy eggs eggs are really high in fat
okay
that's sunk to the bottom see that egg
when people eat eggs and they're
undigested and they don't realize it
their poop sinks to the bottom of the
toilet i'm trying to tell you guys when
your digestive system is not sharp
feezy says okay that's true i have gas
issues
yeah of course of course thank you for
saying that
some people they just won't say anything
back they'll just be like you're wrong
so thank you it's really kind of you
actually
and so you have to understand here even
with air inside that egg that egg sinks
to the bottom
so that's important to know
okay
so
what i'm gonna do is
some of you might doubt that that's not
a real egg and i i actually understand
that okay so let me get this out here
all right
some of you might doubt that that's real
egg so and i don't blame you really
so i just dumped the water on i got the
egg right here
okay
so
that's a real egg
hope you can see that egg in there and
that's the egg yolk right there
see if you can see that just just
because i know that you guys know that i
have
props and stuff you're thinking well
maybe that's just a prop but no that's a
real egg
right
there i just wanted to show you guys
that
so
let's let's keep on moving along let's
go into some nut butters really quick
okay i'm gonna answer some questions too
let me show you enough here we have some
almond butter
there's oil just rolling around on the
top it's not butter right why is he
wearing gloves
what do you mean
do i want raw egg all over the board i
don't just i don't feel like dying i
don't feel like killing a family member
tonight
family member comes in here and starts
using my cutting board with raw egg all
over my cutting board and starts to make
themselves a snack maybe they chop up
some cucumber slices up or something
like that and they get that raw egg on
the cucumber that's the last thing i
want god forbid they end up in the
hospital salmonella you guys gotta
remember you leave your egg salad in the
sun for five seconds they say you can
die
they say you can't leave your potato
salad or egg salad with mayonnaise which
is egg you can't leave it outside of
like room temperature or on a picnic
table too long they say you're gonna get
sick and you're gonna end up dead
there's a reason for that
i know people
two people that died at a table in a
restaurant from salmonella they never
made it to the hospital in time they
literally died at the table
at the table
and then
if you don't cook your chicken
thoroughly
you can die
isn't that crazy so yeah okay i got a
glove on while i'm cracking open an egg
so that's almond butter right there it's
sunk right to the bottom
almond butter when you have a tablespoon
of almond butter
your poop will sink to the bottom
because the almond butter won't be fully
digested because everybody has a weak
liver stagnant sluggish liver the liver
is not working good
and their hydrochloric acid is not
strong so unhealthy poops it sinks to
the bottom so your almond butter ends up
going to the bottom your eggs end up
going to the bottom you see how it works
all of that goes to the bottom
same thing with peanut butter right here
smith and pepper says i have tons of
digestive issues and health issues and
my poop sinks for sure
absolutely
because you can have celiac crohn's
colitis and your poop sinks to the
bottom then why is everybody saying it's
a healthy poop
see where the misinformation is but it
takes it takes
a real
like awakening to know how the system is
so corrupted and and backwards with
everything just everything so let's go
into some questions right
here's one right here show me the
research that states floating poop is
linked to positive health and not
dysfunction i will wait
right
oh you'll wait
just like all the other people with
chronic illness for the last 30 40 years
that waited for 10 years 20 years
how to get their thyroid removed
no research to help them
all the people with
severe chronic fatigue syndrome and
neurological disorders
they waited
everybody with lupus and multiple
sclerosis they waited
everybody waited and went to 20 30
doctors so you'll wait too okay good i'm
glad you weighed
so let's take a look here i got a
question right here
being sarcastic
anthony i'm not saying that i disagree
with you because i believe in your
information
all i'm saying
is this
instead of using peanut butter tahini
nuts for your experiment why didn't you
use a spoonful of butter drizzles of any
oil spoonful of lard
a spoonful of straight cholesterol you
will find that those all things those
float i agree with you that if you have
a high fiber diet your stools are going
to float more than sink and i understand
your reasoning you can still have a high
fiber diet but if you're eating that
peanut butter and then almond butter and
that fat and all that other stuff that
i'm saying poop's going to sink to the
bottom even with a high fiber diet
so i agree with you that if you have a
high fiber diet your stools are going to
float more than sink and i understand
your reasoning and i appreciate your
teaching but blocked bile ducts and gall
stones can cause a fatty stool or
malabsorption of fat not peanut butter
fat
so peanut butter fat won't float
but
some other fat will
here's how it works okay
what happens is people that have
digestive problems in their and their
poop floats just because they have a
black bile duct their poop's not
floating because the fat's not
undigested because of a blocked bile
duct their poops floating because
they're sick with a ton of gas what
happens is this would you have
pancreatitis or pancreatic problems or
pancreatic duct problems or any kind of
duct problem even pancreatic cancer the
reason why your poop floats is because
your entire intestinal tract is filled
with a ton of gas because your liver and
your pancreas are failing to break down
and digest stuff so what's happening is
your
stool is all gas people with pancreatic
disease pancreatic cancer block bile
ducts have the worst stream in gastritis
where it's air that comes out non-stop
where it's pouring out non-stop now
someone may not have that experience of
knowing how that works but i actually
know how that works and i've seen this
so over and over again i've known people
with pancreatic cancer known lots of
them hundreds of them over the years i
talk doctors about lots of patients with
the same thing the gas streams out of
them and pours out of them and that gas
fills the stool and that's what makes
the stool float
important enough so now i'm going to
talk about something else within this
question just so you know so let's go
into so what this person is saying right
and i respect this person's question
question it's great
they're saying why aren't you trying
large so let's try other oil
let's try butter
so anthony why aren't you using butter
i'll tell you why i'm not using butter
right
i got some butter in here and you'll see
the butter float so that's a step this
is a stick of butter
right
okay
and the butter floats
right
but people eat that much butter on their
pancakes every day and their poop sinks
people eat butter in their food they put
butter on their chicken their poop
stinks and it sinks
people put butter in their food and
their poops all sink
all these people eating butter their
poop sinks every day because no one's
just eating butter
no one is just eating a whole stick of
butter sure if you eat ready for this
if you eat whole sticks of butter
like one whole stick of butter two whole
sticks of butter and three whole sticks
of butter in a day
and you poop butter straight out it's
still not going to float even though it
floats as butter here it won't float
after you've gone to bathroom
if you eat three sticks of butter in a
day the sticks of butter are gonna
collect other little bits of debris in
your intestinal tract anyway it's gonna
come out as butter because you're over
you're eating just butter and it's gonna
sink
and that's what people don't realize
if you eat just butter people aren't
eating just butter anyway no one's
eating three sticks four sticks of
butter no one's just downing a whole ton
of butter that's not what they're doing
but if you do down a lot of butter like
three sticks four sticks of butter your
poop's not gonna float your poop's still
gonna sink
the reason why i'm not using butter as a
poop tested here having it float is
because no one eats more than that much
butter and that butter in their poo
still
sinks to the bottom of the toilet
see how it works
so
no one's eating just straight fat by
itself now here's a pure example of this
if you drink a bottle of olive oil most
of the olive oil that goes into the
toilet will sink it'll wrap up with
little bits of
debris that's in your intestinal tract
and all the oil will be in globules and
it'll sink to the bottom of the toilet
but a little bit of olive oil will
surface so you'll still see some
surfacing to the top but nobody drinks a
whole bottle of olive oil nobody eats
sticks and sticks of butter by
themselves on their own they have a
little butter on their pancakes their
waffles they have a little butter on
their steak but their poops are still
sinking to the bottom of the toilet and
there's still butter in their stool
here's the interesting thing if you get
a stool test they'll find butter fat in
the poop that sunk to the bottom along
with the steak and everything else they
ate
so i want to answer a couple more
questions too
karen burkett says i've been doing mmm
for six months now religiously my poops
still sink yeah and i said this last
time too
okay
inside our guts right
this is important to know
inside our guts
we have
lots of debris stuck to the inside of
our guts first of all karen
when someone says they've been doing mm
for six months i don't know what that
means it could be dabbling and no
offense i i'm honored you're doing it
i'm happy you're doing it for your
health but karen
is it dabbling
are you doing the mono cleanse for six
months
are you doing the 369 advance for six
months are you doing the heavy metal
detox movie and the 369 are you doing 32
ounces of celery juice heavy metal detox
lui 369
are you doing the are you doing the
morning cleanse are you doing the heavy
metal detox cleanse
so
are you doing it in supplementation are
you doing anything else so when someone
says i'm doing mm it might be a little
bit of celery juice and then you're
doing a couple of recipes or it could be
a little less or a little more and if
your poop still sinks
you might have a lot more healing to do
you might need to do more you know tools
i'm not saying everybody needs to do mm
and then have a poop that actually
floats midway or to the top i'm saying
it's going to happen to you if you clean
up long enough you'll see it mid-float
and it will be fiber it will be pulp it
will be pectin and any fat in any
protein in that stool is gone you will
have a stool that if it was analyzed by
a functional medicine doctor they
wouldn't find fat or protein in it and
they would be confused
they'd be like this stool
is all cucumber and
lemon and banana
and potato and all these other things
where it's all
fiber
pulp pectin
right
it's all of that
and any protein and fat in your diet
gets absorbed quickly so then all of a
sudden your liver gets stronger and
stronger and stronger and your your your
stomach breaks down everything and it
gets stronger that's what happens when
people bring back their guts they're
doing the mono cleanse for a long time
and they bring back their guts it gets
so strong there's no protein and fat in
their stool anymore even if they eat
avocado that means if that person eats
an avocado the poop still won't sink if
the person has a little bit of nuts the
poop won't the poop won't sink and i'll
tell you why they got their their guts
so sharp and so strong in their
hydrochlor chloric acid hcl was so
strong breaking down those proteins in
their liver broke everything down in
their pancreas
right
sent out a lot of digestive enzymes and
all of that was so keen and so
strong
that their poops took mid flight in the
toilet they took mid-flight they
actually started surfacing a little bit
and they were clean and they were filled
with fiber and pulp and all the fat and
all that even an avocado if you ate an
avocado was absorbed and utilized and
broken down and it wasn't still in the
intestinal tract so here's what happens
people walk around with all this in
their intestinal tract that peanut
butter can stand there for years that
chicken can stay in there for years that
egg can stay in the intestinal tract on
the walls bits and pieces for years it
can stay in the liver all of this can
stay in the liver the peanut butter the
almond butter can stain the liver for
years and it builds up and it builds up
and it builds up and it rots and it
builds up
and when it does
right
your system breaks down a little bit you
don't have that strength of the hcl in
the bio and then what happens is every
poop just sinks every poop sinks every
poop sinks and they sink
but man you do like 369 advanced and
you're all raw long enough that you
clean up all that debris and you do the
mono cleanse and you're all clean long
enough and you're doing that and you
take all the overt fats out and you
build up your liver and you build up
your hcl man you're gonna be cleaning
things up so much that when you drop a
little avocado inside your stomach did
you hear this check this out did you
guys hear this
all the time it happens there's always
somebody in the medical meeting
community
that does the mono cleanse for a year
or two to heal everything they heal
everything and then they say i'm sick of
eating just these these foods i'm sick
of this i'm going to go and have avocado
and i'm going to go and have beans and
i'm going to go and have rice and i'm
going to go to have all these things i
want to have chicken and i'm going to go
and have all that and i feel great and
my system's working great because all
that they did by building themselves up
and strengthening their their liver and
their stomach
and when you take it to that point you
end up going to bathroom you'll just see
fiber come up because all the protein
and all the fat will be gone and what's
happening is everybody on their nut
butter is fine everybody on their eggs
whatever they want to be on chicken nut
butters eggs
whatever it is that they're doing it
doesn't get fully broken down it becomes
a dead weight and it's in the stool
whether your functional medicine doctor
knows or anybody else it becomes heavy
and it sits in the stool and it goes to
the bottom toilet and that's fine you
can still be healthy even though things
are breaking down like your liver is
weakening your hcl is weakening things
are going wrong you can still be a
fairly healthy person
you can be on a medical medium diet
healing yourself and your poops don't
take mid-flight yet because you're not
there yet but it's okay you're getting
healthier getting rid of symptoms you're
getting stronger your poop still sinks
but still
right bruce says nice informative
floater is the most healthy it could be
mid floaters
that's the one when they're floating mid
in in the middle of the water in the
toilet
that's when it's healthy
right i showed you guys
okay
there's no fat in here
cucumbers and celery is floating there's
no air in there by the way
there's the lemon it's liquid right pulp
fiber pectin it's floating banana
floating right
oh that's floating there's no fat in any
of those they're all floating
here's the
chocolate and the cacao nibs
all sunk to the bottom right all sunk to
the bottom
here's the nut butters and peanut butter
almond butter i could put peanut butter
in there right
all
sunk to the bottom that's how it works
that's how it works there's lots of fat
in that there's lots of fat in the
peanut butter okay so all this is
important to know right
there's lots of fat in that peanut
butter so i'm going to go in here and
just get a big hunk of peanut butter out
everybody knows how fatty peanut butter
is they all know this right
okay
so the peanut butter just sunk like lead
and here's what happens you have a
peanut butter jelly sandwich of course
your poop's gonna sink
your digestive system's not gonna be
that strong your bile is not working
that great your liver is not working
that great and your peanut butter is
going to stick to the bottom of the
toilet you're going to see a streak in
the bottom of the toilet that's going to
be the peanut butter streak
someone has a peanut butter jelly
sandwich guess what they're going to
have a streak at the bottom of the
toilet that's how it works
brandy says i've been egg free dairy
free and celery juicing
healing soups heavy metal detox smoothie
lemon water daily no fats until after 12
i could feel the changes no bloating
less inflammation better skin warts gone
boil's gone incredible
you guys had the books yet this is
cleanse the heel check it out
right amazon.com us
51 off medical textbook right get free
the library
someone said in youtube they said you
know what i like the fact that the guy
you know
the guy who says go to the library and
get the book for free no one does that i
saw that on youtube that comment i was
like hey that that guy's cool thanks man
i've always said it go to the library i
don't care if everybody goes to the
library just get it for free then it
doesn't matter to me because here's the
problem
sure
right
everybody has to make a living and
survive right
all of that okay
but i'd rather have you healing getting
the information somehow for free that's
why we do so much for free for free i'd
rather have that i'd rather know that
you're healing i mean in the end that's
what matters i mean
yeah
so
we're live right now
i think we're still live
so you guys all right let's get into
this a little bit more now let's figure
this out
so
we're talking about building up the
digest and strengthening it and that's
what we do that's what medical medium
information does that's what the celery
juice does that's with all the
monoplanes that's what everything else
i'm gonna go you guys we're gonna go to
ig we have a tech problem right now i'm
excited let's go to ig let's do some
cool stuff we're gonna have some fun tic
tac i'll see you there telegram i'll see
you there all you guys i'll see you
there and i can't wait