an incredible Moment In Time
nearly a hundred thousand people
have signed up to the collecting Stone's
meditation Journey
there are tens of thousands of people
around the world right now
that are picking their stones in nature
or should I say their Stones could be
choosing them
what an incredible experience
when you're looking for your stones
which was yesterday
hopefully everybody found their stones
or their stones found them when you're
looking for this when you're looking for
these stones
keep in mind a connection is already
forming in that very moment
as you're even searching as your eyes
are looking on the ground
they're looking on that pathway you're
walking
they're looking
on the side of that Beach
your eyes are looking on that trail in
the woods
your eyes are looking in the parking lot
where you just parked your car
your eyes are looking in the yard
the backyard the front yard
and that intention is there
that intention
powerful meditative State intention
one of the most powerful of all
you're sending a signal
you're sending a frequency
to
these objects
that have been here for thousands upon
thousands upon thousands and millions of
years
how is it possible
that those stones have been here for so
long
and we haven't been here right now in
our physical bodies for so long
and that connection is made
is it possible those stones were waiting
millions of years
hundreds of thousands of years for that
connection to be made
for this very moment in time
it's more than possible
I think when you
walk along
and you're looking and searching for
your stones
like you already have
keep in mind
that that connection grows instantly
once you settle
on those three stones
immediately a connection develops
right there
and it builds from there and gets
stronger by the minute
Stronger by the seconds
Stronger by the hours
already after you've chosen your stones
hours later a connection is developing
a frequency
is being
transferred back and forth
from you to the stones and from the
stones to you and from you to the stones
and the stones to you
we're day two of the collecting Stones
meditation journey I am
incredibly proud of everybody
anybody who hasn't signed up make sure
you sign up link is in the profile link
is in the description and I can promise
you this
if it hasn't already happened starting
yesterday for you this is going to be
the most profound experience
in meditations you have ever had
and I can promise you this
by the seventh day
your emotional state
your soul state will be changing forever
this is going to be the most profound
emotional experiences in your life
I know that's a lot to say
but as we get to the seventh day
you're truly going to feel it and You're
Gonna Know It
deep deep healing is going to happen in
inside of you
because
what we carry
is baggage
and we can't let it go and we don't know
how to let it go
we carry it with us
for days
for months for years
for a lifetime
Old Wounds old hurt
the information from these wounds and
hurts stored up in our cells
we've stuffed it down deep inside
whether it's purposely or not on purpose
it just happened
and it sits there and it percolates and
it festers and it hinders us
as we're moving through our life
and with the collecting Stones
meditation Journey what it does
is it starts to unpack it
but unpack it in a way that you don't
have to relive it
because the stones help you
and prevent you from having to relive
what that hurt was
a long time ago or even recently
the Stone's job is to actually absorb
and take in
those old experiences that became
baggage
it doesn't mean you're going to forget
everything from the past that wasn't
good or not that's not what this is
Instead This opens up new space so new
experiences can find a home
so many people are struggling internally
without even realizing it because Old
Wounds are taking up so much space
inside of them
that it makes it hard to take in
something special
do you know anyone that that's happened
to where something good is happening but
it's hard to see it because you're numb
or it's hard to feel it or experience it
because you're numb
do you know anyone who has gone through
that or experienced that
where something good is happening a
moment's good but they can't really feel
it and they can't really see it
they feel numb or disconnected and lost
a lot of times for people that means
that there's so much baggage stored up
and hurt stored up that it's taking up
so much space inside the soul
inside our being
that it's not allowing for room for new
references and new experiences to settle
in and make a home
and create an inner Joy over time
and sustain and inner Joy
instead when people have good things
happen to them they say they're grateful
but it may not feel like it sticks or
holds it fades away quick and dissipates
quick
and so with collecting Stone's Journey
what this meditation Journey does is it
clears the space it opens up
a channel inside your being
it moves out the garbage it transfers
that garbage that hurt those injuries
those old stifled emotions they're
stored down deep it transfer them out of
you and into the stones
what this does is it opens up
more you inside
because
you should never be defined by your hurt
and your experiences that were really
hardships difficult things that might
have happened whether it's with
relationships or
any kind of struggle throughout your
life
any kind of abuse or any kind of
difficult times whatever it may be
even having chronic illness and having
symptoms and conditions that have been
hard on you
throughout your life that played a role
in having hard situations because you
were struggling emotionally you were
struggling physically
and what happens is that when we have
all that built up inside of us and it's
stored inside of us it's hard to
actually
have something even if it resonates out
there something to really stick
it's hard for it to actually stick
meaning you can have a good experience
but you can then get numb to it and then
you feel like you're taking it for
granted but you're not taking it for
granted you just can't really feel it so
much you thought it was as good as you
thought it was but in the end you're
like I don't know anymore and you're
confused because there's no room there's
not enough room left inside of oneself
kind of like when someone goes through a
really difficult relationship and
they're not ready to get into another
relationship again because they just
don't have it in them they're just
burned out
what happens is all that hurt stays in
there and it percolates and it festers
and we need to get rid of that without
having to relive it or experience it
over and over again we need to get rid
of it we need it to leave us
so that the channel is clear
Clarity occurs and the channel is clear
within us
we need to have the ability to start
fresh wherever we can even on the
smallest levels and the collecting Stone
meditation Journey allows for that
it opens up the door it opens up the
gate
so that when you experience something
good even on the smallest level even on
the smallest level just walking down a
trail and choosing your stones that
experience you'll never forget again
you'll never forget for the rest of your
life that's how powerful this is
this isn't just about collecting a few
stones and having some fun
this is way bigger than that and more
powerful than that the reason why I've
been saying all this time is that you're
never going to forget what's going to
happen and you're never going to forget
this journey is because that's true
you're not
because
what should shouldn't reside inside of
us any more
starts to leave
and so by the seventh day when we're
ready
and we take our stones
and we're gonna get our stones
to the place they need to be
it's going to be an incredible
experience and by the hour right now
there's going to be a bond between you
and your stones that gets stronger and
stronger and stronger because those
stones that are in your possession
are absorbing right now they're
absorbing
pain and suffering
they're absorbing old hurt from the past
or even recently
they're absorbing experiences
that led to emotional pain
you still had the experience but they're
absorbing
a lot of the wounds that were left
from that experience and then
something opens up
and opens up
and it's like a fresh start
and we get clear
and we start to heal easier emotionally
mentally spiritually
and we get stronger and stronger
in every way possible
you're going to see as each day goes on
how powerful this really is
and how profound this really is
and the tens of thousands of people and
this isn't even counting the tens of
thousands that are also doing it that
aren't even signed up now they're doing
it because a family member is doing it
they're doing it because a friend is
doing it and they're not signed up but
they're doing it as well
estimated right now probably 250
000 individuals
are doing the collecting Stones
meditation Journey right now with all of
us
share your experience with the
collecting Stones meditation Journey
I would love to share those experiences
with the community
as your ex as you're experiencing it
as you go through all seven days through
these exercises
share your real or your posts in your
stories and tag medical medium and
hashtag medical medium at the same time
in your stories so that I can see it
because I can't see it if it's just a
post or real
because IG doesn't allow us to see it if
it's a poster real it has to be
tagged in your story
and hashtagged in your story too
if you signed up
Courtney says the download is everything
if you signed up there's a downloadable
PDF
do not miss out so there's downloadable
PDFs do not miss out on those make sure
you're signed up
so that you can get that information
Fly High on YouTube says I absolutely
love this journey I Feel So Close
emotionally with my Stones I feel their
energy it's so purifying and cleansing
prepare for a lot of tears to happen in
the seven day Journey
if they haven't happened yet they're
going to happen in the end and if they
don't happen in the end you're still
going to feel it emotionally
and there's great reason for it
on IG
love this meditation by the way what are
you drinking oh thank you for reminding
me because I actually would like a sip
right now if you don't mind
um
so good
what am I drinking
hmm
it's good it's good
Alexandra Sofia says I had massive
emotional changes by evening of day one
it's mind-blowing explanation points wow
I just kissed my rocks in profound
gratitude you did that too I have just
my rocks too so I have done that as well
so it's good to know I'm not the only
one that did that
just going to read a little bit from
this book right here which has the
collecting stones
meditation journey in it so here it is
the medical medium book do you have a
copy of this
so keep in mind the PDF has additional
information it's not just what's in here
if you signed up there's additional
information
there's a question right here just
turning in have no idea how this was on
my phone playing live bless me
oh incredible I'm so glad that you're
here Tasha
hey Anthony can we choose more than
three stones if we have a lot of
emotional struggles we want to let go of
say like six stones or is three ideal
great question three is ideal
three is important we have to have three
we have to focus on three at a time
because
if it's more than three our Focus
becomes scattered
our Focus
we lose detail we lose connection
three is the number chosen by Spirit of
compassion originally with the
collecting Stone's meditation Journey
going back forever now since I've
learned it from SOC
and although it may feel like you need
four because there's so many different
emotional names or tags or experiences
that you want to name
your stones or hardships or losses
there's so many different things that
you want to name your stones and that's
okay because these are the three stones
you choose for this
meditation journey and then we do
another one all together
we'll do another one I think we should
probably do a few of these
so we'll just prepare for a whole
another one because the reason why is
because there's going to be more names
you want in those on those stones
Erica Malik says are we able to rename
our Stones today
and start a day later yes you are
I'm just reading some comments you guys
I'm so glad we're here right now
um if you just got here listen to the
beginning of this video we're live right
now
foreign
medical medium collecting Stones
meditation Journey
a profound experience that
is going to be life-changing when we
hear the term life-changing
and
we
use that a lot for a lot of different
things
keep in mind
when it comes to this
meditation it's unlike any other
meditation out there
it's unlike
any other spiritual exercise
you'll feel it instantly and you're
going to feel it for the through these
next seven days you should have already
received your day two video in your
email address it's coming from Hay House
not MediCal medium
keep in mind check your promotions and
spam and you can search Hay House in
your emails to find them
so that's important to know I think a
lot of people are looking for the
medical medium emails regarding the
collecting Stone's meditation Journey
but really we have to
be looking for the Hay House emails
for collecting Stone's meditation
Journey so that's important I think I'm
worried a few people will be like where
are they
if you still need help there is a link
in the medical medium profile and
description if you need help so there's
a help link
in
the medical medium
description
Lila Collins says I love Anthony's
energy he's really genuine I'm honored
thank you for being here truly you can
still sign up the link
in the profile and description and start
now
you can still sign up
and it's free
so important
it's free
when you want to cleanse yourself of
challenging emotions
take a walk in nature and keep your eye
out for small stones
that can call to you now that leads me
to this part here
you can choose the size of the stone you
want
you can have them really small
you can have them a little bigger
you can have them bigger than this you
can have one big one one small one one
small one is whatever
calls to you it's whatever resonates
you can have tiny stones
really small ones
size of beans if you want
Pebbles
and then you can have them bigger they
could be
much bigger
and lately I've been seeing on social
some people have some pretty big Stones
I'm like well that's a really big one
educating myself says can disease be
released this way
the emotional wounds from illnesses can
because that's a big
big thing right there because what
happens is we get beaten down when we're
sick with chronic illness
we get beaten down long term if we've
been through a lot and have gone a long
distance with our chronic sickness and
symptoms and conditions
and there's so much hurt that gets
stored up just think about and you would
know many of you who have OCD
think about how much hurt occurs with
family members when you have OCD with
friends in relationships
same thing with anxiety think about how
much hurt has occurred in your life
because you've had so many panic attacks
and how that hurt has transpired into a
lot of emotional hurt through lit
relationships and friends and family and
and just
through life
so anyone with a symptom or condition
comes with also hurt
especially if it's been months and
months and it's taken a long time to
heal because you've been searching and
searching and going to so many different
practitioners and doctors and looking
for answers and haven't found them the
hurt that goes along the way is very
difficult just think about when someone
they look fine from the outside but
they're not fine on the inside and how
people including practitioners or
doctors will say to them well you look
good or friends and family will be like
you look good
I know we can't see the
Tremor you have internally and that
sickness you feel and the fatigue you
feel and how heavy your arms are and how
you just don't have the energy to walk
good we can't really see that but right
now you look really good and so many
people
I think just we just lost um one thing
there so many people
suffer emotionally they suffer mentally
from so much hurt from being chronically
ill
and then when we have all that baggage
stored up in us and everything stored up
so deeply
and it's kind of bogging us down
mentally and emotionally it doesn't help
when we're trying to heal
so the collecting Stone's meditation
journey is about clearing out that space
and I know so many people who have
struggled because they were sick so long
and they were hurt emotionally because
of it they were misunderstood
that's a huge one right there so many
people who have been chronically ill
have been misunderstood
and that misunderstanding that occurs
when you're sick and you're searching
for help can feel very painful and it
becomes a wound and a pattern that gets
internalized
and collecting Stone's meditation
journey is about taking that and
removing that and clearing that out
getting a fresh start
take a walk in nature and keep your eye
out for small stones that call to you
because there is a connection happening
the minute you make that intention that
intention is clear I'm going to do this
meditation Journey
I'm going to collect my stones
the minute that frequency is sent out
right there it's sent out
there are stones
that are there to receive it
so you're three stones
are sitting somewhere in the sand in the
dirt on the trail on the grass on the
ground
on the side of a parking lot wherever
they are
your three stones
are out there
and they're picking up on your
intentions that I am searching for you
I'm looking for you because
because I need help
and IG what does it mean when a stone
falls down to the floor
so you drop the stone
one thing is what was that Stone named
so that's important to know right there
did you already name your stones at that
point before you dropped a stone on the
floor I dropped the stone on the floor
before starting this live
it went boink on the ground and on the
floor and it rolled way over there
it has meaning
it does
and so whatever you named your stones
and the stone that dropped is the stone
trying to run away from you
is the
emotion or the wound
that is getting absorbed in that stone
is it trying to get away from you so you
can't rid it
is it about loyalty to all three stones
is it a test
so that you leave out a third Stone you
leave out one of those stones because it
fell and it went somewhere and they're
just holding now two of them
you can ask yourself a lot of questions
involving that
Maggie over there at IG says I slept
with my Stones next to me on my bed they
were on my bed with me laugh out loud
my stones are very dear to me right now
in this collecting Stone's meditation
Journey
and I do the same thing
Anthony
over there in IG hey Anthony can I name
the stones after my ill organs yes you
can
because a lot of times when we know we
have an ill organ because we've been
diagnosed with an ill organ
[Music]
an emotional storm hits us
like how can that happen with my liver
how can that happen with my spleen how
is this happening with my thyroid how is
this happening with my heart how's this
happening with my kidney and then we we
get we get PTSD from it we battle and we
struggle on our sickness and our
struggle with our sickness and we battle
with it and it takes up space and it
takes up space
and so the collecting Stones meditation
journey is about the stones absorbing
that pain
and those wounds
and that information and clearing the
way
for when the time comes and we need to
let go and we need to release
Victoria says I am here where I grew up
in the Midwest
thousand miles from my home of 45 years
out east
today I felt guided to get three new
rocks at this site of our house
at our house fire in 1967
I began to cry the moment I stepped out
of the car onto the Gravel Road
I knew it was deep healing more to share
this is good for now yes I found Stones
there Victoria thank you
over there on Facebook thank you for
being here thank you for being in the
collective the collecting Stones
meditation Journey which is
unbelievable
Collective of people right now tens of
thousands
educating myself says his faith needed
for this exercise no it is not
faith is not needed for this exercise of
course you can have faith in this
exercise you can use Faith you can
draw from Faith but faith is not needed
in this exercise
it's that powerful
that connection is there whether we have
faith or not that connection is there
whether we like it or not once we start
it that connection is there
and the connection between those stones
and you
is there
it's not breakable
powerful stones are made out of minerals
they're all minerals everything is
minerals
every
single piece of vegetation every tree
every Rock
all the water on this planet every
single living species is made out of
minerals
it's all minerals and minerals
communicate with minerals
Marie I named my Stones low confidence
loss of purpose and depression
powerful
that's powerful
truly
really is
singing sweetly says not this meditation
but after the light blasts I stopped
overeating
it's incredible I'm hearing every day
profound profound changes in people's
lives after the light blast
and it and it keeps on going it keeps on
going for people even months later
and things surface it's it's incredible
okay
name each Stone by the label of whatever
you're harboring that you'd like to
leave you that you would like to leave
you very important to name each Stone by
the label of whatever you're harboring
that you would like to leave you
for example you might name the Stone's
guilt fear and anger or hate or shame or
disappointment or frustration sorrow or
despair
naming the stones is an experience all
in its own
that right there how many of you
found that to be
an amazing or intense experience
naming your Stones I wanted to ask you
guys
what happened when you were naming your
stones
okay so if you guys did day one already
where's day one video I need to catch up
Elaine says videos are only there for 24
hours
so but but don't stop with the rest of
it so make sure though that you get the
video for day two day three day four day
five day six day seven don't miss out on
those
but the videos are accessible for 24
hours
carry these stones with you wherever you
go
how many of you guys are carrying them
wherever you go you're taking them in
the car you're taking them with you
are they on your desk are they on your
table are they with you everywhere
are you sleeping with them at night
get familiar with your Stones as well
take a look at them look at them closely
understand what you're seeing get that
connection
intuitive yoga says over there at IG I
was surprised by what came up I was also
surprised when I named my biggest Stone
grief
as that is the biggest emotion I carry
oh
if I get quiet sometimes it's just I get
emotional too because knowing that
you're carrying that much grief knowing
that that's residing inside of you and
you're struggling with it and it could
be for a long time it's heartbreaking
and
that's the thing about Spirit of
compassion
creating
a meditative a meta a meditation to this
extent which helps so much I'm so
excited about you being here
Sue over there in IG says yes naming
them was incredible because it validated
the feelings and pain
that's
that's amazing because so many people
are going to have a
similar or different experience or some
type of similarity with experience when
they name their stones
when you name your stone
something happens
with their soul
it instantly throws out like a pathway
to the stone
so when you name your stone
instantly a pathway
gets delivered right to the stone
like a connection
a wire
a thread
Barbara says over there on Facebook I
named one of my Stones unloved
but it's a mixture of emotions like I
was unseen unheard unvalidated
unimportant
so I just summed it up with feeling
unloved
but now I think I should just pick one
like unseen for example and leave the
other specific feelings for the next
round of seven days question mark yes
the answer yes Save the others from the
next round of seven days because this
isn't going to be the only one we're
doing because so much of Us carry so
much and have been through so much
and the three names you're choosing this
time will be different than the three
names you choose next time unless you
choose to choose the same names again
which you're of course welcome to do
but chances are you'll be choosing some
different names
as well
carry these stones with you wherever you
go keep them in your pocket so keep them
in your pocket
if you can you don't have pockets try to
keep them with you wherever you go
do not
get worried or scared if you lose one
if you lose one
before the seven days
that's okay
Ambrose says on IG habits Financial
worry judgmental or mine
powerful really powerful
keep them in your pocket if you'd like
or even in your hands
get to know each of your three stones so
get to know your three stones
and get to know the sound of them too
yours are going to sound different
everybody's stones are going to sound
different they're going to have their
own unique frequency and only unique
sound when they get
join together everybody stones are going
to sound different
there's not one stone that's going to
sound the same as somebody else's Stone
especially as the stones are absorbing
that grief
the feeling of being unloved
that feeling of fear shame guilt
Trust
all of it as
it your stones are absorbing all of that
coming from you the sounds will even
change
but no stones are going to sound the
same and no stones are going to be
the same sound if you just got on here
this is open to the public right here of
course this is alive we're doing
so you might come on here and be like
whoa let me check out a w
and see what he's up to this is the
collecting Stones meditation Journey
talk
and we're on day two of the collecting
Stones meditation Journey link is in
description link is in the profile just
so everybody knows
Julie Tuesday over there on YouTube says
I named my Stones trauma loss and pet
deaths
I understand
get to know each of your three stones
look at them when you get an opportunity
and I realize we have to live our life
and you can't just stare at them all day
long you can't just stare at your Stones
every single minute
keep that in mind
that's reasonable
but
look at your Stones when you can
if you're eating or if you're doing
something whatever it is
look at your Stones when you can
carry them with you so you know they're
there so if you don't look at them and
you don't see them carry them with you
so that you know they're there
knowing they're there is really good
because it's powerful because it's
actually
a messaging that occurs it's a
connection that stays there it stays
there anyway but
it only gets stronger when you're like
oh yeah that's right my stones are here
with me my stones are in my pocket my
stones are in my purse my stones are in
my bag
look at them when you can and when you
can get an opportunity study the
surfaces of your Stones you want to know
what book I'm in right here collecting
Stones meditation is in this book
study the surfaces they're Terrain
and so I'm sure you guys are doing that
already getting to know your stones
so that's something you might want to do
have you washed and cleaned your Stones
let's go into that a little bit
I noticed that I saw on social a lot of
people rinsing off their stones
it's a profound experience all on its
own
when I washed my stones
and moved them around my hand like I
showed you in yesterday's video
a feeling was just coming over me like
coursing through my veins
and washing them is this like baptizing
moment it's this cleansing moment
it's this anointment moment
it's a moment of caring it's a moment of
connection occurring so when you're
washing your three stones
and you said she hasn't cried today
which is unusual
that's interesting
definitely
so I think when
that part when we unearth our stones
and there's still some sand and a little
bit of dirt
and some organic matter attached to it
and we wash and clean our Stones there's
like I'm taking care of you
I'm looking out for you I want to see
what you look like I want to clean you
up it's a profound experience all on its
own
Chelsea Williams says I was very
emotional naming my stones and
surprisingly was guided to name them
differently than what I thought I would
that's interesting too
Jesus says on IG this is so cool so
original and beautiful thank you aw and
SOC
well
it's socs
I'm here as a messenger to make sure
I can help you guys
heart scent said I found my stones on IG
you found them
yes it's very possible that you'll name
your stone something different than you
weren't expecting that you weren't
thinking you would name them and that
can happen
that can happen
getting familiar with your Stones
cleaning your stones
washing your Stones a huge part of
making that connection occur
keep in mind
that your stones are there to absorb
and when you're cleaning them up and
you're
washing them
you're getting rid of debris
so that you and your Stones can have
even a closer connection
and there isn't
all the sand and dirt that also has
minerals blanketing over the stones
that's why it's important to actually
give them a rinse give them a wash and a
cleaning
Tamara says my Stones I think are in my
fanny pouch on me like a kangaroo
and IG is inig says I put the opposite
feeling for example
to
confusion I name it clarity
okay well if that speaks to you and
that's what you feel like doing
of course you can name your Stones what
you would like to name your stones
you can
but you don't want to absorb your
clarity
into the stones
you want to keep your clarity
but you do want to absorb
confusion into the stone
because remember this
you want
what's going on
your struggle to be something that
leaves opens a channel escapes so that
space is opened up but of course you can
name your Stones anything you can name
your Stones anything you'd like
and that's okay because your stones are
working for you
and that's okay
so if you name your stone something like
even happiness it doesn't mean your
stones are going to absorb and take
happiness away
but it
but your stones will be able to work
with you on that
that means your stones will be like well
what that person needs is even more
happiness
Agostino says if someone has a difficult
time connecting with the stones will it
still work yes
keep doing the daily exercises if you
don't do the daily exercises and you
don't want to participate
and that doesn't help Julie Tuesday 144
I had trouble naming my Stones I kept
changing their names then I finally
talked to them and after a few
interventions the names were there
trauma loss and pet deaths
I understand
this
is the second day
I am
thoroughly excited about each day after
today today and tomorrow and the next
day all the way to the seven day
on the seventh day
is going to be unlike anything
anybody has ever experienced
I know that's a tall order
but this is
not the normal meditation out there
it's not the normal meditation we do we
sit down and we try to like clear our
thoughts when we go into nature and we
sit in nature this
is profound in its own way
powerful in its own way
and so I'm preparing you guys
because if you haven't already felt
something occurring you're going to feel
it
soon if you haven't already
just choosing the stones
is like a religious experience all on
its own
it's like the spiritual experience all
on its own
and you guys already know because you've
already done it
Iona says my stones are very comforting
they helped me through food cravings and
mood swings
amazing
truly
so I just wanted to tell you guys that I
am
doing this with you we're doing it all
together
very excited
very very excited about
your path your journey
and I'm looking forward to each minute
and each hour and each day with you
share your experience with the
collecting Stones meditation journey I
would love to share with the community
your experience as you go through the
seven days
and all through the exercises I want to
share those experiences with the
exercises and what you're doing but
remember share your real or post in your
stories you have to share your real or
your post in your stories and tag at
Medical medium and hashtag medical
medium or I can't see it if you don't so
share your real and your story
in there that's what I would do
if you can if you can
um I think that
even Dr Nesbitt
is participating in the Three Stones
just so everybody knows
so
Dr Nesbitt
Dr Nesbit always seems to
those are mine
yeah where is yours
Dr yes bit scrabbing his stones
he's got this Stone here what is that
stone
well I don't know if you
let me grab this Stone here
Dr Nesbit Stone
if if you don't know Dr Nesbitt
um Dr Nesbitt is a board-certified
psychiatrist and a board-certified
surgeon but if you don't know who Dr
Nesbitt is
you might not have been keeping up then
in the last three years Dr Nesbit
surfaced I think about three years ago
he decided he wanted to be
public
you forgot this one here
so Dr Nesbitt has his three zones right
here
Dr Nesbit struggling with a few things
so let's just find out
I just didn't want to tell everybody
Dr Nesbitt named one stone alcohol
so Dr Nesbitt says he drinks a lot of
alcohol after surgery every single day
that's the that's alcohol Dr Nesbitt
said that's the alcohol Stone right
there
okay Dr Elizabeth what's that stone
right there
so Dr Nesbitt what did you name this one
Dr Nesbitt is naming this one cigars I
don't know if that's a good idea Dr
Nesbitt Dr Nesbitt named this Stone
cigar
Dr Nesbit has a cigar with his drink
every single night Dr Nesbitt chickens
chicken doctors usually have different
they do things differently than like you
know humans do
you're offended Dr nesbitt's actually
offended now Dr Nesbit calm down
calm down you're better than humans
you are better than humans
doctor is it Dr nesit said damn right
um
chicken doctors are better than humans
Dr Nesbitt what's this one called
Dr navvit says
oh dear
okay I don't know if I should say
anything
Dr nesb what's Dr Nesbitt said that
stone is called gambling
so
Dr Nesbitt
gambling
alcohol and cigars
um
yeah anyway
Darkness but thank you for coming on
today
um by the way if you haven't joined the
collecting Stones meditation Journey
please do please sign up if you can
link is in description link is in the
profile it's free just want everybody
still to know that
yes fruit says on IG is it okay not to
feel a connection while picking my
Stones yes it's okay connection is still
made
the connection is still made and there's
a connection there but it's okay if you
don't feel it yet
just follow the exercises each day very
important Miss dear says what is in your
mug Anthony what are you drinking
well didn't want to say anything but me
and Dr Nesbitt Dr Nesbitt slipped a
little something into
Dr Nesbitt has a flask
he calls it bitters or something I don't
know what he calls it but poof
smells like straight gasoline
and um
Dr Nesbitt he spiked my tea there
and I'm just kidding it's hibiscus tea
if anybody wants to know
my three
whoa Sandra says my three stones
seem to be something and then the
comment went up so sorry that's what oh
my three stones seem to fit like making
one stone only that's really interesting
how is that even possible but that's the
whole point it is possible
it's incredible okay
you guys
I'll see you tomorrow for day three make
sure you actually download the video
that you have that video you watch it
are you make sure you watch the PDF
or you read the PDF make sure
all of it
make sure you fill it out actually okay
you guys
I will see you