we're talking about the best propolis
there is out there on the market we're
talking about total immune we're talking
about cat's claw right there and we're
talking about the immune system and what
happens emotionally when our trust
breaks when somebody betrays us when
we're struggling emotionally when
someone misunderstands us when we feel
all bottled up we can't let it out when
we feel like things are hopeless because
we're being attacked or something when
something doesn't go right or or you
just like a break up in a relationship a
break up in a friendship something like
that happens or huge misunderstanding
how it affects the immune system and
what goes on with that and I'm talking
about how critical it is to have things
to be on the defensive yes for your
immune system having your immune system
being supported on the defensive of
what's happening out there like what
we're bombarded with every single day so
check this out right you guys check this
out okay
let's just say this is your bloodstream
right here okay that's your bloodstream
right there and then you got your immune
cells you got your immune cells in here
that's your immune system inside your
bloodstream okay there's your immune
system right there inside the
bloodstream all right there we go you
get some bad news maybe you're
betrayed maybe a relationship maybe
somebody cheated on you you maybe a
friend cheated on you maybe something
happened whatever it may happened in
your life right
something first thing that happens is
your
adrenals they release adrenaline lots of
adrenaline because your brain received
information do you see this your brain
received information I was
betrayed my trust is
broken something happened somebody let
me down there a
misunderstanding and as it comes into
the brain like we're getting that
information and it's Computing inside
the brain your brain sending signals to
your adrenals right here you see this
boop boop right there see that your
brain is sending signals to your
adrenals if you guys just came on here
we're going to be talking about propolis
talking about total immune talking about
cats claw and why we're talking about
that we're going to be on the defensive
with our immune system protecting us CR
that we have immune system protectors we
get bad news we receive that bad news in
the brain obviously we hear it with our
ears those nerves go straight to the
brain the information gets there and
then the brain sends information to your
adrenals it sends information now to
your adrenals your adrenals then explode
so they release Lots of adrenaline
because it's fight or flight what just
happened what was just cancelled what
went wrong wait a minute you just broke
my trust where's your loyalty you're not
loyal what the heck happened why would
you do this to me why are we breaking up
whatever it is your adrenals are now
releasing okay and maybe it's a long
ride like a divorce or something like
that where it's just constant it's like
one thing happening here then now 3 days
go by everything's leveling out then one
thing happens here would if or if it's
maybe mental abuse or some kind of abuse
on a person those adrenals are
constantly releasing adrenaline so let's
get into it a little bit here we go
that's your bloodstream right
there okay now here comes the
adrenaline that's your
bloodstream these are immune cells right
here you see that you guys these are
immune cells your immune system inside
your bloodstream really important to no
here comes the adrenaline now it's
rushing into your bloodstream you've
been betrayed broken
trust something happened someone would
that was supposed to be loyal is not
loyal you care about somebody they don't
care about you anymore it seems now the
adrenaline is rushing in right here okay
immune cells do not like
adrenaline immune
cells do not like adrenaline adrenaline
when we're upset when we've been
betrayed when there's a trust issue
adrenaline is like poison to the immune
system and then we get that adrenaline
Spike did you ever have the shakes
because of adrenaline happy Saturday to
you too do you ever have the shakes
where right where you're shaking you got
bad news and you're shaking I see that
happen out there all the time with
people and it could be anything
that they're experiencing well that's
adrenaline now yes you have experienced
that yes you too okay that's adrenaline
rushing into the
bloodstream rushing into the organs
social media Terra social media bullying
totally right and it's adrenaline
rushing in and that's why we're going to
protect our immune cells that's what
this is about and that's why you see
that propolis there that's why you see
that cats claw there so as that add
adrenaline is rushing into the
bloodstream right here and I'm going to
make another bloodstream over here too
here's another
bloodstream right there you see guys all
right is that adrenaline is rushing in
here it is it's scorching the immune
cells so our immune system gets beaten
down by it it scorches the immune cells
okay it's a little immune cell right
there you guys can see it and adrenaline
tends to Scorch it we get bad news we
receive it right here in the
brain right information goes from the
brain into the brain stem out the nerves
out the cranial nerves heads out to the
adrenals the adrenals get a message
saying fight ORF flight fight or flight
fight or
flight and then the adrenals are dumping
adrenaline okay
and then that adrenaline goes right in
you know how many people get the flu
they get the flu during some kind of a
strange moment a strange time where
they're under pressure they're under
some kind of stress they're emotionally
going through something and then they're
just boom down with a flu you know how
many people get
mononucleosis because of something
they've gone through and ups and downs
breakups with relationships and then
they just hit the wall and they just
they have mono right how many people
have done that and maybe you're not just
up against the emotional stuff maybe
you're just wearing yourself out maybe
because you have no choice or whatever
it is but the emotional stuff is a big
deal because it floods that adrenaline
into the system the adrenaline gets in
there and it hits the immune cells so
here's how it works as the adrenaline's
going in it's scorching weak immune
cells so weak immune cells
explode weak immune cells explode
they do they die off so as all that
adrenaline goes through during that bad
news you got immune cells dying off now
and as those immune cells are dying off
it's
leaving space for
Invaders it's leaving space for
Invaders Elena says every time I am
severely stressed I get the flu happens
to a lot of people don't think it just
happens to you on that there are so many
people that when they get that stress
when they're under that kind of
emotional turmoil whatever it is what
happens is they get the flu or they get
you know something else or they get the
c or RSV or something like that so okay
so let's make some new immune cells
right here okay we got your immune cells
this is your bloodstream right here all
right there's a reason why I'm talking
about this we can help protect immune
cells we can also put things in us that
protect us in a lot of other ways but we
can protect our immune cells our immune
system there's a way to do it so when
we're going through ups and downs where
we are protected when we're going
through ups and downs if we're dealing
with any kind of psychological abuse any
kind of mental abuse any kind of serious
gaslighting we're up against any kind of
bullies that we're up against yep
anything like that any other difficult
um struggles at all we can protect our
immune cells so they don't get scorched
to death so they don't get scorched and
die quickly so immune cells get scorched
and die quickly what happens is when you
start protecting your immune cell your
immune system and you start putting
things inside of you that protect your
immune system you make your immune cells
strong you also help to produce more
immune cells and more immune cells so
over
here what you see right here okay
is I'm just putting this green right
here
okay that's bone mirrow all
right that's some bone marrow right
there there's some bone marrow might not
even be able to see that there's some
bone marrow all right maybe you guys
can't see
that okay immune
cells many of them get produced out of
the bone marrow your bones producing
immune cells you see this there's the
immune cells being produced out of your
bone
marrow as immune cells are being scored
and dying off from adrenaline shooting
into the
bloodstream okay your bones go into
overdrive to produce new immune
cells so those immune cells eventually
get back into the bloodstream like right
here all
right what happens when we go through a
mar emotional hardships we lose sleep we
don't sleep good we're under emotional
turmoil we don't get a lot of sleep our
immune system tends to drop it loses a
lot of its strength okay that's why I
like to tell family you got to be on the
propolis every day is maintenance not
just when you catch something or you got
a cold sore okay or you got a canker
sore or something like that it's about
maintenance because you don't know when
you're going to get whacked you don't
know that's how it works when we're up
against different things and we're up
against different turmoil our emotional
struggles it comes and goes it's like a
roller coaster ride right why do you
think people say relationships are like
roller coaster rides a lot of people
have said that over the years right
where it's like you're going up and then
you're going down relationships some
relationships could be just friendships
could be like everything's going great
everything's going great and everybody's
going up great up up up they're all
going up and then they're at the top
there and all of a sudden something
plateaus and somebody says something
stupid and
then everybody's going down like
that and then they go back oh we're
making up we're making up friends
friends are making up things seem to be
okay status quo everything's okay
balance them you're going up there all
of a sudden plateauing something says
somebody says something terrible
something happens and everybody's going
to scream I hate you I hate you and
they're down here that roller coaster
ride
is really difficult on the immune system
that's why maintenance is critical Bri
says straighten out the three bottles so
I can read the product okay there we go
hopefully that helps right there there
you go you got the total immune from viy
you got the propolis from vimergy and
you got the cats Claw from vimergy and
I'm definitely going so Anna says please
explain the three bottles so let's go
into that a little bit okay first of all
you guys this is vimergy right here you
guys know work with vimergy right fully
endorse them because it's the best stuff
out there that's the cat's claw
incredible product for immune Health it
matters we got to think about this
anything wrong you see sick people out
there you see people complaining on
social every day I got this I got that I
got this wrong with me I got that I got
aches and pains I got skin disorders I
got this I got that because their immune
system is struggling if something is
physically wrong with you the immune
system system is
struggling if something's physically
wrong your immune system yes is in
trouble that's the whole point you see
doctors offices filled with people
immune system immune system immune
system see people on social I got this
problem I got that problem immune system
thyroid problems this that immune system
I got lupus I got this immune system
that's the whole point right there
py Ren says I literally cannot live my
life without cat's
claw I have people that I know that are
just they're living on cat's claw
they're living on cat's claw because of
the very same thing where they can't
they they they picked up a lot of bugs
throughout their life they've got a lot
of bugs throughout their life and
they've got a lot of exposures their
immune system was up against a lot and
they actually have to be on cat's claw
every day to to keep them stable they
had Lyme disease diagnosis they've had
this diagnosis that diagnosis they've
been to all kinds of doctors they've
seen all kinds of people and their
doctors are okay with them taking the
cat's claw the doctors are okay with
them taking the cat's claw and they got
to be on cat's claw I know people that
actually have to take the cat's claw
every day to keep that immune Health
strong to keep it nice and strong so get
back to it a little bit you guys right
here I got propolis I'll talk a a little
bit about that I got the cats claw right
here and then total immune those three
are from viy that's the brand I trust
and there's a reason because guess what
when everybody had alcohol and all their
crap they didn't people have all these
percentages of undisclosed ingredients
you don't know about in all their
supplements they won't do that it's
incredible really anyway so let's go to
you got your bloodstream here you got
your bloodstream here adrenaline rushing
in here comes the adrenaline it's
rushing in right you were given some bad
news maybe you're going through some
mental abuse maybe just anything you're
having a bad day maybe you're nervous
about something and you're worried and
then those adrenals are releasing
adrenaline the adrenaline is getting
sucked right up into the veins and
arteries and getting in there and then
it's hitting the immune cells it's
hitting the immune cells right here so
you got the adrenaline hitting the
immune cells here's an immune cell right
there and here's the adrenaline rushing
the adrenaline rushes and boom hits the
immune cell right there the immune cell
weakens because that's fight or flight
adrenaline it's corrosive it's Burns see
that right there you got an immune cell
right here here comes the adrenaline got
some bad news I trusted you you totally
screwed me over here it goes adrenaline
boom hits that immune cell the immune
cell takes a hit and it gets scorched
okay now there's a lot of immune cells
you have in your body that will sustain
they will be able to sustain the
scorching but there are a lot of immune
cells different varieties of immune
cells that don't
sustain they don't and then overdrive
your bones right here here's your bones
producing more immune cells there it
goes that's your bones right there the
femur whatever any bone your hip bone
whatever there it is okay that's your
bones we'll make more bones over here
like that those are your bones that's
your bone Miro bone mirrow okay there
you go immune
cells producing where do those immune
cells go they go right into the
bloodstream right from your bones right
into your bloodstream right in your
bones you're up against a new emotional
experience you're up against new
emotional trouble okay once again here
comes the adrenaline rushing in here it
go goes and it's hitting these immune
cells adrenaline hits these immune cells
okay and that's why maintenance is
critical you guys maintenance is
critical you can go through something
that seems mild to someone else someone
could get into a really bad car crash
they're in life support for a month they
come out they recover they're still in
bad shape nothing seems to bug them
anymore
after what they went through okay in
that car
crash and and so it takes a lot to maybe
really shake them up because they've
been there they've been in that car
crash and then you take somebody who it
seems like everything is good there's
silver spoonfed everything's happy and
then little things get to them little
things because they seeming seemingly
have a protective cushy life and then
little things like my friend just called
me an [ __ ] and they Shake they're
shaking over it they're so pissed at
this one friend meanwhile that person
who got to a car crash they're on life
support for a month that's a joke to
them that's a joke but either whether
it's small or large what happens is your
adrenaline can still rush into your
bloodstream all the same that's the
point I'm trying to make right here you
can have somebody where life is going
good I'm not going through any real
trauma but then they're getting really
upset over little things if it isn't
just right and I understand that
situation too because then that goes
into also some OCD as well and then that
could be really triggering too but
either way adrenaline can Rush In on
what someone might think is a really
small thing and somebody might think is
a really big thing right I got so Terry
young says I got my life back a few
years ago using his protocol
incredible that's that's incredible so
let's see what do you think trying to
look here all right how often should you
take these products for maintenance so
ask your doctor what's right for you
always ask your doctor your health care
provider Healthcare you know um Medical
Professional always ask you know bring
the medical medium books to your medical
professionals ask them I've said this
for years and years and years but okay
for friends and family I tell them to be
on cat's claw but ask your doctor if
that's okay for you okay but I tell them
to be on cat's claw every day for some
family members that I know okay who have
been through a lot in their life and
their immune system's always challenged
they're under a lot of stress they got
some bugs that they're working on so I
tell them hey take it every single day
take these three every single day so
what you're looking at you're looking at
the propess right there I
mean I know people that have had canker
sores and they don't have canker anymore
okay I'm just telling you right now I
know people who had canker
stur and they don't have canker sturs
anymore I'm just giving you guys the 411
on that right there
okay yeah I know people that had cold
sores you know cold sores right the
whole C cold sore
thing and they don't have cold sores
anymore fever blisters
anymore yeah and Canker sorus can get
quarter sized in people's mouth Jessica
McGinty over there but but my
30-year-old daughter the vimergy total
immune blend for her birthday she caught
a nasty virus at the same
time her best friend caught it side by
side
her friend was down for 2 weeks my
daughter was over it in 3 days
explanation points this stuff is the
real deal and I know Jessica I know this
stuff is the real deal I know it
is that's why I'm always like this is
the best stuff this is the best stuff
and I'm so glad that you experienced it
that's incredible and I've seen people I
want to talk about canker stores for a
second because so many people get mouth
ulcers so
many and I know people never saw another
one again never saw another one again
they had one every day in their mouth
they had a mouth alcer every single day
in their existence since they were a
child they had mouth ulcers popping up
everywhere since they were a child and
they're like got on the propolis never
saw one again aw gone never saw one
again it's incredible all right I'm just
going to clean this board up a little
bit really quick if you guys are okay
with that
get this cleaned
up there we
go all
right
so you know you can get this you can go
to vimergy.com I just see people's
questions coming up v.com V is inv
Victor I I Amon Mar eerg y v is in
Victor I Amon Mary eerg
y.com vimergy.com you can go there so
it's the cats claw the propolis all
right and you know you guys you know
medical medium info put cat's Claw on
the map the whole lime disease thing
lime doctors use cat's claw now lime
doctors use cat's claw now yeah they do
they do they used to bombard people with
such heavy antibiotic using doctors were
scared they were scared using that many
antibiotics there were so many doctors
out there that were bombarding their
patients heavy heavy antibiotic
therapies and and I heard it all the
time from other doctors there's doctors
they're just scared they're just like we
don't know what else to do and they're
just bombarding their patients with
those heavy heavy
antibiotics and over time because of the
medical medium books and lectures
throughout the years and everything else
cats claw has been taking the place of
certain therapies out there doctors are
shifting gears they have their patients
on cat's
claw I mean it's a miracle to see that
like progress to see that but ask your
doctor you know what's right for you and
how it works for you and if you can be
on cat's claw ask your doctor if you can
be on propolis ask your doctor if you
can be on total immune it's got the
moling and the time and I want to talk
about that in a second too so let's go
let's go into this a little
bit all right so let's make another
bloodstream really
quick right so we got a bloodstream
right
here okay all
right let's make some immune cells nice
big immune cells right here you guys can
see this right why should you do
maintenance why should you
care should you even care you guys
should you even
care all right let's get some bone
marrow let's get some bone marrow over
here that's right your bone marrow get a
little bit of that can you guys see that
it's kind of hard to see a little bit
maybe we can get another color in there
too does that
help little bone marrow right there okay
there's your immune cells okay toxins
poisons herbicides pesticides fungicides
stuff raining out of the sky right sea
Trails dropping out of the sky
okay fabric softeners drier dust
floating in every single neighborhood
coming out of Apartments all those
highly highly dangerously charged
chemical concoctions people are using in
their laundry in their laundry you think
your immune system likes that do would
think do we think our immune system
loves all that chemical charged highly
toxic chem you know the kind that lasts
forever now it's like the sent
from this fabric softener only gets
stronger as you touch your clothing so
all you got to do is touch your clothing
and the smell from that fabric softener
or that detergent just comes out even
more fragrances and more fragrances okay
all the different stuff we're exposed to
you go to the gas station you're pumping
your gas you're breathing in those gas
fumes are you standing right there by
your gas tank are you by your gas tank
and you got your thing in there and
you're just breathing in that petrol
fuel that highly toxic petrol fuel all
goes into the bloodstream so let's do
this
okay as all that's going into the
bloodstream everybody's asking about a
link the link is in the description the
link is in the bio on these incredible
supplements that's the cats claw link is
in the description right that's the
propolis right there okay people are
asking where they can get it that's the
total immune okay viy all right and
that's the propolis pure
right there incredible did you guys hear
what I talked about mouth ulcers and
Canker sours and stuff
okay so vimergy.com link is in the
description link is in the profile why
should you do maintenance ask yourself
that ask yourself why should I do
maintenance I don't know why should I
why should I do it there's a good reason
because we are up against a storm of
crap in the air exposures
everywhere even in our food in
everything we do we're being over
inundated you see what's happening out
there do you see what's happening out
there you guys on social and in the news
how many people are getting sick it's
just like I
predicted it's just like SSC told me a
few years ago remember I told you guys
everybody was going to start falling
apart well they are they are they're
falling apart out there all right let's
go into it here comes the toxic heavy
metals Here Comes the fragrances here
comes the petrol from the gas station
it's coming into your bloodstream you
see this you guys so it's not just
adrenaline anymore it's not just
adrenaline coming through okay so you
got your adrenaline in here too from any
kind of emotional experience it's the
poison coming into the bloodstream it's
the stuff falling out of the sky it's
the falah hide it's the ammonia
everywhere it's all the different
chemicals
everywhere it's going in here and it's
in the bloodstream it's the perfumes
it's the colog it's the fungicides on
your new clothing it's the stuff out
gassing off your furniture it's the
carpet cleaners coming off your
carpets and it's getting into the
bloodstream you see this there's your
immune cells right there do you think
your immune cells really enjoy that do
our immune Sy does our immune system our
immune cells really like all those
incredi charged toxic chemicals no
doesn't and then the immune cells weaken
it's why we have to be on the defense
it's critical we are on the defense with
our immune system it's no joke anymore
it is no joke
anymore very important so let's hit it
for a second all right Christina over
there got rid of all the herpes related
stuff with propolis and vitamin C
actually looking for my vitamin C it's
around here
somewhere yep incredible I want to go
into that with that propolis you guys
stick around I want to talk about the
propolis a little more I want you to
know okay I want you to know how good it
is I do you have every right to know it
shouldn't be kept from you it shouldn't
be kept from you it shouldn't like when
something's really good and something
really works and it's really powerful
why should it be kept from you that's
what I'd like to know all right what you
see right here is your immune cell this
is your bloodstream right here and what
you're seeing in here is all these
chemicals and toxins coming into your
bloodstream every single day Metals
chemicals falling out of the sky
pesticides herbicides fungicides all the
different stuff we're exposed to every
single day fragrances sent to candles
air fresheners cologn perfumes all
getting in here and then that's right
immune cells start dying that stuff
kills immune cells yep and yeah your
herpes starts to rise out because of it
and rise up that's right Epstein bar set
egular viruses HPV too and on top of
just
herpes okay hhv6 hhv7 shingles start to
rise up see these immune cells dying
right here from all the chemicals and
all the toxins you guys see that these
immune cells are dying watch this now
your bone marrow is producing overdrive
bone marrow we need some we need some
immune cells fast immune cells r rush
into the bloodstream here we go but
guess what we don't know how to protect
your immune cells new immune cells go in
and then the chemicals start killing
them off again there we go killing them
off just like
that and that's how it works every day
people's immune systems are struggling
and then what happens is all of a sudden
that's right all of a
sudden an Invader comes in you just got
exposed to the flu you're down and out
you got all this chemical exposure it's
in your bloodstream it's knocking out
immune cells and then just by chance do
you want to call it happen stance do you
want to call it by luck do you want to
call it just bummer luck you get exposed
to a flu here you go right there and now
you got a flu bug right there you just
got exposed you were somewhere and you
got exposed you took a nice deep breath
at a yoga
class nice deep breath in a yoga
class and everybody went breathe in and
everybody was breathing in and the flu
virus was floating around in that little
room and everybody was exhaling and then
you're breathing in and now between the
chemical exposure and the adrenaline
exposure and then you bring in that flu
bug now you're in the flu bug mode it
gets into the bloodstream and now you
got the flu bug in your bloodstream and
guess what your immune system is
weakened so the flu kicks your butt
you're coughing your guts out it's
getting into your
lungs and then you hear about everything
else happening to people these days the
amount of stuff people are going through
with their health because their immune
systems are down we have to do
maintenance we have to do defensive
maintenance it is critical at this time
stuff's happening really fast people are
getting sicker than ever I know that the
media hides it too and they make it look
like everybody's fine and everybody's
looking healthy and you watch stuff you
know on the screen and everybody looks
great but they're not they're not see so
me Taran says do you take them all
together I do and I tell friends and
family to take them all together ask
your doctor what's right for you but I
take them all together right there so
what's your looking at is total immune
total immune is actually Mullen and
Thyme and a little bit of
zinc cats Claw is cats claw that
incredible bark that medicinal bark and
then propolis is the propolis pure we
can talk about too Al over there says on
YouTube is it okay to put them in Juice
yes it is so I got my shot glasses right
here let's get a little bit out okay so
this is what I
do so I get a little bit of water in my
shot glass
all right and you don't have to use a
shot glass you can use something else if
you want you can do anything use a cup
use a big cup it doesn't matter and then
just put a little in there so what I'll
take is I'll take the total
immune I'll drop it in there just like
you just
see okay there you go right and then
I'll take the cat's claw so I'm showing
you guys the cat's claw right
here
right the cat's claw in here
so I'll do a cocktail with these three
here's the cat's
claw and then the
propolis
okay there you
go then you got your propolis just like
that did you guys see that and that's
your propolis propolis
pure I just spilled some water but
that's okay and that's why we're live I
got my glass right there okay I'll show
you guys there's the shell glass you got
the cclaw in there you got the total
immune and you got the propis pure right
there and I take it all in one
shot
amazing it's so good to know you're
doing this for
yourself now listen when it comes down
to things like oral health I have
friends and family that put the propolis
pure right in their mouth
that's what they do and they let it sit
in there and then they swallow it so
they put the Puris pure right in their
mouth direct right in so have friends
and family they're putting it directly
right in and they're letting it sit in
there especially if like someone's got
like some some kind of like sore ulcer
in there in the mouth anything like that
I tell friends and family you go to the
dentist you do any kind of dental
work you should be on the prob list you
come back from the dent denst from
cleanings from any kind of thing that
you're getting done any polishing
whatever it is that you're going to the
dentist for or you get any work at the
dentist office done to your teeth in
your
mouth propolis they got to be on
propolis after you come back from the
dentist you're taking propolis and
you're taking it every single day for a
while a so you don't catch a flu or
something else what happens in the
dentist office it's easy to catch a lot
of different bugs from the drills and
the tools things because of people
touching things like the lamp the light
because they're touching this they're
touching that what I tell friends and
family you tell the dentist or the or
the the hygienist you tell them to
change out their gloves because they're
putting gloves on but they're putting
gloves on to protect their hands from
you they're protecting themselves from
you they're not putting gloves on
technically to protect you when they
have their hands in your mouth they're
putting gloves on to protect themselves
from you keep that in mind so what
happens is they're touching everything
they're doing this and that and I I I'll
tell family you tell them to change
their gloves a couple of times
throughout the process if they're like
well they're 50 cents a glove you pay
for it you pay for it anyway that's the
propolis after dental work after oral
work any kind of stuff like that oral
surgery I mean ask your dentist what's
right for you but I tell friends and
family you got to be on propolis you got
to be on
propolis is is it okay to
take wild the blueberry is shot right
after yes it is
definitely it's what I would
do okay so we're going into propolis a
little bit we're going into cat's
claw so what I love about cat's Claw is
it's like an immune system
modulator so it doesn't tend to wear off
it won't wear off your system doesn't
get used to it right because you're on
it every day it's a immune system
enhancer but modulator keeps everything
balanced so it's like that defensive
nature keeping things balanced it's what
I love about cat's claw all right and so
many people they're up against so much
out there I mean you guys see it out
there like everything from autoimmune
Under the Sun so many people are dealing
with stuff all that is immune system
that's how it
works because that's what went
wrong something had to have gone wrong
first if they got viral or they got any
kind of pathogens or any kind of bugs
it's because their immune system wasn't
handling it properly if they're sick and
they got all kinds of different
conditions that's because their immune
system is struggling you see how it
works you guys Hill over there on
YouTube says vimer pure propolis was a
huge game Cher for me with my head in
thank you aw and
so when people come to me friends and
family come to me guys and they say what
does aw think about this what does a aw
think about doing this and and I sound
like a broken record I'm like propolis
propolis why are you not on the propolis
the stuff is is god-given gifted
Heavenly scent it is unbelievable it's
the combination of Supernatural Mother
Nature Supernatural God it's a
combination of all of that to be in our
hands right now in this day and
age and you got to think about something
like with the propolis you got the bees
Gathering nectar and and and right
pollen from so many different species so
many different flowers from so many
different species with all kinds of
hundreds of micronutrients like hundreds
of phytochemical compounds per species
right and they're all bringing that
back right and then they spackle up some
propolis the bees spackle up some
propolis they use it as a protected
inside the hive to glue the hive
together but it's also antiseptic right
it's a protected it's like the protector
the defense mechanism for the Beehive
it's
incredible and vimergy does it in such a
way they use a process that is so clean
and so pure and so good for the bees
that I can't trust anybody's propolis
out there there's no way I can't I can't
thumbs up for the best it is the best
stuff so you guys we're talking about
the immune system we're talking about
all that let me just clear the board for
another second you guys have another few
minutes to learn some
stuff you guys up for that at all you
guys got you guys got a couple more
minutes all right we just clear this
board off a little bit
all
right we're back okay all right
bloodstream again bloodstream there you
go
okay all
right immune
cells yep there they
are immune cells you know what their job
is your immune cells their job is to
collect debris get ready
that's right everybody's bloodstream
ends up getting dirty dirty blood
Syndrome from debris so what kind of
debris are we talking about we're
talking about everything from plaque
From Plaque
deposits even younger people we're
talking about toxic
calcium yeah toxic
calcium building up in here we're
talking about debris solids it's called
our bloodstream is not supposed to be
filled up entirely with solids it's only
supposed to be partial solids in the
form of micro minerals macrominerals
trace minerals but our bloodstreams get
dirty because of our stagnant livers and
when our bloodstream gets dirty from our
stagnant livers solids
accumulate and when they do your IM
immune system jumps on them you know why
your immune system jumps on the solids
do you know why because it has to go and
break it down and eat it that's what it
has to do our bloodstream gets filled
with solids that aren't supposed to be
there and then our immune system has to
gobble it up and consume it and eat it
and guess what happens to our immune
system it weakens every day our immune
system
weakens and then it dies it dies off in
our bloodstream and then once again you
got your marrow over here your bone
marrow it's overdrive your bone marrow
is an overdrive trying to produce immune
cells to eat up solids that's
right dirty blood syndrome beats down
the immune cells we have to protect our
immune cells it is critical that's why
what I believe in from what Spirit of
compassion has taught me throughout my
life is you got to have a maintenance
immune system plann you have to have it
everyday
a maintenance immune system plan that's
what we have to that's what we have to
okay put something up there in the
tech it's critical for people to
understand this maintenance is critical
big piece of it all on its own all right
so let's
[Music]
go all
right lymphatic system how many of you
guys are in into the lymphatic system
okay that's your
lymphocytes lymphocyte production
lymphatic system okay everybody's trying
to drain their lymphatic system
everybody's trying to get lymphatic
drainage everybody's talking about their
lymphatic system everybody's talking
about lymphatic drainage there's tools
out there trying to drain people's
lymphatic systems but guess what they're
not talking about they're not talking
about how to keep your lymphocytes
strong
you can play with your lymphatic system
all day
long and if you don't clean up the liver
and the liver stagnant and sluggish the
lymphatic system blows right up the next
day or or three hours later do you ever
see that when someone comes out of
lymphatic drainage massage but at the
end of the day they're like this
again just spend $300 and I'm like this
again okay I better go back tomorrow and
do it all over again because their liver
is stagnant and sluggish they're not
addressing the liver so they're
constantly battling the lymphatic system
but let's talk about the most important
part about this lymphatic system means
lymphocytes those babies are a part of
your immune system and what happens is
with lymphocytes they die easy they die
easy and lymphocyte production becomes
minimalized because at some point in
your life it was maximized and it was
just boom lots of lymphocytes everywhere
and then slowly over time they were
broken down they're dying they're beaten
down and your production is not as
strong as it was in the
past and so we need maintenance on
lymphocytes maintenance to support your
lymphocytes big piece of how to
heal I don't talk about the lymphatic
system every day because I talk about
the liver the very thing that makes it
so your lymphatic system gets dirty to
begin with I don't like doing the
topical crap I like going to the root
cause down to really what's going on
what's causing things if you don't clean
up your liver your lympha you're going
to be chasing after your lymphatic
system the rest of your life you are if
you don't clean that sluggish stagnant
toxic liver up you're going to be
chasing after your lymphatic system
rainbows you're going to be chasing your
tail chasing your tail chasing your tail
but one thing people don't realize
overall with the lymphatic system it's
the lymphocytes we got to keep those
strong and if you don't do maintenance
to keep those strong you can play with
your lymphatic system all day long get
drainage do what you want with it talk
about it take some lympo you know
lymphatic system supplements whatever
you want to do but if you don't keep
your lymphocyte strong you're not doing
your your lymphatic system
Justice and that's what it's about so
right here here's your see this these
lymph cells right here so I'll point to
them right here okay all right so here's
your lymphatic system over here you got
your lymph lymph nodes or lymph
lymphatic system right there those are a
little swollen right here and people
have swollen lymph nodes all the time
because why they're lymphatic their
lymphocytes and their lymphatic system
are
struggling you ever did you guys ever
experience that like a swollen lymph
node swollen Li node in your neck around
your throat swollen glands anywhere did
you ever feel a swollen lip node in your
groin did you ever feel one in your neck
somewhere down lower or higher that's
your lymphatic system your lymphocytes
and they're
struggling they're struggling with
something that they're battling if we
don't do maintenance we can't protect
our lymphatic system the lymphocytes in
our lymphatic system and so what I tell
friends and family if you're not doing a
maintenance plan then what are you
really doing for your lymphatics so well
I'm getting lymphatic drainage three
times you know a week that's what I'm
doing but are you protecting your
lymphatics immune system because if
you're not protecting that then you're
not truly really protecting
yourself if you're not protecting your
lymphocytes if you're not doing that
then you're not really protecting
yourself and then what what do I do what
do I do prop list I told you about the
prop list oh that's right I didn't order
it the
propolis critical to be on some kind of
immune system maintenance program every
day if your doctor says it's right for
you
it's a big deal so we just I'll just
recap on stuff a little bit so let's do
that talked about emotional termoil how
adrenaline gets exploded into the system
how it weakens the immune cells talked
about all kinds of air freshers
fragrances all kinds of drier dust all
the fabric softeners the detergents
right the the scented candles the Clones
the perfumes and all that all that stuff
destroys our immune system gets into our
bloodstream right I talked about solid
coming into the bloodstream from all the
junk and the garbage built up eating
away our immune system Katherine over
there [ __ ] says I'm coming from
Connecticut to meet you next month that
is incredible I will be in person yes I
will you guys know about the
collaboration between Iran right Iran
and and medical medium do you guys know
about the collaboration you go to
Medical medium.com you just make sure
you sign
up um but yeah so I'm going to be there
I'm going to try to I'm going to try to
sign some books I'm going to be there
it's going to be fun okay so yeah just
letting everybody know check it out it's
June
15th all
right incredible you guys when it comes
down to our immune system we have to
give it love we have to give it TLC we
have to look out for it and I don't want
to sound like a broken record but I see
people they just they're not taking care
of their immune systems and then they
get sick then they get fibro they get Ms
they get Tinkles and numbness ringing in
the ears tentis vertigo they get dizzy
spells they get the balance problems
they get the tightness of the chest they
get the pain in the neck they get the
migraines they get the back problems the
sciatic pain they get planter fasciitis
they get all kinds of different spasms
and cramps their immune system is
struggling they get all kinds of
different vibrations and Tremors and all
kinds of different neurological problems
they got fatigue they can't function
their jaw hurts trigeminal neuralgia
they have all this going on out there
every single day and they're not taking
care of their immune system and they're
not on a maintenance
plan and it's painful to watch it's
painful to see because the suffering out
there is
horrendous and you see all these good
people out there and they're all
struggling with their health because
they're struggling with their immune
system check out the link in the
description there's the total immune
with the thyme and the Mullen which you
can't I mean that's incredible the
propolis pure right there like I said I
know people they never saw a mouth ulcer
again canker stur were the size of
quarters and dimes in their throat the
doctors were like kerur were in their
throat they're esophagus you guys it was
insane and then you got the cat's claw
right there and I got friends and family
doing the maintenance doing the
maintenance that's why I support these
guys it's the best stuff there is out
there that's why I support these guys
there isn't like 20 things in here where
you're getting ripped off with a little
bit of this and a little bit of that and
a little bit of seamos and a little bit
of this and a little bit of this and a
little bit of this and you can't get
better because it's 20 30 things in a
bottle and all cheap ingredients all
mixed up in there and your body's like I
don't even know what you're taking it's
different when you go Powerhouse and
you're taking that cat's claw direct and
you're taking that propolis direct and
you're taking that total immune direct
there's a big difference than 50 things
in one container cuz somebody comes up
with a brainiac idea and they throw all
this stuff in here a little bit of this
little bit of this little bit of this
here it is when you're doing something
like this and it's like in this form
it's another story it's why people can
get
better incredible information you guys
incredible information link is in the
description check it out so that's vimer
g v is in Victor i m is in Mary E RG y I
can never get sick of saying that
because that company right there is a
God send and when you're doing like that
kind of propolis pure it is Supernatural
stuff you're talking about you're
talking about a combination of Mother
Nature the bees you're talking about
supernatural forces keeping coren in
alive you're talking about all of it
packed in
that just incredible see
guys um yeah here's a question right
here Deborah says if you take total
immune do you need zinc also right look
ask your doctor what your doctor thinks
okay but I have family members on zinc
separately every day taking a little bit
of zinc separately and the total immune
I do I have family members that do both
because they need the zinc they're up
against a lot so I do have family
members that actually take both you know
I have friends that take both I do I do
but that's your doctor it's okay for you
to do that but yes I take the zinc
myself okay I do I take it every single
day I take zinc but I also take the
total immune there's only a little bit
of zinc in the total immune only a
little bit I take the total immune
that's got the time and the Mullen
incredible Heavenly info Rissa it is it
is it is so guys I just want to give you
the rundown on how it works with the
adrenaline how it works with the with
the immune system and what we're trying
to
do what's the point what's the point
seriously what is the point if we can't
take
care of our immune system and we're just
being dragged down by sickness because
we can't keep our immune system stable
long enough even when people do a little
something for their immune system and
whether they know they're doing it or
not they do a little something for their
immune system but what if what if they
did a lot for their immune system and
longterm like a maintenance where it's
long term where all of a sudden 6 months
later the symptom goes away 8 months
later the symptom goes away four months
later wait a minute I can't believe it
but I forgot about that symptom I used
to have it's gone now it's
incredible it's things like this that
matter truly
does you guys you guys check out my
medical meem podcast at Apple podcast I
just released an epen bar episode I
don't know if you guys check checked
that out CHR says says over there in
IG love love love love you you've helped
me so much I'm honored to help in any
way I can truly you guys Queen over
there in IG says is this okay for kids
as well ask your doctor it's right for
you but I have friends using all of this
for their
children using all of this for their
children I have friends doing that every
day Susan love says vimergy heart best
quality out there it is and people know
the difference they know the difference
with vimergy they know what it's like
when they're taking vmer and they know
that difference when they take other
things versus other things and they know
the
difference they understand it they know
it yep what brand uh people everybody's
asking what brand it's vimergy okay
these in Victor I am is and Mary E RG y
That's a propolis pure right there these
three supplements but you guys it
matters you know why I support them too
you know why I actually support BG
because there's nothing like this on the
planet and I don't want it to go away I
don't want it to go away
because if it goes away and I think
about the loss of people's like
opportunities to heal and to move
forward and protect themselves that
right there that that just really is sad
anyway it's one of the reasons why I
also support him because when
something's this good you don't want to
lose it you don't want to lose it that's
true you guys check out medical meem
podcast at Apple podcast I released an
Epstein bar episode check that out out
and I released a bunch of episodes
okay yep the couple of the did you know
a couple years ago you guys a couple
years ago the best propolis you could
ever get out there on the market had
alcohol in it it would burn your your
mouth fuzz it up just a few years ago
the best propolis out there that you can
get burned your mouth up because it was
loaded with
alcohol that's what I mean without viy
how are we gon to do what we got to do
just a couple of years ago like the best
propolis and I see people still using it
out there the best propolis out there a
couple years ago it's just it's loaded
with alcohol it fuzzes up your whole
mouth just burns your
mouth all that
alcohol alcohol
free but but not just that living cortin
is in here naturally in the propolis
living coratin naturally in the propus
think about that for a minute
living corset 10 big difference than
corset tin in a shelf in a dead
capsule living coratin in the propolis
pure that's the difference right there
that's the
difference I just discovered you and
it's been about 6 weeks my symptoms are
healing and some are completely gone
thank you so much for
everything Molina
thank you for being here so you just
found me six weeks ago thank you for
actually giving it a chance thank you
for trying thank you for finding the
information I know a lot of people are
finding the cleanse the heel book I know
there a lot of people are finding the
cleans of heel book right now and I know
a lot of people are finding the brain
saver protocols right now incredible
books and they're finding them and
they're like you know what this guy has
something to say I've never heard this
information before in my life and I'm
healing people people are saying that
every day Angels over there at IG I had
a cold sore show up and started adding
propolis directly throughout the day and
it stopped it from getting
bigger yeah because you know how it
works when in the past it would be there
for a week I hear that all the time hear
that all the time with vimergy propolis
P you guys hear
that that's not somebody that's paid to
say that there's no people being paid to
say that that's somebody leaving a
comment I just read right there on
IG that's saying that literally that's
what happened with their cold sore it
would usually stay there for a week and
it stopped growing that day from using
it Helen over there says my son loves
all of emergy bottles and their colors
yeah I do
too that's
amazing your son has good
taste yeah so anyway people are fing the
pro the protocols book The brains saer
protocols book they're finding cleanse
to heal out there I see that a lot right
now going on out there so there you go
right incredible protocols in here take
the books to your
doctor definitely these are medical
textbooks filled with
information take your time and and
read Molina says yes it was the cleanse
to heal that saved me I'm getting all of
these books they are life saving for
people they are life saving for people
indeed and here is the first one it's
the new edition but the first one
Shamrock says over there the vimergy
propolis was so critical for healing my
MCAS thank you aw so grateful incredible
like I'm telling you I wouldn't know I
would be at such a loss like heart and
soul and such a loss if that propolis
wasn't here for people
Vena says my son is 2 years
old um with autism and I found your page
what exactly can I use to rid the heavy
metals and help heal them um I what I
would do is I would take the books I
would take um the brains saer
books okay I take this brains saer books
to the doctor right there's go through
here and look for the protocols you'll
see the protocols in here customize one
to yourself can take a little bit at a
time you can just do one thing one thing
but the heavy metal detox is what I
would be looking at is the heavy metal
detox ask your doctor if your child can
do the heavy metal
detox children are doing the heavy metal
detox popsicles they're doing they're
eating all kinds of you know heavy metal
detox versions smoothie Bowls the
Smoothie the Popsicles just got to have
the five ingredi ingi it's the heavy
metal detox it's the five
ingredients try to have the five to get
maximum three is the
minimum if you read the information
you'll see you'll understand you'll
you'll like see all those nuances and
all the details that Details
Matter you guys I love you guys anyway
um yeah so check out the medical mem
podcast check out my telegram I'm going
to start leaving some I'm going to start
leaving some um messages on telegram
make sure you get like signed up to my
telegram telegram telegram
telegram all
right and then I'm going to do a little
shot right
here all right let me get some total
immune going next subscribe to the
medical medium podcast at Apple podcast
there's a new episode every week so
please do that let's get a little bit of
water in here I will put a little shot
of water in there just like that all
right here it
goes one
two
three join mm inside scoop on
IG if you can too for some private
messages
and yeah I don't know if you guys are um
I don't know if you guys are coming out
I saw someone was coming out from
Connecticut I don't know if you guys are
coming out um
to the heavy metal detox
launch at at Air1 you guys check it out
when you get a
chance
okay what is in the total immune little
bit of
zinc a lot of thyme a lot of Mullen and
the best quality of of it out there uh
literally the best anyway all are you
guys incredible and I'll talk more about
these you know I didn't get a chance to
talk about really all the details on
these I wanted to talk about the immune
system and why this is so critical and
to have the maintenance but this is the
best stuff there is all right I love you
guys I'll see you guys next time