reading about depersonalization in the
new brain saver books check this out
comprehensive detailed information no
one wants to be depersonalized being
numbed out is not something someone
wants to portray to others or feel
inside I mean we don't want to feel numb
inside we want to be able to feel things
people with depersonalization often
don't feel as though they've experienced
what they've just experienced did you
ever know someone that's gone through
that have you ever felt that your
self-wear you had an experience but did
you feel that experience like it was a
good experience but you're just too numb
to feel that experience maybe you were
with a group of people and everybody had
a good time but you were felt like you
were dying inside like you just felt
like you couldn't connect and you
couldn't even focus or feel as if you
were part of it all
it's almost like a numbness or inability
to connect others
to yourself too so it's like you're so
numb you're so disconnected you can't
even feel like you can make
communication happen with somebody else
an interaction that feels healthy and
then you're doubting yourself every
minute and I've seen this with with
depersonalization so many people doubt
themselves they don't believe in
themselves anymore they feel like
they've lost that confidence and when
you live with depersonalization all the
confidence disappears and then you feel
like you're not confident about anything
even decisions you're making and it's
even hard to even make decisions with
depersonalization
and that's hard too they could be
standing next to a friend with whom they
just took a hike with to watch a
beautiful sunset and they could feel a
disconnect from it all he can literally
be doing something that's really
exciting or fun or something that feels
so good like you watch a sunset but you
feel so disconnected in your mind and in
your head and in your being that you
don't even enjoy it and that other
person that's with you they're enjoying
it and they're like
incredible Sunset and look and you feel
like I I can't feel it and that happens
to so many people it makes it so hard
it can be experienced as a disconnect
from oneself a spiritual disconnect too
and then with with the personalization
you feel like you're not spiritually
connected and you can't make that
spiritual connection and you see others
doing it see other people in yoga class
and they're just like seem like they're
like really spiritually connecting and
they're like well am I connecting too
they're seeing life from a perspective
as if they themselves weren't there and
that's another thing with
depersonalization it feels like you're a
different perspective like you're not
even there it's like you don't exist and
that's something that happens too you
guys I'm reading depersonalization in
the brain saver books really detailed
comprehensive information here
if you've experienced depersonalization
you may have been told you need to find
yourself
I think it's really insulting
when someone's actually really
struggling with depersonalization I
think it's insulting to tell them
you need to find yourself that's what it
really is like just go find yourself
it's more than that it's more than that
one person's depersonalization could be
much different from someone else's and
that's a whole nother topic there
everybody's depersonalization could be
different and is different
it's a large gray area bordering the
threshold of depression and anxiety how
many people do you guys maybe know in
your life that had depersonalization or
suffering with it now that also have
like the anxiety and the depression
along with this depersonalization
the classic variety of depersonalization
is the inability to feel emotionally
that's the classic variety
you're completely numb nothing excites
you nothing gets you upset nothing
matters nothing interests you
and you feel like you're not inside your
body and you don't exist a lot of people
feel this way this is the classic
depersonalization so many people have
this
even within this classic variety of
depersonalization there can be plenty of
variables what I'm saying is there's no
one-size-fits all for all these symptoms
and conditions
just like in depersonalization there's
no one size fits all like your
depersonalization is exactly like yours
and you're the person like no they're
all different there's variables even
with the classic of like I feel numb and
I don't feel like I exist
it's still different than someone else
who feels numb and feels like they don't
exist
the reason for so much variability in
the experience of depersonalization is
the range of causes There's real causes
you guys detailed information become an
expert because you can you can become an
expert you can read the details you can
learn that depersonalization is a
physical problem
physical there's things to actually fix
and that's what's important to know
so these causes range from emotional
injury
which can create a physical injury
inside our brain emotional injury to
toxic heavy metals to adrenal burnout
when we get our adrenals in such a
problem because we're up against so much
stress emotional abuse problems betrayal
broken trust and our adrenals are just
stepping it up and we're shaking
sometimes you know where you feel like
someone just got you so upset they
triggered you so bad someone triggered
you so bad you're actually shaking and
you feel it like you're shaking you just
want to run and scream
so these causes can range from all these
things I'm talking about each cause can
vary too for example when it comes to
toxic heavy metals there are differences
from person to person and what type of
metal or metals are in the brain you can
have a different form of toxic heavy
metal in the brain creating a different
variety of depersonalization
so you can have some different Metals
sprinkled about your brain that are
actually creating your own subset your
own unique variety of depersonalization
inside your body inside your brain
the metals reside inside the brain how
close they are to the emotional centers
of the brain here's something people
don't know about like all the medical
medium information has always been
unique okay it's always been published
first it's always unique
original and here's how it works with
depersonalization
emotional centers of the brain toxic
heavy metals that reside closer to the
emotional centers of the brain
can create the depersonalization so
someone may have more metal or a
different variety of metal closer to a
certain area of the emotional centers of
the brain when someone else
has another type of metal somewhere on
the back end of the emotional centers of
the brain in a different section of the
emotional centers of the brain
and these Details Matter and it matters
if you're healing if you want to heal if
you need the information to heal
becoming an expert having the details
the empowerment when you know what's
wrong and how to heal is just it's an
incredible experience all on its own and
here's the thing if you can't experience
because you're suffering and struggling
with depersonalization and you apply the
information
and you and you learn the details
and that depersonalization starts to
heal that's an experience right there
that's when the numbness lifts up
and the interpersonalization starts to
lift up like a cloud and all of a sudden
you start to experience your own healing
process
while you like everything's being fixed
with depersonalization and many people
have healthy personalization with
medical medium information it's one of
the symptoms and conditions so many
people have but this is so detailed so
comprehensive
it's really worth looking at is brain
fog present do you have brain fog with
your depersonalization
or is brain fog not present makes a
difference that's another variable
and that's what it's about medical
medium books
you look at the brain saver books it's
not one size fits all it's the opposite
it's knowing that all these different
variables can happen to someone and
happen inside their brain and body
a low-grade viral infection such as
Epstein-Barr which everybody has
we've got to remember everybody's got
the ebv's in their livers they got the
ebvs in their body they got the ebvs in
their system
a low-grade viral infection such as
Epstein-Barr can worsen brain fog adding
to the depersonalization so you can have
a low-grade viral infection
causing a symptom like brain fog and a
mild fatigue
coupled with
a variety of toxic heavy metals sitting
closer to the emotional centers of the
brain
and that's where the confusion lies
that's why it's critical to know the
information so you don't get tricked our
fooled or do so you don't get owned by
the system you you get free because you
become the expert and you say oh my God
how come research and science doesn't
know this does it know that you can have
multiple things happening low-grade
viral infection from EBV plus toxic
heavy metals by the emotional centers of
the brain and the different variables
all included
depersonalization can also happen
without emotional injury without
emotional trauma you can go through life
everything's good you're taken care of
you have support life is great
and still get depersonalization I talk
about that in here so it could be
someone without these other variables
and still get the condition learn about
it here I'll see you guys next time