talking about the soul
so I'm excited you guys
some powerful information
so I'm in medical medium right New
Edition
and soul healing meditations and
techniques and by the way are you doing
the Stones The Three Stones
because that's really powerful I can't
even tell you it's incredible it's in
here so
we're going to talk about some other
stuff too good to see you guys
foreign
so everybody is soul searching
someone once told me
you're either soul searching
or you're not
and then Spirit of compassion said
you're either soul-searching
or you're soul-searching
because that's the truth
even if somebody doesn't know it even if
they don't call it that so that's
another thing like
you may run into somebody
and
it doesn't seem they don't think they're
soul-searching on any level they're just
doing their thing living their life
but they don't know their soul searching
they're soul-searching but they don't
call it that
they're not aware that it's
soul-searching right
we soul-search because part of us feels
lost
how many people do you know have that
feeling of being lost that lost
sensation like a sadness
at a certain time of day
what if it's like three four o'clock in
the afternoon and then a strange sadness
comes over
I know so many people that have it at
different times and it's this thing you
can't really explain but it's there if
you guys just got on here we're talking
about the soul we're talking about
emotional detoxing we're talking about
emotions a little bit
we Soul search because part of us feels
lost or we don't feel whole like there's
a piece of us missing
like we're not all of our pieces aren't
there in place right it's just there's a
piece of ourselves missing
or because we feel like we're not living
up to our Soul's potential we
soul-search because of life's hardships
that's another thing too is life's
hardships
make it so we want to go in Soul search
as well right
yeah this is an incredible section of
this book you guys like this is an
amazing section right here Soul healing
meditations and techniques if you want
to read along you could this is
the revised and expanded medical medium
talking about emotional detoxing talking
about emotions
Soul healing all of it right now
after that light blast this is like
a a great place
to go and read and learn and heal
especially after the life last or if you
weren't there for the light blast it's
still an incredible you know place to go
and read and everything
often a negative experience or a series
of them will prompt a person to feel
broken or depleted did you ever feel
broken or depleted like you just had
something happen in your life
right
something happened in your life and it
just pushed you over the edge
like you were on your last tether
if you were a bird you felt like you
were on your last feathers I mean where
you just felt like you were pushed over
hanging on the cliff like done
did you ever use that term where you're
like I'm done
I'm done
right
so many people have felt like that where
they're at a place where like okay I'm
done or this relationship so many people
they're in a relationship that's toxic
there's a lot of emotional turmoil in
the relationship there's a lot going on
in the relationship and they're just
like I'm done I can't take this anymore
I can't handle this anymore
so often a negative experience or a
series of them will prompt a person to
feel broken or depleted and want to feel
complete again it's like I want to feel
whole again I want to feel like myself
again and maybe I don't even know what
myself felt like but I want to feel it I
want to feel
like I got
all those pieces of my soul back I want
to feel like I'm not lost
I want to feel like connected to
something I want that sensation I want
that feeling and if you have chronic
illness and you don't feel good and
you're struggling with chronic illness
then it really amplifies it
makes it even harder
I'm glad you guys came on we're doing
some deep diving into healing the soul
right now what I'm doing right now with
Spirit of compassion and I right now
as we're reading Spirit of compassion's
words right here
and then
I'm listening to try to get additional
information from Spirit of compassion
about all this about how we feel what we
go through all of that so I'm reading
soc's words because these are not my
words
these are Spirit compassions words right
here it's the medical medium book series
that feeling of wanting to be complete
again
that feeling of not wanting to feel lost
that feeling of no one understands me
that feeling of something's missing
that's when we need that soul searching
that's part of soul searching right
there
it can take the form of attending
Retreats how many people attend Retreats
they're looking for something how many
people
are looking for something
so they'll go anywhere and they'll do
anything they're looking for answers or
they're looking for that piece of what's
lost to come back
sometimes it takes going to hear
inspirational speakers seeking advice
from loved ones enrolling in therapy how
many people are in counseling how many
people have had so many
counselors emotional counselors
therapists
psychiatrists
different forms of counselors
because they're like trying to find an
answer why am I thinking like this why
am I struggling how come I feel so sad
inside how come I feel so lost why am I
going through this
I need to find another therapist I need
to find a therapist that understands me
and can crack me
because I'm hard to crack why am I such
a tough nut to crack
how come it feels like nobody can crack
me no professional
is there something wrong with me did I
do something wrong am I crazy is
something going wrong I mean these are
feelings that we naturally feel that
everybody feels at some point in their
life and maybe they don't feel it now
but they might feel it at another time
it's what we do when we're looking to
heal and Elevate our souls to strengthen
our purpose in life we look for help
because we want to strengthen that
purpose we want to unlock something in
our soul and we want to heal
a lot of stuff's coming up in a lot of
people that were at the light blast
by the way I'm at on page 393 so p393 in
Soul healing meditations and techniques
this is medical meaning book one if you
don't have it you might want to try to
get a copy go to the library get it for
free at the library or amazon.com us
it's it's really discounted right now
this book
and it's a book that so many people
found answers to what was wrong with
them and how to heal and it covers
emotional and spiritual and physical
this is one of the most profound books
out there in the world of healing for
people
I can say that because it's Spirit of
compassion's work so I'm not being
biased in the sense where it's my work
it's just I'm the messenger and I wrote
down the words as I heard them
Reina says thank you with a heart I
asked for the light to help heal my soul
that has been stepped on too many times
the first light blast went through me
and such a release instant tears my soul
feels lighter and Freer
and that healing is going to continue
with the light blast because the light
blast isn't
it isn't a person
that's trying to generate the light
it's not a person
as many times as people who met me
throughout the decades and said well
that medical medium guy's a Healer go
see him and everything
the light comes from above and it's not
man-made so I I don't I'm not perfect
I'm like everybody else in the world
not perfect
have my own experiences I have my own
baggage I've had to contend with
throughout my life
just like everybody else and so the
light blast isn't coming from me
pure it's untampered with it's coming
from above and when that happens it's an
entirely different experience and that's
why so many people are profound in a
profound results or or experiences with
it
your soul
resides in your brain something people
don't know
their soul resides here
and resides here
now this is going to sound kind of gory
I know it's kind of a little off topic
but it's not really off topic it's a
little gory
but back in the olden days
the reason why they beheaded people that
was a very popular
technique is because back in the olden
days they sensed
there was an energy all around here
so what they would do is
medieval times they would put it they
would chop people's heads off and put
their heads on spikes
right or Pikes or something they would
put their heads on sticks
on the sides of roads and all that or
they would be head people with
Guillotines right
for some reason they felt like that was
the most satisfying way to end
somebody's life because there was
something more satiating about it in the
medieval days and what they what they
were actually tapping into without
realizing it there was a lot going on
here
but they didn't know that's where the
soul resides and that's why they had a
desire to behead people because the soul
resided in the head
they didn't know that
they didn't know the soul resided in the
head
but they had this innate desire when
they wanted to end somebody's life to
behead them to chop off their head that
was what that is why they did that and
then they had this innate desire to
exhibit someone's head chopped off they
had this innate desire to actually
exhibit it so exhibit the head on a pike
on the sides of Roads or in villages
where they would slay a village and then
they would chop off everybody's head and
put it on Pikes because
they felt that a message was sent more
because and what it was was what they
were detecting
yeah it's gory but what they were what
they were detecting was there was more
energy here even though the whole body
there was more body weight and body mass
everywhere else there was more energy
here
so what they were detecting without
release without
realizing it they were detecting the
soul was here inside the brain so they
had a great desire if they wanted to end
somebody's life back in the in the
medieval the Dark Ages they would
chop off the head
your soul resides in your brain
where your soul stores memories and
experiences
that's where your soul is storing
memories and experiences
they're in the soul when our soul leaves
our body it takes
these experiences with it
when you pass from this Mortal Realm
your soul carries
those memories as it moves onward
your soul carries those memories as it
moves onward if you guys want to know
I'm reading at a medical medium I think
what people don't know if they don't
read the medical medium books you know
how you know when someone didn't read
the medical media books
this is just on another note you guys we
got a lot to cover but
let's get bear with me my silliness but
you know how you know someone did did
not read the medical medium books is
when they say there's no emotional
healing in medical medium information
and there's no emotional detoxification
healing or emotional work
the medical medium books
and there's no or they'll say there's no
emotional support it's like
oh you didn't read the books you just
called yourself out pretty much that
means you've read about celery juice in
one of the books a little bit and then
you just kind of like maybe you did the
heavy metal detox movie but you never
read the books they're so packed with
emotional support it's insane
every time a doctor friend or a friend
or somebody I know
picks up the books again they start
reading them they're like I've never
seen so much emotional support in my
life in a book that also has medical and
physical combined it's the craziest
thing
anyway so I'm in medical medium book one
so when we pass from this Mortal place
this Mortal realm right our soul carries
these memories as it moves onward even
if someone has a brain injury or brain
disease that keeps her or him from
remembering certain things so
hear this for a second so if somebody
has Alzheimer's dementia
if someone is losing their train of
thought losing their mind
and they pass away from a brain disease
even if someone has a brain injury or
brain disease like Alzheimer's or
dementia or something like that
encephalopathy right that keeps her or
him from remembering certain things the
soul will bring all those memories with
it when that person passes on if you
have a grandfather a grandmother or a
family member or a friend that is losing
their mind because they have the
Alzheimer's they have dementia they're
really suffering they don't even know
who they are they lose their memory
completely and they pass away
you have to remember something
the pain and suffering a loved one has
says where did their memories go don't
they remember me how come they don't
remember me how come they don't see who
I am
my grandfather's sitting there and he
knows me I he raised me I'm walking into
the room and my grandfather's saying how
are you I don't know who you are
you have to remember that every member
memory that that grandfather has
grandmother that friend that mother
father that brother sister every memory
that they have about you in their life
is still trapped in there it's in there
just because the brain disease is eating
away neurons it doesn't mean the soul
doesn't take those memories with it
that's the whole point and what I
learned from Spirit of compassion is the
soul takes those memories with
with it
as it leaves
so it's not like that family member
their lives are just completely wiped
out and completely gone it's not like
that at all it it's the opposite yes in
that moment it feels that way but when
they leave and their soul passes on they
have all the memories there they didn't
lose that they know who you are
foreign
father grandmother or friend or family
member's soul is leaving them as they
pass in that moment even if they lost
ability to understand who you were as
they were fading away they still when
they leave and that Soul lifts up
from that body
they instantly know you
Who You Are
every memory they shared with you
everything about you all that they've
done with you every experience they've
ever had with you they know and they see
it and see you as their soul leaves the
body
I think someone said I never knew that
the information's not out there
unless it was
taken from the medical medium books but
this is all Spirit of compassion's
information there's no citations in the
books ever
ever because I'm not taking one piece of
information from anyone
so there's no citations the books are
just unique information from above
your soul also stores your hope people
don't realize that that their soul
actually stores their hope you think you
you think you're hopeless you're not
you think you have no hope anymore uh-uh
that's not true
you think you've lost all your hope no
no no no no no no no no
you didn't lose all your hope
your hope is stored it's stored
in your soul
there's a well of it in your soul
your soul also stores faith
if you have faith in God your soul
stores that faith if you have faith in
Jesus Christ your soul stores that faith
see there's a question on Instagram
heal with Haley says why can't we
access the memories our soul already has
from before this life
there's a reason
Spirit of compassion has told me my
whole life why
and I'm going to be sharing about that
soon
I read that comment because I plan on
sharing about that soon
and it's going to be mind-blowing
absolutely mind-blowing
but I have to share about it properly
too so people
cite the source
because someone's just going to take it
next you know it someone's going to say
oh
this heat well-known
Mastermind guy or healer or whatever you
wouldn't believe what he said and
they're just gonna just butcher it
they're gonna butcher it because they
don't know all of it and they're gonna
try to run with a golden nugget so they
can get more likes and views
and sell more programs
so we got to do it right so people have
all of the info and they know where to
get it so they can heal
foreign
also stores your faith that means if you
have faith in Jesus Christ your soul
stores it if you think you if you're if
you're a Christian and you have faith in
Jesus Christ that for some reason you're
a Christian and you lost faith in Jesus
Christ I promise you this your soul
still has faith in Jesus Christ
if you're someone that's not a Christian
and you just believe in God and God
God is who you believe in and you have
faith in God and you have tremendous
faith in God and then all of a sudden
something happens to you in your life
and you lose faith in God I promise you
this your soul still stores
your faith in God
Thomas Phoenix 82 on Instagram said I
wanted to die
and now I have my life back and it's all
because of medical medium info thank you
aw and SOC
sfc says you're welcome
all right
if you think you lost trust and you had
Trust
and now you can't trust anything anymore
and you can't trust anyone anymore
you can't trust anyone you can't trust
anything anymore because you lost trust
I can promise you this
that you have trust stored
in your soul
the reason for that is it helps to keep
us on the right path so we stay
stay present here
ideally we would all have fully intact
Souls
over the course of life's hardships
though a soul can become fractured and
even loose pieces of itself but that's
okay because
we still never lose our soul
this can be caused by traumatic events
traumatic events can fracture our soul
but that's all right
because her soul can mend and heal
our soul is unbreakable it is
unbreakable regardless of a fracture
regardless
of
hardships beating it down and wearing
and tearing on your soul it is
Unbreakable
this can be caused by traumatic events
such as the death of a loved one so many
people go through
betrayal by a loved one or betrayal of
oneself as well as ongoing traumas such
as the loss of freedom and trust that
comes with experiencing chronic symptoms
and illness I think so many people have
been beaten down with their illness
you guys know about that
you had symptoms
or you still have them because you just
found medical medium and you're working
on your healing process but you bend
down that road and you had so many
symptoms and suffered greatly so bad and
that wears and tears on the soul
many throughout the years I would
through a process that Spirit of
compassion has has taught me to scan
someone
and spirit of compassion would show me
if they had any fractures on their soul
and it resembled cracks in a cathedral
window that's what it resembled when I
would see it through Spirit of
compassion's eyes
because the soul is made out of light
and when someone's been through
hardships
so I think we have a tech problem
so I'm just trying to fix it here
okay
because our soul is made out of light
because
our souls are a form of light
not when a soul is fractured
it looks like the sun it looks like the
inside like you're inside a
the church
and the stained glass windows
there's light coming through the Sun
as for a soul with missing pieces it's
like a house at night that's meant to
have all its lights on except some of
its rooms are still dark
when Soul injuries are fresh
they can result in the feeling of being
lost
foreign
or a loss of connection with oneself
loss of Desire or inspiration to
preserve or Thrive so many people lose
their Inspirations they feel like
they're dead inside they feel like they
died inside they're numb and they don't
feel like there's anything left in them
they feel like there's nothing there
anymore
they feel like
they are not being seen by anything and
they're completely alone and completely
in the dark and that's what happens when
Soul injuries are actually fresh it just
happened
I just got let down that person broke my
trust I feel so injured I feel so
misunderstood and not heard so when the
soul injuries are fresh they could
result in feeling like
you're lost
or there's a loss of connection like
where's the connection there's no
connection
a loss of Desire or inspiration to
persevere or thrive
or even
like life force how many that you guys
know that where you feel like you lose
your life force
because you just
had such a hard time
that's why it's important to be aware of
our soul and that's how you heal
emotional support is understanding our
own soul because people they don't
realize they have this connection to
their own soul they don't know how to
connect to their own soul
when you understand your soul and and
understand where it is and and if it's
been injured and how strong it is and
how powerful it is
when you connect to your soul that's how
you can really do some emotional healing
and rise out of something
that's why it's important to be aware of
our soul wounds from hardships betrayal
and broken trust or emotional hurt often
exhaust a person's immune system
adrenals and other bodies defenses
triggering a physical issue that could
be residing deep within our organs and
body
so it's twofold if you guys go through a
hard time if somebody goes through a
hard time
I know a friend that just got betrayed
so bad just so bad the Betrayal was just
horrendous and he didn't want to live
anymore
but when he really understood the soul
connection that I was teaching him about
it was giving him a chance to say you
know I could get through this you can't
you can't take my soul away no one's
going to be able to take my soul away
but at the same time adrenals can get
beaten down and our immune systems can
can be lowered because we're going
through a lot if we're betrayed it does
play
it does take a hit on our immune system
and our physical body it can beat us
down our adrenals
you go into this
point where
your adrenaline just spikes and feels
like it gets out of control if someone's
messing with you or you had a hardship
someone just
you you know their trust
you don't trust him anymore something
happened and all of a sudden it's like
adrenaline you can even feel like you're
shaking
you get so upset and hurt where you're
and that's the adrenaline now
being released and takes a toll on the
body
sometimes a person's soul injury
and resulting emotional state isn't a
physical problem
yet symptoms often take time to build
quietly in the background so a soul
injury at an earlier time in life could
be the trigger
for the future symptoms or full-blown
conditions to come
if you don't have the right knowledge
tools and resources to take care of your
soul and physical body
we can get in trouble
the medical medium tools are there to
support your physical body and your
emotional body that's how you win it's
both they're there and even if you don't
support your your emotional body
and you heal physically it naturally can
help to heal the emotional part of what
you're going through in your life it can
help heal the emotional
injuries
let's be clear
emotional wounds and soul wounds
are not the reason for physical
suffering
that's important to know
they are not the cause of physical
suffering
they're not the cause of fibromyalgia
they're not the cause
of thyroid cancer they're not the cause
a multiple sclerosis
or lupus
or Lyme disease rather they can act as
triggers
for underlying susceptibilities
when we go through emotional hardships
it cannot go so hard it lowers our
immune system and it triggers us when we
go through emotional hardships our
adrenaline can really get kicked into
high gear because we're emotionally
injured and then we get
knocked down a notch
it knocks us down I can't tell you how
many people
that got into a difficult relationship
and it was there was so much turmoil in
that relationship there was so much
fighting and cheating and betrayal and
that relationship that it lowered the
immune system
and when it lowered the immune system it
broke them down and other things they
had residing inside of them pathogens
rose up and now they have chronic
fatigue syndrome
they become triggers
but you're stronger than you know to
have battled this long and gotten
yourself this far in life now you can
rise above
all this is knowledge so you can rise
above your wounds you can rise above the
injuries physically that you've had
the pathogens
the exposures you can rise above that
and heal your emotions too and Rise
Above any kind of Soul injuries
a person with soul injury
is vulnerable
if you ever hear a friend say I'm not
ready for another relationship I'm still
hurting from my breakup
she's acknowledging that her soul needs
time to heal before she risks putting
herself out there again
so many of us know when our soul is
vulnerable we know that we're
susceptible we know it's like whoa I
can't do that right now
I can't go through that again right now
I I need to step back a little bit my
soul isn't feeling that strong my soul's
not feeling strong enough
along the same lines if you ever observe
someone who's sick with symptoms or
conditions and hasn't been able to find
answers you may see this person
hungrily pursuing spiritual learning in
any form
like religion
spiritual gurus self-help books
meditation Retreats breath work
it's likely because that person's soul
has been injured from all the trust lost
along the way
and she or he is instinctively searching
for ways to make the soul healthy and
complete again
when we fall ill with symptoms that
won't go away or that continue to come
and go we lose trust in our body and
others to help us
there are people who have been sick for
years who turn to soul-searching when
they can't find answers and that's
another thing too I I watched this for
decades
people are looking for Spiritual answers
because no one knows why they're sick
physically
what was really popular back to like 30
years ago 25 years ago was because
nobody knew of course why anybody was
sick with chronic illness you go and
find somebody
and then
you try to find some kind of healer
takes to give you any kind of answer and
there's a good chance they'll tell you
it's because you had your head chopped
off in 1733
in England somewhere
and that's why you're actually sick or
they'll say you drowned still say like
in the 1600s you were
you were deemed a witch in the 1600s
and you were put to death by drowning
because nobody knew any answers right
I remember people would come to me and
they'd be like well I bent every doctor
and now I've been to every
every psychic can heal where I can find
around the planet and I have some I have
some good
good leads one lead is I was drowned as
a witch
in 16 in the 1600s and because of that
that's why I'm sick and I have all these
problems and everything else and spirit
of compassion would say
no
that's not why the person's sick
person has real
real reasons why they're sick and those
are the answers you find in the medical
medium books
sometimes soul-searching will bring
people closer to themselves many times
it will leave them feeling more lost
than ever did you ever go soul searching
and then you feel more lost than ever
did you ever try to find yourself but
yet you feel more lost
did that ever happen to you
where you're you're going to try to find
yourself right
and you think you're going to find
yourself you're trying to find yourself
and then you're like I think I found
myself I do I think I found myself you
guys yes everybody's saying yes but then
all of a sudden you feel more lost than
ever
and then you feel like you're down a
rabbit hole where it's worse
foreign
says I was probably burned at the stake
I don't think so
that's terrible you weren't burned by it
you weren't burned at the stake
many times it will leave someone feeling
more lost than ever under the guise of
help you may have heard the false theory
that illness is just a cry for attention
did you guys ever hear that the false
theory that went around for decades at
Medical medium information had to
disprove
did you ever hear that where it's a cry
for help that's why you're sick
you were looking for attention
did you ever hear that one where you
were looking for attention
that's why you were sick yes
you've heard that
that's another one that has tortured
people for years that medical medium
info had to disprove to help people
they give them answers I can't tell you
how many times I've heard that like
you're just you're just want attention
that's that's why what you're doing
right that's what everybody's told
that just breaks my heart when I even
hear that
you may have heard that when bad things
happen to us we cause them by thinking
the wrong thoughts did you guys hear
that one bad things are happening to you
you're sick because you caused it with
your by having the wrong thoughts did
you guys have that one too
like is that so yes I see that too like
by having the wrong thoughts that's why
you're sick
ajada says it's such a mind screw it so
is such a mind screw it totally is yes
you had that too where you you caused
your sickness by thinking the wrong
thoughts
see these were all made up things made
up theories here by men
my men
here on the planet and women here on the
planet it's made up theories
and spirit of compassion is not
from here so has Clarity on this because
I can't tell you how many times I've had
to rewire someone because they were
positive they were sick because they had
bad thoughts and that's why they were
sick
I've said it before and I'll say it
again
if you are ill or going through a trial
like a divorce
or a loss
you did not manifest it
if you are going through a sickness you
did not manifest it
if you are going through some type of
feeling of like being disconnected
feeling lost feeling hopeless and
depressed you did not manifest it
if you feel sadness that you can't
explain and you feel like you don't no
one understands you and you can't
understand yourself you feel and you
feel like you lost all trust in yourself
you did not
manifest that
you did not attract it
it is not punishment or payback it's not
Karma
if you guys have struggled and you
suffered and something happened to you
along the way whatever you do don't
think it's karma paying you back
in this lifetime
if a child is sick you mean to tell me
that child's karma is why that child is
suffering
Christina B says people all tell me that
so much
the one thing you'll find in the medical
medium information is about freeing the
brainwashing and freeing you up of the
brainwashing and mind control that has
been out there forever
and that mind control is in the
alternative arts and alternative healing
I'm so sorry to say I really am it
breaks my heart and kills me it's also
in the conventional healing too in the
conventional world that mind control and
brain conditioning is unbelievable
there's a spiritual war out there
it really is and it just controls people
purposely so those people can control
everybody else it's like it's
unbelievable
you did not attract it it's not
punishment or payback it's not your Bad
Karma you have to know you're not sick
because of your karma whatever you do
you can't fall into that
so fernica Monica says then why some
then why are some of us so sick is it
destiny
go to the library
and try to get these books out for free
try not to even pay for them
go to the library and get these books
vernica
find a library Wherever You Are
ask them for the medical medium book
you do not deserve to be sick or unhappy
it's not your fault you didn't manifest
it it's not your fault and it's not
Karma I can promise you that
you don't need to travel the world
trying to find yourself I've seen people
who have money travel the world
to find themselves and they're still
sick
Miranda mccola says Anthony can you
please clarify that God does not cause
our suffering
I have a tremendous amount of
information from spiritual compassion
about that very topic
and
I can tell you this
that what I've learned my whole life
since age four and listening and talking
to Spirit of compassion
what I've learned from SOC is that God
does not cause our suffering on purpose
so
Darkness
here on the planet wants us to suffer
God is doing everything
in God's power
to stop that
I'll I'll do a whole I'll do a whole
show on that and I'll actually
I'll actually give you the details to
that because it The Details Matter in
that statement I just said the details
matter in all of it
Soul healing is about reclaiming Who You
Are
because you are already
good enough
who you are already means more than you
know
you are already good enough
it's just about healing now you are
already good enough
Lorraine L says the karma thing is so
overused
you deserve to heal
you deserve to be happy you deserve to
feel whole
aw
is there a reason
we meet certain people like a soul
connection
well it all depends people meet certain
people and it's like whoa that was
the very hardest
experiences I've ever had in my life
because that certain person I met
you know and then you meet someone it's
like
someone actually understands me and it's
like the door opens
and then you meet somebody and it's like
how did this person get into my life
this person is just toxic and dangerous
in this person's in my life and I can go
into details too on details too on how
that all happens these are all topics
that I've I've fleshed out greatly with
Spirit of compassion
with tremendous amounts of details and
information and
so yeah
it's it's interesting
your heart serves as the compass for
your actions
guiding you to do the right thing when
your soul becomes lost
when our souls become lost we feel like
we disconnected we feel like our soul is
busted up and broken our heart serves as
the compass for our actions it guides us
to do the right thing when our soul
becomes lost our heart matters in that
situation your heart is also a safety
net that can compensate for soul
injuries that means when we get broken
down so hard and we have really bad
relationship or something happened in
our life our heart
stand strong
this means you can have a tattered soul
and a warm loving heart
I can't tell you how many people that
I've met that have tattered they've been
tattered along the way but their heart
is warm and their heart is loving and
their heart is caring I've been through
a lot in my life and I still care and I
still want to help and I still care
about people and love people and I know
there's a whole bunch of people out
there they've been through hell and back
and they still have a heart that's warm
and loving and they care
when your soul suffers
losses a strong heart will get you
through with Selfless Love compassion
and joy under the soul
until your soul has managed to heal
compassion is critical
superficial love
that's a matter of the Mind
self Selfless Love that comes from the
heart
foreign
you guys know about superficial love
right
it's a superficial love
love
is not
absolute
love is not
everything
unless compassion is attached to it
that's why you can see somebody and
they'll fall in love with someone
and then they can fall out of love with
someone like what was it
was it just a change of heart a change
of mind what was that how can you be so
in love with someone
so in love with them and then not love
them anymore
that means that love had no compassion
in there
it wasn't attached
they were separated
if you have love
for someone
and it's lost
that means that the compassion is gone
compassion is the glue to love love
isn't enough
you have to have compassion as the glue
for love
or love won't stand a chance love won't
hang in there love won't even Last Love
Won't Be Strong Enough Love is just an
empty word
love is a totally empty word if
compassion isn't intertwined or attached
or somehow involved if you don't have
compassion involved if compassion's not
part of love then love it's not strong
enough
because a tremendous amount of
information in here the meditations that
are in here waves on the beach I love
that one I want to do something with
that with you guys sometime I'm going to
read a little bit about emotional detox
right here this book whoa surrounded by
trees
the healing tools in the medical medium
books blow my mind because they come
from Spirit of compassion
reading time with aw is the best
right there on IG
see Juliet says isn't everything just a
lesson
we try to learn from it so we don't get
burned by that stove again
but no everything's not just a lesson
unfortunately it's not
it's like
you don't need your arm chopped off to
teach you a lesson
is that a lesson
I know a lot of war vets
that lost their legs
um intertwined with a lot of vets
right I have vets in my family the whole
bit and
losing both your legs is not there to
teach you a lesson
we can we can certainly try to grow from
it and learn from it
but it wasn't done on purpose to teach
us a lesson
child abuse isn't there to teach a child
a lesson
so yeah no things aren't there for a
lesson that's not how it works
we can try to grow we can try to better
ourselves we can try to rise above it we
can try to use tools rise above it
but it wasn't there to teach a child a
lesson child abuse and it wasn't there
for for uh
a soldier who's
trying to do something good it wasn't
there
for the soldier to lose their legs
being killed isn't a lesson either for
us to learn
abuse of any kind for someone isn't a
lesson for us to learn we're not that's
not a lesson we're not supposed to learn
that as a lesson
but it happens
you guys I'm reading if you just got
here reading out a medical meme do you
have the revised and Expanded Edition
because one thing I can say and I'm I
can't help it I got to say it again
because it's been said like a thousand
times out there over the years to try to
discredit
the information
when I hear someone say out there like
an influence or something say that you
can't get any emotional tools
or emotional healing or emotional detox
info for medical medium when the books
are filled with them it just tells me
that that influencer never read the
books
perfectly clear that they haven't read
the books
yeah
I'm going to read a little bit into
emotional detox right here lena111
hi aw why do I feel I have no worth no
value
but there is a drive in me that makes me
do
that makes me try day in and day out to
take care of myself maybe my soul is
hurt but my will is strong your free
will is extremely strong
your spirit is strong which is your will
have a really strong Spirit that's
different than your soul your soul can
feel beaten down and it can feel
weakened
boy you got a strong will and your soul
will get stronger too and heal
Lorraine now says people try to
rationalize bad stuff as it being a
lesson
I know they do
and those are usually the people those
are usually the people
who try to deny that Darkness exists you
know they're like there is no Darkness
there is no bad in the world there's no
bad in the world
it's like what bubble are you in because
there's plenty of bad in the world
they're not it's not all lessons well
it's all lessons and even people don't
mean to be bad that do terrible things
out there it's really a Learning lesson
and we're all just it's all we're all
just learning there's no evil in the
world there's no darkness in the world
there's only lessons in the world
foreign
totally inaccurate emotional detox
there's a significant emotional aspect
recovering from any injury or ailment
so there's a significant emotional
aspect to recovering from any kind of
sickness especially mystery illness
especially mystery illness where 10
doctors 20 doctors no answers can't heal
Bend through hell and back
as your body cleanses itself of toxins
and viruses and pathogens
you may find that emotional detox occurs
too when you are healing and you are
cleaning up those bugs and cleaning up
those toxins inside the body
emotions
and emotional detox occurs as well
there's many people where they're
simultaneously that emotional detox
happening
for example if you suffered with chronic
fatigue syndrome since college and have
learned through this book that a virus
was behind your condition
you might feel initial relief and even
Elation as you follow the chapter's
guidelines to restore yourself I can't
tell you how many people I heard this
over and over again for years now it's
almost a decade with this book
and oh my God I can't believe I know the
answer to why I'm sick I feel like I can
heal emotionally now I've been
emotionally tortured because I have
fatigue and brain fog and I can't
function and I can't feed myself and
take care of myself and work
and everybody thinks I'm crazy and
everybody thinks I'm lazy and that I'm
making this up and I've been to so many
doctors including this new Lyme doctor
now and this other specialist
I can't tell you how many people found
this book and were like oh my God I am
finding peace in my heart peace in my
soul to have an answer to why I'm sick
that alone is unbelievable when you
think about it
as your cells release physical toxins
check this out you guys it's incredible
information in these books in this one
here as your cells release those
physical toxins such as neurotoxins
and dermatoxins produced by the very
viruses behind your symptoms
and conditions emotions may bubble up
as your cells release those physical
toxins such as neurotoxins and
dermotoxins produced by the very viruses
behind your sickness your emotions start
to Bubble Up
nobody knew a virus released a
neurotoxin
mm info and now you hear it parroted out
there with no citing it back sorry I
can't help it I have to say it because
I'm not reading info that's out there
like in the sense where it was
discovered here
gotta say it once in a while
you may find yourself angry with the
people who told you your illness was
psychosomatic did anybody tell you that
your illness was psychosomatic you guys
any of you did that happen where someone
told you that your illness was
psychosomatic
like did you guys ever have that happen
where it's like no you're just you're
you're a hypochondriac
you have to be a Kim Miller suggests you
have to be a hypochondriac right you're
psychosomatic Uma Kelly says yes Karen
Churchill says yes
you guys on IG I see a bunch of you guys
saying yes
it's Christy Myers says yes
I saw that Sharon McLean you guys that
has happened to so many people right
it's psychosomatic and it's it's like
that's what you're being told but it's
not that it's not
let's see here's a comment right here
sometimes I think when you've been
through tough times and come back and
Rise From the Ashes your heart becomes
bigger and same with your compassion
thank you
so here we go
when you've had
when you've had all these different
trials
you've been tested
you've been pushed to the edge
you've had so many symptoms in so many
conditions
you've been to every doctor and family
and friends they don't even really trust
any more that you're even legit as far
as your symptoms where hey you're
psychosomatic and you're a hypochondriac
and this probably isn't even real
anymore and you look good too like you
look fine you fine you don't look like
you're sick you look okay you look
normal hey you look good today
it hits it hits us really hard when that
happens so we're just like
especially if we're really suffering and
struggling and it's getting worse and
that's a whole nother level of like oh
my God no one understands me
and then you start healing you find the
answers you rise out of the ashes
whoa every single one of those remarks
that you have gone through and that
hardship you've gone through and people
not people judging you and doubting you
is like a building block
you're building your church you're
building your Sanctuary you're building
your foundation
says so we
so do we need to extra protect our
adrenals when this happens or is it just
part of the detox process and I'm good
and if if a crying spell happens
the medical medium information
is adrenal protective
if you are cleansing and detoxing
with a medical medium protocol
it's protecting your adrenals because
it's not stopping you from eating
if you're going through a hardship
emotionally and you're intermittent
fasting your adrenals are not being
protected
but medical medium information isn't
intermittent fasting
if you're doing
like a 369 or you're doing a 28 day
cleanse or you're doing brain shot
therapies or whatever it is that you're
doing or
the monocleanse or anything you're
actually getting fuel to protect your
adrenals
and that's the problem so many people in
e-better diets aren't even protecting
their adrenals
and so yeah of course it's okay to cry
it's just it's just reliving old trauma
is difficult like if
if you
if you feel you need to relive old
trauma
I'm not judging you I support you but if
you
but if you're reliving old trauma
or reliving
real fresh trauma
it's important to fortify
with for example like the medical meme
information there's so much adrenal
support in the books it's
the books are partially built on
supporting the adrenals
the information from above is so adrenal
protective
when you're really sick with chronic
illness and you're feeling very
vulnerable it's it's not the right time
to revisit some really really really
deep-seated hurtful wounds I will say
this when people go to therapists and I
support people going to therapist of
course but you know and everything but
the point is when they go to therapists
and they're very sick and nobody knows
why they're sick with lupus and fibro
and Ms and and so many different
conditions that could list 100 of them
right
and they're very vulnerable and their
immune systems are really really
sensitive and low and they're reliving
serious serious
emotional turmoil and Trauma
it's very difficult because the person's
already struggling and really really
sick so it's best to get the physical
body stronger so you can eventually then
tackle some of that old trauma
I think where people get it wrong a lot
or they get get it wrong right
because they think that they need to
like say they're say they're doing
like a low-fat protocol where they're
keeping the fats really low
and
they think well I better eat more fat to
withhold
you know to protect my adrenals
but it doesn't work that way the more
fat you eat
the more you stress the adrenals out the
one thing I think where people don't
understand about medical medium
information is that when you're doing
like the 28 day cleanse the 369s and the
mono cleanses and the morning cleanses
and you're doing all the different
right you're doing all the different
food protocols
what people don't realize is that your
adrenals start building up and getting
stronger and stronger and stronger
so the one thing about Spirit of
compassions information for the foods
and the food protocols with medical
medium is that it builds the adrenals
stronger and stronger without wearing
them down it's part of how people get
their lives back and then
and then as they're healing their
adrenals
and they bring in a shift in their diet
like they start eating all this fun food
and really heavy vegan food lots of fats
or whatever it is and they start
bringing all that in they feel better
for a moment because they made their
adrenals so strong
that the minute they started eating all
these like say they brought in all these
burritos and all this was just fun but
they brought in all this fat and they
brought in all this and the bagels and
they brought in the vegan pizza and they
brought all that in
and they're like oh my God I can eat
what I want and I'm feeling better from
it what they're feeling is the strength
of the adrenals that they restored on
the medical medium protocols so what the
medical medium protocols do
is they restore and strengthen adrenals
to such a point that the minute you
start to use your adrenaline you
self-medicate you feel like
like oh my God I feel incredible you
feel the hit from the adrenaline because
you brought your adrenals back so people
come to Medical medium information with
weak adrenals they come to mm info with
weakened broken down adrenals from
intermittent fasting from Bad eat better
diets from dysfunctional eat better
diets from keto diets from carnivore
diets they come to Medical medium
information and diet and medical medium
food protocols they come here with
broken adrenals and then they they start
to restore them with the celery juice
and the eating every couple of hours and
the fruits and the leafy greens and they
start to restore their adrenals and
after a year they finally got their
adrenals so much stronger
that all of a sudden they feel like they
could eat other things so they start
bringing in other stuff and more fat and
higher fat and more things and the
minute they start bringing all that in
it proves itself the adrenals are so
strong at that point that they release
self-medication they release
adrenaline hits and then all of a sudden
you feel euphoric like wait a minute
I feel better now that I'm eating three
slices of vegan pizza and I'm eating two
avocados every day and I'm eating
whatever I feel better and I'm eating
more chicken or something or whatever
they're doing or chocolate
and they're like wait a minute I feel
better and then all of a sudden someone
will put something in their head and go
like oh you were orthorexic before
meanwhile what you were restoring your
adrenals you were bringing yourself back
you were you were blowing lowering your
inflammation
and then
even if you weren't totally fully hail
healed yet and you still had some
problems like a knee problem that
wouldn't quite get to where it needed to
go or an ankle problem that wasn't quite
there the minute you started bringing in
all that fat or bringing in other Foods
your adrenals were so strong from doing
mm stuff even if you're just doing it on
and off it made them so strong that the
minute you brought in some fat your
adrenals were like and just released all
this adrenaline and it became
self-medication where all of a sudden
you're just like whoa it was like bee
sting therapy
but the difference is you you know your
adrenals just got so strong and healthy
that you you can afford to just blow out
a bunch of adrenaline that's that's
what's incredible about the mm info I
know this is really
detailed information there's so much
more I can say about it but I think
that's a mistake people make they don't
realize it like for instance I remember
a couple years ago
right
um someone
I remember this one and I see it a lot
right but someone restored
their health
by doing the mono eating the medical
media monocleens
and they got the medical media
monocleanse from the cleanse the heel
book right I don't know I think I have
it somewhere the Clinton Hill book and
the restored
their
their health
but they did it because they were doing
the medical media monocleanse and they
restored their adrenals and they've got
their inflammation down and they lowered
their viral load and then
they
said hey I'm gonna go and just eat
whatever but good vegan food but I'm
gonna go eat a whole bunch of good vegan
food and they went and they had all this
vegan food and they were eating all
kinds of dishes and delights and going
out to dinner
and they felt great like better because
they restored their adrenals for a
couple of years
and then they started using their
adrenaline and man did it feel good
that's how it works cold White Springs
says fat triggers adrenals yes fat
triggers adrenaline correct because the
more fat you put into your bloodstream
your hearts your heart struggles
so
you know so what happens is the more fat
that's why vegans get sick they're
eating nut Butters just so much coconut
oil and and almond butter and they're
eating so much it's okay to have some of
that if if you want to have some but
what happens is that in when people
become vegan they end up eating so much
vegan cheese which is pure this is pure
fat they end up eating vegan cheese and
coconut oil and they end up eating a lot
of it and cocoa butter coconut I mean
sorry cacao butter right they end up
eating cacao and chocolate more of it so
when you're vegan you're like oh I can
eat I'm not going to eat meat or chicken
I'm not gonna have fish I'm vegan now
but I can have more chocolate incredible
and chocolate's supposed to be good for
me I'll have more chocolate so they'll
do that and then they'll do
then they'll do like more coconut oil
and they're putting like coconut oil on
everything and they're using olive oil
on everything and then not only are they
doing olive oil they're eating more
avocados than they ever did before and
then
they were feeling a little better from
the start because they got off of their
their processed food diet or whatever
they're doing and then they get sicker
and now they're back on eggs
they're vegans that go back on eggs and
every like they're they're not vegan
anymore
and people also heal so many other
things on medical medium
and the adrenals
you know give you a high once you drop
that fat in so here you go you're on
medical Medium you're healing your Ms
your lupus your Lyme disease your
healing your tingles numbness vertigo
aches and pains you're healing your
restless leg syndrome you're healing all
these conditions your eczemas your
psoriasis and now you go and you you
blow up your diet with a whole bunch of
fat in there
and then you get a high for a little
while like whoa
like and that high is adrenaline surging
through your bloodstream and that stuff
can medicate you people don't realize it
but our adrenaline could medicate us
like our adrenals are just like
squeezing out that gasoline that that
fuel
the kerosene and it's like and it's it's
igniting and we are on adrenaline
I don't know how we got into an adrenal
talk adrenaline to oh a question to
happen Renata Renata
so to clarify here's your question right
you're on YouTube so to clarify if we
need to cry should we go ahead and do it
without worrying about our adrenals or
possible adrenaline surges
that could feed viruses if you have to
cry if you feel like you need to cry you
can cry I mean
you're taking care of yourself you're
doing you're doing the medical mean
protocols you're you're strengthening
your adrenals like you do and all that
you do that you've done throughout the
process right all of it
if you have to let out some tears let
out some tears
foreign
so I want to read about this little part
right here which is really powerful too
so
as our cells release those physical
toxins such as neurotoxins and
dermatoxins produced by the very viruses
behind your symptoms and conditions
emotions bubble up
you may find yourself angry with the
people who told you your illness was
psychosomatic we talked about that and
you may grieve for the years you lost
about being unwell so many people grieve
so fernica Monica says self-medicated
adrenaline is then good
using too much of it's not good it's
like you restored your adrenals that's
what medical mean information is always
done for people going back decades it
restores their adrenals makes them
really strong
and then we self-medicate all over again
like I can't tell you how many times
like you got to read the brain saver
books you guys uh the eating disorder
chapter alone is like
mind-blowing right and it talks about
adrenaline and stuff like that right
I've helped so many people that have had
like bulimia right and they were just on
adrenaline highs that's what bulimia is
it's an adrenaline High
and um
and they had to restore using so many
people that were bulimic had to use
medical medium info and to restore their
adrenals again
and then if they ever go back to bulimia
like a trigger happens right a severe
emotional abuse and they go back to
bulimia
it's euphoric because they restored
their adrenals again what happens is
there's this thing what happens is when
your bulimic you run out of adrenaline
as the years go by because you're using
it to propel and vomit the food up right
but what's happening is that then you
don't get high anymore
but when you restore your adrenals
it's like it's Euphoria when you restore
your adrenals and you eat whatever you
want it's euphoric because your adrenals
got so strong they're
peeing out adrenaline and it's
self-medication so you so yeah you got
to be careful like you don't like overdo
your your well you actually created a
Wellspring of adrenaline to protect you
to have you live longer you don't want
to blow it all out
how his health said just made this live
we talked about a lot of things you got
to watch from the beginning and I think
right isn't that funny like it's like
but I'm glad you're here thank you Holly
for being here
yeah think about that I'm listening to
Spirit of compassion right here so just
bear with me I'll just
I'm mumbling a little bit and listening
Spirit of compassion
Veronica says how would you how will how
will you know that your adrenals are
strong after being bedridden for almost
two years
what happens is that your adrenals could
get really strong while you're bedridden
and your bedridden for other reasons
right so someone could be bedridden for
other reasons like in the medical meme
books talks about so you can be
bedridden for another reason but your
adrenals could still get stronger
and stronger
the one thing about since I was younger
that Spirit of compassion
taught me to help people and message
people like taught me so I could be the
messenger
was how to restorage renals
I think one of the things when I see
someone say something like you know
medical medium doesn't address the
adrenaline or so are you kidding oh my
God the books are there's so much
adrenal information in these books I
almost I almost can't when Spirit of
compassion just keeps on giving me more
information about adrenals and I have to
write it down I almost can't handle it
anymore because I'm like oh my God
there's so much information about
adrenals in these books
here's here's what I look here's here's
the when someone goes through a lot of
trauma and they go through a lot of
hardship and they've been really hurt
emotionally they've been hurt they've
gone through a lot I'd like to I know
that a lot of people that they will use
crying as a release they will use crying
as a release okay and
um
uh but what happens is you know the
bottom line and that can if you feel
compelled to cry you can cry but what I
love about
What Spirit of compassion puts inside
these books
like
the information like being surrounded by
trees these are incredible tools like
free as a bird the meditations in here
be watching
I know some people are afraid of bees
but be watching is incredible tool
collecting Stones you guys know I just
did that on telegram the other the other
night like talked about it on telegram
incredible and I collected my Stones I
hope you guys got your Stones ready and
you're actually doing it and did you
name your stones
the sunbathing part here the picking
fruit meditation watching your garden
grow meditation that's inside here
right exercising creativity
um the moon meditation
these are tools to help you navigate to
help heal your soul while you're going
through a hard time
and
placing your energy into these tools can
be really helpful
I mean be life-changing it's life-saving
restoring trust with sunsets
who do you work for oh my God this part
right here this gets me teared up right
here
whatever kind of work you do
whether you're a nurse a therapist a
bank teller a truck driver an attorney a
teacher an artist a volunteer
a stay-at-home parent an executive a
postal worker a weight person an editor
or a landscape crew member there may be
certain reasons you do it
certain reasons why you do that work and
so many other things that I'm not even
mentioning right you work for a paycheck
benefits to support your family to serve
your clients to please your boss
that's the part everyone knows that's
why we work right that's the part
everybody knows
if your job feels like a burden though
if you have a demeaning supervisor or a
grueling schedule if you feel like your
work has no meaning or no one
appreciates you
if you if the inspiration or passion for
what you do is disappearing and you feel
lost then it's time to shift your
mindset no matter what you do no matter
where you do it you work for God
you work for God
repeat this aloud
using whatever term feels most
comfortable for you each day connect to
it and everything will change
when you wake up in the morning and open
your eyes or sit up in bed open the door
to the day and say it
I work for God
and if
if you don't believe in God then maybe
something else fits in
like I work for the higher source
if that doesn't work for you I work for
the light
or I work for the divine
I say every morning when I wake up I
work for God
that's what I say
I work for God
santara's healing said this medical
medium tool has changed my life every
single morning I work for God
it this medical Centaur is healing
santara this medical medium tool has has
changed my life
when I received the information from
Spirit of compassion
yep
if you don't remember to say it when you
first awake it's fine to say it later on
in the day
Cynthia says I work for God on YouTube
I think I have a tech problem I'm not
sure I'm looking
maybe you're a cashier at a grocery
store
you usually arrive for your shift
to a harried to A hurried manager and
hard Shoppers and it's all you can do to
get through until your break without
crying
because this isn't what you pictured
your life
I got a friend who's a cashier
and
she says every single morning I work for
God now
it changes it can change your life or I
work for or I work for the higher source
you guys 20-day brain shot therapy
challenge
it's coming up
we can talk all night
anyway
20-day brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge is coming up it's
it's on the 10th
I'm just letting everybody know
are you guys gonna are you guys gonna
be there download your free shopping
list
make sure to sign up and get your daily
emails with critical information and
details and guess what it's free it's
free it's free it's free
if you if you don't have the brain saver
books
go to the library and get them for free
or take advantage of this the discount
that's on them right now at amazon.com
but go to the library if you can
try to get one out there that would be
fine
then you've got
and here's the thing too
okay
now
if you are in
if you are on the Main Medical medium
newsletter
you still need to sign up for the
challenge very important to get the
download and the daily emails so if
you're actually if you're on the medical
medium newsletter you still have to sign
up
to get the download
20 brain shots 20 days
we're gonna do it
I'm just letting everybody know
if you guys thought the 10-day Branch
out therapy cleanse was insane
you guys have not seen anything yet
I'm just going to be straight out
did you guys hear the the uh
live I did yesterday the reflection the
light blast reflection
and also I did a telegram message about
it too the light blast reflection on
telegram check it out when you guys get
a chance I'm just looking at this
incredible grocery list which is really
cool it gives you information you need
there's the 20 brain shots we're going
to be doing that's incredible all in its
own brain shot therapy is right there 1
through 20. I can't believe it
Stephanie patissi said of course we will
be there my children were practicing the
robot earlier today should I do the
robot then I should probably do the
robot
incredible you guys anyway sign up when
you can get a chance okay Monica says
can't wait for the challenge but I
bought days one through five ingredients
too early ah it's coming up soon though
can you save the ingredients it's coming
up soon
make sure you are following medical
medium on Telegram
you guys bear with me because okay you
guys know I don't do I don't do ad I
don't have advertising right you guys
like my podcast medical Bean podcasts at
Apple podcast is free of commercials and
free of advertising
and that podcast
is supposed to have advertising and
commercials and all that and I refuse to
do it my YouTube doesn't have that
either and we don't do it anywhere else
and my Rumble doesn't even have it so I
just want you guys to know that
that
you know we don't do that here at
Medical medium there's a reason we don't
want advertisements and commercials in
your way
of your healing and information and
everything else
but if I don't say hey myself personally
I have to be my own I have to be my own
person shouting out you guys
just letting you know so I hope you're
okay with that
um all I do is free information free
events
all of it it's free free free free so
not only do I not have advertising
advertisements and commercials in front
of everything like my podcast and
everything it's free
okay and medicalme.com is packed with
information that's free so sorry to
those who had technology challenges
getting on the light blast event my team
is already working on making sure we
don't have that happen again
when you do a large amount of people
it's not easy to do we are working to
make a better experience with the
technology we have
and allow more people to join we are
putting tens of thousands of dollars of
out of my own pocket to make that light
blast happen for everyone
and there's no charge
so
anyway
I'll talk more about adrenals another
time too give you guys more information
if you guys wanted to want want an
adrenal podcast episode let me know so
just just let me know if you want an
adrenal podcast episode
and schmiel says I work for the federal
government when people tell me I work
for evil I tell them I don't work for
evil I work for God that is incredible
that is absolutely incredible I'm so
proud of you that's that's what you
should do exactly umikali says are you
preparing new dance moves for the
challenge uh
you busted me you totally busted me I
was practicing this new move it was
something like this
or something you caught me and I was
working on it
so when we do the uh
the brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
I'm gonna come out with a new move
Holly's Health says your telegram
messages
are so comforting and personal
Courtney M.A says I love Telegram
Courtney
okay I was reading from medical medium
this whole time if you guys just got on
here medical medium
right new addition revised and expanded
right there
this is a book filled with so much
spiritual and physical healing
information Holly's Health aw is it
normal to feel different on the
different days after the light blast yes
it is everybody has a different
experience it's so some people days
later like tomorrow they're going to be
doing a whole bunch of different stuff
it it's
it's like time release
what's incredible I didn't tell you guys
and I'm going to talk about it on the
next light blast
and I forgot to talk about it
um I forgot to talk about it on the
light blast
uh live we just did right just talking
about it and all that
but
you have to remember what's happening
with the light and where it's coming
from it's coming from far away
but it's breaking time and space so
what's happening is that light is coming
it's traveling through time it's it's
literally
beating time itself
and what's incredible about that light
is because that's not light like from
you look in the sky and there's the sun
right
and the Sun is this ball of fire and gas
and so
that sun is a physical light like that
right it's just up there and it's just
burning
the light from the light blast is an
entirely different light and it's just
crushing time and space
to get here like it does from God it's
just unbelievable
the power in it is just mind-blowing
okay
make sure you are on the medical medium
newsletter and also keep an eye on
medical medium.com you guys I'm totally
totally making medicalme.com an
incredible website it already was but
incredible free information so much
information and all kinds of different
incredible stuff recipes recipes Galore
everything and make sure you're uh
checking out medicalmedium.com for
updates on registration for the next
late blast in order to make the next
light blast you guys got to be on it
because I'm telling you now what
happened was with the last Light blast
is it filled up in one hour we're only
allowing over a little over 20 000
people and we had to shut the doors on
it and boom
it lasted one hour and everybody woke up
that morning or wherever and they were
just like wait a minute I'm gonna go
sign up to the light blast what
admission there's no more emissions it's
already full all right you guys
we're gonna do another that's what we
got to do love you guys
thank you for hanging out
God bless you
I'll see