facebook youtube facebook youtube tick
tock
clubhouse making the tomato cucumber and
herb salad we're talking about digestive
problems
digestive issues how many of you guys
have digestive problems and how serious
are they are they in your way
do you have the acid reflux they have
the crohn's colitis you have the gastric
bloating the cramps
the constipation do you have the runs
you'll have the loose stools which is
kind of a funny one because
i'd rather have the loose stools instead
of
cramping bloating can't get
a really hard stool out the hard stool
will not come out
you know that was a head scratcher for
me for years because
over the years helping so many people
for decades people come into my
office i'd hear that somebody like well
i'm only here for
these loose stools and i'm like all
right well how loose are these stools
and the person i've heard this so many
times personally like you know they're
kind of like not
that hard they're not formed enough
they're not they're not good enough and
i'm like but you're okay otherwise right
i'm like yeah i'm okay otherwise but i
just got these kind of
loose stools and i'm like you know what
that's that's actually
okay that's actually okay anyway um
so people deal with bloating they got
sibo they get told they got candida
they got hives right the whole bit
they're told their histamines are up
they're told they got the fructose
intolerance they're told a lot of things
but they deal with a lot of gut problems
of rounded all around and everything
good to see you guys we're live on
facebook youtube
yep we're live on tick tock right there
clubhouse 2 at the same time
going gonna make a raw dish which is
really good and guess what
fat-free raw dish because everybody's
fatting themselves to death
fatting themselves to death that's what
they're doing like
fat fat veg gotta be tahini tahini oil
oil
you know nuts seeds nut butters peanut
butter
the milk cheese eggs butter butter cow
just whatever uh you know anything
sheep's butter whatever they can find
it's just like that fat
and that's all that's all fine and all
until you're sick
got the gallstones you got the kidney
stones you got the liver problems you
got the weight gain coming on later on
down the road
and then you get rid of all those
processed foods all those processed
foods and you're still on fat fat
then you go vegan and plant-based and
you're still tanking the fat that that
and then your digestive system just
starts to break down more and more
even if you made improvements it still
starts to break down and we end up in
the same place and now we're like i'm
eating so good
i'm eating so great i'm eating so good
why is this happening i'm a vegan and
i'm eating so good
i'm a keto animal protein person that
i'm eating so clean
but why am i still getting sick again
because those digestive problems get
worse and worse because no one's
addressing the real problems i'm making
tomato cucumbers out and i got to tell
you guys guess what
the mono eating challenge
is next week forewarning
the mono eating cleanse challenge
is next week i want to give you guys
forewarning okay
and if you want to partake get to the
library to grab a book if you don't want
to get one
at amazon.comus okay amazon.com us
51 off this is a medical textbook but
it's got the mono cleanse in here
you're gonna wanna look at the mono
cleanse to join in this
free mono cleanse challenge
it's gonna be great allison says i
didn't want to give up fat
i wanted to cling to my tahini left out
loud
but when i did it helped me so much
they train us more conditioned we're
brainwashed
brainwashed to eat fats that's what we
are we're brainwashed to just down the
fat
it's like that all the time you know the
thing is you guys
i'm just giving you the forewarning on
this right this mono-eating cleanse
challenge that i'm doing later on next
week it's gonna be three days
three days right later on next week it's
free
i'm not taking it to a private platform
having everybody buy
tickets you know fifteen hundred dollars
a piece tickets
doing all this stuff around it to make
it seem like it's worth the 1500
that whole game get you guys all signed
up for it
no it's free get the book get it 51
off amazon.com us or if you don't want
to spend a penny go
library shopping look and find it at the
library somewhere
in time for the challenge cassandra ray
i did this challenge and it helped me so
much
definitely doing it again awesome
hey guys doing on tick tock so you guys
are you've got the comments going
i got vertigo right now what can i do
have you looked at cleanse the heel
because if you go in here
there's vertigo and it gives you all the
supplementation and dosages
it gives you supplementation and dosages
it's in here
i don't know what else i can do what do
i do i don't know what else i can do
i want to be at your service literally
be at your service
like i killed myself to get this book
done when i did
get it to the publisher get it published
get it print it get it out there for 51
off even though i don't control the
pricing and the answer answers the
vertigo are in here
they're in here if i had where to go i'd
be on the zinc
you you do what your doctor tells you to
do but if i had vertigo i'd be on the
zinc
because it says in here it's
epstein-barr
okay that's what vertigo is it's
inflaming the vagus nerve
i'd be on the zinc that's the vimergy
zinc right there
that's just one thing okay so but it has
to be the right kind of zinc the right
kind
uh catching up on all the podcasts on
tic tac incredible
podcast episodes yeah yeah those those
are amazing episodes
yes we're making a tomato cucumber and
herb salad
we're talking about how much fat
everybody's on
and we can't let it go it's an addiction
and i'm
look i'm not saying tahini is not a
healthy fat
i'm not saying avocados not a healthy
fat they are if you're gonna do a fat
let it be those okay michelle l good to
see you no one else has the answers
you know you know i got a phone call
coming in too
by the way you know it's it's you know
the bottom line you guys
is it's important to know that these
options really do exist when you have a
condition or a symptom
and you're lost it's like i got vertigo
well what do i do if i got vertigo where
do i go
you know and i you're going to
specialist after specialist
hello yeah i'm really sick
i've been to my third specialist uh-huh
yeah i gave over my i handed over my
insurance card
yeah there's a co-payment though i had
to come up with two hundred dollars
yeah they said it was three thousand
dollars in tests
yeah it's my third neurologist i'm so
sick my god i've been to doctor after
doctor after doctor i've been to
naturopaths i've been to
i've been to this crazy like osteopath
and which was i
which was seemed really cool but and
then i went to this kinesiologist and
then i went to this acupuncturist then i
went to
and then i went to this nutritionist and
nutritionist
didn't know anything and then i went
back to the doctor and my gp
yeah i'm just so burnt out wait a minute
wait a minute there's a commercial
coming on right now i have you i have
the youtube on right now
hold on i want to tell you about this
but i just i don't want to miss this
commercial
let me watch this hi i'm dr derrick
weirich
i'm a youtube doctor with a lot of
followers
and subscribers and i've been a
professor
uh at the at the uh hospital university
and
and let me tell you about the new study
that's out now
green tea is good for your skin it's a
new study
and if you keep on following my channel
you'll learn about green tea and other
products that i have
yes but you know what that's not going
to help me this guy's talking about
green tea helping out my skin i'm really
sick
i got all kinds of problems like i'm
i'm fatigued i can't walk good i'm i
can't function good i got digestive
problems that just won't go away
and i don't get it no one has the
answers
i gotta go
you guys make sure you have the book
make sure you guys
are there at the it's going to be at the
end of next week i'm not sure if it's
starting thursday i'm not sure if i'm
starting a friday but i'm
starting it next week three day mono
eating
cleanse challenge you don't want to miss
out right now if you guys just came on
here making tomato cucumber and herb
salad
i'm pumped up we got ig live not ig live
we got tik tok live we got
facebook youtube clubhouse gotta keep
them all in order here
so you guys were talking about digestive
system issues
and yeah allison was pretty funny
lorraine l
good to see you everybody's coming on
here right now
cleansing heal is a great book yeah on
tick tock totally it's it's helping so
many people so
um anka says gastroparesis question mark
can you talk more about it
what happens when you eat too much at
once
if you're somebody that's really
sensitive you got to keep in mind if you
haven't been eating a lot like you
haven't been eating a lot okay it's not
something that you do you don't eat a
lot at once you don't eat a lot of food
at once
keep in mind
that when you start eating more you're
going to feel it
because the intestinal tract shrinks
that's how it works and a lot of us lose
our elastasicity in our intestinal tract
or small intestinal tract
it starts to harden up a little bit if
we've been eating the wrong foods for so
many years
we got pathogens and toxic heavy metals
inside our gut because it happens a lot
and what goes on is then you start
eating more so you start eating a big
meal at once and you got a really large
meal
and what happens is that that large meal
starts to push
through the small intestinal tract and
we can really
feel it we can really feel it and then
we don't think we digested our food but
we did
digest our food we digested it enough
and but what happens is larger amounts
of food
sometimes stretches out the small
intestinal tract as it's going down
and we could really feel that it's one
thing another thing is if it's not large
amounts of food and you feel
your intestinal tract you feel
discomfort
keep in mind that when the nerves in the
lining of the intestinal tract are
inflamed and
foods moving through it's rubbing the
lining
and there are foods that don't rub the
lining that make our condition worse
like eggs keep that in mind milk cheese
butter dairy eggs all of that
doesn't rub gluten bread doesn't rub the
lining
so you may eat that and not feel it okay
but if you eat something like cucumbers
and lettuce like this beautiful lettuce
you might feel it rubbing your lining
because your lining is inflamed it
doesn't mean it didn't digest it doesn't
mean these foods aren't healing you
because these are healing foods
but you're gonna feel it a lot of people
have metals
and they have a lot of toxic heavy
metals they've got pathogens
and they're inside the gut they're
inside the intestinal tract
so keep that in mind there gastroparesis
is in cleanse the heel i talk about it
in there
okay and sometimes with gastroparesis
it's all
electrical so it's all vagus nerve
related and it's coming from the brain
so a lot of cases of gastroparesis are
coming from the brain so keep that in
mind how that works
the brain is not sending the correct
signals or they're not
reaching the gut so that peristaltic
action
happens and peristaltic action starts to
move and do its thing
you're not getting the signals they're
not matching up because a lot of people
have toxic heavy metals
in the brain short circuiting
information
that's running down the vagus nerve
and heading to the gut creating that
peristaltic action so now you're not
getting that peristaltic
action so so we're not getting that
twisting and that massaging that our gut
does as it moves the food down and
through
we're not getting that because the
signals coming from the brain
are not wired like the the um
the brain stem is not receiving
signals from the neurons up in the
larger
the top of the brain so the hemispheres
so those signals aren't happening
they're not going to the brain stem and
then boom not going down the
down the uh vagus nerve and boom not
going down into the small intestinal
tract and that's a lot
a lot of stuff behind gastroparesis
that's why i'm always like we got to get
metals out we got to do that that's one
reason the other thing for gastroparesis
is
pathogen infections they're just not
detectable
so viral loads viral loads inside the
liver
viral loads inside the intestinal tract
causing
lots of inflammation and then that could
get a gastroparesis diagnosis so that's
how it works there
that's just a couple of tidbits good to
see you guys glad you guys are coming on
michelle elsa's cortisone shots are
horrible
yeah i mean cortisone shots are just
they're just so rough they're so rough
i've been meaning to pick up your book
went and got it
went and got the juicer got some celery
amazing
amazing yeah the book is the look the
book is on sale
that amazon but the point is is i'm
talking about the mono eating cleanse
challenge
jerome says my digestive really started
to heal once i got rid of my
multi vitamins the multivitamins wreak
havoc
that's one of those things a lot of
those junky multivitamins even ones that
come from companies that are really
reputable and they're expensive they're
just
junk multivitamins etc and bought the
bimergy instead
that are supposed to be good for my
symptoms which are neurological
of course lemon water and celery is the
holy grail
that's really incredible one of the
tricks
in the industry i'm just going to give
you this to you right now you guys
is the multi vitamin or protein
powder scams and or multi-vitamin
powder scams that's probably one of the
big tricks one of the big scams in the
industry in alternative medicine
so just keep an eye on that you're going
to spend a lot of money on these
multivitamins they're highly irritating
to the intestinal tract and gut
they're irritating to the system they're
they're
garbage even they're high priced garbage
from the best companies out there so
what we think is the best companies out
there
and they use a speck of this in a speck
of that you cannot heal
with a speck of a whole bunch of things
that some
guy at some lab decided to put together
and offer that to the
to the to the board members of the
company and the board members are like
sure that
that that that sounds good to me what do
you think frank
does that sound good to you they got the
multivitamin they priced it all out we
can make a lot of money and it's just a
speck of this and the speck of that
well what do you think what do you think
bob how does that how was that
chairman bob uh the lab guy came and he
showed us the new multivitamin they're
gonna put out what do you think
uh-huh okay let's get it together let's
do it good you got our go you got our
permission
so what happens is you have to
understand how those multivitamins are
they're the worst
they're the junkiest even from the best
companies
they waste your time all of that your
waste your energy
keep that in mind and they're not for a
specific condition
they're not for a specific condition
you're sick with something
that's that's not there for you like
that's not there fixing that problem
if you got lupus is that multivitamin
gonna fix it because i'm scratching my
head on that one
right there if you got ms is that
multivitamin gonna fix it
that junkie multivitamin or protein
powder gonna fix it
because i'm confused on that i've never
seen anybody with
ra get fixed from a multivitamin
you got neurological lyme is that
multivitamin gonna fix it
scratching my head on that one so what
is it
like how does that work but we we get
led all these directions
and then we're just stuck we're stuck
we're stuck we're sick
hashimoto's thyroiditis is that
multivitamin gonna fix your hashimoto's
thyroiditis i'd love to know that
no it doesn't i've never seen it happen
i had decades of people pouring into my
office from around the world because i
was the bizarre symptoms guy
having answers for symptoms for the
first time in our history and chronic
illness right
and people walk in be like i actually
have an answer now
and it's not candida it's not in it
and he's not telling me to go on this
big old bulky multivitamin
and and you know so keep that in mind
how it works out there and it's not my
genes he's not saying it's genes and
it's not my body attacking itself
he actually has an answer he's actually
saying what's happening
and so what happens is that multivitamin
i've seen that used so many times
over the decades they're still doing it
now let's start making a salad
we're going to talk about digestive
problems
what i like about the tomato cucumber
and herb
salad right is
this one's a raw dish it's fat free
and you can i mean you can have steamed
asparagus and thrown in this you can do
steamed brussels sprouts and throw in
this you can throw some steamed potatoes
in this
throw that in this you can throw steamed
red bell pepper if you want
this is a cleanse to heal recipe by the
way you guys just came on
medical medium mono cleanse challenge
next week
have the book i'm not gonna package this
thing up
sell tickets lock everybody out and take
it to a private platform like people do
and then you
spend fifteen hundred dollars for your
ticket you do the mono eating cleanse
where we talk about it and you know and
all that we're not doing it i'm making
it free
but you got to have the book you should
you should you should
um 51 off amazon.com
so i'm chopping up some tomatoes now for
the salad okay
there's a couple ways you can do it make
this look good you go to the library get
the book for free too how about that
like you just go to the library and get
it for free you can do you can totally
do that
i'm in my dishwasher right now getting a
bowl out
we're live what can i tell you so let's
let's figure this out first of all i'm
going to chop up some lettuce let's put
that in here
now you don't have to chop up your
lettuce if you want your lettuce all big
pieces but i'm gonna chop it up
i'm not gonna butcher the lettuce into
tiny tiny pieces but i am gonna chop it
up pretty good
so yeah
bridgette what about ibs talked about
the cause of ibs for years and years
and what's interesting about ibs is
conventional medicine alternative
medicine just believes ibs is
irritable bowel syndrome
that was one i made fun of for a long
time not people having
ibs no way i would never make fun of
that in a million years
but i made fun of conventional medicine
and alternative medicine for years
because of that one sarcastic being
sarcastic about it think about it
so the all the technology we have
all the medical research and science
all the alternative research in science
all the medical universities right
all the big pharma right all the big
corporations
all the big insurance companies all the
entire
kitten caboodle right the best they can
come up with
is you have ibs that means
you go to the doctor i don't feel really
good in my stomach down here and
i kind of go to bathroom it kind of
hurts a little
no answer think about that do you ever
think about that
all the great minds in the medical world
all the technology and all they can come
up with
with everything they got is you have
ibs really i got ibs i got a diagnosis
finally got an answer
what is that irritable bowel
okay wait a minute i know i have an
irritable bowel
i i know uh can i have an answer please
you have irritable bowel syndrome okay
so it's a syndrome
uh it's a i have an irritable bowel
syndrome that's not an answer
okay i talk about in the medical
medium series streptococcus causes ibs
and there's reasons why strep gets fed
and we eat the foods we shouldn't eat
that feedstrap and then we have
antibiotics throughout our life and the
strep gets worse
we end up with ibs talk about that all
the time
yes it's awful it hurts and makes you
feel nauseous
yeah ibs does it does
um
so yeah
so i'm reading reading comments right
now it's a vegas nerf
so really uh really the vegas nerve that
went up the comment went up i gotta look
forward again see if
i could get that comment back
on tick tock the vagus nerve is medical
medium information
causing these problems so people that
know gastroparesis is vagus nerve that's
not
that's not just out there that's always
been medical medium medical medium
information
uh nausea associated with vagus nervous
medical medium information
for years anxiety with vagus nerve is
medical medium information for decades
the other sad thing is is that
all this stuff that comes from medical
medium originally people just it just
got out there and got out there from all
the lecturing the teaching the
publishing the books and
and it's like and people can't find
their way back
they just can't find their way back to
know where it originates from
science research doesn't know the vagus
nerves related to any of that
so what someone in the alternative
medicine world just woke up one morning
was like
huh no it it comes from
the source that i've always had this
information come from
vagus nerve causing symptoms
and it being vagus nerve is medical
medium information
doing some salad right now
but think about it though diane says
any tips for diarrhea from crohn's
disease
well look i can tell you this if you
check out the cleanse the heel book
go to the library get it for free if you
want or 51
off i'm doing the mono cleanse challenge
next week
mono mono eating
is an incredible tip
an incredible learning how to
mono eat for a little while
i've offered that
for decades for people with crohn's mono
eating bananas
look do what your doctor says ask your
doctor if it's okay to try anything
medical medium if you would like
um take the book to take the
the cleanser heel to your doctor show
them the mono eating section say hey can
i do this for my crumbs
so i'm making some salad here we go
right there so i'm gonna chop up some
tomatoes gonna put that in there
let's do that
got some beautiful tomatoes right here
you guys don't be afraid of tomatoes
when they're ripe and
juicy like this they're so good for you
really really good for you i'm going to
cut them this way
karen churchill said had large i had a
large raised
mole like growths on my face
my daughter looked at me and said mom
those lumps are almost gone hardly
noticeable now
thanks to the wavy thanks to your way of
eating incredible
incredible good for you i'm so proud of
you too so proud of you
if you lower the fats they go away
quicker
the fats slow down our healing
i want you guys to know that the fats
slow down
are healing keep that in mind okay
they slow down our healing
interesting right so i love when you
hear the hole
you need fats for your brain fats
healthy fats
your brain needs them you'll die without
them really
really
you'll die without sugar that i do
though you'll die without glucose
your brain dies without glucose it
doesn't die without fat your brain's not
made
out of so much fat as everybody says
it's made out of it's made out of
glycogen storage
hardened glycogen deposits that's the
majority of what makes makes up and
creates up all the glial
cells it's not fat
so misinformation about fat just gets
everybody in trouble gets them in
trouble but
there's reasons for that you're not
supposed to get healthy
if you get healthy by chance and you
learn how to kick out the bad you know
processed foods and you
at least keep yourself going that way
right
that's not what the industry wants
the pharmaceutical industry wants you
sick they want you dying
they do they do they need you sick
in order to keep them going chopping up
some tomatoes right here
i think you guys know that though
so i'm making a salad just working on it
as you see you guys there's fats already
in every food
there's fats in this beautiful lettuce
right here this butter leaf lettuce has
fat in it
it's got omega-3s in it usable omega-3s
usable right real bioavailable
and keep this in mind
you think you're on a keto diet you're
not on a keto diet
you're just on a healthier animal
protein diet
or if you're plant-based on a keto
plant-based diet you're just on a
you're just on a healthier vegan diet
based basically right
so keep in mind that no one goes into
ketosis anymore
that was given up a long time ago
because people die when they go into
ketosis
so the whole ketogenic diet is just
really a trendy name for something no
one even enters into like
you're actually doing why go keto now
well you're not going to go into ketosis
so number one flaw you don't want to go
into ketosis either
but it's the number one flaw of diets
that are created of nobody knowing
what's going on
because what happens is if you eat one
avocado on a keto diet you can't go into
ketosis
you can't i don't care what practitioner
you go to what diet expert you talk to
what trainer you talk to
what blood test you had looking for
ketones you can't you can't go into
ketosis
if you have one avocado in that diet
because the avocado is a lot of sugar
cheese is a lot of sugar you can't go
into ketosis eating cheese because it's
a lot of sugar
if you have a small little handful of
berries
you can't go into ketosis so if your
ketogenic diet allows you to have
berries and you'll notice that
the keto diet allows you to have all
this like berries
green apples cheese the keto diet the
ketogenic diets have
you know it's avocado it's nuts it's
seeds
years ago the keto diet
okay was a dangerous test
they removed everything with sugar out
of your diet
they removed the avocado which is sugar
they remove yeah sugar
avocados got a lot of sugar in it it's a
fruit it's a fatty fruit it's got a lot
of sugar in it
they removed the avocado they removed
all nuts and seeds peanut butter which
is sweet
peanut butter sweet there's nuts are
sweet
a walnut like they're they have a
sweetness to it because it's part sugar
right
they removed all the nuts all the seeds
and they put people literally on no
calories that that are derived from on
any level from any kind of carbohydrate
or sugar
and then they watched people die because
their brain went so void
of glucose so the ketogenic experiment
was an epic disaster that killed people
but they kept the name but they brought
in sugar is what they did
and even meat has sugar in it so what
they would do is they would boil
the sugar out of meat because meat has
sugar
right the animal's blood the animal's
blood
is sugar that's how it works
the blood inside an animal is
sugar your blood has
glucose in it it's sugar right
so they did was the ketogenic experiment
many years ago decades ago
what they did was they removed the sugar
out of the meat
they boiled the sugar out of the meat
right they didn't fry the meat and give
people fried meat
they didn't give people broiled
beef they boiled the sugar out of the
beef
and they only gave that to the people in
the experiment the ketogenic experiment
and what they found was when they took
out every
single molecule of sugar the person got
sick lethargic
lost their thinking process couldn't
function and either
died or went into a coma
or just could barely function
so they realized the ketosis experiment
was
a dangerous one a really really bad idea
so now the ketogenic diet we have today
there's carbs in it everywhere
there's carbs in it everywhere they also
notice with the old ketogenic diet when
they started bringing that in
to the mainstream there was already a
little bit of carb
in here wheat germ wheat germ was
allowed in the old ketogenic diet
you know you were allowed to do wheat
germ so you had a little bit of
carbohydrate in places right you had a
little bit
but people were getting heart attacks
and strokes they had no antioxidants
they had no
they had no leafy greens of course they
didn't even have iceberg lettuce anyway
they didn't have oranges they didn't
have things that keep you healthy and
strong
is what they didn't have so people would
get heart attacks people would get
stroked
people get heart disease real fast to
get those cholesterol problems off the
chart they get everything all wrong
and so then the ketogenic diet had to
make it like a transformation you guys
and they had to start putting sugar in
it so one of the first starts of the
sugar was green juices
so green juices entered the ketogenic
diet green juices
and green juices that had a little bit
of glucose in it
because some of the vegetables are like
green juices with beet in there that's
glucose
green juices with carrot in there green
juices and then they started putting in
a few berries and then they started
putting in the ketogenic diet
avocado more sugar you see
there's putting more sugar in your
ketogenic diet guess what
ketosis stops then they put a little
cheese in there oh high quality cheese
in your ketogenic diet
that's good for you right and they put
that in there and then they put butter
in there which is sugar
it's not just fat butters sugar
sweet it's like butter's sweet
it is right not candy sweet but it's
sweet
there's a sweetness to it okay and then
in these foods had nutrients in there
they had nuts then they put nuts and
seeds in the ketogenic diet which were
sugars
see and the green juice and the berries
and the avocado and the nuts and seeds
had nutrients in it which started
helping get
people get a little bit better and
they're and it's like they're
redesigning a screw-up and they're tr
they're like redesigning it it's
unbelievable what happens they're trying
to redesign the screw
is what's going on and in the end all
they did was make a healthier animal
protein diet
that's all a healthier animal protein
diet that happens to have
a few more antioxidants and some
nutrients here and there and you get a
little bit of berries if you want you
got a little bit of that
you get a little bit of you know you got
your avocado which is your healthy fat
because avocado is good for you
sure it's good for you but if you're
trying to heal from chronic illness it's
not your best friend but it's still good
for you
and then people were craving more sugar
and they're craving more sugar so they
had to offer something in there so then
they started throwing in all the
chocolate
butter fat with a little bit of that raw
sugar in there or honey and
raw sugar but people were craving more
sugar in the ketogenic diet so they had
to put more things in there so they had
to put
more green apples and more berries and
they had to put something in here
and now there's keto stuff that's like
keto donuts and cookies and cakes now
it's that's keto friendly that's keto
friendly it's got this many grams of
carbohydrates that's keto friendly
and that's how it works you see it's all
a game of
not knowing what the heck's going on
it's a game of scam it's a game of all
this
but everybody just walks into it like
you walk into it uneducated and
everybody walks into it uneducated
they're like
you just walk right into it like oh what
really that's keto friendly good let me
have that oh am i in ketosis nobody
knows
but what happens is you end up binging
and that happened all the time
because there was no sugar in their diet
because no one was eating avocados in
the original ketogenic diet they weren't
eating nuts and seeds and berries and
they weren't eating anything that they
were
binging they'd be like
they'd be keto for a week and binge
because they needed some kind of glucose
for their brain
you see how it works they needed glucose
now the keto diet is doing celery juice
so that's in the keto diet now
so celery juice is in the keto diet now
celery's got glucose in it still
you can't go into ketosis if you're
doing celery juice you can't go into
ketosis
and but they're doing celery juice it's
helping the real problem so then
someone's tagging
ketogenic diets really helping people
look this one person's getting better
this one person's just lost 50 pounds on
a ketogenic diet for the last six months
there's no other person and what's
happening is in the ketogenic diet
they're putting in things that help you
they're like old medical medium tools
they're putting in
celery juice and they're putting in some
juices
and they're putting in a little of this
and they're putting in a little
spirulina then they're putting in there
they're actually
they're actually putting in things then
they're putting in some spinach in your
keto diet now for the first time
then you're putting in cilantro in your
and then they're saying the ketogenic
diet is getting you better
not the things that get you better like
asparagus and cilantro
and spinach and berries and whatever and
they're not saying
in the celery juice they're not saying
those are what's getting you better
they're wrapping it up in this keto keto
bowl
that's keto that's getting it better so
this is really interesting stuff on how
things work you know
yeah let's make a salad we're still
doing that
very very interesting
when you think about it right so what
i'm going to do
is i'm going to
chop up the cucumber a little bit okay
so i like chopping up thin slices so i'm
going to do that right here you guys
and i'm chopping it up on an angle a
little bit so they don't roll off the
cutting board
so if you do a little one did one rolled
off how do you like that
so we're gonna do a little bit of i like
them kind of thin like this
don't like them real real thick
right okay
my trigeminal neuralgia is just about
gone
now healing my digestion thank you reena
i'm so happy for you seriously i really
am if you guys just get on here
medical medium mono cleanse
challenge next week i'm pumped up
actually pumped up janine
what about hc's g drops it's terrifying
hcg
the hcg
terrified popping some cucumber on here
not a fan at all probably one of the
most ridiculous things because what they
did is they just starved you to death
they just they put you on 500 calories a
day
got people exercising on 500 calories a
day you'd end up binging yourself to
death i've seen so many people just
binge themselves like crazy it stresses
out their adrenals stresses out their
liver
they're sicker than ever before from hcg
people get sicker than ever before
they go into it well whoa something's
changing something's happening
man and then they get
screwed over in the end because that's
how it works
the world of guessing games in the
industries and everybody involved
just really they're just playing people
in so many ways not everybody
but boy my god they just play people in
such an
incredible way okay we got that going
let's get some red onion here
so a little bit of red onion in the
salad do a little bit of a thin slice
right here okay
nice and thin don't want real thick
pieces
you know since i'm going to be eating
this is the way i like to do you can do
it the way you like to do it
right i'm going to cut these down the
center
a couple times pop that on here
make them a little salad let's put some
herbs because this is an
herb salad let's do that next let's get
some herbs on this
yeah we got some dill
look at that beautiful dill right here
you guys
reading comments as we're going along to
got some dill right here i don't know if
you guys like dill i really do
pop a little bit on here like that
there we go got some parsley
let's get a little bit of that on there
too
you love dill marissa
so i'm gonna do some parsley and i'm
finely chopping the parsley
so i'm just doing a little fine chop
here okay if you guys don't mind
weight issues
is derived from a stagnant sluggish
liver
just letting you know it's medical
medium information
friend of mine just told me that they
were listening to some kind of
opera somewhere and then a commercial
came on between the opera
and it was this doctor
saying how weight gain is caused by
an overburdened stagnant liver
to sell a product right first of all
medical medium publish this first
it's spirit of compassion's information
that our weight gain is derived from an
overburdened sluggish liver
and there's no scientific study that
discovered it prior
and there's a doctor sitting there
reading liver rescue book
not telling anybody and then saying in a
commercial to sell her product that it's
coming from weight loss is coming from
an overburdened liver
just like come on i think it's a
twilight zone personally
but i like the twilight zone
it's all right
makes life interest interesting you know
all right so we got this herb salad
we're moving on and i'm not
telling people that i'm the source so i
can just be like oh i'm the source it's
just that how are you going to find out
how to heal because
what what this person did is this person
also offered a bunch of things that
makes your problem worse
so it's like okay your liver is causing
your weight gain because it's stagnant
sluggish i'm doctor whatever
and then she went on like something like
that that this is the cause of it and
then here's the powder i want you to be
on here's the
protein powder to help your liver
whatever it is and you know
and it's like no you're not gonna help
anything with that you gotta learn how
to do it let's get some dolls in here
so what i like to do with the dolls is
i'm going to wet it i'm just going to
grab a couple tiny pieces of dolls this
is atlantic dolls right here
garlic is optional so i'm chopping up a
little dolls
careful chopping up dolls right it
slides on your board a little bit under
the knife
keep keep that in mind if you're going
to chop it up use it culinary wise
put a little dose on top of the salad if
you're sensitive to onion and garlic you
don't have to use onion and garlic you
can keep the red onion
out okay if you're
not sensitive and you like a little bit
of garlic we can use a little bit of
garlic i got a garlic bulb right here
let's grab one
one clove garlic and onion
kills viruses and bacteria
i'm just mincing this garlic really
finely on the board
you guys see you guys are looking
right a little bit of garlic on top of
the salad like this
now let's make a little bit of an orange
dressing
you can squeeze orange directly on top
how about that that's actually really
funny that's why i like being live
you don't know what's going to happen
orange could go flying towards your face
and smacking in the nose
i'm gonna squeeze orange right on here
that's what i'm gonna do put a little
lemon on this one too
right you can pop in some steamed potato
in this
you can pop in pop in some steamed
asparagus
brussels sprouts you can do a lot of
great stuff on here
happens is if you got bacteria
inside your gut right and viruses inside
your gut
it's not going to want to get killed off
it's not going to want to go
bacteria and viruses don't want to just
leave
they don't be like okay throw my hands
in the air and i'm going to go they've
been living in you for a long time
they've been grown by the classified
medical industry
grown in labs out of eggs and they've
been put out into the world
purposely so that you have all these
different pathogens inside of you
right that's what the the weaponized
biological warfare you know
all started before 1920. so they started
learning how the classified medical
industry started learning how to
propagate all these bugs and then they
were like whoa we could actually
create illness in people to feed the
medical industry for years to come and
the publicly the publicly known medical
research and science will never be aware
of it unless they discover it as time
goes on
and it was a really great incredible
scheme
of all time when you think about it
you've got the classified medical
industry
raising all these bugs behind
everybody's backs and then you've got
your publicly known medical industry
like the medical schools and all that
pumping out doctors right
and doing all that stuff in research and
they're two worlds
and they in the private industry the
classified industry released all the
bugs
in 1920 1930 1940 1950
all the herpes simplex ones and herpes
simplex twos right
all released you know so everybody
thought that
woodstock is why herpes simplex 1 went
around and herpes simplex 2 went around
it was because of woodstock in 1969
and it wasn't because of woodstock and
everybody having free sex in 1969
because that's what they blamed it on
that's not why simplex 1 and simplex 2
went around simplex 1 and simplex 2 were
released
before night right around 1920 early
before 1920 it was released and they
were
releasing it publicly with nobody
knowing it and they were putting it out
there so people would get simplex 1 and
simplex 2.
and then people would pass it around by
the time woodstock came around and
you know that age of free love came
around in the 1960s
everybody was passing around their
simplex ones and simplex twos but it
wasn't because really because of that
it was because it was put out there to
get passed around you see how it works
and so the classified industry put out
all these bugs all through the 1920s
and 1930s and 1940s and the epstein bars
and the cytomegaloviruses and the hhv-6
were all put out there
and then the publicly known medical
research science never knew why anybody
was sick they still don't know now but
they stumbled across the bugs along the
way and was like whoa
that's that's a virus we see under the
microscope meanwhile they're just
discovering what was already known by
the classified industry
put a little bit of lemon on here
right that's the salad right there
you can have this with so many things i
mean look how beautiful that is you guys
on facebook youtube what do you guys
think on tick tock you see that
right not bad
you guys see that mono eating cleanse
challenge
next week do not miss it
have a book ready so you can
learn from it you can pick one of the
mono
eating cleanses you can pick one of the
mono eating diets
in this book you can pick the banana one
you can pick the papaya one you can pick
the steamed potato one you can pick the
peas one
steamed peas you can pick one and it's
three days of getting your health back
together
i'm gonna be doing it i'm excited about
it right
51 off amazon.com us get
a book for it okay i did this whole
thing
where it's like you know what i want
everything for free is what i want
i don't want to close this thing off
sell tickets
anybody who wants to join has to pay
1500 2 000 and then we do this and make
a big deal about i don't want to make a
big deal about it
i just want to be having some fun talk
about the power of the model eating
cleanse
right and and everybody hop on board
let's do let's get healthy
how fun is that okay guys heading off to
ig
next in a few minutes and gonna make
another salad gonna talk about some cool
stuff going to have some fun
adele says we are so lucky so lucky to
have you guys here
add some egg to the salad just kidding
just kidding that was really funny on
tic-tac he had me go in there
you had me going and then i saw at the
end of the comment
just kidding yeah
looks good right you guys on on tick
tock
fantastic thank you lorraine right
robinson right lemon balm love
you am i gonna see you guys on uh ig
right and i'm gonna turn clubhouse and
tick tock back on too elizabeth good to
see you
selena good to see you so you guys
deborah good to see you
i'm gonna go on ig in a couple minutes i
hope i hope you guys come with me i'm
excited alright
love you guys take care