cultivated blueberry wild blueberry
every time I see a cultivated
blueberry every time I see it in the
store or I see somebody using it I feel
bad there's just something that comes
over me because it's weak I support it I
like blueberries of all kinds but it's
not the same blueberry it's not that
adaptogenic power it's not that high
antioxidant rate it's not any of that
the anthocyans are different it's not
not the same thing so I'll give you
little differences here a wild food can
survive on its own through drought
through floods through freezing Tundra
cold the cultivated blueberry was a
blueberry that wasn't just growing in
the wild so it's not like hey you know
these blueberries have been around for
thousands of years not true the
cultivated blueberry was a spinoff a
spin-off a cultivated spin-off from its
cousins the wild blueberry big
difference with the wild blueberry
versus the cultivated blueberry what
happens if a disease hits a crop if a
disease hits a crop the crop can get
annihilated and we're going to have
disease hitting crops in the future
because of all the GMO crops are not
going to be able to be strong enough
they're not going to be able to sustain
a massive blow and that will be coming
in the future with crops the difference
with what I'm saying is like a
cultivated crop like say the cultivated
blueberry if a fungus comes and
eventually becomes strong enough and
hits a sensitivity in the crop and takes
out an entire cultivated blueberry crop
worldwide which it can it can do that
for virtually any crop by the way if it
does this the whole crop goes the
difference with wild blueberries is
there are hundreds and hundreds and
hundreds of different strains of wild
blueberry plants in the same crop in the
same like if you look at a wild the
Blueberry Field this is important to
know there are hundreds of different
Geniuses I like just saying it that way
there are hundreds of different
varieties hundreds of different strains
they all look the same almost it's all
wild blueberries it's all sitting in the
field the difference is that there are
different plants even though it's the
same plant all within that field that
means that if disease comes to the wild
blueberry crop it may only take out one
or two species of plant amongst the
entire field of wild blueberries if a
disease comes to a cultivated crop it'll
wipe the entire cultivated crop out
that's how it works check it out W
blueberry a whole case $20 off for a
whole case if you buy a case of the W
blueberry juice it's $20 off it's a case
of 12 use code wild2 link is description
link is in the profile I endorse W mins
because it's the best stuff there
is