[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William the
medical Medium you're listening to the
medical medium radio show where each
week we talk about the most advanced
health information out there it's
important to know that because it's
decades ahead of what's out there now
and anywhere in alternative medicine
conventional medicine and chronic
illness in chronic illness and it's
important to know because you can work
on healing and not have to wait 10 20 30
years for answers we're talking about
Liver Rescue but we're talking about
fatty liver which is actually in the
liver rescue book this is really
important fatty liver is a big deal and
I want to cover it cover it as if you
don't think you have fatty liver think
again because there's pre pre pre fatty
liver basically fat buildup in the liver
over time before could even be diagnosed
so it's really important to know how it
works with fatty liver so that's where
we're really going going into it I mean
who has 5 10 years for answers 15 years
for answers to wait I mean to wait and
wait and wait because you you know you
lose time and that's the whole thing
with chronic illness people lose time I
mean there's so many people that were I
mean diagnosed or not diagnosed with so
many different conditions with
neurological problems symptoms all kinds
of different symptoms Galore everything
different diagnoses and they you know
they had to go from Doctor to doctor to
doctor including with lime and multiple
sclerosis and getting diagnosed with
this and that and Hashimoto and
everything and all they needed was
answers and and I've given answers to
people to get them free to escape that
whole trap and that marry go round of of
having to go to everywhere doctor to
doctor and going through all these
different treatments and everything else
there are ways of actually healing there
are ways of getting out of that trap and
there are ways of getting out of mystery
illness there really really is tens of
thousands and now hundreds of thousands
and even close to Millions now at this
point are getting answers like with the
celery juice turning their lives around
and with other things that we brought
here so the whole point is look there's
so much to learn and with fatty liver we
got a lot to learn and it's all about
Liver Rescue it's in Liver Rescue so if
you don't have the Liver Rescue book um
you know one thing just you know
whatever you do the book is so big and
there's so much information in it that
you just you can't get it from the radio
show it's just not going to happen I
could do a string of radio shows and
it's not going to happen so if you can't
afford a book for whatever it is $15 $20
or whatever it is go go to the library
and uh take out the book there or
whatever you need to do to get one get
one in your hands so you can work on
healing it's so important so fatty liver
is where we are that's where we're going
so let's start let's figure it out so
you know as we go through life as we go
through life we eat to survive and we
have we run into like challenging
circumstances
any this happens in life you know it's
it's how it works and we're under stress
we're under pressure and it can hold us
back from eating healthier foods I mean
come on right you know that you know
that it can hold us back I mean from
eating healthier foods absolutely we're
trying to live we're living to survive
we end up eating to survive it's not
quite not everybody has the resources
not everybody can sit on a boat all
summer
long you know what I mean can sit on a a
yacht all summer long and get meals made
for them it's not everybody can do that
you know you know these cute little
meals made for them and the perfect lean
fish and protein and little salads and
fruit salads and and all these other
things and you know and you're just like
you not everybody can live like that
where they're eating healthier choices
where they're they're able to say oh no
hold off the gluten give me a real tasty
dish with no gluten and no whatever in
it and then there's some Chef kill
killing themselves literally killing
themselves trying to make all this
flavor happen and put all this this you
know healthier food together and
everything here's a little here's a
little quinoa couscous and a little this
and put a little this on who has that I
mean I mean usually we you know yeah how
do you live like that it's not easy it's
not easy not everybody has that those
resources to go into the health food
stores either I noticed that and
actually just buy all the fresh produce
they can possibly buy and all the
whatever the leanest cuts of meat if you
like animal protein and if you're in and
if you're and if you're vegan or plant-
paste all the whatever it is that you
want and get avocados and all the other
things and all the different fruits and
vegetables and it's it's amazing how
it's not so easy and if we're treading
or back treading or whatever is
backpedaling through life and we got all
these jobs and responsibilities and got
bills and got this and that and not much
money or whatever it is that's going on
and then chronic illness hits and
chronic illness it's sick you're just
trying to push through the day and
there's nothing really easy about it and
so what can happen is you end up eating
a donut you end up eating a donut and
maybe when life was good for some I've
had people tell me hey life was the best
ever when I was able to eat donuts and I
was doing good and I was working a
zillion hours and I could just scoff
down a whole crab load of donuts and be
back off to work it was no big deal
that's the good old days you know what I
mean so maybe it's that maybe it's the
opposite for somebody but you end up you
know like when life's ult and everything
you can end up eating a donut because
you may be on the Run trying to keep up
the demanding
schedule and and all of that and you
might look you might be out of time and
can't find another option in the moment
or hey I'll have that slice of pizza
someone may decide easily because it's
easy get a slice of pizza and they're
there in the moment hey a bagel with
cream cheese a buttered croissant ice
cream you know maybe as an after dinner
treat chicken parmesan right chicken
parmesan at some kind of restaurant I
don't know a hot dog at a stand on a
street or you know not even a stand I
mean what about a food truck the food
trucks that are like making all these
kind of Abominations gastric
Abominations that probably taste amazing
for me right you got the food trucks
it's unbelievable and so you know what
about some barbecued ribs cuz you're you
know your friend is paying for it so you
end up getting some barbecued ribs and
uh buffalo chicken wings how about that
maybe some shrimp fried rice this is
making me laugh by the way a piece of
chocolate cake or maybe a fried egg or
two or a slice of bacon a little here
and a little there these are foods that
get us by when life is harder and goes
faster than we can keep up with I mean
am I right or am I wrong I don't know
maybe I'm wrong maybe I got it all
wrong so whether we know it or not we
eat like this to get by we eat like this
to survive
sometimes we eat like this for happiness
of course too we're up against all the
world it's impossible we get all wound
up we get emotional it's completely
understandable I mean if we eat foods to
comfort ourselves I mean yeah like we do
and you know we we want flavors to
satisfi our satisfy our cravings and
even get a sense of companionship
absolutely absolutely but if we were
more conscious about food you know we
had a little less going on maybe we
would take care of ourselves I
understand I do and and what if we're
fortunate what if somebody's fortunate
and they have they have the resources to
pursue all kinds of other ways of eating
and you know they can look at a trendy
diet right they can get into a trendy
diet that seems incredibly healthy
they'll go less often on a croissant or
pizza they'll go less less often on
pizza and they'll look for leaner cuts
of meat and and cut out all grains and
processed foods like all the trendy
diets want you to do right they all want
you to do that go with leaner cuts of
meat bring in lots of vegetables and
make sure and don't eat any fruit don't
eat any fruit and and you know avoid all
fruit whatever you do that's what they
do right and it's like cut out all
carbohydrates maybe we can do that one
of those trendy diets and isn't that the
answer isn't that the answer to do one
of those trendy diets you guys me leaner
cuts and meat cut out all the pro
processed foods right
you know clean things up stay away from
the grains the whole bit bring in some
bone broth right well that's cool could
go to yoga afterwards after you know
what I mean get some bone broth in you
you know the whole bit and make sure
we're doing some chicken chicken on a
salad or something like that we're
trying to follow these cool trendy diets
we'll do an egg a hard-boiled egg in our
salad and maybe that's better than all
the processed foods and having a slice
of pizza and doing this and that and
maybe it is kind of better but it is is
it the answer not as much as you would
think trust me on that not as much as
you would think it's the answer when it
comes to avoiding one thing and I'm
telling you right now when it comes to
avoiding one thing and it's called fatty
liver and if you don't believe me you'll
get one later on if you don't think
you're going to get one now you know the
funny thing is when you're young you're
just indestructible it's just like
you're indestructible you know when
you're young it's like basically when
you're young it's just like hey follow a
trendy diet if you got a stuff you nose
and you're starting to get a little bit
of bloat maybe your digestion is nothing
you know not doing that good and and you
just when you're younger it's like who
cares you can still go out hiking you
can still go go you know swim in the
ocean or go to the beach you could still
do whatever and hey I'm on this low carb
low carb no carb trendy diet right now
hey I'm on a keto diet hey I'm on this
diet whatever I'm doing lean cuts of
meat and it's kind of an easy fix or
whatever it is when you're young it's
indestructible when I'm tell you when
you feel indestructible but when you get
older and I'm not talking about people
who are young with chronic illness
that's a different story talking about
people that're really not dealing with
too much when you get older
and you get into your late 30s and that
liver is picking up and that liver is
getting fat in there and nobody knows
about it and it could be all the trendy
diets you want or ever thought were fine
and good and you start getting older and
all of a sudden that liver starts
backing up and it starts throwing
symptoms and then you're doing you're at
the hormone doctor and nobody knows
what's wrong and then viruses are
starting to pick up and your thyroid
starts to go boink because of Epstein
bar and you're just like and you're 42
years old and you start breaking out
some kind of weird funky rash and all of
a sudden something else is happened and
the liver is getting fatty and nobody
knows about it and then it's begin it's
getting fattier and fattier with no
diagnosis and just going through life
then you're getting hot flashes then
you're getting this then you're getting
that you hear what I'm talking about no
no one talks about that no one talks
about that or anything like that it's
amazing the the information is so
Advanced what happens in like with Liver
Rescue and all the rest of the medical
medium series that I can't even talk to
doctors too often because it's almost
like I have to say okay just give me a
stupid shot real quick give me a stupid
shot and I'm not talking about doctors
at like you know that are lit literally
like it's just trying to help people I'm
talking about all the trend the trendy
guys out there now that are just like
you know trying to trying to build a
platform on Pro get rid of the processed
foods and do this and bring in that and
then they end up stealing from the
alternative Community that's already
been doing it for many years and years
and years it's crazy and just give me a
stupid shot it's like they're like no no
you don't do you don't do uh you're
going to get diabetes if you bringing
any fruit y give me another stupid shot
right there it's like don't you you're
getting get diabetes if you bring in too
much fruit too much sugar not good sugar
is bad for the liver too bad for the
liver oh yeah no don't be doing potato
it's the worst food ever oh wait a
minute got lectin oh it's got this oh
wait a minute don't do this don't bring
that in either no you should be on fats
and lots of fats and then you should
have okay yeah you should have greens
and green juices yeah when did you when
did that Dawn on you the green juice
part and the greens what part of your
career did that Dawn on you was it four
years ago only how about how about that
Dawning on you 40 years ago that's what
it should be and it's like and what
happens is you just you know when you
talk to the trend setters out there that
want you on high fat high protein diets
and they just of course they want you
you cleaning up your diet and everything
else you talk to them it's almost like
oh my God they don't know anything about
the liver know nothing about how the
Body Works they don't even know
understand Epstein bar until the
information we put out there really they
knew about Epstein bar but they didn't
know what it did nobody knew nothing and
the information is saving people's lives
right now from the medical medium is
saving people's lives across the board
millions of people actually on the
planet right now are getting help from
that so but when it comes down to like
understanding just the basics of how the
blood works and how if you fill it with
fat how bad it can really be and how you
get that pre fatty liver over time and
then you age quicker it's all cute all
fine and dandy when you're 28 years old
all cute and all fine when you're 21
years old it's just fine
oh totally fine go get sushi go out and
get sushi go do this have a drink just
oh yeah have fun go you know slice of
pizza on the weekends totally fine but
get back on your no carb diet just all
catches up it's all cute when you're 31
years old and you're 23 years old
whether it's a guy or girl whatever it
is but I'm telling you right now the
liver doesn't like it unless you take
care of yourself and learn how to take
care of yourself so you don't end up
getting a chronic illness so you can
actually help yourself and anybody who
has a chronic illness you can help your
liver now and really do something about
it and really turn it around it's
amazing how it works it's
amazing they don't know in the medical
field they don't know in alternative
medicine yet they don't know in
conventional medicine yet how to
forewarn somebody to really help take
care of themselves how to help somebody
so they don't get themselves in trouble
so they could really heal or actually
not get sick when they're chronically
ill to heal and when they're not
chronically ill yet chronically ill yet
how to heal it's amazing how the
industry works it's incredible and
you'll find those Trend Setters all
they're doing is selling crap just
selling Gobles and gobbles and gobbles
and gobbles of supplements they send
this trend setters gobbles us up build
your platform hang your head on a stupid
idea and sell millions of dollars in
supplements and you know what maybe
that's fine then maybe that's fine maybe
that's fine you know what I mean maybe
it's fine maybe it's fine they're making
$4 million a month and they're just
selling you crap supplements maybe
that's fine and there's you know selling
you on some some camany idea and
everything and they're just all about
high fat diets and all about no carbs
and stay away from fruit and they're
selling you supplements and everything
else maybe that's fine they're selling
you collagen they're selling it this
they're selling you anti-lectin stuff
they're selling you whatever it is they
selling whatever it is they're selling
maybe that's just fine and
dandy maybe it
is but I'll tell you right now I mean I
don't think it's that fine I'll tell you
right now because isn't it about getting
someone better learning the truth
understanding the truth and getting them
better isn't it about really proactively
making sure someone doesn't get sick
because it's so awful when someone gets
sick and they stay sick and their life
goes they're I mean I've seen people
lose things I've seen people lose
everything from being
sick
everything you there's a lot of homeless
people out there you don't think a whole
bunch of them weren't sick it's
unbelievable of how it works and so the
compassion has to be there and it has to
be there and it has to stop any chronic
illness and it has the information has
to be there someone said what's the
point of your books I said what do you
mean what's the point of the
books what do you mean the point is to
make sure that you can protect your
family protect your children make sure
you have the answer so when you do get
sick neurologically or anything I don't
care what it is you can actually do
something about it just like the celery
juice that nobody knew about no one knew
about until we brought it to town and
then it gets it gets it gets destroyed
out there it gets destroyed out there
cuz people are just they all of a sudden
you know like don't do this do this do
this whatever all these people like
these just making up stuff meanwhile
here's where it comes from here's what
you do with the celery juice and it gets
rid of fatty liver cuz what happens is
once your liver starts getting
fatty everything else starts going down
the drain slowly you age your skin a
ages everything ages along the way and
you just you all of a sudden your liver
just says hey hey ho we're done we're
done I can't really protect you so much
anymore so all those toxins are going to
just age your skin really quick you're
going to stretch it out it's not going
to bounce back you're going to have all
this acne keep on coming and going
you're going to have all this other
stuff keep on going these skin problems
it's not even just that you're going to
have all these heart stuff later on down
the road you know the thing is with the
younger crowd they don't think they're
ever going to be 60 years old they don't
think they're going to be 60 years old
they don't I've talked to people they
don't they don't believe it they don't
believe it they don't believe they're
ever going to be
60 is the craziest thing they don't
believe they're going to be 40 you know
back many many years ago a few decades
ago when I was doing this cuz I was
doing it and the information was just as
advanced as it is now in fact it's the
same information how do you like them
apples and all the books the medic
medium series information I was giving
30 years ago that people say is Advanced
even people say the doctors say And
scientists even say that this is where
where it's going in medicine as far as
this is the most advanced information
out there in chronic health I knew that
information 30 years ago cuz it all came
from the same Source but I remember
talking to younger people back 30 years
ago people did think they were going to
be 60 years old someday they did think
they were going to be
55 they did think they were going to be
64 now the the younger crowd they don't
think they're going to be 60 it's
unbelievable and and that's not good
because it makes you not want to really
take care of yourself to actually look
out so that's just one aspect of it but
here's how the liver Works let's go into
this and let's start let's start like
chopping into this a little bit I hope
everybody's having a good a good time
anyway so far okay so bear with me bear
with me the one thing about Liver Rescue
the one thing about this book The one
thing about these radio shows that are
based on Liver Rescue if you don't have
a copy you really should get one you
really should get
one I someone said to me the other day
you just want to sell books oh yeah I
just want to sell books sure that'll
that'll do me real real good too it's
it'll do everybody else a lot of good
for
sure but it it it's not what people
think it's not all roses and authors
know that it's not all roses it's not
how it works if you can't afford a book
whatever the download is or whatever the
print print is I don't know what the
download is 13 14 15 bucks or the print
or whatever it is you can't afford one
to go to the library and get
one what happens is that that um that
when it comes down to blood and your
blood the more fat inside the blood
constantly on an everyday basis a
barrage of fat that we enter into our
bloodstream will create that pre- pre
fatty liver that won't be diagnosed it
will create that condition now a lot of
you are probably who cares about fatty
liver maybe you didn't even want to
listen to the show because hey I don't
have fatty liver who cares who even
gives a crap who cares I mean I I know
that because because when you talk to
people about fatty liver they're like oh
that's not me I don't have any fatty
liver yeah sure sure because you know
what happens is that the majority of the
country has a fatty liver it's in
different stages that's the whole point
and why is a fatty liver even B bad why
is the pre fatty liver even bad it's bad
because other symptoms and conditions
you have are based upon that fatty
liver I mean literally other symptoms
easily because chronic illness which is
are like viruses and sign of our liver
they Prosper they proliferate they grow
they do their thing because you can have
a because of the fatty liver and the
high foot and the high fat in the
bloodstream and that that that's how it
works just basic CFS that me CFS chronic
fatigue
syndrome that right there if you if
you're bombarding yourself with fats all
these years and you end up developing
Epstein bar related chronic fatigue
syndrome because that's what it all is
you end up you you end up developing
that and then what happens your liver's
sluggish it's doggish totally sluggish
not functioning
good and and it's get it's it's preatty
and it's all in the way of healing from
even chronic fatigue syndrome do you see
how this works Hashim modus thyroiditis
which is Epstein bar related where the
Epstein bar virus drills itself into the
thyroid and gives people gives gives
people
hypothyroidism that virus starts out in
the liver liver gets sluggish gets fatty
gets pre fatty gets
doggish and then what happens it it the
virus you know proliferates it grows it
moves forward it prospers it lives a
very good life it drills into other
glands such as the thyroid and so forth
I what about multiple sclerosis I'm just
giving you these basic ones I there so
there's hundreds ones I could ramble off
what about multiple sceris Ms same thing
all starts with a virus in the liver and
the virus gets doggish the immune system
in the in in the liver can't fight off
the virus easy and the liver gets
sluggish stagnant doggish the whole bit
and what happens is the virus Prosper
does its thing creates a whole bunch of
neurotoxins gives rings off a whole
bunch of different diagnoses including
multiple sclerosis including Lyme
disease the hope it everybody that's
ever had a diagnosis of lime has a liver
condition I kid you not every single
person who's ever had the diagnosis of
lime whether they had lime not had lime
or whatever it is has a has a liver
that's in trouble that needs
help and when the liver starts getting
better and you start taking care of it
then you can get anything better
anything and everything better how do
you like that I'm going to say it again
when the liver gets taken care of when
it's
nurtured when it's brought back to
health even when you don't know it's the
problem or something's going on inside
there in the whole bit and it's being
brought back to health when the liver is
cared for and coddled and loved and
treated right any kind of illness is
possible healing
anything and it's important to know that
it's important to know
that it's about you healing and it's
about you getting better it's been my
mission since I was young and the only
reason why I do the books is so it can
spread out far and wide and get into
somebody's hands and to get in
somebody's
hands someone said to me the other day
you're so popular you're the most your
most popular person in health you
started the celery juice Trend which is
worldwide and Global your books sell
everywhere all over the country all over
the world all these things why don't you
sell something why don't you sell
something you could sell something and
make hundreds of millions of dollars I
go because you know what that has
nothing nothing to do that you know sell
something anything whatever whether it's
supplements or this or that it has
nothing to do with somebody really
getting better it's about getting the
information in their hands and and not
to be derailed by derailed by greed and
other things because I want to sleep at
night knowing you're getting what you
need in your hands so let's dig into it
let's take this serious cuz if you take
it as serious as I do as far as the love
I have for everybody and making sure
that you get what you need and the
information and it's there for you it's
there for you and don't be confused or
tricked by someone that says oh I did
the medical medium protocol it didn't
help me there is no medical medium
protocol the the books are filled with
classic information that's Timeless that
is there for someone if they read
through the books will find what they
need for themselves because not
everybody's the same everybody's
different and the books are geared that
way to help every single person that has
a different condition in a different
problem in the way and the stage they're
in it's not just oh I tried that for 2
weeks tried what for 2 weeks I never
just put out some like some protocol
protocol where you do this for two weeks
and that's what you do and all
everything gets better I've never done
that ever don't get confused by the by
by the Clones which are the trolls that
do those things or people that they're
just they just if they haven't done
anything they maybe tried celery juice
for a month and that's it but they're
eating all this other crazy stuff cuz
they're on 10 different trendy diets or
they have a whole another different
practitioner thing going on that's
having them try something different or
whatever it is don't get derailed by
that cuz you're going to be robbed of
the answers you make sure you soak
yourself into study in these books and
the radio shows are to give you glimpses
of what's inside these books so you can
have a window into healing and getting
to where you need to be and there are
millions of people globally who are
doing things and healing thousands and
thousands and hundreds of thousands in
the US getting rid of the worst skin
conditions every day they're walking
getting out of whale chairs because
they're doing the right things they're
finding the answers you got to apply
yourself and you can't get confused by
someone who hasn't applied themselves
that actually have a loud voice for some
reason on social media and say I tried
that for a week and it didn't work
meanwhile they're doing somebody's
trendy high fat
diet and they're making their liver sick
so always keep that in mind so what can
I do for you what can I do for you here
we go let's dig into it deep because
it's all about what can I do for you
right now so here's the deal
blood thickness is the deal breaker
that's the deal blood thickness is the
deal breaker that's the liver's deal
breaker that's the liver's deal breaker
baby it's the blood
thickness it breaks the
liver that's what it does really
important to know you know what doctors
are supposed to say when you go into
when you go into um the doctor's office
you know what they're supposed to say
let me give you a window okay this is
the window so somebody goes into the
doctor's office all right and and and
Physicians need they need a simple blood
test in their possession it would
literally turn medicine around it
doesn't exist but it would be a miracle
if it did a miracle they need a blood
fat tester that's what they need to
determine blood fat
levels you you just you know how like
when you you know you're doing the blood
sugar diabetics they need the you know
you prick the finger literally you just
need you don't even need it to be like
that it could be literally something you
stick under your armpit for a minute to
determine your blood fat
ratio and this is different this isn't
your fat your your your fat ratio like
if you hop on a scale this is blood fat
so it would measure it would measure
okay your blood fat levels just like
diabetics when they they measure their
blood glucose Coast
levels and this is what it's supposed to
be when you get a physical exam so the
doctor can instantly say whoa what was
your last
meal so yeah what was your last meal
your blood fat is off the charts what's
going on here at this is at this rate
you're going to develop a fatty liver
gout or heart disease or kidney disease
or kidney failure for all that high
fat even if it's healthy diets or trendy
diets that are healthy that are high fat
they're not even supposed to be even
they're just supposed to be like whoo
what's in your
blood listen what did you eat last night
by the way and the person would say well
I ate at a restaurant last night and I
ordered chicken with broccoli I thought
it was a pretty healthy dish chicken
with broccoli okay well what was
yesterday's lunch that was yesterday's
dinner what was yesterday's lunch the
doctor should say oh I had a turkey club
on a gluten-free bread on gluten-free
bread and I really didn't eat much of
the bread I just kind of ate the turkey
club little bit of cheese and turkey or
whatever I thought that was good lots of
protein right lots of protein okay well
what was your yesterday's breakfast the
doctor should ask well let's see I had
two eggs I had a slice of healthy bacon
it was free range or it was you know
farm raised and it was it was a healthy
bacon and um and I skipped the toast
because I'm you know decided to be low
carb have a low carb free
morning the doctor should should lean
forward and say that's great you skip
the toast what we really need to be
concerned about though is how much fat
is in your
diet a simple blood test I just did for
you is showing high fat in your
bloodstream and if it's been high fat
for a very long time because this has
been your diet and even even worse diet
even before you're eating kind of
healthy then we're in trouble so
recapping all the meals indicates that
it's always consistently high and you
know what you're
doing the doctor should say you're
starving your liver of oxygen you're
setting the stage for cancer you're
setting the stage for illness and
disease yes you're setting the stage for
cancer even on a healthy high fat High
trendy diet that's right that's right
you don't have to eat wheat of course
good job doctor should say you don't
have to have
wheat exactly exactly but maybe you
should bring in a little bit more leafy
greens a little bit more fruit and the
person might say well I'm not on any
fruit I'm I can't eat any fruit I'm I'm
not allowed to have fruit I don't want
to get diabetes I don't want
fruit and you should actually doctor
should say you should even try some
healthy carbohydrates clean
ones and some more extra
vegetables that's how the medical world
should work on planet Earth planet Earth
is
backwards it's backwards when it comes
down to the health of the human race it
always has been don't get me wrong
there's life-saving technology and
life-saving Medicine absolutely you
better believe it but I'm talking about
chronic illness whole different
thing whole different
thing okay big difference it's like lamb
and chicken big
difference I'm just straight I'm just
saying it straight so you know the whole
thing
is the doctor should have the concern
that it shouldn't be about the sugar and
the carbs it should be about the fat and
it shouldn't be about fruit being
eliminated you don't want the fruit
eliminated I mean that should be a
concern you don't want fruit eliminated
sadly blaming sugar as the cause of even
a fatty liver is a huge mistake in the
health industry right
now this mistake exists because sugar is
never eaten on its own it's always eaten
with fat once again causing problems
it's not the sugar that's the
problem see fat and sugar are always
eaten together so then all the so-called
experts are like get rid of the sugar
and they see improvements temporarily in
a lot of people but they're still
getting fatty liver and they're going to
still get sick down the road and they're
still going to get chronic illness down
the road even on the most trendiest nice
clean
diets because the problem was sugar and
fat together and it really hurts the
liver that's what it really is and it's
not the sugar part it's the fat part
that's the irony but the sugar gets the
blame unbelievable if this is too
mind-blowing for you listen to the show
again listen to it again until a little
voice of reason pops up
somewhere and says you know what you're
right how why would you fill your blood
blood with fat Non-Stop and starve your
blood of
oxygen and and yeah and fatten up the
liver so it becomes more dysfunctional
and Miss more dysfunction over time why
would you do that when fat actually in
the bloodstream starves the bloodstream
of oxygen in the organs of oxygen and
the daily basis every day of your life
making you age and then with all that
getting pathogens like bacteria strep E
coli that's just the name a couple and
if you're into lime bacteria is whatever
then sure lime bacteria will Thrive
first of all Lyme disease is viral just
read my book medical medium learn the
truth and before you throw rotten Tom
Tomatoes at me and and and try and to
and try to light light my apartment on
fire make sure you read the book so you
know the truth about lime anything can
prosper in the BL blood that's pathogen
pathogenic viruses bacteria when the
blood fat is high anything it's not just
about stupid fatty liver and I say
stupid fatty liver because yeah like
fatty liver you guys like oh who's got a
fatty liver who's got a fatty liver
isn't that for older people they finally
get diagnosed with a fatty liver oh
that's not me no no no it's way bigger
than that it's way bigger than that and
the fact is we do eat sugar with fat all
the time happens all the
time so when you think about it it's
always it's like it's an unhealthy fat
too sometimes in many in many different
situations no one's sitting around
eating gobs of Standalone sugar they're
mixing it in coffee and cream they're
having it in cakes and cookies and
pastries along with fat in every last
one of those it's in barbecue sauce
which goes on pulled pork which is fat
that's sugar and fat it's eaten As a
treat such as candy cane a candy cane
after a high-fat Festival meal not
acknowledging that sugar is always
consumed with fat is a prime example of
both the conventional medical and
Alternative Health Industries operating
with blinders on basically the AL
alternative industry and the
conventional industry is
blind they have tunnel vision that only
allows sugar into view but not fat which
is protein and that's the problem and
when a theory is seen from that limited
perspective it's easily becoming law and
you'll see it on all the doctor shows
you'll see it on all the whatever you'll
see it on all the channels and the
networks it's all about oh carbs and get
rid of your sugar oh drop all that
you'll see it it's like a virus
itself and just protein protein no
they're not saying it's fat fat
protein's fat and just bringing and
bringing and I'm not saying you have to
live in a box and not ever have if
you're into animal protein not ever have
some animal protein if you're into if
you're into if you're vegan or something
in in plant-based not having avocado
it's not about that it's about the fact
of how many years and especially if
you're chronically ill if you want to
get better you got to stop the fats for
sure you got to lower the fats maybe
even stop them completely shut them down
and learn how to eat without it I give
the answers in all the books how to eat
fat free I do I do and maybe it's about
that if you're chronic Le because I've
seen it save lives and turn around
people's lives that never could heal
from any kind of lime never could heal
from any kind of Ms never could heal
from anything serious chronic fatigue
syndrome for so many years never could
heal from anything and they got fat free
they got fat free doing lots of leafy
greens lots of celery juice lots of
fruit they brought it in and it turned
their lives around and they got better
and and they started building muscle and
they got out of they got out of the bed
that's right that's right no other diet
could have done it and didn't do it no
other diet but I get it the trendy diets
are the people that are living their
life feeling relatively kind of good
just got a little weight on them they
take out the processed foods knock out
all that get on some trendy exercise
program and they think they struck gold
Eureka no no no no no it doesn't work
like that it doesn't
so so sugar with fat you guys is the
problem and when it's healthier sugar
with healthier fat it's less of a
problem but still a
problem and so the fats have to lower or
get reduced so they're not saturating
the bloodstream you have fats once a day
if you're into you know some animal
protein eat animal protein once every
other day and learn how to eat more
sweet potatoes learn how to eat more you
know bring in more leafy greens
cucumbers red bell pepper sweet potato
yes all of those things learn how to
bring in other Foods you know bring in
yeah bring in bring in you can bring in
a whole bunch of bringing even bring in
avocado avocado is lower fat believe it
or not so one thing the vegans and the
the vegans have is that when they do
high fat like the avocado it's still
lower than than animal protein fat which
which makes it so they could eat a
little bit more often unless they're
really struggling with an illness then
just fat free is
important but when you're animal protein
you bring the animal proteins down hey
if you're vegan you're vegan and plant-
based you bring all those nuts and seeds
down you bring those oils down too you
bring all that down too you have to you
have to when you get rid of you can get
the liver cleaned
up and sure you can have some fats once
in a while and you can use it under the
GU of protein people are in like denial
they think protein has no fat in it it's
unbelievable they think protein has no
fat in it they think protein's protein
there's no fat in it it's not
true I mean it's just it's it's
unbelievable seen a commercial where
this little snack pack it's got pieces
of ham pieces of cheese and and and some
almonds in the snack pack you rip it
open and what did they say they just
called it a protein pack are you kidding
me it was a fat pack it was a fat pack
an overt fat pack I've never seen
anything like it cheese straight fat
plus sugar inside of it which is the
lactose which is a diabetic
Nightmare and and it illness and disease
causing nightmare because cheese feeds
every virus Under the Sun every virus
there is that causes all the different
autoimmune diseases every single lupus
every single whatever every single skin
condition every single condition you
name it connected to connective tissue
disease everything it causes and That
Snack Pack had pieces of
ham or pieces of turkey you had an
option it had some almonds in one little
container a three containers like a
three pack or four pack I had some
cheese it had some cheese squares turkey
squares and and some almonds and it was
called a protein pack and that's how the
brainwashing occurs it's unbelievable
that was a fat pack keep your blood fat
nice and thick stay off of fruits though
because you don't want to get diabetes
stay off of the very thing it has
antioxidants that bring blood to the
bloodstream how do you like that that
actually keep
that actually help Drive oxygen that you
inhaled in your
lungs and when we breathe oxygen and
it's filled the pollutants every single
day like it is those antioxidants and a
piece of fruit help to block those
pollutant so the oxygen gets clean it's
clean and it goes into the bloodstream
clean that little fat pack the person
had on the TV commercial with the little
squares of turkey and the little squares
of cheese and and and the almonds that
fat pack does nothing for for that you
you you all that does is cause oxygen to
diminish in your in your in your body
and stay dirty and keep the blood dirty
and keep the blood dehydrated which is
the next point if your blood Fat's too
high if it's too high you got the least
amount of oxygen in there but you got Le
you got the least amount of water it
pushes water out in a bad way it makes
you
dehydrated and that gives you an
illusion of losing weight when people go
on these high-fat diets they actually
don't know these high protein high fat
diets no carbs and they're not doing any
fresh
fruit with with they're getting
dehydrated and they're like whoa I'm
actually losing weight really quick out
of nowhere no you're not losing fat
really quick out of nowhere you're
losing water weight and you end up
getting dehydrated it's a whole another
thing the higher the fat is in the
bloodstream on a daily basis the less
water in there and the liver needs water
to cleanse it it needs oxygen to keep it
alive because the bloodstream driving
straight into your your liver is low in
oxygen naturally it has very little
oxygen in it and it's filled with
poisons toxins and then really good
nutrients going into that bloodstream
and it's going in the liver and the
liver has to sort it all out and when
the liver has to sort it all out with a
big pile of fat in the bloodstream thick
blood fill the fat going into that liver
and it has to store it out to try to get
nutrients out to find try to find
Precious Precious valuable glucose
somewhere to keep it alive so the liver
can keep alive so the liver can send
that glucose right up to the heart and
then up to the brain because guess what
your brain runs on sugar it doesn't run
on
fat your brain has traces the tiniest
traces of omegas in there and guess what
you can get those from a pack of
blackberries the brain is made out of
sugar glucose glycogen it shrinks on
people because of years and years and
years of having fat in the
bloodstream and it's a brain shrinker it
shrinks the
brain high fat high protein no matter
what it is whether it's a vegan diet
whether it's a paleo diet whether it's a
hell just come up with a new name and
there are some new names out there for
diets I'm not going to I'm not going to
mention the names cuz it's like you know
I'm not trying to attack any personal
doctors and other people I I'm not it's
not about attacking people it's the same
kind of thing it's all the same stuff
it's a trendy high fat High you know
high protein diets it's not like
whatever but what it is is it's a brain
shrinker diet that's what it is cuz your
brain is glycogen stored glycogen
stored it's sugar it has to be it's the
only way to keep the brain cool it's the
only way to keep it cool so it doesn't
burn up it doesn't burn
up the concern about fevers is that they
cook the brain that's what in medicine
the concern is it's a very good
concern because you don't want to cook
the brain and that's with fevers
the brain is a delicate delicate
delicate thing and it's filled with
glucose to protect it so it doesn't cook
the glucose diminishes over time in the
brain of somebody and they're on a
chronic high-fat diet all the time for
many years and the liver sluggish or
doggish or whatever it is turns into
pref fatty liver whatever it is it
doesn't whatever would happens is the
brain suffers over time as the years and
years go on and the Brain
atrophies but you wouldn't know when
you're just like okay you're eating bad
anyway then you pop onto a trendy high
fat diet with high protein diet and you
think you're doing stuff you're good and
you are it's a stage it's a step but it
doesn't stop there and you got to learn
one vital vital thing critical thing one
vital critical thing you got to lower
the fats whatever diet you subscribe to
you have to lower the
fats you I don't take sides because it's
not about taking sides it's about
delivering you the information that no
one else
has and you need that
information if you don't need it you
don't think you need it fine fine that's
fine with
me it's all right I respect that totally
respect that and you can kick dirt in my
face too man I'm pretty tough I totally
respect
that but I would take the information
work on your healing process move
forward bite the bullet work on it do it
that's what I would
do blood fat stops oxygen it stops
oxygen it dehydrates you it stops water
it stops
water it's not possible to lock down a
standard oxygen percentage of blood
entering the liver because it depends on
what somebody's eating science and
research will never be able to know the
percentage of oxygen that's going inside
the liver with the blood that heads up
heads up up the highway the hepatic
portal vein right into the liver they'll
never be able to determine this because
everybody's eating different and
everybody's on these high fat diets so
it's going to ratio different this is
all advanced stuff by the way in the
liver rescue book I mean science that
even know that they're not even thinking
to do something like that and they
should maybe 30 years they'll have that
test that's what I mean by being
Advanced it's the whole
point so that's the whole deal is you've
got to be careful with that much of the
rest of the blood entering through
thetic portal vein is carrying toxins
pathogens viruses
Pharmaceuticals minerals vitamins
enzymes amino acids antioxidants
phytochemicals from plants and Foods
nutrients fats and more if you're eating
fruit lots of
antioxidants but people aren't eating a
lot of antioxidants they're not they're
just not so they're not getting a lot of
good minerals and vitamins and
antioxidants up into the liver so that's
a whole problem all on its own
so fat thickens the
blood and that's the thing we have to be
scared about it matters it really
does so the central nervous system runs
on sugar I'm going to tell you right now
it runs on glucose the central nervous
system drinks glucose the brain is the
central nervous system it drinks n it
drinks all of the new glucose produced
delivered into the body and old storage
of of of glucose in the liver the liver
keeps the brain Alive by releasing
glucose constantly at different times
when someone isn't eating right to keep
your brain from atrophying this is
highly Advanced
information the central central nervous
system
drinks drinks glucose every cell in a
nerve every nerve cell needs glucose or
it dies
very important right there and when the
blood fat is high it loses its
opportunity slowly and painfully every
single day of somebody's life when
they're eating all that high
fat that's the kind of deal we're
talking about so it's really
important as long as it's seemingly a
seemingly new trendy everyday diet
consists of higher levels the fats which
is under the GU of protein the hidden gu
of protein as the main calorie Source it
will burden the liver probably and
almost possibly resulting in an
undiagnosed pre fatty liver or fatty
liver
condition regardless of whether
someone's exercising and doesn't have a
scrap on their body a fat doesn't have a
scrap on the outside of their body you
know of of
fat you still can have that pre fatty
and fatty liver and it'll catch up to
you later on no matter what and give you
a heart attack that's the whole thing
too cuz it can and it will it give you a
stroke I talk about this in a lot of
radio
shows lots of people athletes just
Strokes why are they getting strokes The
Blood fat is so thick that's
why and it's it's amazing how it works
the liver blood vessels constricted with
fat burdened overburdened
so our livers can sense what we eat I
got to tell you something pretty
interesting your stomach is stupid our
stomachs are stupid that's the stupidest
organ in the body science of research
doesn't know this yet it's the dumbest
organ in the body it has to be if it
wasn't we'd be in
trouble if it was smart if your stomach
was smart we'd be in trouble because we
don't have a lot of resources this the
body
knows the body knows we're created in a
way because we might be eating different
things that we're not supposed to eat to
survive we might be having that
barbecued chicken we might be having
whatever it is we might be having
something at the wrong time we might be
having some kind of greasy oily meal we
might be having something we might be
having a bunch of eggs that aren't good
for us but we're surviving and it's what
we need to eat because we have no other
options or we're living on a different
part of the planet we have no money no
resources or we're living here in the US
no money no resources we're just eating
to survive and we're eating all kinds of
different things the stomach has to stay
Stupid it has to and the liver stays
smart that's how it works and there's a
reason for that there's lots of reasons
for that the stomach is just a pouch
that gets its marching orders from your
brain that's the whole point it's an
important tool it's an amazing tool the
stomach is am it's an amazing organ it's
unbelievable but it should not sense
what we eat eat and give us too many
fore warnings cuz if it does it cheats
us out of surviving on planet Earth we
don't have a lot of options many of
us but the liver is so smart it knows
what you ate 10 days ago and It prepares
itself in case you eat it again how
about them apples how about them apples
your liver is so smart and science
research has no clue to this this is not
information they have on any level it's
so smart it knows if you eat Friday
night pizza and it gets ready to produce
the bile needed to try to break down all
that cheese fat and oil on Friday
nights even so when you skip that pizza
on Friday night and decide to eat a
healthy salad it pumps out all this bile
cuz it's used to you actually eating
pizza on that Friday night every Friday
night and you'll it just bile will come
out it's another confusing reason why
people say well I just can't eat all
these vegetables or can't even because
they're they're they're their their
liver was trained being smart trying to
think ahead of you to actually put out
bile to help you and break down and
disperse those fats to save your life
and your pancreas is
life and to try to thin out the blood
the best it's in capacity best its
capacity can to make sure you don't
stroke out someday because the liver
thinks it's smart a stomach stupid the
liver is really really really
smart if you eat a cheeseburger big old
juicy greasy cheeseburger or a healthy
cheeseburger once a year on your
birthday your liver will actually
documented recorded have it in its
information base and in it cells and not
forget it and actually prepare
itself on that 365
day of the
year that's the power of the liver but
we don't treat it good we treat it like
crap we do and it's not our fault at all
it's not it's not our fault and it's not
the trendy doctors that you know don't
know what the hell to feed anybody
really in the end it's not it's not it's
not anybody's fault it's not their fault
it's not anybody's
fault but knowing the truth is how you
can actually turn everything around but
if you avoid the truth then it's your
fault then it's your fault then it's our
fault if you avoid the truth if you
avoid the information
to do something about it and it could
become your
fault and maybe it's not your fault in
the end anyway cuz there's so much
misinformation out there derailing
everybody so you know what yeah I'm
wrong about that and I apologize
terribly wrong actually terribly wrong
because it's so hard out there and the
misinformation is so thick you can't
even cut through it with a
knife so yeah the bottom line is your
liver we got to take care of it we got
to avoid fatty liver I don't even know
who's going to listen to the show I know
lots of people listen thousands listen
to the show I get it but I don't even
know if people are interested in fatty
liver when I was going to do this show I
was like who's who's interested they
probably think they're going to get a
fatty liver when they're 50 60 years old
who's going to listen to this
show but it's one of the most important
shows that's the irony that's the irony
of Health that's the irony of what's
going on in our health and what's going
on in our
lives and so we got to think about all
these
things so the bottom line is the
pancreas needs to be protected by the
liver so we always got to think about
that because the liver protects it
protects you from
diabetes by trying to keep the glucose
strong and denouncing the fats so let's
think about all this you guys I really
love you and I really appreciate this
this has been you know I've been a
little bit more Punky I guess and a
little bit more
Sparky probably you know a little bit
more of a pain in the butt when it comes
down to all these things it's just that
I'm up against a lot of the trends out
there that are trying to always get in
the way and keep people sick and it just
gets you it gets you in the heart it
gets you in the gut a little bit because
when you see people suffer when they
don't have to
suffer because of something out there
that's happening it hurts anyway drink
your celery juice get the Liver Rescue
find out what else you can do I love you
guys I want you to take care bless you
God bless you and talk to you again
let's do the next show let's do the next
show I'll be there with you all right
bye he