now
fancy that
you guys you know what's amazing
you don't need to cleanse
the body does it itself the body
cleanses
on its own
that's what we're told right
you don't need to
clean your blood
you don't need to detox
you don't need to cleanse
you don't need to
get rid of any poisons inside of us ah
the body does it on its own the body
just
magically clears every toxin out
the body just gets rid of all of our
poisons all of our toxins
naturally you don't need to do anything
but then when your fingernails are
falling off
you got fungus on your fingernails and
your toenails
your fingers get crusty you get all
kinds of weird stuff with your skin you
get eczema you get psoriasis
your teeth just start falling apart as
the years go on
you get the vitiligo you get the weight
gain no you don't need to cleanse no
your body just takes care of it all on
its own
it doesn't matter suffering from
depression
anxiety depersonalization
right
pain in the body fatigue you don't need
a cleanse no the body just does it on
its own magically your body just
cleanses on its own you guys because
that's what the professionals out there
tell you
say
that's with all the different health
gurus and professionals
and the medical world right and
everything else like you don't need you
don't need a cleanse you don't need a
detox what your body is supposed to do
that naturally every day you just gotta
exercise you just gotta eat a balanced
diet
eat a balanced diet i recommend and have
moderation eat moderation and do your
exercise your body cleanses on its own
don't listen to anyone like medical
medium or anybody else that your body
actually needs to cleanse and detox
things
so then the years go by and you start
like falling apart
or madness starts happening and you're
just having all these different problems
with your health no you don't need to do
anything of course not
just keep out of keep it up keep eat
balanced eat moderation you don't have
to cleanse you don't have to detox
so you know what i hear that out there
good to see you guys coming on here
michelle miller just saw you there
kimberly miller
natalia coming on tj coming on you guys
are all coming on
cat lady it's good to see you guys all
of you guys right and so guys we're live
on tick tackle live on telegram we're
live on rumble or live on youtube we're
live on facebook we're live on something
we're live on everything right now right
but isn't that incredible
think about it i heard it the other day
heard it the other day a friend of mine
who's a doctor right i was trying to
reach out to him because he he contacted
me and then i reached back out to him so
i called his office and was like is he
there what's he doing it's anthony i got
a couple of minutes he had a question
for me
and then their personalized dietitian
slash nutritionist there
at the doctor clinic had me on the phone
and said i just want to talk to you for
a minute mr william because i have
different views on how the body works
and i said
all right tell me
how's it how does it work
like how what's your views you really
you know you you want people to juice
and you want people to cleanse but the
body doesn't work like that i've learned
that the body cleanses itself you just
have to eat in moderation you have to
have a balanced diet and i sat there and
i was like uh-huh okay my eyes were kind
of rolling over and i was like okay my
eyes are kind of looking my i was
actually like they were like starting to
roll over i was flickering my eyes were
flickering and i was like okay tell me
tell me like yeah and you just have to
exercise and then everybody's body
handles itself on its own and i said
listen
i've heard that before many times
but what are your patients like well
they got all kinds of problems mr
william they come in here sick with
everything and i'm scratching my head
and i go okay well do you think they
need to cleanse a little
well
no
their bodies handle that well then how's
their body handling anything on its own
when they're coming in there they're
like the walking dead coming in there
she was like yeah they can't walk they
got aches and pains
some people need to be carried in some
people have all these
horrendous skin conditions some people
have depression so bad some people have
all these problems i go yeah and do you
think there's something inside of them
that needs to come out that shouldn't be
there well i don't really know what that
could be maybe it's climate change mr
william do you think it's climate change
that's causing problems with all my
patients
and i was just like
i was banging my head on my desk when i
was hearing it
and i was like and i was being really
nice i wasn't the combative medical
medium you know when he's
when he's like i am doctor so and so
i was like okay listen
it's not climate change that's making
everybody sick okay
it's not
it might be
everything everybody's doing
like burning fake logs all that fake
chemical those fake logs you guys know
about the fake logs you burn them in the
fireplaces because it's coming on
christmas and thanksgiving maybe it's
from all the air fresheners and the
scented candles you guys know
everybody's lighting sent the candles in
every one of their houses right now and
they're poisoning their children and
their pets and they're killing
themselves they're killing themselves
right now with scented candles thousands
of chemical soups put into that chemical
into that candle to purposely destroy
your life
and so
i sat there telling this person right
this dietitian nutritionist for that
clinic
before the doctor came on and i
i said look
it's the scented candles
it's the
burning fake logs it's the fire pits
it's not climate change it's all that's
making people sick it's the fire pits
it's the colognes it's the perfumes it's
the toxic heavy metals it's the
pharmaceuticals people are taking it's
the fungicides it's the pesticides it's
the herbicides and it's making their
blood toxic it's the pathogens it's all
that stuff and she was like well you
know i've been reading up about
epstein-barr really because what have
you been reading i said to her what have
you been reading because guess what up
until the medical medium book series
nobody knew epstein-barr caused one
symptom
yeah well i thought i saw an article
that they say now that science study
recently came out that it's linked to
maybe a thyroid problem i go yeah and
that was medical medium book one
yes it was linked to a thyroid problem
yes you're just regurgitating
information that came from the book
originally oh i guess that must be why
the doctor wants to talk to you
the thing is you guys what's happening
out there by the way listen i'm going to
be juicing some pomegranate seeds
because
you need antioxidants to battle what's
happening inside the blood you need
phytochemical compounds
the
anti-juicing people out there
are really ridiculous at this point oh
no juicing is not good you need to just
use a blender or a bullet because you
want to preserve everything in there
okay real smart
because it doesn't do the trick it's not
enough
almost says so no burning wood the
burning wood thing
is so toxic to the body
you're burning all that wood the fire
pits the fireplaces i'm not trying to
rain on anybody's parade but literally
the human nature wants to burn
that's what human nature wants to do
they want the gas fire like you go to la
and they got the gas fire pits every
single house in malibu and wherever
every single house all over la all the
way down everywhere from up north all in
california they're all burning
they're all burning the gas
the gas fire pits you go into some of
these houses and they just boom they
click a switch and
you've got gas burning flames everywhere
right oh it's so nice you kick back oh
that's so nice isn't it
they're contributing to climate change
that's for sure you know what's funny
everybody's like climate change climate
change
but yet everybody's burning everything
under the sun they're burning gas
they're burning like all their fire pits
their gas fire pits their wood by fire
pits they're pumping perfume cologne air
fresheners pumping into the air they're
pumping they're burning scented candles
you know the whole thing with the plague
the whole thing with the plague has
literally propelled everybody to buy a
scent to candle and poison themselves
and kill themselves
it's like i'm running away from the
plague so i'm now i'm in my house so i'm
gonna now kill myself with some scented
candles chemicals and kill myself right
there you seem fine to me chris you said
you love this topic chris do you see
that in california
i see that everybody's
killing the environment with the scented
candles killing the environment with the
fire pits
i mean it was like
you gotta worry about climate change
that's the reason why everybody's sick
i'm just gonna light my big old fire pit
right now i'm gonna have company come
over and i'm gonna hit the gas button
and i'm gonna light the big old gas fire
pit so everybody could sit there with
the martinis and look at the gas fire
pit and kill the planet it's hypocrisy
right
the bottom line is
all this crap goes into us
we're poisoned on a daily basis don't
juice no don't juice
no mr william you're wrong you shouldn't
juice anything you should eat your
celery sticks crudite is the best way to
do it maybe chop up a little bit and put
it in your tuna casserole your to your
tuna salad
don't juice it
anyway you guys i'm gonna do some
juicing
this is the sale is still on for the
mm-900 hds
90 off it's the biggest sale ever i told
you the other day what's going to happen
is this
if i don't say anything about it
the sale is going to be over i'm going
to be in the car in a passenger seat
when somebody's driving me somewhere
like if i'm like a passenger or
something or i'll be driving which i try
not to do
okay because i get the readings
spirit of compassion is telling me about
the people next to next to me at the
light this person at the light this
person crossing in front of me that
person has a heart condition who's
crossing in front of me the person next
to me has got a neurological condition
person next to me has got high anxiety
so i hear that from spirit of compassion
nonstop
so i try not to drive too much because
the last thing i need is to be hearing
about every single person that has a
problem as i'm on the road in traffic
right
so i'm in the passenger seat and i'm
looking at comments and stuff and i
start seeing people saying hey do you
know where i can get a juicer hey do you
know where i can get a good g-suit deal
do you know when the mm-900 is for sale
and it's right after the sale ends i
roll down the window and i scream
i scream because there's nothing more i
can do i don't even know what to say
if you have to burn wood to heat your
home i totally get it
home i completely understand
but most people don't have to burn wood
to heat their home they burn wood
and poison everybody else
in the neighborhood and everywhere else
and the stuff just goes in the
atmosphere
all that burn wood when every single
person is lighting a fire inside their
home do you know how many cords of wood
that is billions of cords of wood going
into the atmosphere and the aliens are
flying by on their spacecraft saying you
idiots
you idiots
that's what they're doing
the aliens in the spacecraft are flying
around up there and they're flying
around and they see
millions of homes and chimneys puffing
out smoke
all those dead trees
because they want to entertain
themselves
and they you know what i mean and the
aliens are flying by saying you idiots
just destroy the planet
and the spacecrafts are flying around in
the atmosphere and they see all those
people with their fire pits
you people gather around with
marshmallows and s'mores
and the fire pit going in the middle and
everybody drinking and you got the fire
pit with all that wood burning and the
space spacecrafts are going starting
with a lighter fluid to start it
squeezing all that lighter fluid on it
and the spacecrafts are going by saying
that you know you guys are killing the
planet
breathing in all that smoke
anyway the mm-900 is 90 off
it's
it's it's the best sale i've ever seen
okay i'm going to show you how it works
we're going to do some stuff
the sales on right now by the way it's a
black friday sale
for this machine you won't be
disappointed
it's it's it's a mind-blowing machine
it's a medical device
it's literally a medical device i always
say it rather be on this medical device
than some other medical device
so what happens is you guys juicing is
critical for toxic blood
everybody has toxic dehydrated
chronically dehydrated toxic blood they
walk around with toxic blood you see it
in their eyes you see it everywhere
their blood is toxic you could see it in
their skin you can see it in all kinds
of different ways
they walk around chronically toxic
that's how they walk around i've already
told you guys
okay you got the pathogens you've got
the metals you've got all that different
stuff but everybody's bodies are like
crying to get rid of this stuff
crying let me just ask you something
have you seen anybody in their young age
have you seen them later on in their
older age
is there somebody you knew 30 years ago
they kind of looked slim they kind of
look kind of together they kind of look
kind of like healthy like and then you
see them 30 years later 20 years later
they're bloated
they're thicker
their head for some reason grew where
their head is twice the size of what it
was when they were younger did you ever
know how that works did you ever see
that
you ever see everybody's heads
do you ever did you ever wonder that
everybody's heads gets
big how does it get big their skull
doesn't grow
but years later their head is bigger
than it was and it's not even about
weight their head got swollen frugivore
bare their head got swollen you guys see
this before
30 years ago dino says yes 30 years ago
their head was half their size how did
their head grow
tell me
how did their head get twice as twice
the size do you guys know
maria says wow venus is puffed yeah
puffed right puffed rice or something
how come toxic buildup tj
how come everybody's head exploded
that do you see it down the road
20 years later darcy lee 20 years later
you guys on tick tock do you ever see it
inflammation inflammation is what you
guys are saying
you guys on telegram you've never seen
this before hey lynn fouch that lynn
thank you for being here by the way and
you're really really generous
you're really a generous person i read
your comment um in the last youtube
so
how does it work
i think that's the same len that left a
comment in youtube you can correct me if
it's not but
how's that work how does everybody's
head get so big
i've seen it
face gets fatter patty says
maybe
or does their does their head just grow
into this large head
you see them when they're 20
they've already stopped growing
you see them when they're 45 and their
head is huge and their nose is big their
nose grew twice its size i don't get it
is your nose still growing
is your head still growing no your head
stopped growing your nose stopped
growing but look darlene's is
interesting
that's from toxic blood
everybody looks like a bloated tick
later on
they all like look like a bloated tick
do you ever see a tick on a dog
do you ever see like a tickle you ever
pull a tick off a dog
right you pull a tick off a dog that's
been on there way too long
and it's this big old bloated tick
it's the craziest thing
you look at somebody later on you're
years late you look at them when they're
in their 30s look you can even look at
politicians whatever you see them
pictures of them when they were 30 you
see pictures of them when they're 60
like what happened your head grew three
times bigger how did your head grow when
you don't grow anymore
it's the same thing with some
celebrities right you see some
celebrities like when they're 20 years
old 25 years old then you see them years
later and their heads are like twice the
size like what happened
from being toxic for too many years
toxic for too many years toxic blood
does some crazy ass in the body
that's what toxic blood does it does
some crazy ass in the body that's
what toxic blood does i mean it's really
incredible how it works right
but no no no you don't need to cleanse
no you don't need to cleanse you guys
just eat a balanced diet whatever you
think is balanced let's do that let's
trust everybody on what they think is
balance
right we can do that
yeah
it's not fat i'm talking about their
heads don't explode because of fat you
need to know that that's part of it
because the brain does gather fat so
there's too much fat in the brain
meaning additional fat but it's not just
about its swelling they got so toxic
that their head
swelled up it's swollen their head got
so swollen that it enlarged that's why
the person's head is twice the size or a
third size bigger or a quarter size
bigger than it was back 20 30 years ago
because the swelling became so chronic
that the head had to make room for it so
the head had to expand like the whole
head expanded to make room for that
swelling that's from toxic blood right
ken's ken lewis says i was so swelled up
but you don't need a cleanse no
i'm dr sessions
i'm doctor i'm i'm dr shin
i'm the chiropractor and i'm a dino i'm
an md i'm a chiropractor i'm an md
you don't have to cleanse
five tips to make yourself healthy get
my collagen powder
that will do it get my apple cider
vinegar chewies
that will do it
get my fruits and vegetables in a
capsule that will do it
but don't eat fruit five top tips as my
head swells bigger and bigger
bigger and bigger and i need another
implant in another root canal
what happens is that we get toxic we
don't know what a balanced diet is we
don't know what's going on but we just
turn into a toxic mess as the decades go
by
and that's what happens
you guys
frederick says wouldn't it be
head
lymphatics too
lymphatic system runs through your head
not all of your head but it runs through
a part of it yeah that swells up too
being toxic
absolutely
but it's more than that your spinal
fluid becomes toxic
your spinal fluid becomes toxic that's
two that's the one there too
you got no room for the spinal fluid
anymore
the spinal fluid gets full of so many
poisons and toxins it slowly graduates
into everything needs to make room and
that person's head is now so big
compared to what it used to be 30 years
ago their head is big now
but they stopped growing 30 years ago
but their head swelled up
because of the spinal fluid too it's not
just lymph lymph it's just this much of
it spinal fluid is a big part of it and
then there's other stuff too and blood
is the really big part of it blood being
toxic for so long that your blood
vessels just start to swell everything
expands even your skull starts to expand
and then it weakens
so then you're walking along and you're
60 years old you're walking along right
oh and you slip down and then boom you
crack your head the doctor's like i
don't know how that happened you
shouldn't have cracked your head open
from that fall
yeah
healthy liz good to see you glad you're
here
so do we need a juice no
no i just sit here for fun
i'm just doing this for fun i'm just
sitting here
okay
spending my days and my hours trying to
show you guys how to juice
for no reason for no good reason
all these years for 35 years i've been
trying to get you guys to juice for 35
years i know you guys are but i've been
trying to get people to juice for 35
years for no reason at all no you don't
need a juice i'm just doing it
cindy says what would you see in a live
blood analysis if you had toxic blood
nothing because you would see nothing in
a live blood analysis because they don't
know what toxins are looking for
the only thing you can see in the blood
is what you're actually you can look for
what you can actually look for
they can't look for a metal on a live
analysis
they can't see it they can't look for
air freshener chemicals in a live
analysis they can't look for scented
candle poisons in a live analysis they
can't look for smoke you breathe in from
somebody's chimney next door all night
long sifting in through your apartment
in your house they can't see any of that
they can't
and that's one of the problems
blood tests
are all antiquated
live blood
um test analysis live blood analysis are
not even they're antiquated too so
everything's antiquated right so you got
to take health in your own hands you
could be somebody that waits and waits
and waits and weights right on telegram
you guys could be somebody that waits
and waits well wait for science to come
out with their new thing i'll wait for
science to come out let me wait for
science to come out for their new thing
yeah i'm waiting too i'm waiting too
yeah i'm gonna wait for science to come
out that's what i'll do you know
and i got a friend here who's waiting
for science to come out with all kinds
of stuff too and we're all waiting for
science to come out the next thing hey
hey we don't have to do anything they
say we don't have to cleanse i went to a
health professional and they said you
don't have to cleanse you hear that we
don't have to cleanse right now right we
don't have to cleanse
and then
you're good until you're not
everything's okay
until it's not
you're healthy
until you're not
the whole bit frederick says the problem
is metal in the organs though not the
blood right correct
there's still some metal in the blood
but it settles in the organs
sits in the organs and rots frederick
spot on that's exactly the information
the metal sits
and the metal sits in the liver too
builds up builds up builds up and then
kind of releases a little bit
right so it does releases a little bit
gets to the brain and then sits in the
brain and builds up and builds up
sometimes there's some highway in
between
but it builds up
just eating moderation
i'm gonna have more cow
lots more cow
well it's moderation i'm gonna have a
big burger every night a grass-fed beef
burger every single night
i'm not anti-animal protein i'm not
anti-vegan you can same thing with
vegans i'm gonna have five more avocados
tonight the liver gets stagnant and
sluggish
and then it spills out the poison after
a while it gets stagnant and sluggish
it's your filter and it can't filter
anymore so your liver can't filter
anymore and it's spilling out the poison
now because it can't filter anymore so
your liver is just spilling out poison
because it can't filter anymore there's
no way it can filter anymore
and that's what happens with the liver
right
and then we don't know what to do and
you can't change the filter let me just
go change the filter
let me do that
it's like i'm gonna go to a clinic and
they're gonna change my filter hold on
you guys
just gonna get my filter replaced here
you can't change this filter
it's not changeable you have to cleanse
it we have to get a juice in us once in
a while
it's not
we're up against things we've never been
up again
against ever before in our history we're
up against more poison more problems
than we've ever been up against in our
history we can't just change our filter
we have to clean it we have to clean it
you guys there's new chemicals man
there's new chemicals every day they're
making
the chemical
industry
is sitting there
making a new chemical
every day
right
it never gets tested
they don't know if it can kill you or
not
and they release it
and it's in your perfume
your perfume
your scented candle your fragrance
it's in your
gmo food even
it's everywhere
okay
and
these things build up our system for
years and years and years
they do
let's do some juicing
it's critical so what i'm going to do is
look i'll run a little bit of celery
through here i think that's what i want
to do now
what i love about celery
they said nobody's drinking it you know
what i love about celery i'm gonna be a
little sarcasm here right no one's
shrinking it nobody all right
no one wants to talk about it because no
one's drinking it
youtubers stop talking about it because
no one's drinking it no one's drinking
celery at all
meanwhile
a couple of the biggest corporations and
food on the planet are putting out
celery juices pretty soon
because the whole world's drinking it
it's going to be more popular than soda
down the road right
and because everybody is drinking it
and a lot of people are just hiding that
they drink it every single juice bar
it's their number one drink
every single juice bar on the planet
right now sells more celery juice than
anything single juice there is
there's more celery juice in the
supermarkets being sold you know the
fake ones with the hpp not the fresh
ones every single day it is the largest
crop in produce on the planet they can't
grow enough of it
thousands of farms every single day
are being like are putting this stuff
out you don't want hpp what i love about
doing it this way
it's this isn't hpp you guys hpp is no
good for me
hpp is high pressure past graduation you
can't use high pressure pasteurization
with
celery juice
you can't do hpp it can't be high
pressure pasteurization because i'll
tell you what that is
it kills the phytochemical compounds so
you can get healthy
yes stay away from hpp
you know what you can probably drink
something in hpp
and it'd be okay
but not celery juice it has to be juiced
fresh
it has to be you got your juicer
yesterday and was the best for juicing
celery cynthia it's incredible for
juicing pomegranate seeds i'm going to
show you guys that it's incredible for
juicing it's incredible for juicing
anything
saves people money and it pays for
itself you guys
how many things in your life pays for
itself i just want to ask that question
you guys aren't tick-tock how many
things in your life pays for itself
like pays for itself right
like
you buy something does it pay for itself
food prices are going up
this machine lowers my food costs
so what i see out there is food prices
are going up right
and i'm like well okay
this is squeezing every last drop out of
the stuff
so then i'm using less produce for my
juice i'm getting healthy and staying
healthy
that's what i love about it and it pays
for itself it's the biggest sale ever
for the mm-900 hds 90 off free shipping
go to megajuicers.com the link is in the
description link is in the bio on tick
tock the link is in the description too
for you guys on youtube
seriously
yes celery juice is going to be more
popular than anything else down the road
it's going to be more popular than
anything else
kelsey bach kelsey kelsey didn't you get
rid of 51 symptoms or did you get rid of
because i know you leave comments i
always read them all the time and you're
really supportive for other people in
the community which is incredible
because you're always like you're always
like helping people when they're down
and stuff
kelsey
is there like 51 symptoms now or 53
symptoms he said i had other omega
juicers the mm900 is the best incredible
wendy says my megan mm-900 is the best
i love it i really do
henna says
mm-900 hcs is the best juicer
it really is it really is that's why i
stand behind it a billion percent i
endorsed this product i endorsed it
every day
you guys
hundreds of companies
reach out to me
and they're like please endorse us
please endorse us
you know the medical media we want your
support i'm like no
no
no you got way too no your product is
no i can't no
no
and
when omega said look we can we can try
to save people money i'm like all right
i'm talking i'm listening you're talking
i'm biting
i'm listening
the chronically ill
people who have chronic illness
they don't have a lot of money
they've been through hell and back
how can we save a money and also try to
get them healthy
well we can do something where we can
make it so they buy less produce so
they're saving thousands of dollars by
the end of the year or whatever hundreds
of dollars and they get to save hundreds
of dollars or whatever it is for each
person or family
and
and they can get healthy i said i'm in
i'm in
colleen says omega omega service is
great had a problem with the part they
they are replacing it yeah if you guys
have any problems with parts or
something with them call them i mean
contact them very quick in getting back
to me and in shipping the park free of
charge paying only shipping i've learned
it has a 15-year warranty oh my god the
mm-900 has a 15-year warranty
i didn't even know that
that's incredible
amy says mm-900 has made juicing so much
easier for me and easy cleanup exactly
exactly
kristin hope said i used other juicers
this juicer is awesome celery fiber
comes out bone dry
bone dry man you guys if you just came
on we're not just juicing i'm gonna
juice some pomegranate seeds but not
just that we're gonna talk about toxic
blood i want everybody to have all the
information they have they can get all
the information they can get in every
way possible so that's what i want
that's what it's about okay
so i'm gonna strain this celery juice
for a second well actually what i'm
gonna do is show you the pulp
right so the pulp is dry
this pulp is not wet and sloppy
it's not wet and sloppy
it doesn't have to be put back into the
machine over and over again which
doesn't get juice out by the way
you can't re-juice pulp
it's not possible it comes out the way
it's going to come out wet and it's
going to stay wet i got a friend that
keeps on putting it that they put it
back into the machine 100 times and i
was over their house and i was watching
them and i was like look you just have
to keep on putting it back in they had
this crappy juicer and i said all right
fine go ahead and they kept on putting
it back in over and over again and i was
standing there scratching my head said
you know it's still wet right
anyway it comes up comes out dry it's
where the money is saved i'm just
letting you guys know it's the mm-900
hds the best sale ever
i have to tell you guys if i don't tell
you
then what's gonna happen is you guys are
gonna tell me
you're gonna tell me hey i need a juicer
which user do you use when is there a
sale i just bought it full price
when i hear somebody buy this juicer at
full price
even though it's worth it i get really
upset
why do you think i only tell you about
the juicer you guys
when it's on sale
like i want you to save so much money
where you actually get it on sale
everybody else that's behind something
or they put they they're they're
involved with something
they want you buying it full price
that's what they do because i know i
know people all in the industry and they
want you buying everything full price
right
it's like
i only talk about the juicer when it's
on sale because i want you to save tons
of money norma norma says how do we save
the nine dollars is there a coupon quote
it's in the checkout when you go to
megajuicers.com and you're purchasing
the juicer you'll see the 90 off in the
checkout it's the mm-900 hds though
that's the one or you're gonna buy the
wrong juicer and you're gonna be like
why is the pulp still wet the link is in
the bio the link is in the description
let's talk about toxic blood
and then maybe we're gonna juice some
pomegranate because that's incredible
for toxic blood too so we'll do that all
right
all right so let's let's string in the
juice
you gotta strain your celery juice
very important to do okay
you have to strain it
you can't add anything to it it's not
gonna work
so you say that the plastic is more safe
than stainless steel so
no way i don't trust plastics at all
it's fine if you don't trust blast lucas
it's fine okay
but here's how it works right
so
metal on metal so let me show you
something i don't have
i don't have
gears right now in front of me with the
other juicers okay but i'm gonna make
two gears for you
this is not cheap
plastic this is bpa free plastic that
the juice is touching there's a
difference
this is not cheap plastic so that's
important to know okay that's a metal
gear i just made so i'm making a mock
metal gear so lucas hang on right
i know you're smarter than me
lucas i know
hang on
okay
i know you're probably saying i don't
trust that
i understand i'm glad you're here i'm
gonna make two fake gears
okay
in a lot of juicers cold pressed juicers
they have two gears made out of
steel these are mock gears
okay
pressing print says i love the juicer
thank you for the medical medium truce
you're amazing president thank you okay
so ready here's two mock gears so now
they're on here they go
they're on
there they go
now you're juicing and you're running
your vegetables and fruits through your
juicer with your metal gears so lucas
are you getting the message yet
did you ever have a brake pad that wore
down to its metal do you guys know
anything about cars you guys know a
medical medium book one i told you about
the car stuff
okay medical media book one in the
origin story if you guys are interested
so there's your your your juicers on
your juicer's on there's your metal
gears
so now run your vegetables through there
okay i'm gonna run this piece of
cilantro through there
roll around
get my cilantro through there okay i'm
getting my cilantro juice
i'm real smart
do you know what happens
you're metal on metal baby
you know what metal on metal is
it's like your brake pads hitting your
rotor and you hear
[Music]
tiny particles of metal are going into
your juice as each month goes by each
week goes by each years go by lucas are
you seeing this
i hope you didn't leave
okay lucas
oh wait there you are yes but what about
plastic can't wait to tell you
okay
metal
takes a lot to get out of your body
it gets into your organs into your
intestinal lining it gets into your
liver it gets into your brain
metal doesn't come out of the body easy
so here you are you're juicing with your
metal juicers there you go and your one
more year goes by and you're now eating
more metal another year goes by oh i'm
getting healthy i'm drinking my juices
and you're getting more metal eventually
that metal is going to build up in your
liver your brain your intestinal tract
see how it works
that's how it works
and what happens and people don't
realize
is that there's a difference this isn't
cheap plastic
this is high quality technology plastic
bpa free
and any plastic residue from anything
plastic even bad plastics because this
isn't bad plastic bad plastic
still comes out of the body with
cleansing
your juice
literally can take any plastic you've if
you ate plastic from fast food
restaurants from 10 years ago and that
plastic is still in you your juice that
you're juicing from something high
quality like this is taking that plastic
out of your body from 10 years ago but
get this
you know how hard it is to get metal out
you got to do the medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie you got to do the
wild blueberry you got it's hard to get
metal out
and here you are with all the different
juicers with all the metal the
centrifuge metal
the the gears of metal
and that's what people don't really
understand
and guess what someone left a comment on
youtube
on youtube i think on the last one you
guys could go look for if you want right
somebody left a comment
saying they were using the metal juicers
for years
and they couldn't get results and then
they switched and they got results
because they were stopping to get metal
poisoned
right
pk good to see you i see you leave
comments every now and youtube
so the point is
is that you got to think about that and
how that works like the difference
this isn't even about choosing you know
what is this is about information that's
critical when i think about it right
so these are great if the metal gears
were fine i'd be having metal gears man
i'd be like yeah give me the metal gears
give me the metal gears
i'll take the metal gears they're fine
they're safe why wouldn't i use them
then
you'd see a juicer here with metal gears
right here
but you're not going to see that
i think i had a little too much celery
for us today
sorry you guys what happens is
i took like six celery force before i
came on today
what happens when i'm trying to pour
this and the juicer's in the way because
i'm trying to do it on camera right here
and i don't want to pour it over there i
want you guys to be able to see it i end
up spilling a little because
everything's in my way over here
just bear with me
when you guys pour your juice out try
not to do it jammed up against your
juicer try to pour like try to give
yourself room so you just don't knock it
everywhere like i just did
you want to strain it you don't want to
add lemon you don't want to add anything
you don't want to add water or ice or
nothing into it let the sodium cluster
salts flush out the liver and clean the
body
that's really important to know
okay
blenders don't have metal gears grinding
against each other keep that i saw that
question
blenders don't have metal gears grinding
against each other
so blenders don't have metal gears
grinding against each other i know
someone said well what about the metal
in a blender
i love answering these questions because
i want to help i really do i want to
help i want to help get your brain
cleaned up i want to help get your liver
cleaned up i want to help get you guys
better
is what i want how do you strain your
juice
you just use a strainer i'd use a mesh
strainer right here that's what i do i
use a mesh
strainer is what i do you can do
different ways of trying to strain it
but it's important to strain it because
celery juice has to be
has to be on its own it has to be by
itself the juice it's an herbal
extraction so what you're looking at
here you guys is an herbal
medicine extractor
that's what you're looking at
celery
is an herb it's not a vegetable when you
use herbs to heal life changes so what i
love doing i love juicing parsley
through this juicer
i love doing that like i do like one or
two celery sticks and then i throw some
parsley in there i love doing parsley
because you're juicing herbs this is an
herb
this is a
herbal medicine maker right here
that's what this is which is really
great let's do some pomegranate seeds
i don't want to bore you guys with a
three minute clean out with this so what
i'm gonna do is
i'm gonna pop off pop up another one
real quick
have another one we're going to do some
pomegranate juice for fun we're going to
talk about toxic blood
we need
antioxidants to stop oxidizing so let's
talk about that right now i think that's
really important okay
everybody's slowly dying
everybody
is slowly dying
on the planet
it's death by a thousand cuts
they poison us
the industry is poisonous
the pharmaceutical companies poison
us the chemical industries poison us
right
the illumination
flying all the jet planes in the sky
dropping chemicals down on us is
poisoning us
right all the different household
antagonists
that we're actually taking and and doing
and spraying on ourselves and cleaning
supplies and carpet cleaners are
poisoning us
right
the water supplies are poisoning us
the smoke in the air is poisoning us
there's always some pyros that are
purposely paid to like the worst fires
in the state of california there's
always pyros that are that are paid to
like the worst fires in australia and
everywhere else so everything just burns
down and forests burned down and the
planet just just basically a planet just
declines and all that with all that
smoke right
we go around
and
we slowly die
because of mankind
evil mankind the evil part of it
the evil ones at the top the echelon the
high echelon
they literally want you to die
slowly so they kill us slowly with all
of this
and then we're not getting enough
antioxidants
in us to battle it
so we're not getting enough antioxidants
in us to fight
what i love about the juicer or a juicer
forget this juicer
just any juicer you got a juicer use it
any juicer
what i love about the juicing like
juicing
is you're getting something out of the
food you can't do if you just eat the
food and chew it
you can't get enough if you do it this
way we're like you can't get enough that
way
and so and you can't get enough by
saying i'm gonna have a pomegranate here
do you want to share my pomegranate with
me
right
i'm dr jonzo and i learned that
pomegranates are good for you and hey do
you want to share this beautiful
pomegranate with me have a little bit
here have a slice that should be enough
antioxidant for you you don't need more
than that you need my colostrum
supplement
you need more than that you need more
than a little bit of this and a little
bit of that
and a little bit of this you need more
than just a piece of an orange once in a
while you know what i mean you need more
than that
and so what happens is in order to
battle what the death by a thousand cuts
are doing out there and then the health
movement they're doing death by a
thousand cuts to everybody too they're
poisoning everybody with the vinegar
poisoning everybody with the caffeine
the health movement yeah alternate
medicine wants everybody dead on
caffeine they're poisoning everybody
with caffeine you don't believe me
it's true the caffeine industry has
completely taken over the alternative
health industry they own them now
they just want you on caffeine 24 7
right it's there it's death by a
thousand cuts everywhere you guys so if
you don't know how to defend yourself
then what
what are you gonna do
and so what i love about the juicing
it's a way to basically say
yeah no sorry
no
not gonna you know what
rain all you want on me
chemicals coming out of the sky
because you can't say the term anymore
right
bringing all you want on me
all the dioxins
renal you want on me perfume users
right because there's pesticides and
perfumes they're actually made of
pesticides
rain all you want on me
pharmaceutical tap in the tap water
bring all you want wherever you want
but i'm going to be battling your ass
i'm going to be battling you with
antioxidants antioxidant power because
here's the problem everybody's dying
slowly because they're oxidizing did you
know that
did you know your brain is oxidizing
every day it oxidizes that's why
everybody's brain shrinks that's why
when i talk to my doctor friends who
have worked on cadavers they've cut open
people's heads and they've looked at
brains they're like oh my god that
person's brain is half the size it was
when they were younger what happened
their brain shrunk it oxidized
so what happens is the brain just
reduces in size you get older and did
you know your brain gets empty in the
middle of it did you know when everybody
gets older
they start getting a hollow brain down
in here
a hollow brain they get a gap because as
they get older everything's oxidizing
and being eaten on the inside out we
oxidize so we're all dying slowly here
while they're poisoning us here and no
one's really and then you'll hear you
don't have to juice
just keep a balanced diet
let's get a little bit of pomegranate
juice going you guys
right
all right
dr faun md i see you over there
amazing
glad you're here
you know look i got to tell you guys
something it's sunday right i'm honored
you guys are here on your sunday i can't
even thank you enough for being here
it's just so great to have you here
green blue says the head gets bigger the
brain gets smaller correct 100 percent
elizabeth right health with liz no one
talks about that no no one talks about
that but you know what's funny liz
on a little personal note right
all i do is bring new information
i mean unless i'm wrong unless i'm wrong
or something and i don't
but i bring new information and new
information every single month every
single week every single year and
someone will still say he doesn't have
any new information like what
what do you think i am the lectin guy
that only has lectin information for the
last 10 years and that's all he has
this is that people don't cite back to
where the original information comes
from here
so then it doesn't seem like i was the
originator of like these pieces of
information because it's it gets taken
out of here so someone takes it and they
run off with it
and then they go they run run away
it's fine the point is is it doesn't
help others if they don't know where it
all comes from
it's just it's really amazing it's
amazing
maryland says are you using the green
ring for prom pomegranate cheese i am
definitely using it that means you must
have an mm-900
so i'm gonna move this celery over here
and put this on the back here i'm gonna
get some pomegranate juice going
right
you get a little bit of this in here
i've never heard anywhere in hell
my whole life 35 years professionally
doing it i've never heard anybody talk
about how everybody's heads got bigger
except ego
only thing i've ever heard is the ego
got bigger with somebody's head yeah
your head's getting too big because of
your ego that's the only time i've ever
heard it
charlie says i've been dabbling with mm
for three years now hey dabbling's not
the worst thing to do that's great
dabbling with mmm for three years now
and i have reduced many symptoms now i'm
ready to go all in now and get fantastic
results charlie lagoa
cool man
cool
listen you're allowed to be a dabbler
i i welcome medical medium dabblers you
want to do a little celery juice i stand
behind you you want to try the medical
medium smoothies i stand behind you you
want to you want to look at the
different angels in the in the medical
medium first but i stand behind you you
want to dabble in medical medium i stand
behind you but whatever you do
don't write a post one day telling
anybody that i've been doing medical
medium for four years and it didn't work
for me because you're gonna then stop
someone else from trying medical medium
and never getting a chance to heal
and it might have been somebody that
wasn't gonna be a dabbler they might
have gone all full in on it and you're
gonna tell them basically don't do
medical medium because i did it for four
years and it didn't fix me
meanwhile you might have been a dabbler
basically what i'm saying is it's
perfectly fine to be a dabbler but thank
you for actually exactly 100 you i'm
honored you're here tristan marie said
my daughter was on here last time
sending you many hearts
from her or me all good
amazing
it's okay dabbling is fine you guys i
love you for dabbling
sounds incredible if anybody wants to go
full-on they want to go into the
protocols they want to go deep into it
i'm i'm totally there
incredible
amazing
so what i'm doing is pomegranate juice
right now
what i love about the pot what i love
about this juicer i'm just going to give
you a quick run down on the pomegranate
aspect okay
that comes out bone dry
i ran a lot of pomegranate seeds through
there that comes out bone dry
okay so that's that's interesting
so
that's coming out bone dry
but here's the difference here's what no
juicer does
no juicer
juices the seed
they only juice the pulp around the seed
so that's important to know
the mm-900 is the only juicer that
squeezes the chemical compounds the
fight the antioxidants and phytochemical
compounds inside the seed
so keep that in mind
that means when you drink pomegranate
juice out there right when you go out
there and you drink pomegranate juice
you're not drinking all of the benefits
you're only drinking
part of the benefits so when
pomegranate juice is offered to you out
there
it's only half there
it's not all there
it's kind of like talking to somebody
that's lost their mind you know it's
like they're not all there right you
ever run into that
bad things happen they got so much they
got they got all these
medals inside their head
they're getting what people call like
all old-timers but it's really
alzheimer's and they're not all there
it's really sad sad process right which
happens
it's like the same thing with
pomegranate juice you're drinking
pomegranate juice but only part of it's
there it's not all there it's just not
there
and so what happens is with the
pomegranate seed you have to juice the
seed itself and that's how life turns
around
to protect you remember i was talking
about antioxidants battling the you know
death by a thousand cuts
all juicers need to be strained
all juicers
there's no such thing as well i juiced
with this juicer but why are you
straining yours no actually that's a
technique that all juicers are supposed
you're supposed to strain the juice
after every juice
any juicer you juiced with doesn't
matter what company what brand
you have to strain
the juice you have to strain the celery
juice you have to so the celery juice
can work trying to answer questions
while we're doing some fun stuff and
talking all right
let's pour some pomegranate juice out
here
there you go
now the difference with this juicer is
you're going to squeeze
much more out of the pomegranate seed
much more you're going to squeeze the
seed
not just the pulp around the seed
so now you've got a whole other level of
medicine right here
and it's a different color
that's the color pomegranate cheese is
supposed to be
so
keep this in mind if you've ever tried
pomegranate juice on the shelf
or anywhere else it's supposed to be
this color
it's not supposed to be the fake color
where it's just
the part there color
where it's the color of the juice that
was around the pulp right
it's supposed to be the color
of
the juice that was inside the seed
see the seed
there you go
that that's an incredible that's
incredible right there i can't even tell
you you know when you drink that
and i got it i got and i got to tell you
something now
just know that the pomegranate seeds you
buy
that are de-seeded meaning the
pomegranate you go to the health food
store go to the grocery store and they
already have them where the seeds are
out of the pomegranate like they used
equipment to get the seeds out of the
pomegranate
just know that when you buy it that way
it's been laced
with a preservative
from a chemical company that they give
these food companies to lace them with
as a preservative so
it's best to buy them this way
if you do buy the seeds by themselves in
the grocery stores because they already
were shelled and the seeds were put into
a package and you're like whoa
pomegranate seeds already done for me
and you buy the package
rinse them really well
rinse them really well because they're
sprayed
with a preservative chemical
on them that's why i love making sure
you get them from your pomegranates here
okay cordina says please help
love celery juice but makes me so
nauseous
so
is the astringency so you might be
somebody that doesn't like anything
bitter would parsley make you nauseous
probably right anything astringent
is that what it is like if someone made
parsley juice you'd probably be like
i can't drink this
right
were you ever nauseous before so your
whole life so this is something i want
you to be your own detective were you
ever nauseous before
ever
with anything like were you nauseous
last week with some other type of food
were you nauseous yesterday when you had
some dinner
were you nauseous the other day when you
got when you were talking to a friend
and for some reason you you know
whatever or something's happening like
were you nauseous anyway
did you get the point is is did you go
through your whole life you're never
nauseous ever and then you sip some
celery juice and it was the first time
ever you got nauseous or you're somebody
that gets nauseous pretty easy and you
can get triggered easy so if you had
something like celery juice because it's
so astringent
and the taste is kind of shocking for
some people it made you nauseous because
you're already somebody that's sensitive
and you actually get nauseous all the
time i want you to be your own detective
what i would do if i was nauseous from
it i would start with two ounces then
two ounces i would do just two ounces
that would that would be a little little
shot glass two ounces right i'll go get
a shot glass right now
so if i was somebody that was nauseous
by it
i would start really small
that's what i would do
so cordina says i do have a sensitive
stomach in general so that's why so it's
it's just because you have a sensitive
stomach in general right
exactly
so
what i would do if that's the case is i
would take a shot class
and i would just do like one ounce two
ounces
maybe just do that and try that
this has been like so fun you guys i
love answering questions i want to help
in any way i can
i really just love all that you guys are
doing
that's the pomegranate juice right there
re-watch this live if you came here give
me a thumbs up or a like or whatever you
guys can give me right
and we were live here on rumble we're
live on youtube we're live on facebook
you can watch this on rumble you can
watch us on youtube so you can rewatch
this live on rumble or youtube subscribe
to my youtube channel when you get a
chance subscribe to my newsletter please
you guys so you know where i am what i'm
gonna do what i'm gonna do what i'm not
gonna do
all the different information the free
recipes all the stuff going on subscribe
to my newsletter go to medicalmedium.com
or you can see the link below in the
profile or see the link in the bio or
see the link in description
and one more thing
i just want to ask you guys
is
check out my amazon lives
they're a hoot they're a who
follow me on my amazon live platform
link is also there too for you to find
those are fun it's the medical medium
cooking show and the medical medium
cooking show i show you tips that i
never show anybody anywhere anyhow
many of them are just personal tips that
i do in my kitchen so that's something
you guys can do remember the mm-900 is
on sale it's the best sale i've ever
seen this machine on yet it's a it's a
money saver it cuts your produce in half
or at least apart it saves you hundreds
of dollars as each month goes by it pays
for itself this juicer right here has
bought me juicer after juicer after
juicer with the money i've saved so what
happens is i bought less celery and
because i bought less celery and less
other things and this juice is more i've
saved so much money it's paid for itself
it's 90 off at omegajuicers.com check it
out
i just know i love you guys you guys i'm
going to go live again
i'm going live on ig
the link is in the bio over there on
tick tock
right
and and on amazon you'll see the link
for amazon live the medical meme cooking
show the link is in the bio on tick tock
and the link is in the description you
guys
are any of you guys going to me with uh
going going to me again going with me to
ig
you can also be on telegram i'm going to
turn telegram back on
i'm going to turn tick tock back on so
tick tock's going back on telegram's
going back on and then i'm turning on
instagram
and do you guys want to hang out again
maybe maybe we'll talk about some
different stuff maybe it'll be a little
bit of this
a little bit of that
maybe things will get crazy
maybe they won't
we'll see
all right