we're live right now this is day two
medical medium heavy metal detox cleanse
challenge
how how is everybody doing because when
you're getting those metals out
it feels good it feels good because the
metals live
in you rent free i said something
yesterday that
i haven't talked in depth about before
and it's the mind control that metals do
when they're in the brain when someone's
severely depressed
it changes and shapes their life
when they're severely depressed because
from an unknown origin of depression not
just because they had a great loss or
something tragic happened and they're
depressed because of that or they're
suffering from depression
from you know maybe maybe a relationship
breakup or anything like that that's
different those things happen in life we
know that right
and then we know why that depression is
connected right
but what about the millions and millions
hundreds of millions of people on planet
earth
that are suffering from sadness that's
unexplained depression that's
unexplained
mega depression the kind where they
can't function can't do anything can't
get out of bed
can't make decisions can't can't get
empowered can't just move forward in
their life right
and that depression is because of those
toxic heavy metals inside the brain
and what that means right there those
metals do a lot when they give us our
symptoms and our conditions when they
give us that social anxiety when they
give us that nervousness
when we're sweating for no reason but we
just think it's because we're a nervous
type
you know you're a nervous type you know
that's why you're sweating
that's why your palms are soaking wet
and your your pits are drenched and
just going up to talk to somebody and
you're sweating and you're nervous about
anything
and you're getting you're even tremoring
with it that nervousness that's from
metals
that's what that is it's not that you're
someone that's a super nervous type
no the metals actually shape who we
are in so many ways and that's what
metals do metals cause adhd
they cause brain fog they cause autism
they shape who we are in many ways
and no one wants to talk about it no one
ever wants to know about it that's just
the way it works conventional medicine
forget it they don't want to go near
metals net metals or in all the
pharmaceuticals
they're in antibiotics cold medicine
thyroid medication just in everything
you know cold white spraying i became a
nervous type
after my removal of amalgams
yeah yeah i've heard that story a lot
over the years too
and and i understand so
metals do a lot to us but what are we
doing
to the metals what are we doing to the
metals what are we doing to the
industries that cause all this metal
stuff air fresheners
why do i always talk about air
fresheners air fresheners
why do i do that why do i talk about
scented candle send to candles right
i remember someone made fun of me it was
last year and
it was social media influencer and they
had uh
a little bit of a decent following and
they were you know they're known out
there and
what was happening was all this stuff
happening in the world and i'm sitting
there talking about air fresheners
and they said what a jerk that medical
medium is
there's things happening in the world
right now and all he cares about with
his old big old platform is
he just cares about air fresheners air
fresheners what a jerk
and they actually said something made a
little video and put it around
and it's like are you kidding me like
you know and they were saying that they
were like are you kidding me he's just
talking about air fresheners oh yeah
air fresheners are poisoning people
poisoning your children poisoning your
babies
no one knows you fill in your babies
with with
all up with metals and it's going to
shape their life
yeah it's serious stuff now people are
talking about
air fresheners being bad and fragrances
and stuff like that you know after all
the years of work i put into it
of course don't give medical medium
credit but make sure you take but try to
take medical medium down
because he talks about it you know it's
crazy so
the point is is this stuff matters and
what are we doing to get the medals out
well right now we're day two of the
heavy metal detox cleanse
challenge this is an important time i'm
excited you guys i'm gonna make the
heavy metal detox smoothie i might make
something else too it's gonna make a
little pudding with some honey and add a
few things and
have a little fun and we made the
applesauce yesterday it's really
exciting
do you have the cleanse the heel book i
just want to ask if everybody has it
this is critical it's on page 179 heavy
metal detox cleanses in
cleanse the heel amazon.com us it's
imperative to have the book someday in
your life
i know some people say i'll get it
someday it's like well are you going to
heal someday
are you going to get better someday or
are you going to get the medals out
someday
are you going to take it serious someday
what are you going to do someday you're
going to get the book
okay and so anyway amazon.com us 16.99
that sale price is ridiculous for this
book and
it's really incredible because it makes
it affordable for people
51 off try to get at the library if you
want to
but that's the book right there saving
lives around the world
heavy metal detox cleanse is in here
and this is a special time so
let me cover a couple of topics that are
really important okay
so what metals do is create a mind
control situation
and the powers that be in the industries
partly know this you know i talk about
the mercury man
the mercury man i've talked about that
in the past books the medical medium
books
the mercury man is an is an ancient
industrial figure that has been making
sure that mercury
is in our lives in a negative way
it always has been it goes long before
your time long before your parents time
long before their parents time
generation after generation it goes back
a long way
and the mercury man is the mercury
industry
in the mercury industry is one of the
most powerful industries probably in the
world that makes
the caffeine industry look like a joke
really and the caffeine industry is a
powerhouse because
they're also in the mind control
business too caffeine industry
the job of the caffeine industry is to
make sure that mommy's in every
and every baby on the planet gets
addicted to caffeine that's the caffeine
industry's role
and caffeine industries role is to make
sure that big pharma uses caffeine in
every drug and they do by the way
they just don't list it in ninety
percent of the drugs but caffeine's in
every single drug that big pharma does
right
so the mind controls the caffeine
industry but the mercury
industry is the quiet evil large
industry
powerful industry that if you got to
think about a a silo a rice to a grain
of rice
right the caffeine industry and big
pharma
is like this this tiny little grain
of rice the mercury man in the mercury
industry
is this silo of rice that's the size
it's like it's like the richest people
in the world you you'll see the richest
people in the world
publicly right you'll think oh whoa hey
wait a minute let me just look this up
forbes or
let me just look up the richest person
in the world is this no
it's not the richest people in the world
aren't listed
they're trillionaires not billionaires
the richest people in the world that
control the world are trillionaires
so it's important to know the difference
right and that's the illumination
they're the trillionaires and then euro
and then when you're a billionaire right
you're the top billionaire you're just
kind of like a public
you know you're just like that public uh
facade for others like oh that's the
richest person in the world no it's not
it's no it's not there's richer people
in the world that controlled world war
ii they're trillionaires now they
controlled world war
one and they're they were grandfathered
in they controlled world war
ii they controlled the wars they control
everything they're the they're the
richest people in the world they're
trillionaires right
you don't hear about them because you
won't and they're the ones that pull
strings you know and the mercury man is
in that
category it's not in the caffeine
caffeines
a mind control big industry right but
the mercury industry is oh my god
you couldn't even imagine what that is
that's a difference so
and that mercury industry is in
everybody's head
it's in our head it's in our brains so
it's the
tourette's it's the spasms it's the
ticks that's mercury in the brain
so my hey my son has tourette's my son
has mercury
in his brain my daughter has tourettes
my daughter has mercury in her brain
my son has severe depression and he
almost committed suicide some mercury in
his brain
my daughter has severe depression she
almost committed suicide it's mercury in
her brain
this is serious depersonalization
parkinson's disease alzheimer's dementia
mercury mercury mercury and these are
just some of the things that ocd
ocd's crypto link i remember i did an
ocb thing a while back
and i think i did the ocd post right
and and all of a sudden i got attacked
right by all these ocd trolls right
and it was just coming left and right by
the thousands it was unbelievable
there's
thousands and thousands of ocd trolls
saying
how dare i say that ocd is caused by
toxic heavy metals how dare i and
they're just coming by the thousands you
guys
thousands literally in three days time
eight or ten thousand uh ocd trolls you
don't know ocd
uh i'm dr so-and-so i'm nutritionist
so-and-so
i've got ocd and you don't even know
it's not metals
and it's like oh my god ocd's caused by
metals
that's what it's caused by it is always
will be
it was it is now it's always going to be
and so it's these metals
i remember talking to somebody many
years ago right who had ocd really bad
really bad there's different kinds of
ocd and there's different levels of ocd
right so and one person that
their ocd was was was their head even
connected to their body
so she believed her head wasn't
connected to her body she would have to
be
she'd have to be in front of a mirror
all the time and then that ocd would
calm down when she'd see her head on top
of her body in the mirror
and then she would be away from there
for a little while trying to function
and then the ocd would kick up ocd would
kick up and all of a sudden
because you'd have to go and find the
mirror again to make sure her head was
attached to her body
that was that kind of ocd there's people
that i've known somebody that was
that would drive to work and they would
just hit a pothole in the in the road
and then they're worried they ran over
somebody or something so they'd have to
go
all the way around and they would be
late for work because they'd have to go
all the way around and drive down the
road to make sure they didn't hit
something and that something isn't still
on the road and they'd go back around
and back around and back around
and they'd be an hour late for work
every morning and then get fired
excessive compulsive disorder is real
and i mean i've seen it all in the 35
years and then the thoughts
thoughts are another thing too
repetitive thoughts and the thoughts and
thoughts and nothing can soothe it and
not just the thoughts but the taking
action
that's when ocd gets really really bad
not just the thoughts but the action
taking right
like did i close your refrigerator did i
close it it closed well i can't sleep
it's four o'clock in the morning because
i've just checked 57 times
from the time i went to bed at 10 a 10
10 at 10 p.m at night
and the thoughts of going to die like
you know am i gonna die or if i say
something wrong someone's gonna die
and it's something bad gonna happen and
it and goes on and on that's mercury
that's the mercury man the mercury man
has
tremendous power over mind control
over mind control over the human race
that's the mercury man
okay and you know
let's go into this a little bit deeper
in a whole bit
so we'll talk about how metals work
let's just get cover let's get into the
lemon water we got a lot to cover it's
going to be
a big day
so i'm going to talk in a little bit
about how ocd works how
electrical impulses hit heavy metals in
the brain but i want to get started at
least on lemon water
before we go into that that's the plan
let's do it
lemon water you gotta hydrate
remember that that's important we're day
two if you just came on here
the heavy metal detox cleanse a2 i'm
looking for a lemon you guys
right i'm gonna squeeze half a lemon in
here you can do a whole lemon if you
want inside your 16 to 32 ounces of
water i do half a lemon sometimes i do a
whole lemon all depends
all depends right someone just said how
do i get metals out
on tick-tock we're day two of the heavy
metal detox cleanse first things first
for the person on tick tock do you have
the cleanse to heal book
right amazon.com 16.99
51 off get the book peach 179 heavy
metal detox cleanse learn how to do it
you could do it you could do it
gee said g colgan says i had ocd for
decades
thank god things heal
incredible things do heal
they do heal elizabeth isn't that funny
lll
hey what's going on here
what's he doing okay
16 to 32 ounces i know someone to come
on and be like hey
how do what metals what are you talking
about metals
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water hydrate
in the morning what happens is hydration
is important because how do you get
anything out of the body that's toxic
how do you get anything out of the body
that's toxic
when you're not hydrated
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water not hot
not hot water right
medical medium information started the
whole flushing the liver with
lemon water that's original information
from medical medium right
and then all of a sudden years later
years later i do the lemon in hot water
because someone
you know you know someone shifted gears
out there and
the trending world and we're like oh
okay let's let's
ruin something that originally that
originally comes from medical medium
spirit of compassion let's destroy it
and let's make sure now it's hot water
so no one benefits from it
the details matter it matters okay
and it's not eight to twelve ounces of
lemon water some people do a cup of
lemon water and make sure it's hot and
they got their lemon in there ah they
did it okay this is great
no in order to flush the liver in order
to flush the liver and body of toxins
has to be lemon water that hasn't been
killed off
it has to be raw not cooked lemon
raw lemon details matter
and it's that raw lemon and the 16 to 32
ounces of water
that makes the wheels go around okay
really important
we're going to cover that i'm going to
cover lots of stuff so we got the 16 32
ounces of lemon water
that's the first thing an empty stomach
so let's head into
running some celery through if you guys
just came on here we're talking about
mind control we're talking about the
mercury man
we're talking about things like ocd talk
about tourette's too we'll talk about
all the different stuff depression
anxiety we're going to talk about how
metals work in the brain
how how metal interacts with electricity
so that's important to know all on its
own
we're going to talk about how the five
ingredients work in the heavy metal
detox smoothie and the heavy metal detox
cleanse that
that makes it all happen we're gonna
talk about that how cool
how cool i'm excited i'm gonna do a
little quick
uh celery run you guys don't mind
because this is the second part of the
cleanse get some celery juice going
right
looking around okay
here we are
get a little celery juice now celery
juice is critical because
this is a complete electrolyte
what that means a complete electrolyte
just so you guys know
is it means it goes to the brain
every single part of the brain
neurotransmitter clio cells neurons
left hemisphere right hemisphere
complete electrolyte doesn't get stopped
we eat food and we drink drink
to get an electrolyte somewhere
in our body functioning working getting
it to our nervous system and brain
that's why we eat it's part of why we
eat we're
gathering electrolytes celery juice is a
complete electrolyte
it helps dislodge metals it's not a
metal remover
but it will flush metals out that have
been removed
by like say the heavy metal detox
smoothie
but what the celery does
is it helps to loosen metals
so they pop out easier
mercury lead aluminum cadmium
nickel arsenic calcium
[Music]
toxic calcium which is a
toxic heavy metal
interesting right that's interesting
medical medium information classified
aluminum as being a heavy metal
you guys just so you know
science doesn't believe aluminum is a
heavy metal they'll say it's a light
metal so
medical medium you're so wrong you you
included aluminum in there
classification of a toxic heavy metal
is the damage it does neurotoxically
to the brain or the damage it does
to the body that constitutes a toxic
heavy metal a reclassified aluminum
purposely i did it years ago
because does this make sense to you well
aluminum is not a toxic heavy metal it's
not a heavy metal it's a light metal so
we shouldn't worry about it
let's make sure we get lots of aluminum
in our brains and body let's make sure
aluminum
does that make aluminum safe to you no
we have to classify it as a heavy metal
we have no choice
or no one's going to take aluminum
series when it's actually a dangerous
metal
i just bought your book from amazon
and i don't read books can i just say
i'm honored
for real can i say i'm honored
that's actually incredible and
thank you for thank you for getting the
book because it's going to help you
and that's what i'm here for and that's
what it's about
[Music]
i want to make sure you get a chance and
every opportunity to better your life
don't add anything to your celery juice
i know i sound like a broken record but
no
ice no ice cubes no water no
lemon juice my god talking about
annoying
you want to know what annoying is you're
sitting there spending years trying to
get the celery juice out there in the
world so people can get their life back
and then
somebody in the health industry is just
like oh add lemon to your celery juice
and everybody's adding lemon to it and
i'm like okay you're not getting
benefits you're not getting benefits
you're not getting benefits huh what a
waste
[Applause]
[Music]
i mean you if you sometimes you can't
help people if you want to help them i
mean you can do it i mean
there's just so much in the way right
so much in the way renata says
renatabanada says aw is it okay to chop
and trim my celery stalks before i put
them
in a bowl of with warm water
and do so i i would probably i wouldn't
chop them if you're gonna do i would
probably give them
you know what i would wash them whole
first
and get some of the dirt out heavier
stuff out or anything any kind of dirt
around and dirt in the inside stocks
right i'd probably
wash that out a little bit first before
i chopped
and and did you know i'd do the little
dish soap in that point right
natural dips dish up a little bit in the
bowl in the whole form at least for a
little bit and then chop it after and
give it another rinse if you wanted to
the reason why i don't like to chop it
up in pieces and small pieces
you chop it up in small pieces and put
in a bowl you're losing celery juice in
between all those chops
and it's in there and you're kind of
like it's kind of like bleeding out you
know
it's kind of like bleeding out
all right can we do a i see another
question i want to answer questions to
you guys i don't want to just talk over
you guys
susan says can we do this on a budget
watching the amount of celery you are
using and adding
up the money does it have to be organic
well first of all the juicer i used cuts
the celery bill in half
so that's the mm-900 hds it's an
investment right it's a it's a couple
hundred dollars or if it's on sale it's
200 and something dollars
but um but susan so the juicer i had
actually squeezes more juice out of the
celery so the pulp is really dry you get
more juice so
that alone can can cut the celery juice
bill down a lot so then eventually you
pay for the juicer by doing that and
then whatever in the whole bit it's
awesome
okay that's one two is um
yeah you can use conventional celery now
i get punished for that
i can't tell you how many lashings i get
right that's one of one of the areas i
get lashed really bad
is the whole conventional celery thing
so people do posts about me out there
they do posts
they do articles they try to rip me down
all the time it's just it's i guess it's
just 24 7 thing out there so one of the
ways they do it is
he likes conventional celery celery is
on the top
you know the top the top 12 or top 10
you know
most pesticide radiant crops they say
out there but what they don't realize
is that it's there isn't a top ten
pesticide
ridden crop there isn't top ten anything
conventional is practically spray the
amount it's a schedule of three times a
week
one of the most difficult things i run
into is how nobody knows anything about
farming that writes these things and
tries to attack people so
here you are you're trying to attack not
you but the people will try to attack me
and say he supports conventional
celery and and it's the the top spray
crop
no it's not there's only
all conventional crops of all foods
conventional foods
outside maybe a couple are sprayed on a
schedule of three times a week
that means broccoli that means
everything conventional everything
conventionally zucchini conventional
cucumber conventional tomato
they're sprayed three times a week it's
the schedule for all conventional crops
so they'll say they'll say hey you know
he supports conventional celery it's on
the top ten
there's no top ten they're all sprayed
three times a week
just like organic produce is sprayed
an organic produce is sprayed with the
msg nicotine spray
right that's what they do so they use
the msg caffeine nicotine spray
and that's what's sprayed because those
are neuroantagonists so that's what's
sprayed on all the organic crops you got
to wash
both both for one both foods right
but the the whole thing is that celery
conventional celery
you got to wash it and yeah it outweighs
what residue is inside that celery when
it's conventional so definitely i
support you
if you do conventional celery a hundred
percent because that celery juice
is gonna be fixing things in you and
cleaning out things in you more so than
what's on that celery
it's going to be cleaning out and fixing
you and getting you better
that conventional celery i mean this is
just common sense stuff
really this information but it shows you
the alternative movement
nobody really knows anything about
anything and it's really sad
anyway we just did some celery juice you
guys if you just got on here this is an
interesting one you don't want to miss
we're talking about mind control and
we're talking about some other things
too electricity in the brain
all of it and we're juicing celery too
but
and we're gonna make some stuff
hopefully if we got a chance so this is
day two the medical medium heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge
just gotta remind you once again you
guys you've got to have the cleanse to
heal book
it's on sale in amazon.com us uh
51 off this book specifically is so low
there
i i don't know if somebody at amazon
just you know just doesn't want me to
keep the lights on or whatever it is but
they got this thing priced so low and i
love it because i know that even though
it costs more to print it i just know
that people are getting an opportunity
to heal and i love that
love that so take advantage of that
price why they keep it there right now
so let me strain this you have to strain
your celery juice
and that's really important to know got
to strain it
let's do that
it's critical to keep any pull out
any leftover little fibers or
pulp you want out okay so that's
important to know
so that's your celery juice right there
your lemon water
hydrates you it helps flush
the toxins out in the morning flush the
liver and the body
the celery juice flushes the liver too
cleanses the body of toxins too
but also loosens up metals
it's a complete electrolyte that goes to
the brain
electrolytes get magnetically pulled
into your brain and brain stem
important though okay so if you're an
electrolyte and you're swimming around
and you're swimming around
and you're swimming around in the
bloodstream swimming around in the body
right swimming around in the blood-brain
barrier right
across the blood-brain barrier into the
spinal fluid if you're in electrolyte
and you're swimming around you
magnetically get
pulled up to the brain and get stuck
there electrolytes get sucked
into the brain they get sucked
into the brain so when a complete
electrolyte in celery juice gets into
the brain
it's an entirely different experience
than partial electrolytes that get
sucked into the brain
partial electrolytes complete
electrolyte
partial electrolytes okay just take
any herb or vegetable here's cilantro
which we're going to talk about that's a
partial electrolyte partial right
you take broccoli a partial whatever
vegetable you want is a partial
asparagus partial celery complete
complete complete
that's why it has the power to help
dislodge metals it's a complete
electrolyte
okay if you just got
on here okay just got on here with you
in the cleanse the cleanse the heel
heavy metal detox cleanse challenge
right here so we've got the heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge right here okay
heavy metal detox smoothie
the cleanse we're in the challenge all
of it here's the book
really important to have this book right
here make sure you have this page 179
we're day two so if you just got on here
you're like what is this
hey what is he doing what's going on
what are you doing
if you're here and you're doing that
then stay here for today and stay here
for tomorrow
because tomorrow's day three don't miss
it all right
it's fun it's fun all right
we did before we make the heavy metal
detox smoothie
let's talk about our topics a little bit
and let's cover the last couple
remaining things on celery juice don't
mix anything in it
don't don't add the water don't add the
lemon like i said earlier don't add
apple
you blow it you blow its power you blow
its power
it's why celery has to be in its herbal
form that's herbal medicine i used a
medical device which is a juicer
and i juiced it and that's herbal
medicine sitting right there you guys
if you chop up a celery stick and throw
it in
a tuna in a tuna sandwich or something
right or you're mixing tuna fish and
mayo and you throw some tiny little
celery bits
it's not going to work if you do crudis
hay
and you got a little dip of french onion
dip and you got a little this and some
ranch
whatever you're doing you got your
celery stick it's not gonna work if you
chop up celery and throw it in a salad
it's not gonna work
it's an it's an herbal extraction you're
creating from an actual herb and you're
trying to get a larger amount of its
juice
by itself extract it from
the pulp from its skeleton
okay it's important to know fiber in an
herb or vegetable is only to hold it up
so it can find
sun it's not packed with nutrients
sorry to say it's not packed with
nutrients
so the fiber the fiber in the stem
of cilantro just say for example because
i got cilantro here
the fiber and the stem of cilantro was
just to hold it up
to get it to the sun be like hey sun sun
hey
get in that shiny bright sun it's a
skeleton
we don't digest it it doesn't provide
nutrients
so when you juice something with a
really good juicer
you're extracting the nutrients and
leaving its skeleton behind
okay that's all and what you're doing
with an herbal extraction like celery
juice
you're doing just that you don't want
anything but the juice the herbal
extraction just like you're doing an
herbal tea of some kind and you're
trying to do that extraction
today's in for lots of information today
when you guys have you just came on here
get your notepads out get your pens lots
of info a lot of different stuff
it's day two the heavy metal detox
clench challenge
if someone's sensitive sensitive and
they're sensitive to celery juice a
little bit they're sensitive to whatever
this is really toxic
they're really toxic do smaller amounts
of everything smaller amounts of
everything it means they're really
really toxic
i could do four ounces of celery juice
six ounces eight ounces
four ounces of heavy metal detox
smoothie eight ounces
you'll work your way up a little bit of
spirulina maybe in some coconut water a
little bit of this maybe a little bit of
that i'll show you i'll show you
right love the info nancy nancy newman
cool i'm honored you're here thank you
it's fun info all right i'm trying to
read comments at the same time
juggling i'm juggling i'm juggling all
right
let me throw a cap on this baby
because i might just knock it over and i
don't want to do that
all right before we make the heavy metal
detox smoothie let's talk about the
information
that information is critical linda says
what about the fiber and fruit
well the fiber's good was fiber's fine
that's the whole point
five are the pulp in fruit it's the pulp
in fruit
okay so fruits pulp more so than
fiber vegetables fiber
so that's the other thing too pulp and
fruit
pectin pulp fruit right
wild blueberry right here pectin and
pulp
we ms shrew is fiber
pectin pulp right it's fibrous
but not fiber right pectin pulp
fiber fiber
stems of the vegetable
anyway and fiber in the pectin pulp
which is fibrous and fruit holds the
fruit together
so you have a piece of fruit when you
when you
chomp on that fruit your body disregards
it
it disregards all the or or discards
all that pulp in any kind of fibrous
pulp
right it discards that you poop that out
in your toilet
but you it's your body extracted all the
nutrients
from all the juice and the cell and what
was in the cell structures
and then the fiber helps us go to
bathroom
when we have problems inside our guts
and we can't go to bathroom like
constipation issues inflammation right
tiffany says are we not supposed to are
we not supposed to cut out the stems of
the cilantro into the heavy butt no
stems go in there yeah stems go in there
it's fine
absolutely i throw the stems in i'm
gonna do that in a little bit
yeah all right let's move forward a
little bit
there's a lot of juice in the stems a
lot of juice in the stems
keep that in mind lots of juice in the
stems
all right when your brain gets filled
with microscopic
nano bits of metal from all the
different places we get it air
fresheners colognes perfumes clones of
perfumes
there's pesticides in clones perfumes
you got do you guys love you love to
smell pesticides
you love it when someone sprays a
perfume on them
you love it when someone sprays what's
so called a clean perfume
perfume on them you like pesticide smell
isn't it nice
doesn't that pesticide smell so good did
you know that
that every single perfume and cologne
company has pesticides in the in the
clone of perfume
i'm not talking about traces i'm talking
about pesticides
not traces pesticide
do you like the smell of pesticide
because that's what perfume is that's
the smell of perfume
did you guys know that did you guys ever
smell pesticides from a farm spraying
it's perfume did you know that it's
cologne did you know there's rat killer
rodenticides that all the farms use for
their crops
did you know it smells just like cologne
identical you can't miss a bee
did you know that all the different
sprays for all the other different crops
did you know
did you know insecticides around your
building in your apartment building has
perfume in it
because it is did you know they're both
the same
in many ways did you know all perfumes
have a small amount
and sometimes large amount of pesticide
in them
you like that so let me just smell
somebody's perfume that's great oh i got
to go somewhere i'm going to be out in a
store and restaurant oh
that's great that's some perfume someone
has on there
yeah i get it uh whoa you want to smell
nice okay
thank you for the pesticide exposure
thank you kindly thank you kindly
this information you will not hear
anywhere else
until someone takes it and doesn't cite
it back to here which
i saw today earlier which was really
frustrating when i saw what happened
today
someone some influencer literally was
like
reading verbatim out of liver rescue and
didn't cite medical medium
nobody knew the liver did all these
things blah blah blah but
yet you know all right
sluggish stagnant liver because fats
burden the liver
and pesticides and all these other
chemicals and toxic stuff that gets
inside the livers medical medium info
viruses that get inside the liver making
it sluggish and stagnant byproduct in
the liver
causing all these problems medical
medium information it's amazing
people can just take it and not say
where it comes from
mv doom i got so annoyed when i see
people rip off mm info you then you must
be like
really awake and seeing it out there
like you're meaning like your eyes are
on it out there totally totally i got
friends all the time to contact me and
just like oh my god it just makes
everybody sick actually makes my friends
sick makes my family sick just makes
that people who you know care about like
preserving information so people get the
rest of it so they can heal it's like it
makes it makes a lot of people it's
disgusting really
hurts people because they can't get back
to where the infamous information is
so metal and metal exposure
is rampant right now so when you're
doing the perfumes clones of scented
candles and air fresheners
that's metal that goes directly to the
brain through the sinus passage
i'm not talking about just in the lungs
and it finds its way to the brain that
way which it does too
mouth too the mouth you smell perfume
you're
eating it it's landing on your mouth
while you're talking to someone
it's landing in your mouth it's coating
your whole throat right down
and you're swallowing that perfume
you're eating that chemical company that
chemical giant's perfume
chemical companies create the
ingredients for perfume to come together
just think about that a little bit right
this isn't a 10 an attack on perfume
it's just a reality check of how much of
it we got in us because i smell perfume
you just walk outside you smell it's
blowing off people on the street
then you can just choke it down be like
thanks for that pesticide spray i really
needed that right now
thanks for that thanks well that's great
god
i'm sure you're poisoning your children
too at the same time not that they
it's their fault it's not their fault
because the industries they betray us
because they're
they don't let anybody know you know and
that goes back to the heavy metal world
the heavy metal world toxic heavy metal
world is a really
really silent industry
it's in everything it's in nano sprays
on everything it's in fungicide on
clothing it's
it's it's all over the place you guys
it's not just aluminum foil that i
showed you and open up every day
it's everywhere okay and then it's in
pharmaceuticals all the pharmaceuticals
metal deposits interrupt electricity
swimming around in your brain
metals can make decisions for you
and they can push you to make some
pretty shitty decisions
and and make you feel like a bad person
in this at the same time
confidence issues come from toxic heavy
metals many times
not all the time but a lot of the time
confidence issues you guys
comes from toxic heavy metals inside the
brain
confidence issues yeah
metals really do shape the fabric of our
lives
i know and they control too they control
us
what happens is electricity swims
through the brain and hits the deposits
of toxic heavy metals and ricochets off
that's how ocd occurs ocd occurs because
there's a deposit of toxic heavy metal
such as mercury sitting on a neuron
an electrical impulse keeps on hitting
it over and over again
and bouncing back up and when it bounces
back up
another one's coming down another one's
coming down
so let's just pretend let's just pretend
this pencil is a neuron
okay just pretend this pencil is a
neuron right
and you got toxic heavy metals right in
the middle
let's just pretend it's in the middle
okay so you got toxic but a little bit
of mercury aluminum right in the middle
of that pencil
an electrical impulse is coming down
that neuron with information
and as it's coming down real fast i'm
going real slow as it's coming down it
hits the deposit
and if the deposit's big enough it
explodes and bounces back up as it's
going back
up another electrical impulse is coming
up behind it
and crashing into it that's where
i better check is these lights go on
these lights are on but i better
nope nope i shut them off i know i shut
those lights off
um i better check i better check to make
sure this lights are off yep they're off
right
yep they're on nope they're definitely
off
i'll check again let me see
okay my anxiety's starting to rise now
i'm trying to have an anxiety attack
because i don't i know i shut those
lights off i know i shut those lights
off
i gotta look again god damn it oh
yep all right oh
my god now i'm having a panic attack
because i did it four times
already and i'm going to do it one more
time
yep i sit down i shut it off
i've heard that a thousand times when i
was practicing for 35 years
that's just that variety of ocd
that's a positive heavy metal
sitting on a neuron an electrical
impulse keeps on hitting it
each electrical impulse keeps on hitting
it and
part of that electrical impulse gets
ricocheted back
that's what that is that's what that is
that's you in the car ingrid see that's
me in the car
oh you poor thing oh god oh
and here's the other thing that
electrical impulse you guys
is carrying information information is
in that electrical impulse going down
that neuron
so cutting across that neuron is
information
and that information
okay can blow up
blow up right when that information in
the electrical impulse hits that
deposit of toxic heavy metal sitting
inside the neuron
it could blow up and mess your head up
and now your foot you're frustrated
you're you're
flustered that's it you're confused
you're
you're off your game you're stressed out
when you shouldn't be
saskia why are there many different ocd
mine is different i'll tell you why
because there's many different toxic
heavy metals and amounts in different
places of the brain
someone might have toxic heavy metals in
the emotional center of the brain
someone may have it in the frontal lobe
someone may have it everywhere
someone may have it sprinkled about the
left hemisphere and then on the right
hemisphere have
larger deposits and someone may have
more mercury and someone may have more
lead and someone may have mercury and
aluminum when someone has aluminum and
copper
someone may have a little bit of all of
it someone may just have one r2
mainly and lightly on the others it
changes
everything everything
it's advanced information the info is
amazing tick-tock honored
thank you for being here and tick tock
thank you spread the word
say hey check out this cleansed heel
book
it's saving lives around the world
and i think i'm going to turn that back
on
51 off amazon.com us make sure you check
it out
before we make the heavy metal detox
smoothie let's cover a little bit more
let's go
how do the five ingredients work why is
there five things in the heavy metal
detox movie
why is there because there's one more
than one toxic heavy metal that's one
thing right there all on its own
right there's different depths of your
toxic
heavy metal you may have a toxic heavy
metal
deep in the core of your liver not just
on the outside
or adjacent lobe you may actually have
toxic heavy metal very deep
in the core of the liver you may have
the metals in the lining of the
intestinal tract i'm not talking about
inside the intestinal tract i'm talking
about in the lining itself
smack dab in the middle of the lining
you might have
toxic heavy metals in the brain
but in the brain stem a whole nother
game
when those metals in the brain stem and
it brings them in flames
whole another game right there on its
own right
susan i've been trying to figure out why
i stress out when nothing is going on
it just added more stress to my life
trying to to find
what was wrong with me absolutely and
you know what
it's it's it's a tricky situation too
because then we're seeing the
neurologists and then we're seeing our
fifth doctor and our temp doctor and now
we're seeing you know
another nutritionist who's got the keto
diet down they think and then you get
and then now you're seeing an rd
and now you're seeing a chiropractor
right now you're seeing
now you're back to a do and a naturopath
and back to a specialist and a gp and
now you're back to
another neurologist and now you're at
the pulmonologist's office too to boot
absolutely and guess what
the mercury man is laughing his ass off
the mercury man laughing laughing
laughing
because the mercury man is grandfathered
in with documents inside of a vault
that originally stemmed from the mercury
industry back over a thousand years ago
and you can't touch those documents
they're trusted in forever those
documents will say
mercury will never leave us our lives or
the industries
it will be there forever doesn't matter
if the dentist stop putting in her teeth
it's everywhere it's in medications it's
all over the place
that's the mercury man all right
which reminds me here's one way the
mercury man gets in us right there
the mercury man gets in is through fish
oil supplements
methyl mercury methyl mercury
traces the essence of mercury so it goes
straight to our brain
never do fish oil supplements eat fish
you're better off i'm not i don't eat
fish
i don't eat fish they're filled with
dioxins and metals right
but the point is is you can eat fish
and still do the heavy metal detox
smoothie and cleanse and still
heal you can still eat fish if you're a
fish eater
fish oil entirely different
entirely different the mercury in a
piece of fish is way different
than when it's in this form right here
that's the form it becomes methyl
mercury
that's the form that gets to your brain
all right are we having any fun yet are
you guys
bummed out so no mercury in vimergy
right
vimergy does not add mercury to their
supplements no
all right let's move forward you guys
um heavy metal detox ingredients let's
go into that
why is that important okay
fish oil is different than dha keep that
in mind
say like a plant-based dha supplement or
so forth
entirely different fish oil is
a billion heads and tails and fins
of of millions and millions and millions
of fish
thrown into machines and pressed and
squeezed down
to create the fish oil for the fish oil
industry
right all right
cilantro wild blueberries barley grass
juice powder
atlantic dolls right
okay and spirulina you're looking at
five things right here
five things one two three four five if
my ocd kicks in i'm gonna count it over
and over again one two three four five
one two three four five right so
the whole point is is you're looking at
five different things
guess what you're not looking at
guess what you're not looking at where
is the bentonite clay
bending my clay where are you been like
clay
where are you where's the charcoal
charcoal that was in somebody else's
brain scheme
someone's big old brain scheme uh-huh
where's the charcoal
where are you zeolite
zeolite why is zeolite not in here
see why it's not in here uh-huh nope
nope nope and we'll talk about that why
these aren't in there
see light's not in here garlic
where's the garlic why is the garlic in
here
i mean i like garlic garlic's in recipes
garlics and medical mean recipes but why
is it in the heavy metal detox smoothie
where is it okay
and what else what else do people like
to say remove metals what else do people
come up with like takomini stuff
that removes metals so let's go into it
a little bit why aren't those things
in here one is bentonite clay
is really aggressive on the intestinal
tract it doesn't remove toxic heavy
metals instead it'll make crohn's
colitis celiac ibs a hell of a lot worse
it'll make uh intestinal problems a lot
worse
and it's damaging to the lining of the
intestinal tract
so bentonite clay is the last thing you
want to ever take or consume no matter
what never mind in a heavy metal detox
whatever the heck
that's one thing right there said to the
next one charcoal
charcoal suffocates your intestinal
lining
it stops nutrients from getting to your
liver to get into your bloodstream to
get into anywhere
charcoal suffocates good bacteria
good bacteria but yet helps bad bacteria
thrive do you know why
charcoal removes oxygen from your
good bacteria bad bacteria
thrives with no oxygen do you see how it
works charcoal
in your gut proliferates the bad
bacteria making you sicker
making bugs grow while killing your good
bacteria because you build
good bacteria thrives on oxygen
bad bugs don't like oxygen
because oxygen kills them charcoal
makes you sicker that's why it's not in
here
that's just one reason you don't swallow
charcoal you don't swallow it
okay oh wait where's the chlorella
chlorella where are you where are you
chlorella where are you
you're not in here either you're not
part of the five
chlorella doesn't remove toxic heavy
metals and
if it ever did it drops it along the way
which makes you sicker chlorella is also
filled with bacteria and has put a lot
of people in the hospital
it's not monitored it's not checked
properly and chlorella
tends to harbor bacteria because guess
what
bad bacteria thrives in chlorella why
hmm why does bad bacteria thrive in
chlorella
spirulina's antibacterial
bacteria doesn't thrive in spirulina
i mean vimorgy independently tests their
stuff for bacteria anyway
but it doesn't thrive in in spirulina
why does bad bacteria
thrive in chlorella that means there's
something in chlorella that feeds bad
bacteria hmm
so let's be another hack in the industry
of alternative medicine you should be on
chlorella
i'm dr hack make sure you're on
chlorella here's a chlorella supplement
on dr hack oh heavy metals we only
learned about that because of medical
medium for 35 years
so let's come up with our own little
thoughts of what can take metals out
here's some chlorella
and then there's zeolite medical medium
book one
there's like a line in the book
can you zeolite at the time there was
one zeolite
at the time i trusted enough that you
can use for gut
for the gut situation because there
wasn't atlantic dulce available and i
use atlantic dolls to remove toxic heavy
metals from the gut
so i mentioned that you could use
a zeolite at the time but that
ship has sailed not be not just because
you can get atlantic dolls
okay i never said zeolite can remove
anything out of the body it was
intestinal track if it was
surface intestinal tract if it was
surface
in the gut health section of the book
this is an example where people take
advantage
of people they'll say medical medium
said zeolite's fine
it removes from the brain it doesn't
remove metals from the brain
it never does it never can it can't
leave
to move metals to the brain it can't get
to the brain to remove
metals it can't do it doesn't have metal
removing ability like that right
so one reason why i don't talk about
zeolite
is because the unedible zeolites entered
the industry
and they manufacture the unedible
zeolites
with the edible zeolites
you guys get where i'm going
okay unedible zeolites are like asbestos
they're dangerous to swallow
unedible zealites are dangerous
to swallow they're
dusted on edible zeolites the industry
has totally effed up and they've
actually ruined it
not that it was even that good anyway
because it wasn't
but everything's been dusted the
manufacturing process
is not trustworthy and the details
matter
i will never recommend zeolite again i
did it
years ago i've recommended it eight nine
years ago
for the gut only when there was a
zeolite i trusted
because there wasn't atlantic dulce
around
so that's the understanding about that
so people know
how things roll okay if i don't
recommend it
there's a reason that's all
if i don't recommend something there's a
reason if i don't recommend chlorella
there's a serious reason if i don't
recommend
zeolite there's a serious reason if i
don't recommend charcoal
to swallow it's a serious reason if i
don't recommend fish oil
there's a serious reason and supplement
companies have their own free will
and you can't control them you can't
control a supplement company they got
their own free will
so let's talk about the five ingredients
that do work let's go into that
and trust me the uneditable zeolites
which get dusted on the edible zeolites
are dangerous it turns into like an
asbestos powder inside the intestinal
tract and i will never take the zeolite
because i could never trust if that
stuff was dusted
because it's like you're gluten-free and
non-gluten-free if something was
manufactured
and they have to put if they manufacture
something at a factory that's also
manufacturing nuts and seeds and you're
allergic to peanuts and nuts
and it says on the package this may
contain nuts
even though there's no nuts in the
ingredient list you hear what i'm saying
you guys
this may contain nuts on the package do
you ever see that you grab a package and
you're like hey
you know there's no nuts in here let me
see this package here there's no nuts in
here but it says may contain nuts
what you're not seeing on your zeolite
your zeolite product
is may contain a zeolite that's unedible
that's basically like asbestos
because they use that in industries
and may contain that
i could do what i can to protect
everybody the best i can but
i can't beat out a thousand admin being
paid
on social media with the mlm companies
trying to get everybody to do stuff
because people just i just can't stop
whatever
janet says is dolls okay for hypothyroid
yes it is the reason why there's
confusion with hypo and hyperthyroid is
the
they don't know science research doesn't
know what causes it unless they got mm
info because it's epstein-barr
and guess what dulce is good because dos
helps to defend you against epstein-barr
yeah all right five ingredients
okay right here five ingredients why do
they work
how do they work
cilantro
cilantro has a trace mineral salt
attached to a phytochemical compound
that trace mineral salt attached to a
phytochemical compound
enters the brain not only
fuels the brain with the trace mineral
salt electrolyte
but cilantro's gift
to us unlike other things is
phytochemical compounds that remove
toxic heavy metals
from the brain are attached to the
electrolyte
that's cilantro special gift
let's move on to another one and we're
going to go into a couple things
the wild blueberry the wild blueberry
right wild blueberry juice frozen wild
blueberries
a lot of blueberry powder if you can't
get a hold of by the way those wild
blueberries
those frozen wild blueberries try to get
a hold of a juice
like the wyman's one is the one i trust
and i'm working with these guys and i'm
proud of it
because the fact that they can get this
stuff out of a field which you couldn't
believe the process
stick it through it the juicer and and
get it to us
is a miracle i never thought that drink
that dream i thought would never exist
when i was a child and i wanted people
to have this kind of medicine it's like
that that was unimaginable
and then the vimrjiwa blueberry powder
right that's an option too if you can't
get a hold of you know which is
incorrect this stuff is like
incredible it's gold right the wild
blueberry
emily says i can only find dulce flakes
harvested on the shores
of maine ah maine anyone know
if this is okay to use i do it's
fantastic to use
fantastic so the wild blueberry
it's the gatherer of metals both in the
brain
and the liver other organs too there's
antioxidants in the wild blueberry
that that aren't even documented nowhere
near documented
food science is at its infancy there's a
reason for that
because if food science is truly allowed
to press
forward and not just look at a few
nutrients like they do it's allowed to
press
forward big pharma would have to then
put a mandatory lock down on your wild
blueberries and they would then
encapsulate it and they would take it
away from you right
if food science was allowed to push
forward
and they knew that there are up to 30
antioxidants plus
even more undiscovered in the wild
blueberry undiscovered if they knew that
and they knew what the wild blueberry
did and how it removes toxic heavy
metals
they would stop they would say nope wild
blueberries dope no one's allowed to eat
them
you're gonna have to get a prescription
by our doctor
frozen wild blueberries have been sold
out
of the grocery store it's only temporary
because
here we're in the we're in the harvest
season right now so light heart light
heart it's good they're going to get the
frozen they're going to get them out
there
wyman's will get them out there they're
in the harvest season right now this the
harvesting time right
this is right now the harvesting time
that's why
i use this right now too like if you're
out of the wild blueberry i happen to
have some backups
but if you're out of it that's why i use
the uh wild blueberry juice i put that
in the smoothie i put two to four ounces
in the smoothie boom
right or i take shot glass of it every
day whatever but that's why i use that
and then you got the vimergy well
blueberry powder
you have that one you got that option
just of energy v is invictor
i m imergy.com i'm not sponsored by
these guys
but yeah tastes so good tastes so good
by the way this tastes so good it's it's
it's it's crazy when you taste it
i i don't even know what to say all
right let's go into the next stuff
dried cilantro anthony not a great
option frozen cilantro
is not the worst that could work
but you got to put it in the smoothie
right when it comes out of the freezer
you can't turn it to yuck and muck
cilantro works best with living water in
it froze you don't want you
frozen is still sketchy but you can
still use it
but you can't use the dried really it's
just it's not going to cut it but i mean
you could pop a little dried in there
and you got
you know you got like i mean at least
the connections there even if
something's missing
you know so let's move on
the wild blueberry chemical compounds
that dislodge toxic heavy metals but
hold on to them
the wild blueberry holds on to metal
holds onto metal
that's what i love about it barley grass
cheese powder
another binder of toxic heavy metals not
barley grass
broadly grass cheese powder a binder
i know we've been here for a while you
guys so let's keep on moving through
i don't want to keep you all day because
we still got more time
more fun more play coming up spirulina
that is the toxic heavy metal remover
it even removes radiation radiation
that's what i love about spirulina
radiation
what removes radiation right
chlorella doesn't
but spirulina does okay spirulina is
also
um an incredible weapon against toxic
heavy metals binds on to it grabs onto
metals helps to bring them out now why
are all these five together and then
left atlantic dulce which is the best
one for the intestinal tract now
have no fear if you don't have atlantic
dolls
you can keep it out and still do the
cleanse and still do the heavy metal
detox smoothie
it's atlantic dolls not pacific you
don't want pacific dolls atlantic dolls
you don't want pacific sparrow lena you
don't want pacific spirulina i talk
about that all the time
why you don't oceans are too polluted
and the garbage patch has shifted
more than a couple of hundred miles
the garbage patch is actually
embroaching the pacific
coast it's really sad
so yeah i don't like pacific spirulina
so
this one's the best anyway it's better
even if i like pacific if pacific the
ocean was still
like good or good enough or even better
this is the best one out there by far
the cleanest and the most potent
that's the bemidji all of these work
together
so that the metal doesn't drop
so that the metal doesn't drop right
all this works together
so that the metal doesn't drop
so if i'm a wild blueberry
moving through the body i'm a wild
blueberry
i gotta get those medals out of the
person i gotta get the medals out of the
person
i gotta get it well there's the metal
i'm gonna grab the metal let me grab it
i got it i got it okay i got the metal
i'm gonna take it down
we're gonna take it down kick away now
if i was chlorella
i'm corolla i'm chlorella corella i'm
chlorella
i'm chlorella chlorella clara there's
metal oh good there's metal oops i'm
dropping it
hey there's the metal dropping oh my god
dropping everything
see let's make smoothie
let's go let's get two cups wow
blueberries
if you don't like the taste of cilantro
it's because you're highly toxic
you got the toxic heavy metals
you don't like the taste you're loaded
with metals
you don't like the taste get the wild
blueberries in there
let's keep on going where's my bananas
two cups of wild blueberries let's pop
into bananas
let's go
got it moving
michelle l hazard control laugh out loud
if you're sensitive to anything you can
always use smaller dosages
that's all or sip some and sip it later
i'm going to put a little dose in there
got that get that let's cut it orange
it's getting orange
let's go to that squeezing orange in
here making the smoothie now
excited this orange doesn't have a lot
of juice in it if you get an orange and
it doesn't have that much juice in it
you can go with two juices
two juices no two oranges
so guys we're covering some cool stuff
if you just got here
i just saw somebody on tick tock i think
say what's this about you guys
somebody on tick tock say hey what's
this about
what's he doing who is he
all right we got some orange in there
i'm gonna put a little bit more
no that's actually enough orange in
there actually
i'm gonna put this is day two of the
heavy metal detox challenge i'm gonna
put
some uh the wyman's wild blueberry juice
in here
i'm saving this on youtube by the way
saving this on youtube
all right let's get some cilantro in
here boom
cup of cilantro we've got dulce in there
what am i missing
i'm gonna put a little bit of the energy
while blueberry powder
is it better to stick to the celery
juice
or do the metal detox
huh we're in the heavy metal detox
cleanse
you do the lemon water wait 15 to 32
minutes you know upon waking you do
lemon water wait 15 to 30 minutes right
16 13 ounces of lemon water
and then you move into the celery juice
right
can you go to the library when you get a
chance and pick up cleanse the heal
can you do that is just go to the
library get it for free
don't even do the 51 off at amazon.com
with this book specifically and that 51
off isn't with like all amazon books
it's just with this book right now it's
and amazon go to the library
a little bit more blueberry they control
the price and for some reason i think an
angel has intercepted into the amazon
machine
and has made that book so inexpensive it
costs more to print it
it's it's actually a miracle so
it's definitely an angelic price because
that book
got the barley grass juice powder in
there you guys so that's the vimmers you
brought the grass juice powder
vimmergy.com not sponsored stuff is
amazing
that's their blueberry powder right
let's get the spirulina in here too
barley grass juice powder
hey ew i got the barley grass powder
i got the barley grass powder no barley
grass
juice powder it's the only way it's
going to work
it's the only way where's the top on
this thing
huh
here it is
all right
make a smoothie
lindsay hill talks about the substitutes
you guys
no it's not powdered cilantro i saw that
no it's not
cleanse the heel has the substitutions
mango you can use frozen mango i got
mangoes here
can do mangoes right
details matter you can use papaya as as
a
substitution too
and if you want to substitute for banana
right
so we have the heavy metal detox
smoothie right here
pretty exciting
i'm pumped you guys on ig
i'm gonna make the other option really
quick with the coconut water option i'll
make that
i'm going to make a little pudding
on ig god willing if all goes right
and let me give you a couple tidbits
that are really important here too
okay so apples are critical
eat an apple that day try to do it
before noon
if you can't do it before noon do it
afternoon
try to get some apples in your diet you
can make an applesauce you can eat one
apple you can eat a half an apple you
can eat two apples
two apples would be best okay
if you want to take this cleanse further
keep the fats out of your diet for the
rest of the day
don't do the radical fats but don't do
the radical fats before noon no avocado
toast no oils no nuts and seeds and nut
butters no almond milk
no soy milk no oat milk none of the
radical fats before noon
right and use the recipes in the book
throughout the day
because they're fat-free recipes and
cleanse the heal if you use those
throughout the day
you can take this cleanse and get more
metal out faster and do healing faster
instead of getting the metals out on us
the slower pace
you can do it on a quicker pace right
the books you got the recipes it's 75
recipes in that book
over 200 symptoms and conditions details
matter they're in here
75 recipes you can't go wrong can't go
wrong
all right you guys i'm taking off and a
little
while i will be on instagram and i'm
going to turn tik tok back on
i'll turn clubhouse back on i can't wait
to see you guys again you guys know i
love you
thank you for being here by the way