It's at the end of the night. I just
came back from Cafe Gratitude night one
of the popup dinners, the pizza party.
And I got my pizza right here, which is
actually amazing. I got more than one
pizza, though, cuz you know, I might be
eating them different times. This one is
the Mediterranean Putin. This is
amazing. I'm just going to take a bite.
Can't help
it. Oh, that's insane. All right, let me
see what else I
got. Another one here.
Okay. So, oh
yeah, right here it's the veggie medley
with the uh broccolini and then the um
potato cheese. This is really
good.
Mhm. That's
insane. That's
insane. So good. But here's the thing. I
even got a couple more
There's one right here. It's probably
one of the other ones. Obviously, there
is. Wow. And then I got one
more. So, am I going to eat all four of
these tonight? No, I don't think so.
But I am going to eat definitely one of
them for sure. Maybe I'll eat one and a
half cuz I really didn't eat anything
today. You know, I just been so busy.
Didn't eat much. just spending on a
little bit of coconut water and some
other stuff. So, but now I'm hungry. So,
at the end of the day, I'm going to eat
you guys. And um I'm so excited about
this. This is a collaboration medical
medium and Cafe Gratitude with pizzas.
Unbelievable. The first pizza
collaboration ever in Cafe Gratitude
right
here.
And and they're delicious. These are
worth flying out of the country, flying
from another country to here to actually
just taste these. They're that great.
Oh, by the way, the crust, chickpea,
potato, and sweet potato. How about that
for a crust? That's unique. That's
amazing. Medical meme pizzas. Cafe
Gratitude. Anyway, you guys, I'm just
going to start eating. That's what I'm
going to do. I'm going to move this one
over for a second. I'm going to bring
this one back over here. And I'm
actually gonna just start, you know, I'm
going to have dinner. Why
not? I'm eating dinner at I don't know
what time it is. It is
11:00. Soon to be 11:30. I don't know
what time it is. I'm eating dinner at
night. Late at night.
Amazing. Anyway, I'm going to enjoy
this. Lots of
[Music]
love. So good.