[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now also we
can help people and get people feeling
better and moving forward because when
you're dealing with anything that is in
your
way in in health on any level with the
health of your body health of your mind
you know your soul your spirit your body
your physical nature whatever it is if
we're dealing with something and it's in
the way and it's hard it's hard because
you the world is hard enough to live in
it's hard enough to live in it really is
and um for all walks of life for all
walks of life for sure I mean for
different reasons for some for different
reasons for others but it's it it's a
difficult place it's not a it's not such
a easy easy place that's why we always
that's why we always when we raise our
children we protect them and we we look
after them because we know we know the
world is a scary plays and as our
children grow up we're like we're
nervous we're nervous we're nervous when
they go off to college we're nervous
when they enter High School we're
nervous um you know when they meet
people we're nervous and there's reasons
why we're
nervous because let's face it okay yeah
the world is hard and we want every
opportunity we can and best best and
safest and and um and opportunity for
our children just like just just like we
would want for even ourselves as adults
and and just because the world is always
a difficult place in so many ways so
when we're sick we don't feel good we
have symptoms that we have symptoms that
that even though they have names to them
and some don't have names to them CU you
know in in chronic illness it's just
it's it's not cracked up to where it's
supposed to be it's not it's not up to
that point and um but if we have
symptoms whether they're named or not it
gets difficult and because most all
symptoms most almost all symptoms are
mystery they're mystery and that's why
that's why we need hey look and who has
10 years or 20 years to wait for an
answer on a symptom we got to do our
best now and we have to do what we can
now that's what the show is about
because this is the only Health show
where the information here it doesn't
come from contaminated sources it
doesn't come from sources like interest
groups and medical funding with strings
attached to it The Botch research I talk
about all the time the lobbyists in the
medical field the internal Kickbacks the
thumb on the scale and all kinds of
science and research so it pushes it one
way for reasons to F because of funding
persuaded belief systems that that get
so saturated they take over and they
don't let any new ideas come in to
private panels of
influencers that have to go a certain
way and vote a certain way on the
medical field both alternative and
conventional because of money involved
to health field payoffs to trendy traps
can you believe that stuff's in the way
of getting us better I mean it just
blows my mind it blows my mind and
you're not going to get any of that here
the information here is pure it's clean
it's untampered with it comes from a
source I was born to here at age four I
received a a a voice that was speaking
to me perfectly clear I dedicate it my
entire life because cuz I had no choice
I dedicated my entire life with working
with that voice and making sure the
information and the and and what we need
to heal and move forward is clean it's
pure untampered with and doesn't have
all that stuff I just mentioned and
that's what the shows about so it's the
only Health show that has that because
even information that's swimming out
there on the Internet or anywhere else
could have contamination to it in one
way or another even if there's jewels
and gems to pick from it that are pretty
good there's also some traps in there we
don't want that we don't want that so
that's what this is about
today today we're talking about eating
disorders and and this is a serious
serious thing we're going to cover the
serious eating disorder aspects that
that we know about but we're going to
cover also the other ones that aren't
serious but they're annoying and and
there's a lot of things involved with
eating disorders there's a lot more than
I think people
no and you know and when it comes down
to eating
disorders okay there's a lot of messed
up stuff going on I'm not talking about
the people suffering with the eating
disorder I'm talking about the way it's
viewed and understood in medical science
and research talking about contaminated
sources of information talking about you
know skewed funding and everything else
and all that stuff I talked the know
panels of influencers when it comes down
to eating disorders it's in a way that's
really not that helpful of course we
have emergency medicine for people who
have severe severe eating disorders and
and and you know
and emergency strategies that are
involved that are out there that have
saved lives and I'm not denouncing that
but at the same time there's really not
a lot of helpful stuff going on out
there in the medical world for people
with serious serious serious Eating
Disorders it's just it's not there it's
not there sure if they took a few
billion dollars or2 billion and they put
it just to eating disorders it would be
amazing and they and they opened up the
you know and they freed they freed
everything so it wasn't just so just
trapped with you know problems in the
industry if they freed it to open to
ideas and let really wonderful people in
medicine say what they need to say and
help people way they need to help we can
move forward but it's like that with a
lot of diseases and illnesses and things
we struggle with but with eating
disorders it's really it's really sad
because it's it's really a place that's
not tapped into it's a place that's not
tapped into at
all it's really and in fact they try to
it's like black and white they try to
black and white it where it's like okay
it's mental you got a mental disease you
got this eating disorder um you're
losing weight you're skinny and um we
got to do something drastic about it and
um and but but but there's nothing
there's no in between it's it's rare to
find that and we just have to talk about
it we have to talk about it we're going
to talk about every kind of eating
disorder what do you mean by every kind
what do I mean by every kind of eating
disorder what do I mean by that there's
so many you couldn't believe it you
wouldn't believe it you won't believe it
it's unbelievable actually
so that's what today's show show is
about okay everybody um I know there's
so many different illnesses there's so
many different um things that are
complicated in the health field and I
and and we have so many shows that we
have to do the list is unbelievable you
I've been talking to Spirit and then
talking to my assistant and um we've
been putting putting together a list of
what we have to do and what's ahead of
us and I'm just like oh my God dear God
I'm like this there's so so many
different different illnesses different
conditions different
misconceptions um it's just it's it's
mindblowing but spirit and I said you
know what Eating Disorders we're doing
that right now we're doing that right
now we're doing that so that's it um hey
Make Way gain way Make Way for for for
the thyroid healing book coming make
sure you get that on your list you won't
be
disappointed um there 's a section in
the book on cancer there's a section in
the book on cancer I think is going to
blow your mind information that nobody
knows in the cancer
field and um nobody knows yet and so
it's really exciting that's something
that you might want to you might want to
get the book for just that alone but but
there's other things too in the book
that are really exciting really exciting
and I don't think you'll be disappointed
I talk about how a healthy thyroid can
help heal somebody body's unhealthy
thyroid and and how that can happen wait
till you read that and then that's
really exciting too I talk about thyroid
medications but but really about how it
works with medication for thyroid I talk
about thyroid testing on how it's not as
easy as everybody thinks even when the
numbers seem to come out right or
something seems to come up like Auto
antibodies or something like that for
Hashimoto
when that happens I talk about that in
detail I talk about the Undiscovered
hormones that the thyroid has that
nobody knows about nobody the
Undiscovered hormones that the thyroid
has don't miss out on this I won't let
you down on this this is this is going
to be exciting um so here we are let's
get let's get into this let's figure
this eating disorder thing out because
all the years and the decades I've been
doing this since the beginning okay I've
seen it all I've seen it all with eating
I've seen it all with eating and and and
I'm just going to kind of I'm going to
talk about a few things here now guess
guess who has Eating
Disorders the whole world the whole
world has an eating disorder of some
kind some way somehow some shape some
size someone everyone has an eating
disorder yeah do you believe me you're
probably mad some of you he's saying I
don't have an eating disorder I got it
down pat I got it down I got it I got it
straight they come the Eating Disorders
range from being
brainwashed
brainwashed on how to eat originally
from the 1920s 1930s from the 1930s
actually
1933 1933 when the schulls were invaded
with how you need to eat and that was
taking away healthy diets from families
that knew had that that had a lineage to
knowing how to feed their children and
feed their husbands and feed their
family and feed feed their loved ones
and that was Stripped Away by
1933 because this new doctrine came in
this law came in about about how you
should eat about how much protein you
need and how many vegetables you don't
need and how many fruits you don't need
and it's all about protein and protein
became cheap cuz the industry exploded
right before World War II so animal
protein became really really cheap and
was became affordable purposely
purposely at this time I'm not saying
all this cuz I'm anti-animal protein if
you like it fine I'm just telling you
how it
went and healthy diets that predate 1933
where families raised their children
on out of the gardens and so forth were
starting to be like thrown on the back
burner and in the school system it was
inocent it was was right there in the
school system the law became here is
what here's what you need vegetables are
down here that's that's the lowest
amount you need that's the smallest
amount of things you need and what's at
the top of the the top here you you got
to have lots and lots of protein that's
at the very top and the protein has to
be animals so it can't be nuts and seeds
and it can't be leafy greens and it
can't be those things at all it has to
be the animal products this is when the
animal world made made a deal with the
government with the school systems and
they all kind of got together and a deal
was made in
1933 that alone created Eating Disorders
eating disorders that you think are
healthy but we're following the rules of
the government on how to eat in 1933
which still sticks to us from our
grandparents to our parents and so forth
to us and in some way we still have a
fabric of a little bit of the the eating
disorder that was given to us that was
manufactured and given to us how do you
like them apples huh how do you like
them apples but that's just one one
little piece of eating disorder
information that you'll never hear
anywhere else but here that's just one
little little
piece there's there's other pieces the
whole world has an eating disorder I'm
going to tell you that right now there's
no question because in all kinds of
different places the world there's
there's places where people are starving
they get Eating Disorders because
they're starving because you're
rationing the whole bit just instant
Eating Disorders there's there's places
where there's abundance of food but the
way our bodies are viewed and the Eating
Disorders can occur right there there's
Eating Disorders everywhere there's
eating disorders in all the colleges
every single college campus from A to Z
from here to there the kids are all
having eating eating disorders I'm not
talking about bulimia which we're going
to talk about and I'm not talking about
anorexia which we're going to talk about
which is in the college campuses too
that's not what I'm talking about I'm
talking about drinking coffee till
2:00 drinking coffee just till till 2:00
no breakfast it's drink coffee all the
way to 2:00 that's what you do 2: 3 in
the afternoon and then alcohol at
night you know and then of course some
food but unhealthy food and then alcohol
at night that's that's an eating
disorder meanwhile that that group those
group of people that still do that even
not in college what we do here now that
we do that at work think that the only
eating disorder people out there is
people with bulim and anorexia and
that's the only thing and that's the
eating disorder no wait a minute that's
no no no no no no no no no nope nope
nope it's not how it works Eating
Disorders are rampant rampant rampant
adults that have to drink every night
and have a glass of wine that's an
eating disorder it's not just about
alcoholism or anything like that it's
not about that it's not even about that
so
much alcoholism of eating
disorder it's an eating
disorder that's right have I said that's
right enough lately I don't think so
that's right that you know it just
alcohol alone isn't you know that having
to be in the diet on a regular basis in
someone's life on a regular
basis isn't there's any heating disorder
there would you believe it and then
there's emotional Eating Disorders on
all kinds of level there's OCD Eating
Disorders yes everything's got to be
perfect in regiment it down to the bone
without a health problem I mean without
no health problems that are there that
are present what I'm trying to say is
that there's people that are dealing
with health problems and health issues
they have to eat regimented because they
got to keep their adrenal strong they
got to keep their electrolytes going
they have to keep the nerves transmitter
because they got underlying conditions
did I say that fast enough dear dear
Lord
um you know basically what this means is
that people with health conditions yeah
they have to eat every two hours I talk
about that all the time Spirit has
taught me that every hour and a half
depending on what kind of adrenal
problem somebody has depending on a
liver problem all these different
things and that that's even difficult
enough and that can create different
kinds of eating disorders for different
reasons but we do the best we can but
what really creates eating disord
orders really creates them is this
notion this notion that we need three
meals a day and three meals a day only
that creates them because then if
someone has a health problem and they
have to eat every hour and a half and
they have to munch on celery sticks and
a handful of nuts and some apple slices
someone's going to call them call them
out and say hey you got an eaing
disorder if you have to eat every hour
and a half and you have to eat an apple
and and and celery sure we could say
that but really what that's doing is
saving somebody's adrenals and saving
their health and rebuilding them and
recovering them but someone who
regimentally regimented has to eat three
meals a day and believes anybody else
who eats different has a has a problem
that's an eating disorder that's one
right
there that right there that becomes an
OCD variety of eating
disorder also you know so here's the
thing that's how confusing it all is see
what I'm trying to say is if someone's
actually doing a protocol that's
regimented the proper kind of protocol
that's there to rebuild their health and
heal it's needed and you have to do it
even if that's someone when they don't
need that anymore it's hard to break and
that's what I meant by it being possibly
an eating disorder maybe 2 years is what
you needed to rebuild your adrenals 2
and A2 years is what you needed to build
your rebuild your adrenals but now you
know you're afraid to leave that one
hour to an hour and a half of of of of
grazing and you're afraid to to go 2 and
1/2 hours that day or 3 hours and you
get nervous and that's when it can
become like that but that but that was
to rebuild your adrenals that was to
rebuild you that was to heal you and
that's no problem because you can get
past that but it's hard to get past it's
hard to get past so many other traps
that are out the real traps traps in the
industry like I just said that date back
all the way to
1933 and those are
serious and those are really serious
and then you got of course you got the
when it comes down to emotional eading
emotional eading that means you know you
got stress it's one way of coping with
stress but I'm going to talk about that
let's talk about that now why does
somebody emotionally eat they
emotionally eat and I'm going to tell
you right now what it
is not because they're missing something
necessarily meaning they're missing
something in their life whether it's
love life or anything
else that's not really totally the
answer they're emotionally eating
because they're trying to get enough
glucose to the brain it's so critical
and to the liver they're getting to try
to get to to uh compensate for any kind
of stress that they're under some people
have they have glycogen storages that
are really down low in the brain because
the brain is made out of glycogen which
is a
carbohydrate and I swear to God if some
says the brain is made out of fat one
more time I'm meaning in the health
field a professional and expert says the
brain is made out of fat one more time I
I don't know what to say anymore because
I'm going to tell you right now it's not
made out of fat there are traces traces
of squalling traces of of of Omega-3s
traces in the
brain I
repeat traces do you know what traces
means traces mean
minuscule very small amounts tiny levels
of fat in the brain the brain is
made out of cells and glycogen
carbohydrate stored that's why the brain
atrophies when you don't use
it it
atrophies it's made out of carbohydrate
the brain thrives on sugar and it stores
an abundance of glycogen because what
runs the brain is that glycogen is that
carbohydrate that's how literally how
how messages get through the
brain that's how it gets through the
brain it's really important to
understand this it is because people
lose all their glycogen in the brain
when they're under stress they start
losing their glycogen they start losing
their glucose and they start needing
bagels and they need donuts and the
emotional eat they're under stress
they're under stress for one minute and
they're gobbling down anything they're
gobbling down something Pizza they're
gobbling down anything they can find
chocolate whatever they can find and
they a lot of times people gobble down
all the wrong stuff when they're under
that kind of stress which makes you
gobble down more because it can it it
can get in the way of sugar and glycogen
getting to the brain it could get in the
way of that getting to the brain and
then if you have a body image if someone
is a body image and they think they got
to be really skinny and they think
they're
overweight and and and they're starving
themselves of carbohydrate and then it
making them binge later that that's
that's a whole recipe for a
disaster but on the emotional end of
eating the emotional scale of eating I
mean it ranges from all kinds of
different levels
everywhere I mean you go under stress
you need to eat
something and I'm not talking about when
boom you just got the news you just got
a divorce meaning your partner just you
know threw divorce on you walk through
the door and said you know we're done or
your soulmate or whatever I'm not
talking about that that might not you
might not eat it all when that happens
for for a month you might starve
yourself I've seen that happen all the
time where you don't eat
anything because you're too sick you're
too sick from the trauma to even eat
anything but then later on after that
once you start recovering from that
trauma you might start eating eating
eating eating because your brain is like
oh my God I lost all that glycogen from
the trauma I need as much sugar as
possible or say you're in the workplace
and you're up against you you got some
really difficult
people you got some really difficult
people at the workplace they're driving
you nuts and you're just like oh my God
and you're just eating yourself eating
yourself sick and I don't blame you one
bit 100% I've been under a lot of stress
over over the years my God now hearing
spirit and helping people out in the way
I've had to help out people and all the
offices that I've had over the years and
helping people out and as much as I did
this since I was a kid you name it you
know I would just be like all right you
know what I'm going to eat that right
now I'm going to eat
it my brain needs that fuel I'm going to
eat it oh it's not a good choice though
I get it I I know I didn't pick a good
choice I C came to uh to a bad choice of
food a circum to was bad choice of food
look look the deal is that everybody's
got a eating disorder I have to be
honest I have to be straight if you
think you got it all sewed up and you
think you got it all down you think you
got it down
perfect uh it's possible you don't and
that's okay there's nothing wrong with
that I think we're too hard on people
that are bulimic and anorexic we're too
hard on people way too hard hard we make
it like the whole world has it sewed up
except for them I mean come on that
that's ridiculous and also terrible
terrible because that's what happens
that's what
happens because you know women and men
mostly women okay that have the anorexia
that have the
bulimia all right they feel like it's
just them just them only and I feel like
everybody's eating perfectly whatever
that may be
and that they're they're screwing up
it's disastrous it's not true it's not
true there's so many different eating
disorders in so many different levels
and ways I can't even cover it in a show
there's no way it's not even possible
I'm going to try to cover what I can
just the OCD variety of eating is
unbelievable what people want what they
do of what they like of what they're
what they pet or what they like or what
they're afraid
of afraid of trying something new having
that tuna fish sandwich every single
lunch every single lunch for 30 years
that's an eating
disorder 40 years having that tuna for
lunch every single day every other day
for lunch and then grill cheese on you
know maybe a couple days a week and
that's it and that's their lunch and
it's regimented and has to be that that
way for 40 years that's an eating
disorder I'm tell you right
now you see what I'm you see where I I'm
I am here with this it's really
difficult
C so it's just to what what degree
somebody has an eating disorder and
what's the underlying cause of one with
bulimia and
anorexia 90% of the
cause is heavy metal toxicity to the
brain mostly Mercury mostly Mercury
inside the brain that came from some
Source from childhood or from pre Source
in the womb or from pre Source before
the that from the parents or like I said
from childhood Mercury entered the body
somehow some way into a child into a
baby that is the future of a possible
anorexia or bulimia that's 90% 90% easy
90% or more the other 10% or less
depending on where we are in the world
or what where we are but the other 10%
or less is some kind of emotional trauma
some kind of emotional trauma that
happened to the brain that caused
emotional scarring in the brain itself
on a physical level not just on a soul
level on a physical level on a physical
level something
happened but that's much less much less
much less on the scale for anorexia and
bulimia than heavy metal poisoning and
here's the problem with the heavy metal
poisoning Professionals in the field of
you know the whole bulimia field of
bulimia field of of anorexia those
professionals don't know about the
Mercury have no clue that the Mercury's
causing this on any level or started it
they don't have a clue about that that's
a problem they just think it's all just
emotional all just scarring all just
emotional and they do the best they can
and they help people out the best they
can I completely understand that and
completely respect that on every
level but
but it's it's the Mercury it's the
Mercury toxicity it's the mercury
poisoning and that's what it is that's a
big
[Music]
deal that's a big
deal so when it comes down
to when it comes down to Healing bulimia
healing anorexia one thing we have to
understand is that there's an adrenaline
Factor I've talked about this before for
instance with bulimia when you vomit it
it forces the adrenals to flood the
whole body with
adrenaline this becomes a
distraction if it's if okay say it's say
you have bulimia because 10% the 10% of
the people have bulimia it's because of
an emotional trauma well by
vomiting the adrenals flood the body
with
adrenaline it becomes
euphoric all that adrenaline hits the
brain and it actually is like heroin
it's it's it's like heroin it's like a
drug and it gets into the brain it
saturates the brain it
completely takes over the
brain and that becomes extremely
addictive so addictive that you get
addicted to the adrenaline Factor you're
getting addicted to the adrenaline
surge when it comes down to pimia
there's an adrenaline
surge so it actually it the adrenaline
starts to then you get trained where
before you vomit if you even think about
vomiting your adrenals start to rev up
and they start releasing tons and tons
of epinephrine like we're talking loads
of epinephrine saturate the body run up
to the brain and it actually makes you
vomit and then you're in the Trap it
becomes a severe addiction severe
addiction to Adrenaline and that's what
the real thing is happening now say
you're somebody with bulimia and you got
the mercury poisoning which is the 90
90% or
more and you got the mercury poisoning
in the
brain and it's that variety of that that
variety of bulimia the same thing
happens when you vomit the adrenaline
goes to the brain and it eases it eases
it helps electrical impulses bypass the
Mercury which actually feel like a cure
for the illness for that moment so
vomiting becomes this instinctive
wanting to cure the problem through
using epinephrine for using
adrenaline and it become severely
addictive and we're in the binging and
throwing up binging and throwing up
binging and throwing up and then body
image can fit into any of that because
body image is into every here's the
problem too it's body image will will
fall into any kind of anorexia or any
kind of
bulimia that say heavy metal caused or
trauma caused the reason why it fits in
because it fits in with everything every
single person right now on planet Earth
especially women they all have to deal
with body image it just so happens that
if you got the mercury poisoning too and
the addiction to the adrenaline from
vomiting and you got the normal body
image worry that every girl has growing
up on planet Earth right now because the
world makes it happen like that when
that happens and it's added into that
then that's what takes the blame only
body image takes the blame because
professionals don't know there's mercury
poisoning involved professionals don't
know there's a serious addiction to the
adrenaline like no other like a serious
drug so they Point only to body image or
some kind of mental
illness and this is this is why it's so
hard so someone with bulimia if they
know they're addicted to Adrenaline and
they have to fight that addiction to the
adrenaline and if they could just bypass
that they can be free they could be
free and that's a big deal that's a
really big deal and also another thing
too is is a carbohydrates critical for
healing anorexia or bulimia and I'm
going talk about more about anorexia but
for bulimia a carbohydrate is critical
for healing it because if you starve
carbohydrates someone with bulimia it
only makes it worse they'll end up
binging on carbohydrates just like a
person without bulimia does you put
somebody on a no carb diet they're going
to go on binges or they're going to have
alcohol at night they're going to do
something they're going to do something
they're going to break their diet
someday and when they do it's going to
be crazy binging what they think is
crazy binging it's going to be eating
four slices of pizza and then back on
their no carb diet for three weeks and
then boom binging again with five Bagels
then boom back to the no carb diet it's
just though they don't have bulimia they
don't have the addiction to the
adrenaline and they're vomiting all the
time so but if you take somebody with
Bimi and you starve them with
carbohydrates God
forbid then you better believe they're
going to they're gonna go on a
binge they're going to go on a binge and
they're going to vomit and they're going
to get the adrenaline high so they need
a healthy carbohydrate but if you give
them a bad carbohydrate mentally they're
going to be like whoa I got to throw
this up now I'm filled with bad
carbohydrates I'm filled with bagels and
donuts that's why fruit is so critical
for someone with bulimia I've helped
recover people with bulimia over the
decades with just fruit because they
could eat all the fruit they want they
knew it was a healthy carbohydrate and
here's a problem right now
in the industry right now there's a
contamination that got into the
alternative world of healing and now
it's Inc conventional too started in the
alternative world of
healing and and it's the no fruit anti
fruit
movement don't ever let that
contaminated um belief system get in
your way they used it they they're using
it against you you don't even know using
it against you I remember the first
person who who brought
this into the system I know why they did
I know who it is I'm not going to
mention names but I know why they
brought it in they brought it in so that
you wouldn't eat fruit but you would buy
their supplements that had fruit in
it and that's how it started just it was
it was unbelievable it was the perfect
timing for this contamination to bust on
the scene because at the same time there
were all these people trying to get away
from Bad sugars so it was perfect it fit
right in and it took over now fruit was
thrown into the whole basket it's been
disastrous and that's what I mean when I
talk about at the beginning of the show
that very thing I talk about about this
information is not contaminated it's so
critical to know this and when you're
dealing with bulimia fruit is the way to
go because if if if someone with bulimia
knows they have the adrenaline
addiction if someone with bulim knows
that fruit is a healthy carbohydrate
that they need and it won't cause a body
image problem if that's even factored in
eventually if that becomes the
escapegoat then fruit is the answer
because the carbohydrate can get to the
brain it can help heal the brain cuz the
brain's not made out of fat it's made
out of glycogen this was figured out by
science actually long ago I mean they
figured this one out but it didn't fit
it didn't fit the
industries it didn't fit the
industries that's a whole another story
of why this is happening where why the
the brain is they're they're avoiding
the the fact that the brain is the the
experts right now are avoiding the
fact that that the brain is is is filled
with
carbohydrate and we're going to do a
whole show on that
someday that's on the list that's on
that big list so somebody with bulimia
has to have fruit in their diet they
have to they have to get the
carbohydrates to help the adrenals they
got to keep the blood sugar balance
because once blood sugar drops that can
create bulim all on its own when you
have it already when you're addicted to
the adrenaline issue it's critical it's
got to go to the brain it's got to help
the brain heal and then you got to do
the heavy metal detox you got to do the
detox smoothie you got to do the right
kind you got to get a little bit of the
swine spiruline in there a little bit of
the vimergy barley grass juice in there
you got to get a little bit of the um
you got to get some wild blueberries in
there you got to get a little bit of
dolls in there you got to get a little
bit of cantro in there every single day
and you got to start taking the Mercury
down and you start taking that mercury
down and a couple years later the fight
won't be so
hard and the person will get stronger
and stronger less occurrences will
happen less addictions to Adrenaline
will happen and less mercury in the body
will happen and somebody can actually
heal from bulimia without being
force-fed massive drugs told they have
this unbelievable mental illness and
suffering occurring this is serious
stuff and you know this can happen of
course they need a support system
anybody with any illness especially Bia
or anorexia needs a support system and I
know that I know that's a difficult part
if that's not there boy does that make
it hard and I get
it I get
it so maybe you know somebody and you
give him a little support on it a little
bit goes a long way a little bit goes a
long way you tell us somebody with
bulimia that the whole world isn't
eating disorder they're not the only
ones you tell somebody that so the shame
falls down and and gets Stripped Away
the shame and the guilt and everything
else that comes with it that shouldn't
be
there
that shouldn't be there because that
gets in the way too like no other so if
you know somebody with anorex you tell
them look everybody's got an eating
disorder to some degree which just yours
is yeah yours has gotten to a serious
point we need to do something about it
absolutely but it's important that
people and that was another thing too
that helped people with bulimia and
anorexia that I met over the years and
many of them was that they were like
what do you mean everybody else has an
eating disorder I said no everybody else
has an eating disorder I don't care who
it is I don't care if somebody thinks
they got it all sewed up something
something's going
on something's going on here's the thing
we all have to eat we all have to eat to
survive we all have to eat to live we
have to eat to live here on Earth we
have to survive that's our fuel intake
that's what does it that's what's
critical we need that fuel intake that
is so important so it's easy for
anything to to slip through her fingers
in one way or another it's easy to eat
the wrong things it's easy to drink
alcohol it's easy to do things that
we're not supposed to do starve
ourselves or whatever it
is that's how fast and and and
easy that Eating Disorders occur and can
occur it's that easy so so let's go into
some other stuff here anorexia
definitely Mercury problem also a
percentage of of if something terrible
happened meaning something really
really intense emotionally some kind of
experience some kind of abuse something
happened um that that and here's a
problem with anorexia and bulimia you
can have a combination of both you could
have mostly Mercury and then yes some
kind of emotional physical abuse happens
too in that person's life and then you
got the combination of
both so with anorexia it's about getting
you know it's about the heavy metals too
getting the heavy metals out in some way
some some some way some shape I noticed
that I've seen fruit heal people with
anorexia more than any other food
because mentally it fit in perfectly
where they felt they were eating
something healthy they but then what
they were getting were carbohydrates
that were so needed for every organ so
they didn't atrophy and with anorexia
your organs atrophy but you can get
those organs to come back but they
atrophy everything gets smaller pancreas
gets really small pancreas gets really
small and you can bring that pancreas
back everything gets small brain gets
smaller pancreas gets smaller it's not
just about thinning out losing weight
and being really really extremely thin
it's not just about it's about the
organs the atrophy and I know I I know
there's there's some doctors that know
that that the organs atrophy they
totally understand that that's that I
don't think that's
new but what is new is that fruit is
critical for bringing back organs that
are atrophied with somebody with
anorexia and that's a big deal that's a
big
deal and in with somebody with anorexia
when you have the mercury poisoning in
the brain sending signals not to eat
creating nausea in the Vagas nerve
creating nausea and no appetite in the
Vegas nerve because you can get a signal
that goes wrong with Mercury creating
non-
hunger and you know with anorexia when
that happens fruit is the greatest
weapon it's the greatest weapon because
it doesn't feel it doesn't feel so
overburdening it doesn't feel like you
just ate a loaf of bad bread it doesn't
feel like you ate you know a steak and
somebody with anorexia forcing them to
eat chicken or forcing them to eat steak
could be
disastrous very difficult on them very
difficult cuz that's what happens it's
like eat e eat person has to eat we got
to get milk in them we got to get it's
all the wrong
Foods someone with anorexia you got to
get avocado milk in them you blend
avocado with water in the
blender and that's something that's
really really good for somebody with
anorexia got to do banana milk throwing
bananas in the blender with water and
doing lots of banana milk it's critical
for somebody with anorexia because once
you feed the brain and your brain make
the brain stronger even if there's
vomiting in between this with both
anorexia and
bulimia if you feed the brain when you
do get a chance or say with somebody
with anorexia that they you know I
listen I you may be dealing with this
and suffering with the anorexia for
years you you know better than anybody
but if you do eat something you might
not eat something for a long time after
that if that happens we want that
something to actually pay off so if you
get the banana milk in you or you get
some melon in you and you get the the
critical carbohydrates to the brain and
to the organs to stop atrophying and
then you end up not eating because the
because of the reasons of everything
above with anorexia then then at least
you fed the
organs even if the weight's not coming
back yet something to to
understand you
know people who drink coffee every
single day and they have to rely on it
that's a disorder that's a disorder
right there it's as simple as that
people eat too much chocolate every day
that's an eating
disorder people have to eat chocolate
every day and then they have to switch
and get the better chocolate and they're
still eating it every single day to
throw it in their smoothies they're told
by some experts out there it's the
greatest thing for your Health that's an
eating disorder I mean they're high on
chocolate you can't tell but you're
you're high on chocolate all day long
and what that does is that does weird
things it suppresses hunger in different
ways it does different stuff it maxes
out the adrenals you could still have
some chocolate but that literally con
constitutes an eating disorder I yeah
this is a tough show this is a tough
show we got to stay light-hearted about
it at the same time when it comes down
to those
things it you know and then the
obsession about foods to
avoid Obsession about foods to avoid now
if you have a reason why you're avoiding
a food if you know you got like the
Epstein bar virus you don't want to feed
it eggs you better believe you need to
avoid eggs absolutely you have to avoid
eggs you need to you don't want to feed
a virus of food once you learn that
that's what feeds a
food but if you're avoiding a food
there's no reason at all you're not
dealing with a health problem and you're
avoiding a food that's really not that
bad for anybody and you're avoiding it
because you heard something about it and
you're avoiding with everything you
got it's probably not there's probably
other things you do in your diet that
are probably worse put it that way I
mean there's so many different ways to
go it's unbelievable and then there's
underlying illness freeding disorders
there's
hypoglycemia there's adrenaline issues I
mean there's adrenal fatigue
hypoglycemia electrolyte deficiencies
neurotransmitter deficiencies in people
every single day people suffering with
all kinds of problems people that are
getting diagnosed with bipolar but
really they're having serious problems
with their blood sugar and they're
diagnosed with bipolar being bipolar and
and really they just have a blood sugar
problem where it's going up and down too
fast and it can't stabilize because of
adrenals in the liver because the liver
is sluggish there's 15y olds 18y olds
19y olds were really sluggish
livers and and so they can't balance the
can't balance the glucose in in their
blood so they're they're having mood
swings left and right up and down then
they get thrown in diagnosis then they
get put on riddle and then they get put
on they get put on all these kinds of
drugs and and whatever it
is and then you have that going on when
really and all that does is end up
creating an eating disorder when really
someone needs to teach somebody that has
hypoglycemia caused by either adrenal
fatigue when they're young or a liver
problem how to
eat cuz if you if you don't then it
could become a serious eating disorder
and lead to an eating
disorder and so for instance when you
have that kind of up and down in the
mood swings you have to eat every hour
hour and a half and it has to be
something that has a sodium in it like a
sodium in it in the sense where it has
to be celery stick it has to be some
spinach it has to be um um you know it
has to be some spinach celery has to be
some guacamole has to be handful of nuts
has to be um uh cucumber slices
apples has to be lemon water all these
different things you need in and out of
it all um raw honey lemon water that's a
great mix if you put that together and
you can even put a little touch of sea
salt in there if you wanted to and make
a drink out of that there's different
things there different ways of keeping
bruly balanced or maybe you're just
having some trail mix but it's every
hour or maybe you're just having some
hummus every
hour but that's what you need when it
comes down to anybody with any kind of
hypoglycemia that's getting mood swings
meaning the hypoglycemia mood swings
where it's like up and down and all over
the
place you have to eat like this and then
someone could say hey that person is the
eating disorder because they have to eat
every hour to keep themselves balance
now they have a real reason why they
have to they have a condition that's
developing and this is a real way of
fixing it just like if someone has
straight adrenal fatigue this is a real
way of fixing
it but the eating disorder can come from
somebody else complaining to bet to
somebody about what they're doing and
how they don't like it that alone can
can be challenging and creating a
disorder I mean there's also blame
everywhere everybody's blaming everybody
what they're eating and if they're
eating right everybody has their own
idea of how to eat and what to eat it's
insane and that alone can create to
eating disorders in every single person
I'm going to tell you right now the
information I've ever given out in food
for illnesses and food for problems and
everything else and how you eat there's
reasons behind it reasons that research
signed stor understand or reasons that
are just that are above the trends out
there about how to stay healthy and
heal and that's
different and I'm saying that's not even
100% perfect in the sense because if
someone's doing that and they finally
heal and they're better they might be
afraid to stop I've had people that have
healed themselves from the worst worst
adrenal fatigue on the planet I mean
literally they were just they couldn't
get out of bed they had neuro fatigue
and adrenal fatigue from from a virus
and from the fact that they're adrenals
were spent I couldn't even get a bed I
had them eating every 45 minutes every
45 minutes I recovered them got them
moving again got them out of bed got
their life back 3 years later they were
stronger than ever but afraid to drop
the every 45 minutes they would call me
and say look I'm afraid I'm afraid to
stop eat it's to stop eating every 45
minutes because it saved my life I would
say no you're good you're acting like
you're you're acting like you're going
to get your eating disorder now you can
go an hour and a half you got strong you
can go 2 hours you got strong you can go
if you had to you can go 3 hours if you
had to you got strong and then they have
they have to break it so even when you
heal somebody they can get a little bit
of a of an OCD or a little bit of a
eating sore even after you healed them
from a terrible illness or something
that was terrible or something that was
keeping them down in their life so just
imagine when that's not even in the mix
and all the people out there just this
is how you eat this is how you eat this
is the new way this is the diet you want
to be on um you have to have all this
chocolate you have to have all this you
have to have this it's
unbelievable and yeah if you're anorexic
that just means you're you got a mental
illness and that's really what it is and
you need to eat eat eat eat
eat there's more to it than that of
course you have to eat but there's more
to it than that there's so much there
there's so much
there the people that avoid food all day
and drink at night that's a terrible
eating
disorder I mean there's a people that
they're out in the workforce every day
they're out there every day they avoid
food all day they just avoid food all
day long well then they then they have
these reasons
why I that's a that's a major drinking I
mean that's a major drinking disorder
too that can happen but there's people
that avoid food all day that don't drink
and then eat that one meal at night you
know and and mean but there's some
people that legitly they they have a job
and they're forced to do that I mean I
know nurses that literally don't have a
a minute to eat anything I mean they're
running around all day long it's so
difficult for them to even have a snack
I mean you might be one of them right it
is so difficult to even have a snack or
to eat right or for lunch and and and
the lunch the lunch room in the
hospitals alone are just terrifying
they're better than they were 20 years
ago but they can they're still not that
great especially if you have a health
condition you're trying to work with or
adrenal fatigue and you're pushed all
day long as an nurse and at home you get
home and you're just eating and eating I
totally understand but this it's yeah so
it's hard to avoid now creating some
kind of small eating disorder because
you're forced into it you're pushed into
it totally agree well let's be happy
about something it's okay to have Eating
Disorders okay it's okay to have some
kind of eating disorder and guess what
we all got them we all got them in some
way some shape some fashion somehow we
all have some or one or something from
high school kids to college kids to
adults in Workforce to um to to the
older generation to Elders I've Seen It
All I've Seen It All I've seen people in
their 80s eat a big big pie filled with
wheat and lard and everything but eat
the whole damn pie like a whole
pie and and you know like 85 years old
but but eating a whole pie at
once I've seen it and you know and then
stuffed and can't breathe how how I've I
seen it I've had people call me in that
condition or I've had somebody call for
the because the grandfather ate a whole
pie I've seen it
all and and and and the grandfather
would tell you he's never had an eating
disorder his whole life he' been eating
fine his whole
life and then then I then I hear from
the grandchild I hear for the grandchild
um his granddaughter that he's been he's
been eating till he can't breathe on and
off his whole life always been stuffing
himself so I mean it's just like this
it's like this getting your liver
stronger is important with any kind of
eating disorder that means getting lots
of leafy greens when you can getting
lots of fruits and leafy greens if you
eat animal protein minimize it to one
serving a day there's nothing wrong with
that so what I'm not against animal
protein you could have one serving a day
of it if you're a vegan don't eat
barrels and barrels and nuts have a
handful of nuts periodically throughout
the day a a couple of handfuls do more
leafy greens do more
fruits do some winter squash do things
like that if you're 100% raw you don't
have to do you know a winter squash
that's cooked or whatever you can be all
raw do lots of leafy greens lots of
fruits if you're plant-based and all raw
you can do some nuts and seeds if you're
vegetarian if you're vegetarian try not
to you know overdo fish make sure it's
salmon if you're doing fish it's a
better one than most of
them and if you're you know if you're a
meat eater and you're big on meat eater
meat eating just do you know one serving
of meat day make sure there's more leafy
greens more vegetables more fruits
especially leafy greens in your diet to
help your liver clean up it can prevent
any kind of eating disorder getting the
liver cleaned up getting more fruit in
the diet gets glucose to the liver and
the Brain which can avoid even the most
basic food disorder eating disorder it's
incredible if you're feeling like you
got any kind of Health concern at all
you want to keep your adrenal strong you
want to eat every 2 hours if you feel
like you got adrenal fatigue you eat eat
every hour if you feel like you got
neuro fatigue you eat every hour and you
just do this every day and you have
snacks all day long and you keep enough
food going in that's important for any
kind of adrenal issues even liver issues
even brain issues bipolar ups and downs
mood swings all that kind of thing okay
very important ADHD all of it you want
to keep food coming and you don't want
there's nothing worse than having add or
ADHD and not eating for 4 hours but then
taking medication but not eating for 4
hours and that's a disaster for for an
eating disorder like that's that's
heading to an eating disorder that alone
I'm giving you every T tidbit I can in
the in the time we
have so these are some this is this is
all this is all just part of it all and
I know I'm harsh when I say look I know
I'm harsh I when I say anyone who still
thinks the brain is made out of fat we
being told right now by professionals is
professionals just don't know no the
brain isn't made out of fat it's got
traces of fats and they are important
but they're nothing like the importance
of the carbohydrates and the glycogen
that's stored inside the brain that
keeps electrical impulses moving and it
keeps the neurotransmitter strong
glucose is actually one of the most
critical components to an electrical
impulse inside the brain running down a
neurot neuron to save your butt every
day and this is done through
carbohydrates don't eat donuts don't eat
bad Bagels don't eat tons of loaf don't
eat loaves of bread it's not kind the
kind of stuff the carbohydrates I'm
talking about get the winter squash the
sweet potatoes the regular potatoes if
yet if you don't like those do lots of
fruits bananas papayas I know you know
whatever you can mangoes apples oranges
bring them all in look I love you guys
thank you for being here for this show
it went by so quick I don't even know
what happened I hope I got enough
information out I'll just keep on doing
shows over if I have to doo I love thank
you for being here this gift that God
was given to you it wasn't given to me
for me it was given to me for you I love
you dearly take one day at a time and uh
take care bless you bless you byebye