weaker than people's livers already are
out there so we're making two kinds of
guacamole two kinds of guacamole
interesting not so bad on the liver
compared to what people are Downing
right now at this time of year and we're
making hummuses we might make three
kinds of
hummus
crazy making ice cream mango ice cream
is the one I'm choosing to do I'm pumped
about that okay what else am I making
what else got a cre T I got the
guacamole I got that I got oh Walnut
butter don't miss out on that and I'm
going to hide the label right here just
like I do and that is a very popular
brand what you see here is an inch of
oil on top of a very popular Nut Butter
that's out there that people eat every
single day and people don't leave me
some of them but just so you know oil is
added to the nut Butters the really good
nut Butters the seed Butters all of it
out there oil hidden oil is at it that's
what they do people don't realize that
and we're going to make a walnut butter
without that and this is what it's going
to end up kind of looking like you ready
I made this Nut Butter months ago I'm
pretty sure it was months ago and do you
see the oil spilling out no you see
actually nut butter in here but not oil
spilling out how do you like that
there's another one too check this out I
made this one
too right take a look take a look take a
look take a look look look look and what
you see is how come where's all the oil
where's the oil no oil and I make nut
Butters almond almond butter peanut
butter you name it and that's the key
because everybody buys oil added in
their nut Butters and they don't realize
it and it's really sad so we're going to
talk about that all that oil on top of
that nut butter right there and when you
get nut butter and it doesn't look it
was freshly made pretty recently by a
company and then they put it out there
and then over time though as the thing
settle a few months later the cupboard
all that oil Rises right there that's
the that's the whole thing I want to
talk about too but anyway it's not about
that entirely because we're making all
that with the mm 1500 right there best
sale ever in the mm500 $140 off
$140 off get it for somebody for
Christmas if you waited all year and you
don't have the MN 1500 hands down the MN
1500 saves people money I'm watching out
there all the time I'm just going to say
this I'm just going to say this but the
users that are getting popular because
they got money behind them and
advertising and influencers behind them
those juicers spinning baskets and
everything else they don't squeeze
enough juice out of the produce and so
essentially you're throwing away money
and people who are chronically sick are
trying to juice every day people in the
medical mem Community who juice a ton of
stuff they can't just be buying cases
and cases of produce juicing it and
having not the results because you're
not getting enough nutrients extracted
from the juice it's not actually doing
its job get the juice out and they're
throwing away produce all that leftover
pulp is getting thrown away so if you're
somebody that's really wealthy and you
don't care and you just you you want to
use the juicers that actually only
extract some juice but not a lot you're
running lots and lots of prod then fine
that's fine but a lot of people want to
save money and a lot of people want to
be able to actually juice like celery
and everything else without actually
spending a ton of money saving thousands
over the time so that's what I love
about the M 1500 the 900 this is the mm
1500 right here you guys know I work
with the mega link is in the description
link is in the profile but we're talking
today about eating to protect your liver
so eating foods to protect your liver
because what people don't realize they
have overburdened stagnant sluggish hot
livers that are filled with fat the
liers get dysfunctional and then your
cholesterol gets out of whack everything
else gets out of whack deficiencies
start to happen because your liver is
the great converter let's talk about
that for a minute if you just got on
here I'm going to be making a ton of
food you see everything here if you're
getting kicked off IG I see a whole
bunch of people getting kicked off of IG
so it looks like IG is definitely going
to be doing some serious censoring on
this one so what you do is go to medical
medium.com and go there I'm streaming
live right now at Medical medium.com so
go there and see me there you can see me
also on telegram you can see me in other
places too um yo
amazing good to see you right there I'm
glad you're here I'm glad you're here
see guys you can go to rumble you can go
to telegram you can go to Facebook you
can be on IG right here people are
coming IG you can be on YouTube watching
this right now and also streaming live
on medicalmedium.com right now so you
guys we're going to make some food we're
going to talk about the liver a little
bit too so what happens with people's
livers is that they actually burden them
and they don't realize they burden them
so they overburden livers every single
day and that's what we're kind of taught
we're not taught how to protect our
liver how to look after our liver how to
get our liver in a better place and then
over time our liver stops working the
way it should work it doesn't produce
enough bile and when that bile isn't
produced we get in trouble and all that
fat sits around it doesn't break down
good enough it sits around in our
bloodstream then it eventually collects
in Our arteries then it collects in our
veins and over time we get problems
where we have all this plaque jacked up
all around around our blood vessels
veins arteries our liver gets sluggish
another thing too you go to the doctor
doctor takes blood work the blood work
comes back you're deficient in this
you're deficient in that you're
deficient in this and all these
deficiencies over time partly happen
because your liver is the great
converter what it does is it actually
converts the
nutrients and we don't have good livers
these days so we don't get good
conversion because you want good
conversion every single nutrient you eat
almost every single nutrient you eat
nutrients that come from your leafy
greens nutrients that come from your
onions your broccoli your radishes your
carrots everything your lemons your
limes your Tomatoes your avocados all
those nutrients have to be converted
they go into the liver boom they go up
the hepatic portal highway right into
the liver here and when that happens
your liver says whoa It's conversion
time so your liver has to anoint and
bless the nutrients is what it has to do
and people don't realize this they think
that if you take a whole bunch of
supplements the supplements are going to
work for you you take a whole bunch of
different things are going to work for
you and partially that partially that's
true but your liver still has to
methylate it still has to convert it
still has to anoint and turn and change
the nutrients around around a little bit
it has to bless them enzymes from the
liver attach to the nutrients carry the
nutrients along change the nutrients too
and then the liver has to store the
nutrients at the same time but if we
overburden we beat down our livers we
drink alcohol we do all kinds of stuff
we eat really greasy food fried foods we
eat too much oil in everything we get in
trouble the liver ends up weakening and
when it weakens it can't convert it will
not do that conversion that we need so
we walk around our liver is getting
tired it's getting stagnant it's getting
sluggish and then it's not doing its job
every day and then we go to bed at night
and our liver is tired it's too tired to
work hard for us all night long so what
happens when you go to bed at night your
liver starts to work that's when it
clocks in mainly clocks in in the middle
of the night that's where it starts to
bag up all the garbage all the junk all
the toxins all the poisons they get
bagged up in the middle of the night and
you got to keep that in mind right so
when we sleep our liver working while
we're resting that's how it works our
liver working while we're resting think
about a whole bunch of elves inside your
liver and they're making all kinds of
toys and they're doing all kinds of
stuff and they're using Hammers and saws
they're working all night long while
you're sleeping and resting but when our
livers get tired and they get beat up
and they get overburdened and they get
fatty and they start to get sluggish and
stagnant when they work in the middle of
the night they're not as efficient our
livers are not as working as they should
or efficient as they should so in the
middle of the night we sit there and
sometimes people toss in turns some
sometimes people have more gas sometimes
people have they're waking up in the
middle of the night sometimes people
don't feel good when they're trying to
sleep they're tossing and turning and a
lot of that is liver spasming out the
liver the liver being stressed out
overburdened stagnant and struggling so
people get liver spasms they don't even
know it a lot of people live with liver
spasms have no idea that's what's
happening and inside their body they got
an unhappy liver every single day that
wants to perform that wants to move
forward that wants to heal that wants to
get better but it just can't do what it
needs to do and every single day it's
repeat right we then overburden it again
we do alcohol we overburden it with two
much fat we end up eating too many
treats and when we do that our liver is
like oh here it goes again so let's talk
about bio reserves most people walking
around have low bile reserves what that
means is their liver is not producing
enough bile to break down the fats now
bile does more than break down fats bile
breaks down a lot of different aspects
of the food but fat is one of the number
one things that the bile actually does
but our bile is low for most people
walking around we have low bile and what
happens is food rots in the gut when you
have reduced bile levels inside your
liver bile that's not potent it's not
strong one problem that happens when
your bile is not potent and strong is
that it's not doing its job when it goes
up the bile duck when it gets into the
gallbladder our gallbladder start
getting wasted they start becoming a
trash compound they start start becoming
a trash dump and when our gallbladder
becomes a trash dump okay and it can't
be cleaned out we get in trouble then we
get the gall stones then we get the sand
in the gallbladder then we get all the
different gallbladder spasms and
problems a lot of people have to have
their gallbladders removed but when your
B is strong and potent and really
aggressive you can't collect a lot of
sediment inside the gallbladder you
can't collect a lot of Sandy sediment
stones and so forth inside the
gallbladder when the bile is really
vibrant it has vitality and it's strong
and it actually is Gusto what happens is
if it's not doesn't have that Gusto if
it's not that strong if your bile is
weak and you're producing less bile like
most people are the sludge builds up
inside the gallbladder the gallbladder
needs to be awaken it needs to be
shocked it needs to be pushed hard and
if our bile reserves are our gallbladder
is going to get stagnant too so boom we
got the liver that's stagnant and
sluggish and then boom we got the
gallbladder that's stagnant and sluggish
you see how it works that's what happens
there's people out there that're like I
want to do gallbladder flush I want to
take care of my gallbladder I got gall
stones I'm worried about gallbladder
problems and then what they don't
realize is they got liver problems they
had liver problems first not Gall
gallbladder problems first had liver
problems first so what happens is when
your bile is your bile reserves are low
stagnant sluggish and dirty and fill the
trash and garbage and then weak it goes
into the gallbladder and doesn't come
out easy and then the gallbladder gets
fatter and fatter and fatter and fatter
the gallbladder gets heavier and heavier
and becomes a sack of mud a sack of
stones a sack of sand so a lot of people
walk around and they got basically a
sack of stones and sand inside their
gallbladder it's just this little sack
that's filled up and how did it get like
that because bile was weak for a long
time bile reserves were low for a long
time and because of that all that trash
and garbage and poisons and toxins that
came out of the liver as the liver got
stagnant and sluggish they all landed
inside the gallbladder and there wasn't
enough body bile to go in there and
flush and push and flush and the potency
of the bile wasn't strong enough to
dissolve dissolve bile is extremely
powerful it's a dissolvent it's supposed
to break down fats and dissolve them
that's what bile does but when it
weakens it can't go and do that as much
so it enters into the gallbladder and it
can't do its job it's weak
it's lost its viscosity it's lost its
power it's not as powerful as it needs
to be it's not as stringent and that AR
stringency is gone away from the bile
and when it's gone and away from the
bile we get in trouble the gallbladder
starts to get Gnarly nasty filled with
junk garbage and sand and becomes a sack
of mud and that's what happens and
people walk around it could take years
you could be walking around through your
life and it could take years and your go
bladder just builds up and builds up
more slug you know more sludge in there
more problems inside there and then boom
it hits us we have the spasms we have a
problem we're having a we're putting
castor oil packs on our gallbladder we
live like that and that's a it's not a
fun place to be it's taking casserole
packs and you're looking up things and
you're using all kinds of stuff you're
on the internet what can I do for
gallbladder what can I do for
gallbladder then we're in that hell
which is oh my God I don't want to get
this gallbladder out the doctor says
it's going to turn Gang Green they did
an M they did a CAT scan they think my
gall bladder's got a problem what am I
going to do what's going to happen and
then you're back into the emergency room
then you're back in the doctor's office
and your gallbladder is becoming a
problem it's getting heavier it's
getting the sand it's getting the slug
the sludge in there and meanwhile how
did that even happen it happened because
the liver wasn't taken care of the liver
wasn't nurtured there wasn't enough Good
Foods going into the liver there wasn't
enough nutrients going into the liver to
shake it up to wake it up to keep it
going it wasn't there we starved our
liver of nutrients we starved our liver
of the things it needs like the glucose
and the nutrients and the trace mineral
salts and everything that the liver
needs we starved it we didn't do it on
purpose it's not your fault it's
nobody's fault it happened it just
happened and that's how it works we're
not taught we don't know what to do a
lot of us don't have the access to do so
or the resources and we just go through
life and our liver gets stagnant and
sluggish and eventually the gallbladder
pays the price and so many people get
their gallbladder out later you know if
you can do like a
futuristic futuristic history with
people okay you look at a person you see
them now like they are hey they're doing
good they're out in the street they're
doing stuff they're playing pickle ball
they're having fun or they're out there
playing tennis and they're having fun or
they're swimming or on their be on the
beach they're paddle boarding they're
doing what they want they're biking
they're having a good time you're like
okay that's great right they look like
they're in good shape they look like
they're taking care of themselves or
they're just living their life and then
go go 40 years ahead of time and you see
and it's like a war zone right people's
lives change things happen I had a penic
out I had you know pentis I had a
gallbladder out I had that I had this
other problem here I got this other
problem here here you know I got four
nodules on my thyroid I had a thyroid
surgery I had this times change and life
changes as the years go on but how do we
get to that point when it comes down to
gallbladders okay that is Cash Cow for
the hospitals Cash Cow for big Pharma
Cash Cow for the industry the medical
industry it's the gallbladder business
and a big part of that is because the
liver has lost its Gusto it's been
nutrient deficient over time it's not
converting the bow weakened it's not
strong it's not potent it's not going
right up into the gallbladder it's not
driving deep into the gallbladder and
pushing out the sludge and pushing out
the garbage instead we get in trouble
right Ron says cast oil packs can help
break up gall stones and kidney stones
as well I've never seen them break them
up I like CER oil packs I like them for
pain relief for people I do kind of acts
like an outside it's kind of acts like
an anti-inflammatory like a quick relief
anti-inflammatory so I'm not against
castor oil packs I think they're great
but I don't see them actually break up
kidney stones in people it's you know
but I see them give people relief though
when they got the kidney stones and the
gallbladder stones it gives them that
relief that I've seen for sure all the
35 years I've been doing this I see it
give people relief but they still end up
if they're you know if they if their
gallbladder gets all filled up with that
sand and that garbage and they don't
have enough of that liver power to do
what it needs to do to help get that
bile up there to break it up that's how
we get in trouble so our bile duck boom
as the bile is going up there it's weak
it's not as strong and it doesn't have
that strength in the stringency and if
it doesn't have that astringency it's
not going to actually dissolve what it
needs to dissolve and then sediment
turns into mud that mud forms into
Stones periodically depending on what's
really in there and then boom you know
that's where we get in trouble and
that's what happens very important
information if you're into gallbladders
if you're into livers we're talking
today about how to eat a little better
especially during the holidays when
we're dealing with anything in our life
chronic illness any kind of issues and
if we don't have chronic illness how do
we stay healthier during the holidays
talking about that too and one way is to
treat your liver right take care of your
liver make sure your liver is in good
shape you can do that while while going
through Christmas while going through
the holidays while going through New
Year you can take care of your liver
there's ways of doing it and that's what
we're going into now so let's go into
liver a little bit more which is really
important so our liver is the sponge
it's the filter I've been saying this
for years it's the very thing that's
holding all the toxins all the poisons
right all the different things that
we're up against viruses pathogens
bacteria all inside the liver the liver
becomes that sack right there that sack
that filter do you ever see a fish tank
you ever see that little carbon filter
in the fish tank it's sitting in there
in the fish tank that carbon filter it's
bubbling out right and the filter is
supposed to be actually keeping the tank
water cleaner for the fish and all that
all the different toxins that are in
that water it's supposed to go into the
carbon filter that's what your liver is
it's like you're the fish tank you're
the water tank right here and your liver
is the filter in that fish tank right
there so that is your filter now what
you don't want is you don't want your
filter getting old and nasty and gnarly
and fill the junk in garbage you don't
want that River being filled up with all
of that okay when it's getting nasty and
early and getting filled up with garbage
we get in trouble because the garbage
has to go somewhere else so where does
it go your lymphatic system so the more
your liver is stagnant and sluggish the
more your lymphatic system gets stagnant
and sluggish lymphatic system is the
Overflow so let's go into lymphatic
system a little bit I know a lot of you
guys love lymphatic system I hear a lot
of people talking about the lymphatic
system everybody's going for the
drainage right you lay on the table and
they're like okay here you go and
they're rubbing everything and they're
working on your your lymph right they're
doing the whole thing you're like whoa I
feel better now then they're working on
your abdomen they're pushing down in
your abdomen and you're like okay I'm
less bloated they're squeezing
everything out but what people have to
realize is it fills back up fills right
back up the next day fills right back up
the next week fills right back up it's
your overflow if your liver is nasty and
gnarly it dumps everything boom over
into your lymphatic system that's how it
works right I see people out there they
want to do lymphatic cleanup but they're
not doing liver cleanup they're doing
lymphatic cleanup but they're not doing
liver cleanup and that's where people
get in trouble it's like they're focused
seeing on their eyes on the wrong ball
they're lymphatic lymphatic lymphatic
lymphatic meanwhile it's the liver it's
the liver it's the liver that you have
to work on so your lymphatic system
doesn't become the garbage dump and the
garbage pit for when your liver is
completely stagnant sluggish and
overloaded very important to know right
there so if you guys are into lymphatic
systems and you want to take care of
your lymphatic system you want it
healthy you want your lymphatic system
clean you want the color of the fluid
and your lymphatic system clear because
right there people don't know it but
they got the pus they got the yellow pus
inside their lymphatic system and that
yellow pus is because of the Overflow
from the liver pouring into the
lymphatic system that's what it is Li
liver gets overloaded your liver gets
burdened over burdened and stagnant and
sluggish all that overflow gets pushed
Boop into your lymphatic system and here
we are we're in lymphatic hell we're
getting the lymphatic drainage we don't
feel good our lym we're swelling we're
get the lymphodema we're not doing so
good we're always a little extra swollen
than we should and people get worried
about that and what's happening is our
livers are overburdened and let's go
into night time a little bit when we go
and sleep at night going ready for bed
and that's it it's time to go to bed we
click off the light and as the we hours
of the morning start kicking in your
liver is working it's working overtime
and that's what it's doing it's trying
to take the junk up and clean it up and
bag it up and get ready so it wants to
be flushed out in the morning we wake up
in the morning and we don't flush it out
that's what happens we wake up in the
morning and we're not doing our celery
juice we're not doing our lemon water we
end up doing something else wake up in
the morning and we end up putting fat in
our diet right fat in our breakfast and
when we do that we overload the liver
again we don't give our liver a chance
to recoup flush out the poisons and
toxins the liver stays stagnant and
sluggish and
then the liver can't push all that
garbage in the right spots the B's weak
the bile is actually lost its strength
the bile pushes up into the
gallbladder it takes some junk up with
it it doesn't get dispersed it's not
astringent enough our gallbladder starts
getting sicker our lymphatic system
starts getting mucker and yellow and
mucus and pus and every day we walk
around swollen we walk around with all
this junk in our liver and a stagnant
sluggish liver and then the holidays
come so that's the next thing too and
all of a sudden the holidays come along
and we're just like eating whatever
we're eating we're over this person's
house family's house friends's house
we're at the
office we're seeing everybody eat what
they want there's cakes there's cookies
there's treats there's Donuts there's
Bagels there's everything under the sun
there's the cookies with Christ tree
designs on it there's cookies with like
Rudolph on there and we're eating it all
and we're thinking too much sugar too
much sugar when really there's a lot of
fat in there and that fat starts to
burden in the liver starts to drag it
down and in the holidays we're like no
no it's New Year's Eve is coming I'm
gonna make a pledge I'm gonna commit I'm
gonna start January 1 I'm going to get
this weight off of me I'm going to do
everything I can and we're back to that
again
so let's talk about like another thing
that takes a hit at this time of year so
what am I even talking about your liver
takes a hit at this time of year big
time your gallbladder takes a hit big
time this time of year your pancreas
takes a hit big time this year any year
this time of
year so what happens is that this time
of year those three things take a huge
hit right there and guess what our
stomach takes a hit too unfortunately
when all that's taking a hit let's go
into that a little bit so a lot of
people have gut rot in their intestinal
tract in their colon gut rot why do they
have the gut rot because their food's
not breaking down one of the reasons
their food's not breaking down is their
HCL is low their HCL is low their little
gastric glands these tiny little glands
inside their stomach get weak and beat
up over
time and we end up
killing those little gastric glands they
don't work as good we don't produce the
HCL we need that hydrochloric acid isn't
breaking down the protein we're dumping
protein in we're dumping all kinds of
stuff in and our HCL is not breaking it
down and that protein goes down into the
gut and it starts to
rot and then your liver is like I don't
have enough bio I can't break down the
fat I can't break down some of the other
nutrients I can't break down some of the
other particles and boom now we have
that problem too you got rotting fat
going rancid you got rotting protein
going bad everything's going sour it's
fermenting did you ever run into that
with people at all where you smell it on
their breath do you get a breath test
from them get the breath test right
you smell it on the breath right did you
ever get that with someone where it's
like you just smell it it's fermented
it's sour it smells like sourdough it's
like hey man did you just have sour
dough
bread dude did did you just have sour
dough bread or
what is that what you had because guess
what that stuff stinks it's fermenting
you got a soup in here stuff is rotting
you got all kinds of different protein
and fat down in the bowels and they're
rotting yeah all that ammonia is being
produced the ammonia is actually going
through your body it's coming out of
your skin it's coming out of your
armpits it's coming out of everywhere
it's coming out of your ass it's coming
out of your mouth it just stinks the
ammonia and then all that broken down
ammonia that's just rising and floating
everywhere is lifting off taking off
getting stronger and stronger and your
your proteins are not breaking down and
more fermentation is happening and more
rotting is happening it's called gut rot
so people walk around with gut rot
that's what they
do heavy fatty meals hit the pancreas
hard and the pancreas has to pump out
insulin that hormone has to be pumping
out and when it's pumping out that's
another thing let's go into that a
little bit so we talked about the
stomach people's stomach gastric glands
don't produce HCL
they can't break down the proteins their
liver can't break down the fats as good
so the liver right the bile weakens
we're in that your gallbladder gets
sluggish fill the junk sediment sand all
kinds of different rocks start to
actually get produced in there and then
your pancreas has to produce lots of
insulin because we're eating so many
Abominations we're eating so much stuff
that's fun we're having too much sugar
and fat combined we're having it
combined and when we do that we're
getting insulin resistance so
everybody's walking around at this time
of year like on the edge your A1C is
about to go up they're they're about to
get a piece of plaque broken in an
artery going up to their brain or lung
they're about to get something else
happened have a heart attack people
stroke out this time of year A lot of
times because they're dehydrated their
body's filled sluggish filled with all
that dirty blood syndrome their pancreas
too much insulin so much insulin
resistance it's out of control and then
their liver is so sluggish and stagnant
the food's not breaking down and
digesting good doesn't it sound like a
nightmare yeah it doesn't seem like a
nightmare but it is for so many people
the thing is with sugar just so we don't
confuse things you need sugar to survive
but when we eat a lot of sugar and then
fat combined together the pancreas has
to work even harder and produce more
insulin and then boom we're blocking the
sugar from getting into the cells
because of all that fat that's there and
then we get nutrient deficient from that
all on itself it's a whole another story
in insulin resistance and diabetes and
everything but we don't need to go there
right now let's start making some food
I'm excited you guys thanks for actually
listening to some of this fun
stuff put the dummy back right there so
I just want to let everybody
know I'm making two
guacamole I'm making a few different
hummuses hummus hummuses I'm making also
some Walnut
butter which is really cool make sure
you actually grab a book someday you
know you grab Liver Rescue there's so
much information about the liver here
it's an amazing book cleanse and heel is
another book you can get too right there
which is an Incredible Book right there
too so many ways to eat take care of
your liver so many different protocols
all right let's go let's try to do
something let's try to make something
happen here what can we make first we're
also making a pea hummus which is really
really interesting I got to say right
let's see if this this is on it's on all
right let's start with
something I think we're going to have
some fun let's start with some
regular actually let's do the guacamole
first yes I feel like doing that a
little bit more okay so I got avocados
let's
roll so I'm cracking them open right
here let's get a few of them
go here
okay I saw someone say what book is it
it's a lot of different books right here
right you got the cleanse to heal okay
you got the Liber rescue as
well these are two incredible books if
you don't have them already there it
is all right so we're making some
guacamole right now this is going to be
fun so I'm cutting open the avocados
right now now what I like about making
guacamole with the mm500 and this mm500
is
$140 off right now it's the best sale
I've ever seen on the mm 1500 never seen
a sale like it it's
$140 off if you guys are looking for
something like this so I'm cracking
cracking open a lot of avocados I want
to make a couple of different guacamole
really quick here this is really cool
let me get another avocado
going these are really nice avocados I
love when the avocados are nice like
this
incredible all
right okay so what I'm going to do is
get a couple of things ready
too going to grab this to and use
it okay right there now let me get a
couple of things together too I got a
little bit of salt if you like that you
can put a little bit of salt in there
okay you can throw a few tomatoes in
there if you want to actually do that
that's not something that uh that people
see normally if you make a guacamole in
here which is really cool you can put
some tomatoes in there I got some lemon
and lime which one do you like I'm going
to go with some limes right
there I'm excited about this this is the
kind of food I like to make my family my
friends during the holidays and the
crazy thing is when they're out there in
the world they're getting into all kinds
of stuff all kinds of trouble and then
they land here at the medical medium
kitchen and they're just like eating all
the good stuff they're like why is this
so good why does this taste good like I
could have been eating this instead of
what I've eaten you know the other day
you hear what they've eaten it's like
whoa you know I have a friend that just
is on the road all the time and then
it's like I wish I had some of that good
medical medium stuff right now all
right so I got some
lime all right I got some spices I got
some hot pepper take a look at this can
you see this you guys cayenne pepper
from my garden right there okay I'm
going to make two kinds of guacamole
one's going to be an herb guacamole one
is going to be a guacamole that's the
simplest most basic guacamole you've
ever seen probably let's
go get a spoo
out you go you guys know I work with
Omega on the mm 1500 it's an incredible
machine for so many
reasons all right going to run some
avocado in
here excited link is in the description
it's in the bio it's $140 off right now
you guys know
that I usually don't even I don't even
talk about the juicer unless I know it
can save people money like if there's
like a a sale on it or
something
right so I'm throwing some avocado in
here like this I love making
guacamole it's one of my favorite things
to make it's coming out really
nice what there you
go run some avocado through
here now I don't know about you but like
when I make guacamole for family and
friends I I get a lot of avocados I sent
a friend to the store I was like hey
could you go and get like some avocado
for me I need a bunch of them I'm making
it for family some
guacamole and then what I'm going to do
is put some lime juice right in here too
right into here I'm going to drop some
salt in there
too someone said why do you juice
avocado well I'm not juicing avocado the
machine is actually
set for avocado it's got this little
setting thing in there I'm going to drop
some salt in here a little bit of
that then remember this is really basic
this is really
simple
this isn't just a
juicer dude this isn't just a juicer
this is the mm1 1500 we're gonna make
hummus with this thing we're gonna make
hummus we're making guacamole with this
thing are you
kidding this isn't just no way this is a
really
basic guacamole I'm making right
now pretty
cool now I put a little bit of pinch of
salt in there I put some lime in there
I'm going to squeeze a little bit more
lime in here too I like doing it like
this boom how cool is that now I am
going to make this one a little spicy so
I am going to put this in
here can't help
it I do like the heat so I put you know
pepper hot peppers almost anything the
only thing is you might get somebody
like a family member or a friend and
they're just they're not into the
they're not into the hot
pepper it's a little too much for
them I'm going to make two kinds of
guacamole this is the basic one right up
front
here whoa you see that hot pepper come
out right there there's the hot pepper
it ran right through yeah that's
insane all right that's one kind of
guacamole
nice you really like that all right let
that run
out shut this down so there we
go okay I'm going to mix it just a
little
bit I'm excited about that this is
without herbs or anything except for the
cayenne pepper I'm taking show you right
there that's one guacamole all it has is
lime in there and a hot pepper cayenne
pepper so it's got an edge to it okay
now what I'm going to do is pop a little
bit of garlic powder right in it as well
so drop a little garlic powder on
there you can spice these up all you
want any way you want I'm going to put a
little bit of onion powder too right on
that
guacamole
boom that's a basic one with some spices
added into it it's got
lime set a little bit of lime there take
a look you guys we're going to do it
this way today there it is that is
one nice little
guacamole and I am going to now make
another one really quick I'm actually
proud of this one right here it came out
really good I'm popping some lime on
there boom okay moving along make
another one right here got another
Bowl all right this one is going to be
the herb one I'm running some herbs in
here I'm running some other things too
in here I'm kind of looking into looking
forward to this actually let's crack
open a couple more
avocados
nice
nice there we go that one's got a
stubborn little pit in the
center okay let's grab another
one that one's still hard that one's
still
hard you don't want them so soft where
they're mushy they they're getting the
brown spots too many Brown round spots
they're getting fermented a lot of
people use fermented avocados and don't
realize it they make a guacamole and
it's terrible I'm doing lemon with this
one if you guys are okay with that got
my
lemon all right pumped up about this
let's
roll
okay
avocado is not a real heavy fat okay it
is an overt fat but it's not a real
heavy one keep that in mind it's easier
on the liver easier on the system if
you're dealing with chronic illness if
you're dealing with with all kinds of
other
issues digestive problems it's really
it's so much more gentle I'm a big
avocado fan anybody who knows medical
medium and they and they say hey he
doesn't like avocado it's not exactly it
I really do like avocado it's just that
so many people come to the medical
medium Forefront Frontier putting lemon
in here they come to the medical medium
Frontier because they're really sick
let's face it that's why they're doing
it I popped a little bit of little pinch
of salt in
there I want a hot pepper in here too
I'm going to pop that in there as well
okay there you
go they come into it where hey I'm so
sick I need answers I need medical
medium books I need to learn how to heal
and then it might say look you might
want to back off on Avocado if you're
really sick and just work on some of the
other protocols but if you're
not if you're not like if you're like
hey I'm not that bad I'm working on my
healing have some avocado have some
guacamole
definitely so now what I'm going to
start doing is putting some fresh herbs
in here too any
second okay guacamole is a holiday dip
it's holiday
fun okay now let's start doing it start
doing some killar stuff right now I got
some oregano right
here straight out of the garden I want
to put some oregano in this
guacamole I got some
parsley right here I want to run some
parsley in this guacamole too this is
also out of the garden as well there we
are right there got some curly leaf
parsley let's get that in
there so this is an herb
guacamole I love doing it this way get
ready for this okay two Sage
leaves two in here boom boom two Sage
leaves in there
bam squeeze a little bit more lemon
nice another little pinch of salt Bo
boom this is the herb guacamole get
those herbs in there that's what we're
doing there okay I'm going to run a
little tomato in here too some yellow
tomatoes inside this
guacamole is this exciting I don't know
is it just me because I'm I'm having a
blast every time I take this baby out to
do this kind of thing it's like so
fun here we go you guys want to know
anything about this juicer
does all kinds of different things it
doesn't just juice it's like a
Nutritional Center you can make all
kinds of things hummuses guacamole all
right I'm putting some fresh tomato in
here love doing that yellow
tomato incredible all right get that in
there all right pop a little bit more
avocado and finish this one up there's a
hot pepper in here there's lemon this
time in this one the other one has lime
if you think there isn't a difference
there really is a difference some people
like it with lemon some people like it
with lime I like it with both some
people say tomato some people say tomato
just call the whole thing
off here you
go okay we did some tomato got lots of
avocado in here I'm going to put a
little bit more herb I'm making a big
one there we go
incredible pumped about this let's throw
a nice curly leaf parsley down in here
look at that you guys right out the
garden there we
go and I'm really into like herbs so I'm
I'm even going to do a little bit more
oregano this is a medicinal guacamole
just so you know this is like a medicine
guacamole this machine is a medicine
maker keep that in mind this machine is
a medicine maker look at that herb
coming right out you see this herb
that's pulverized check take a look you
guys that's herb that's pulverized so
nutrients are easy to receive that goes
in there look at that it's pulverized
herb that is incred incredible that's
insane let's mix this up got a little
bit more coming through all right juer
you talking to me are you talking to me
juicer are you saying you got a little
bit more that's coming out I want to
hear you come on juicer Keep It Coming
keep it
coming that's the
way there we go going to mix this up
take a look let's shut this down you
guys that's the medicine guacamole right
there so what you see is intense herbs
in there you got Sage fresh Sage right
out of the garden you got parsley you
can go the store get stage there get
stage get partially there right there
you go you got it all and I'm going to
take a little taste are you guys okay
with
this bear with me a little bit okay I'm
going to take a look over here I'm going
to pop it right into this this bowl for
a second a little bit of
it there you go
all right let's get a little
taste all right do not fall do not fall
I got a cucumber right here let's do a
little
crud that's
sick that's insane right there double
dip is that okay can should I flip it
around oh yeah that's insane right there
mhm hey guys you see that a so good we
got a lot more to
do hope you guys are ready cuz we're not
messing
around all right all
right let's get that guacamole over to
the side let's move over this lemon
okay
okay see
here what I'm going to do is
I think I got a lot of things let me
actually do this first you guys let me
clean off a little bit of this because
we got some stuff to do I'm excited
about
this guacamole is one of those things
where you know you know it's good for
you for so many
reasons all
right there we go
grab this one right here all right guys
I want to show you how you can assemble
this let's do that right here I know
people are asking right
now all right so what you're seeing
right here is with this machine is I'm
using some different parts I'm not just
using the juicer parts for like juicing
right it's really easy to use like
earlier I used the juicer
apparatus Implement I used it earlier
right to make
juice right now what I'm doing is I'm
using this piece right here from the
mm500 I put this in this is for the nut
Butters this is for the guacamole this
is for the hummus so I put this in there
you see how it works I wanted to show
you this and then there's this little
piece just like this right here check it
out little piece and that little piece
goes goes right in that piece and it
goes right on here boom got it together
just like that pretty
cool all
right
um
see going put this back on and use it
here okay so I'm using this for
guacamole right here so I'm going to
take it apart for you is what I'm going
to do about
that um if you do this right here see
and that little piece is there too you
guys and that's the piece right
there all right that is the same system
as the other
one all right I'm going to make some
hummus let's go let's get going on
this let's make some garbanzo bean
hummus
is what we're going to
do all right and let's get a bowl out
for
that could be a little bit of avocado
left over in this hummus but I don't
care you can rinse it out you can clean
it out really quick I got the sink right
here I can take this rinse it right out
but I'm going to leave it in because
there's no really worry about it there's
no need if a little bit of guacamole
ends up in my hummus that's fine but if
you're somebody that wants to just give
it a quick rinse easy to do you can put
it back on you can make other stuff so
what I have right here is a bowl of
chickpeas garbanza
beans you guys can
see and I'm going to make hummus get
this I'm GNA make it without using
Sesame tahini I'm not going to use a
whole bunch of tahini in here I'm not
not going to dump a whole bunch of olive
oil in here either this is easier food
on the liver that's what this is keep in
mind
it's easier food on the liver so what
you see is sesame seeds take a look you
can get the flavor of Sesame in your
hummus without burdening the liver with
too much
oil too much tahini you don't need to do
that you can make a hummus and just use
some sesame seeds in here get it ground
up all the same in there that's that's
the difference so let's
go let's drop some of these garbanzo
beans in here right
here you can make hummus without olive
oil without tahini check this out right
I got some I got some garbanzos coming
through you guys look this is easier on
the
liver you realize like how very little
this is a handful of sesame seeds much
different than a tablespoon of tahini in
somebody's Hest right look at this see
have the seeds going there so very
little but yet the flavor is knock your
socks off flavor is insane like it's so
good look dropping that in here this is
a basic hummus you don't have to go too
crazy Mary says best thing is that
juicer takes less than five minutes to
clean it's so quick I could have
actually cleaned this whole part right
here had you guys wait probably would
have done it in a minute and a half
right
all right so what you're seeing right
here is hummus being made do you like
it's spicy do you like your hummus hot
how do you like it well I'm going to
stick another hot pepper in mine okay
I'm going to put half of a hot pepper in
mine right there there we go and I'm
going to keep keep it coming I'm going
to get lemon in
here I got a lemon squeezing the lemon
right in here there we go knocked out
that
seed nice lemon
juice just like that
ready some more sesame seeds dropping in
here you guys got to realize the reason
why this is liver friendly that amount
of sesame seed is nothing compared to a
tablespoon of Sesame butter it's nothing
compared to that like seriously you can
drop some garlic powder in here why not
you can just go straight in
here got the garlic
powder we got the lemon in
there there we
go all
right this is just this is
incredible we're going to put a little
touch of salt people that come over
they're like where's the salt you know
where's the salt there we go little
touch of salt in there
and what you're watching it's a
phenomenon what you're
watching is some serious hummus being
made this is garbanzo bean
hummus I mean I'm already going what two
three four people can have this already
I'm making a big one check that
out this isn't a fancy one this isn't an
herb one look at that look how it's
coming out you guys is that insane or
what I got so many things to make right
now I'm so pumped look at that all
right I'm going to mix that up these are
the sesame seeds I used I'm going to put
them back over here I'm going to move
the garbanzos over
here so much to
do yep
cool throw that in there try pie this
like
this so good all right I'm going to mix
that up
let me show you right here that's
hummus
right and there isn't a tablespoon of
oil there's not a tablespoon of olive
oil there isn't a tablespoon of tahini
in here it's easy on the liver easy on
the
bile bile production in the liver
people's livers can't break down enough
fat then it sits in their colon their
small intestinal tract it goes r it and
it feeds everything that shouldn't
feed so I'm just mixing this
up and we got some
hummus let's pop that into a little Bowl
right
there here we
go I'm going to get some in here you
don't have to put put it all unless you
want to there we
go all right check this out
of
guacamole you got people coming
over back to the crud this time it's
with hummus made from the mm 1500 I'm
going to take a
radish so
good we got so much more to make I'm
going to be eating all day love it how
long does that last
huh
frally made put it in the fridge last I
don't know a
week
more maybe
longer so good maybe longer all right
next on the express
way on the aw
Express we got some black beans right
here just so you know um
the this hummus right here looks like
it's
dry it's not sloppy wet if you want a
sloppy wet one put in a little bit more
lemon right but this is not actually as
dry as you think it is right there it
would never smooth out like that I'm
just trying to show you right here but
if you want it like watery if you want
your hummus like water like watery like
not just like like creamy not just
creamy but you want it like water-based
put more lemon in
there can't please everyone okay let's
go we're going to do some black bean
hummus right now which I'm actually
excited
about next on the list let's
go
yep turn on the machine black bean
hummus coming right
up right put your black beans right in
the machine guys just so you know this
machine is $140 off that's best price
I've ever seen with the mm 1500 it
juices it makes food you can do healthy
foods that are easy on the liver it
doesn't get any better than that I'm
going to drop a lime in
here got to put a spin on it when you
throw it in the air that's what I do I
throw a spin on it
right okay I'm dropping lime right in
this black bean
hummus this is going to taste so
good so good get the black beans in
here all right you can put herbs in here
you can put anything your heart
desires but the goal is not to put a
whole bunch of oil in there not to put a
whole bunch of like tablespoons of of
tahimi in here you don't have to do that
drop a little
salt a little pinch of that I'm sorry
but I'm going to drop another hot pepper
in
here
hopefully you're okay with that you can
put fresh garlic in here I'm using the
spice which you can do fresh that's
fine look at
that you're
watching the medical medium cooking show
we're making food fast we're making
guacamole after guacamole we're making
hummus after hummus we're gonna be
making mango ice cream
what else what else right look at that
black being and hummus coming right up
do you want some herbs in here because I
do I'm going to drop some parsley down
in here and I'm going to drop a little
bit of oregano down in here
too I might even put a sage in
here that's medicine we're talking
about
people would love this if you actually
served it to them they would love this
dropping these black beans in here let's
get some more
lime look at that am I
multitasking
yep we got more lime in there now we got
our black beans in there
boom look at
that all right you
guys now the black bean hummus is more
moist black beans tend to have a lot
they tend to hold a lot more fluid water
for the holidays you can make these all
these different tips from
here all these different
recipes for your friends and family
during the holidays all these
dips yeah that's a fun funny one all
right and then you have your black bean
hummus now you can put tomatoes around
it if you want but that's your black
bean hummus right there this is
very good now I did this one without
sesame seeds but I'm going to do the
next one with sesame seeds Okay this is
an amazing one right
here I think this is one of the people
Pleasers you have people over it's the
black bean hummus can really do it all
right
guys let's switch it
out what am I going to try now what am I
going to have now this is crud with the
black bean hummus are we crushing it or
what should I go with carrot is that
cool
okay are you okay if I do onion whoa
some reason that hot pepper actually
extra hot what about onions did you ever
eat onion like this
look
next Janette Anthony I just
got
Janette
Anthony on Facebook I just got an 11
week white puppy and naming her angel I
was inspired by your dog Angelic rescue
me choked up anybody any anytime anybody
even mentions my dog that rescued
me in my life after I rescued my
dog in her
life no it gets me choked up all
right all right next one on the list
ready
lentil hummus have you guys just got on
here it's the mm 1500 I'm making two I
already made two guacamole I already
made two hummus is I'm making a third
hummus right here what you see is fresh
collar greens which I'm going to show
you a little bit how I like eat my stuff
like in the collard greens and the
mustard
greens crud T going on got the avocados
everything everything's here but I'm not
done I'm making a p hummus the P hummus
you're going to see me cook it up a
little
bit and then we're going to run the P
hummus through here that is a really
really killer killer hummus I'm excited
about that one all right let's go look
at all all this food and it's sure
looking
good
I
lenos check it out cook
lentils cook lentils cook lentils lentil
hummus low fat no
fat okay all the beans are cooked I
didn't put them in raw look at this
lentil
hummus should I say it
again watch you
guys
okay we're running some Len little
hummus through
here look at that is that
incredible I'm going to run some spices
in here a little paprika knock a little
paprika down look boom I'm Gonna Knock
some garlic powder down you can do fresh
fresh garlic right in
here some cumin I'm Gonna Knock some
cumin down here in my lenal
hummus
boom Gonna Knock some mustard
seed mustard seed right there down into
my lentil
hummus Mustard
Seed yeah I'm gonna run some
doul
into my lentil hummus check that out
right there I got a nice little bowl of
moist
dolls Atlantic dolls what
else okay and I'm going to put lemon in
this
one all right let's
go okay let's get another lemon going
got to get the spin on it that's the key
right there oh lost that one went a
little too further F further up
front but you got to have the spin on it
it's not the first time aw didn't lose
something he threw up in the air which
juicer is that mm1 1500 link is in the
description link is in the profile
like
seriously get the lemon in
there total complete Nutritional Center
I call it the medicine maker you can run
all your fresh herbs through here make
your hummus make your guacamole I'm
going to make a roasted
toasted Walnut
butter you guys psyched for that Walnut
butter
boom I mean come on how cool is
that pop a little bit more parsley in
this one right
here let's get a little parsley in there
I got dols in here this is a lentil
hummus I got spices I'm going to pop a
little bit of salt right there okay some
more
lentils we're almost
done this one tastes so good
remember what you're not
seeing remember what you're not seeing
you're not seeing me pour olive oil in
here canola oil which when you buy
hummuses they're loaded with Canola
Olive
mix you're not seeing that there's no
natural flavors in here you guys natural
flavors that are in everything there's
no natural flavors in
here that's juicer is everything
Courtney ma says hey good to see
you I read your
comments All
right you know what I'm going to put
some sesame seeds in this one though
that I am going to
do now you can do the sesame seeds and
it doesn't burden down the liver because
think about you're only using this much
even if you used a lot of sesame seeds
it's not going to equate to even a
tablespoon of Sesame butter you can use
this whole Bowl you see this it's very
little this is a low low fat item here
my Omega mm 1500 is so easy to clean I
just read that on IG right
there I didn't let you down right it's
that good isn't it right okay so much
easier to clean than my last two juicers
yeah I stand behind this juicer for a
reason cuz it's that good saves people a
ton of money you can get it on sale
right now my sister my sister and I were
struggling on snack ideas for my mother
because her diabetics her diabetes state
is 70 she's 75 years old thank you for
your tips you're
welcome happy to help in any way
possible shape or
form all
right
that's it right
there so what you see right there
okay let's get a
spoon let's get a
spoon so you're seeing a lentil hummus
right
here and this one's moist too and creamy
I'm just letting you know you can always
add a little bit more lemon if you
really if you want it like watery like
some hummuses you open up at the store
they got natural flavor and citric acid
and all kinds of crazy stuff in there
there we go this is definitely an
incredible one right there there's
lentil hummus right in front of your
eyes the sesame seeds were
pulverized right in there let's take
this
out let's get one
more little Bowl
here take a look you guys
what I'm going to do is I'm going to put
some of this lentil hummus right in here
I'm dying to have this
one okay this back
here all right get
ready get
ready how many of you already have the
mm1 1500 and will be making these dips
that's the question I have look at this
radish right
here all right that's so
good that is so good what about a piece
of broccoli are you a fan of
broccoli can I get some up here on this
broccoli take a
look so good all right that's a l hummus
let's go we got stuff to make stuff to
[Music]
do get ready for
this we're going to mess it around
get ready for this I got the pan
on and we're going to talk about the
liver a little bit because we got more
things to
make all right cleaning up the board a
little bit too so just bear with
me there we
go no cleaning task or chore is beneath
the medical
medium I clean up every
day it's right all
right I got the pan on I'm going to make
the P hummus next so I'm going to do it
with the other machine
here and I am even going
to okay you
guys
so what's really cool
here is I
got the pan
on and I'm going to show you guys some
PE hummus in a second but we're going to
talk about the liver for a moment now if
you got just got on here just so you
know like what am I doing like what is
going on we're talking about easy
recipes on the liver we're talking about
stagnant sluggish liver how people walk
around with that they have a fatty liver
bioproduction is minimal and so many
people they can't break down their fats
their fats go
rancid food rots in their gut intestinal
track and ferments and feeds everything
in there that shouldn't be in there
pathogens bacteria viruses and so
forth and we're talking about how
there's so much sludge in people's
gallbladders that sits there because the
bile reserves are so low the bile can't
get to this the gallbladder it's not
astringent enough it gets into the
gallbladder but it's fill the sludge
it's weak weak it's not potent and then
all that junk builds up in your
gallbladder like I was talking about
earlier and then people's stomach glands
are weak they can't actually break down
their proteins properly their HCL is low
then all you got all this putrifying
protein with gut rot right we talked
about that I'm giving everybody a little
quick
rundown but even with all of that I'm
talking about how we can do things for
ourselves that are easy on the system I
just made some killer recipes
that are easier on the system than
anybody's like stuff that they're eating
these days with all the different fats
in there all the different combinations
people are eating way way too much fat
in their diet at this time of year they
mix fat and sugar together they get
insulin resistance their blood sugar is
totally out of whack right their livers
are burning down more than ever they
start gaining a little bit of weight I
made some incredible guacamole just like
that that quick we made hummuses we made
guacamole we're not even
done and we got some other stuff I got
this pan on so here's what I'm going to
do this next thing I'm
making you guys is a pea
hummus so let's go into that a little
bit I got some peas right
here think look frozen
peas pan getting hot yep it's getting
hot frozen peas are and then you put you
don't put water in your pan you don't
add water you just keep it just frozen
peas if you have fresh peas that's a
miracle if you actually have fresh peas
that's actually
incredible but I'm using frozen
peas get them right out of your freezer
dropping them right down in here just
like
this right in the pan can you see
that all
right okay now that pan is getting hot
so the goal is you make them
toasty you actually don't add water you
don't add oil so you don't want to add
any kind of oil to that pea hummus you
can add sesame seeds to your P hummus
later which we're going to do but you
don't have to add oil so this is so cool
so on the pan right
there they're going to get hot now I put
the I put the heat up high but you got
to watch them so once they start popping
they kind of like popcorn you need to
keep an eye on them you don't want to
burn your pan you don't want to burn
them or overcook them but you want to
get them toasty enough that's what makes
this hummus so incredible if you can't
do beans or lentils this is another
option how many people they just won't
do beans completely understand there's a
lot of people that don't do them not
judging you at all I think that's great
if you don't do them it's great for what
you're doing and then but the peun
hummus is that other option for so many
people that don't have hummus but one
and Colleen says I avoided peas for
years thinking they were carbs so they
were bad for me same with potatoes I'm
so thrilled to have them both back in my
life thank you for doing that for
yourself Colleen that is really special
and really
great all right let these babies cook up
a little bit let's get that Heat going
there I might even throw a lid on it for
a few minutes so let me find that lid
where are you what's going
on
aw's kitchen
[Music]
here we might have something down
here we got a
lid the chances of that so get that
cooking and we're going to talk about
the liver a little bit
more all
right and I'm going to make some Nut
Butter I'm going to show you some nut
butter butter that's what I'm going to
do let me do
that all right you guys take a look at
this for a second I want to show you
something I made
these I don't know is it months ago how
long was it you guys remember when I
made these take a
look
okay do you see any oil come
out you didn't see oil come out right
it's not pouring out this has been
sitting for quite a while I don't know
two three months maybe it's four months
now I mean don't quote me on the exact
time but it's been a while at least it
feels like a long time right take a look
this is what I'm talking about about
being easier on the liver do you guys
catch my drift right now it's another
one right there it's N A different kind
of nut butter one was hazelnut butter
the other one was
cashew okay now it's actually there's no
oil in
here right there's just pieces of nut
butter right
there okay about two months ago or so
Fabian spot on bro spot on two months
right so I just want to show you
guys okay now why do we even care about
these jars of nut butter that I made two
months ago why so I want to show you
[Music]
something show you something little
magic
[Music]
trick I got a popular Nut Butter
brand that just says it only has
nuts
take a
look did you see
that
okay that is not a
trick that is not a
prank you're looking at a of oil they
came off the top of that jar of nut
butter that is not a
hoax no it's not see
because most of all the nut Butters out
there oil is added and mixed into it it
reduces the cost to use cheaper bulk oil
even if it's the same oil as the peanut
meaning the same type right peanut then
peanut oil almond an almond oil Sesame
Sesame oil right but they add more a lot
of times it's not even the same oil but
they add more and then the oil comes
from a different part of the world it's
comes in bulk it arrives at the nut
putter companies and then they have all
that oil that's bulk and then they have
all the nuts and they do a mix they do a
mix there's a reason for
that and so I wanted to show you why is
it important because it's hard on the
liver so we're making recipes that are
easy on the
liver is what we're
doing so we're making a nut butter but
first of all I have peas cooking right
here I'm going to move this oil over
here for a little bit bring these over
here
too all right I just wanted to show you
that that's really important and that's
just one right here I mean I got a whole
bunch of jars in the back of different
brands that I purchased a couple of
months ago like two three months ago and
they sat and then they all have that
much oil at the
top but mine can sit and not have
that the ones that I'm talking about in
mine are made out of the mm 1500 so
we're going to do that all right these
are cooking going to make a p
humus here we go
so these are frozen
peas I'm getting them toasty I want to
show you guys take a
look what what would you want in your
pea hummus I'm going to put some
different spices in here some garlic
powder
right there we go let them cook let them
toast up and cook a little bit longer
going to put the lid on them for another
minute which is going to Fast Track it
okay
and I'm actually going to clean this
really quick so
quick what I'm doing is giving it just a
quick
rinse like this I don't know if you guys
can see me over there I know on IG you
guys probably can't see
me but I'm giving this quick rinse and a
quick
cleaning this just
great I'm just going to use it again
right here for the P
hummus all right here we
go check this out guys see the parts
coming back really quick I don't think
you've ever seen me do this
before
right I see him come back look at that
boom all
right cleaning the mm 1500 as we
speak is it been 2 minutes
already someone tell
me
okay has been 2 minutes
all right was that 2 minutes was that
three minutes was that a minute and a
half okay let's get the part back in
that let's get this piece back
in see you guys all
right
on sorry guys I'm multitasking again Big
Time bear with
me showing you how to clean the mm 1500
and I'm getting the pce ready for a p
humus you guys see this you see them
toasting up right here okay lost a
couple but that's okay all
right all right so that's in okay that's
in
right this little part right here going
to put right there like
that that's in
done give it a quick rinse that's
in
okay we're ready and our peas are just
about
ready here you guys popping and
crackling
here these were
frozen did I tell you these guys were
frozen there's a pee in the batch that's
got a little bit of a funny look to it
did you ever see that where you get one
out of the batch frozen
peas it's got a different look to
it all
right nice let me get a bowl let's make
this right
here think I'm going to go with a little
bit bigger of a bowl I want to make this
way I'm going to put some sesame seeds
in with this beus gives it unique
flavor maybe if you don't want that we
can do something
else all
right all right this is
done shut off the
burner
[Music]
okay guys be chicken with my head cut
off
man I'm like a chicken with my head cut
off I know you can't see
this you see what I'm
doing these peas are popping hot and
nice you guys see
this oh
yeah I'm like Dr nesbet with his head
cut
off we have a hot pan here
all
right let's
go fire this up mm
1500 $140
off stuff I get myself into I'm like
yeah I'll do like 10 recipes in just an
hour let me do
it I get myself involved with yeah
I'm G to put hot pepper in this
one you know I just always push the
limit is what I do someone else would do
like
what they would just do a live
that had like one recipe or
something I'm making P hummus I'm going
to drop in a hot
pepper these are
hot
okay you want lime or
lemon lemon that's what you
said
okay lemon is going in
here do you want spices little lemon
juice one through the other end is
really lazy right there all
right what else do you guys want herbs
in here
I'm going to put some oregano because
medicine fresh
oregano that's really incredible
medicine for sure let's get fresh
oregano in there do you want garlic
powder in here too because you're doing
a pea hummus little garlic
powder what about onion powder what
about cumin which I actually really love
inside of a pamus whoa that's going to
be incredible let get some more peas in
here here we go these These are hot they
just came off the
pan so good let's put a little pinch of
salt you don't have to put any in but I
got people coming
over it's the
holidays
all
right that's
right every one of those peas is going
in I don't
care I don't
care there you
go
okay all right so now I have a p humus
here here I got lemon in there I got hot
pepper in there I got a little bit of
salt you can garnish this any way you
want let's do something with it right
now let me
do something let me put some tomato
around it which actually would really be
good I would love that chop up a little
tomato right around it here if you guys
don't mind slice it up make it look good
too some tomato
pieces
there we
go little tomato fresh tomato garnish
right around the side here and I'm going
to put a little bit of onion on the side
too you guys don't mind I don't know
about
you nice little onion on the side too
look at
that okay love that couple of cherry
tomatoes over here
so what you have right here is a
beautiful pea hummus you saw me toast it
up they were just frozen peas ran it
through the machine it's got some hot
pepper spice it's got cumin in it it's
got um garlic in there it's got lemon
this is actually going to taste
incredible and I am going
to put it in
here nice I'll do that why not I'll put
the whole thing in there
yeah okay that's insane right there look
at
that what do you think got a radish try
this okay that's
insane that is so
good no
way
believe oh so good all right Walnut
butter let's do that that's actually
going to be a fun
one
okay that pan is still really
hot
okay watch
[Music]
this
okay hands
on get ready
walnuts going in the
pan got some Walnut butter coming
up while those are toasting
up I am going to straighten this out
really quick clean off the
board there you go
okay
guys so what I just did is I put walnuts
into the pan because I'm going to
lightly toast them I don't want to burn
them I don't want to toast them too
much you want to toast them lightly if
you're into toasted nut Butters if you
don't want roasted toasted nut Butters
then just do them raw do the walnuts
Raw
I'm a sucker for Walnut butter during
the holidays I'm going to be
honest there's nothing more tastier it
kills peanut
butter but that's just my
opinion that's just my opinion okay you
might like something better let me show
you something here this is a color green
for my garden right here this is what I
like to
do
now I'm over here at the buffet the aw
Buffet I got lentil
hummus well I got
guacamole whoa spicy herb
guacamole all right get me some spicy
herb guacamole put it right in that
collar green just like
that okay come
on put a little bit of onion in that
collar green look at this this is the
way I like to do it get ready
put a little Atlantic Coast
doul on that guacamole right there with
the onion you guys see coming together
now nice that's how I like to do it just
what you see right there okay and then I
roll that baby up and I make myself a
little guacamole B burrito with a leafy
green an amazing leafy green right there
with elevated biotics because this came
right out of the garden if you guys know
medical medium information you'll know
about elevated biotics that are
naturally on your produce that's growing
in the garden that elevated biotic
that's on there microorganisms that
people don't have their fingers on end
up in your Elum producing your own B12 I
talk about
that in the book it's in the medical
medium New Edition so I have this right
out of the garden which is
incredible okay these are starting to
get
hot let me move them around my walnuts
okay says my little guacamole
burrito I'm just going to tell you guys
all
right and I'm going to make you guys
Walnut butter you can do with almonds
you could put almonds on the pan you can
put almonds in the oven really quick on
a baking you know baking
sheet and you can toast them up you can
have them
raw if you want you can Sprout them to a
degree if you want sprouted um nut
Butters Sprout your almonds for a
day soak them Sprout
them
so
good all right you guys I don't want too
much heat
here
okay so I'm going to give I'm going to
actually change this nozzle
over now I'm using the I'm just not
taking the 1 minute or two minutes to
clean it you guys that's all so I got a
spare so I'm going to do the roasted um
Walnut
butter right from
here it's the same the same setup I had
over there but I just didn't want to
clean it
okay and I'm going to do the same with
the mango all right this is just about
ready we're
good this was on a really hot pan these
guys got toasty
up I don't like to burn them and I don't
want to actually overheat like really
overheat if you're going to roast like
when you buy a roasted Nut Butter they
were
overheated so then they go ran it
quicker okay so what I like to do is
just give them a light toasting and then
boom do it this
way all
right
great so let's go and do
this I'm going to take them right out of
the pan if you don't mind and I'm going
to use this bowl right
here all
right oh yeah you guys got
hot you guys got hot I
agree if you guys are getting kicked off
if you're if you're trying to get back
on and you hear that one second where I
go are you getting kicked and and I'm
gone are if I'm getting kicked off go to
medicalmedium.com watch me stream live
there go to rumble watch me stream live
there telegram so this is
Walnut
toasted Walnut butter you're witnessing
this right
now check this out you
guys remember you're not going to get
this all that rancid oil bulk oil they
mix in with the nut Butters most
companies mix in with the mut nut
Butters you see that that's not going to
be
there oh these are
warm so this is
Walnut
butter
handmade with a rolling
pin handmade with a rolling
pin
let's get some more in here
nice that is actually really
good over there tiny paw says I've
ruined two neutral
bullets while attempting to make my nut
Butters this machine is a beast oh yeah
you can't make if you if you do like
neutri bullet vitam mix whatever and you
try to make nut Butters
oh I've seen it destroy them I I I
personally have destroyed those
machines and that's why I actually um
started working with aega on this
machine
because you can't beat it I'm sorry but
you can't beat
it it's not possible out there I know
they try but they just don't and they
can't really good all
right I could put more in there I can
make a higher
pile Oh still
good all
right let's jar
it you guys I mean is this
incredible here are all my spoons here
you
are so I'm putting
freshh Walnut butter see where's all the
oil it's you mean you have your natural
amount in here but there's no add it
see you're not killing your liver you're
not burning it down you're not
everything I talked about at the
beginning of this show about your liver
all that information I dropped on you
really quickly all that information I
dropped on you really quickly yeah about
your liver and overburdening it this is
nut butter without doing that these
these
facts and
details and incredible pieces of
legendary
information can change
lives simple as this it's like you get
chipped away Death By A Thousand Cuts oh
I'm GNA have some healthy nut butter o
boom Oh you know and it's filled with
oil oh I'm going to go and do this boom
didn't know it's like death by a
Thousand Cuts there goes a incredible
Walnut butter hand freshly made I did it
with a rolling pin in front of you I was
like you guys are making it by no I did
it with the machine a medicine machine
there you go that's what I'm talking
about right
there okay Barbara says Barbara cabone
says the machine is so quiet
quiet it is really quiet there it is
take a look you
guys and there's no oil dripping out of
these but guess what was dripping out of
that other one and anyone if you let it
sit even for a little while all that oil
gets in there it's crazy all right I'm
not done I got to make some ice
cream all this fun food for the holidays
and now I need my ice cream
let's go okay because I don't want to
spend a minute cleaning that out I'm
just putting the uh attachment right
there let's get the nut butter out of
the
way oh feels nice and warm it's just
warm and fresh fresh Walnut butter so
good and I didn't even put salt in there
you can put salt in there if you wanted
to but it didn't
even but I'm not okay
all right I'm going to make some mango
sorbet really
[Music]
quick oh still
frozen okay let's go it's been out here
for a while all right I need a bowl for
that got a nice Bowl right
there
okay
roll
try to get another
[Music]
goal
please all
right
yep still nice and
[Music]
Frozen now you can put it
in more icy frozen this one's defrost it
a
little but not a
lot making mango sorbet right out of
here I mean seriously guys
let's keep this going why am I
quiet this one is a little bit more
defrosted but it's still incredible I'm
going to have a good time having some
here
think I'm out of it's out of control
man it's freaking out of
control this machine is running away
from
me little bit
more nope all right I am made a freaking
mess because it wasn't Frozen
enough the rbet wasn't Frozen
enough come on Salvage it
fast here we
go Salvage
it note to self do not let the Frozen
mango sit out on the counter for the
last 4 hours really bad idea note to
self your Frozen mango ice cream is
going to be still kind of icy and still
kind of
good that's your Frozen mango ice cream
right there
okay um note to
self it's really good
though oh yeah I got some bar righta
well it's
cold so
cold
what about one of
these
okay oh brain freeze crap I hate when
the brain freeze comes don't you guys
hate
that I don't like when the brain freeze
comes oh so
good too
good all
right
guys cleaning up the board really
quick I find that when I clean the
kitchen I go into a meditative
State here you
go see you
guys don't miss out if you've been
waiting for this
machine do not miss out and I'll tell
you why
it's $140 off don't miss out I mean come
on for the
holidays I don't know what I want to eat
next I really don't know is it
guacamole is
it P
hummus
yeah
hello somebody
here
yeah what's going
on is somebody at the
door
okay hold on hold
on
yep I'm not decent so hang on there I'm
not decent I can't open the door yet
yeah
yep yeah well I'm not decent so just
just hang in there all right all right
I'm in the
door hey what's
up man what do you got going
on what are you doing
man I was um just kind of on a binge
lately you know and I just
thought but maybe I can get some like
real food or something you
know so I wasn't sure what you had going
on
so hey man are you doing this
again what's
here what is this
oo
oo this looks really
good that aw hey can I have some of this
man I got the
munchies m
it's so good I think I ate one I just I
think I had some of my hair in here are
you okay with that
man this is not
bad so I was on a three-day
binge mhm binging for three days man I
was so
so gone I don't even know my name
Bryce my name Bryce I remember but I
couldn't remember my name for three
straight days man three straight days
man this
girl this girl was hanging out with me
man and she said that my name was
rice after 3 days I called myself rice
instead of
rice this chick
and we were at Burning
Man I think I'm still at Burning Man is
it still going on because I I I never
left and this chick named me rice and I
actually thought my name was
rice I think her name was summer man
summer yeah I thought she was the
coolest and then some other dude that
was with her called me pork fried
rice and then it became my
nickname and we were on all these
Edibles um okay I think I'm going to go
I just want to fuel up on some good
stuff it's really
good I can't see my hair is in the
way look so good
okay I got to
go where are
you R
Ry the door's that way
I don't know about Bryce I don't know
about you
guys but I think I'm going to have some
more guacamole in a Mustard
Leaf this is a mustard green right out
of the garden and I'm going to have just
a little bit of guacamole on that and
then I think I'm going to do a regular
guacamole I'm going to show you right
here so I'm going to do this one right
here okay so I'm going to put my like
burrito my mustard Green Burrito right
there so I'm going to put this guacamole
right in it just like
that I'm also going to pop some onion in
here too take a look just like that too
okay I think I'm going to put a couple
of
radishes couple of radishes that's a lot
of guacamole for each one of these
rollups you can put less it's just it
gets real heavy fast you could put more
I'm happy if you put
more okay and I'm going to pop some
tomato right on top of here as
well okay and I'm going to pop some dots
back on here too did I show you the dots
earlier okay and I think that is going
to be my mustard
green
my mustard Green Burrito right there
mustard Green's at the Garden and then I
got everything else packed in here with
the
guacamole I'm going to take a bite bite
into this one
but that's a lot to send down really
fast like I was before
so I mean come
on I mean come on right
seaweed
hero I haven't seen your comment in a
while on YouTube where did it go where's
all your lyrics man I read them all the
time so
good have a little bit more you guys
okay where's my manners where are my
manners you guys 14 $ off check this
out these lives help us so much thank
you
aw I try my best all right
guys I will see you next time watch this
from the beginning get that liver
information down become a liver
expert make sure you get that liver info
down become a liver expert
okay if you can
come a liver
expert all right you guys let's see you
later see you till next time God bless
you um I don't know if I'm hey make sure
you uh subscribe to my
telegram if you like this video thumbs
up you don't like it middle
finger but still
subscribe okay and and what else I don't
know my telegram medical medium
newsletter medical medium bulletin
because you want the medical medium
bulletin each week of what you missed
you can catch it in the newsletter so
sign up to my newsletter go to Medical
medium.com link is in the description
and bio to and know that I love you guys
I know you guys are working really hard
on your healing and health and I'll see
you next time