pour a little tea here
today is day five
if you could believe it
day five that's a little nettle tea
day five of the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
I'm making gluten-free
breakfast cookies
gluten-free oatmeal breakfast cookies
with bananas I'm excited so that's what
I have in front of me right here you
know what I wanted tonight I wanted
something like this this is what I felt
like eating for dinner tonight okay
hopefully that doesn't offend anybody
hopefully that doesn't get anybody upset
like why is he eating oatmeal cookies
tonight for his dinner
is that bad what's the medical medium
eating what's he doing
maybe he's not doing good he's eating
this this is great though I got some
raisins right here I'll show you guys
some oatmeal
I'm gonna move this out of the way if
you guys are okay with that I'm gonna
let this steep a little bit
some nice tea with honey in it okay and
I have the gluten-free banana oat
breakfast cookies right here
there we go it's right out of cleanse
the heel that's what I'm doing how is it
going with your Stones The Journey
today did you walk with your Stones
walking meditation with your Stones
where are my Stones right here took a
walk today with my stones
right are you putting them on the
windowsill are you letting your Stones
get some light on them through the
window are you looking through the
window while you have your Stones when
we look through the window
regardless of what scenery is on the
outside of that window if we look
through the window
something happens here with our neurons
something happens with the emotional
centers of our brain
all kinds of Memories We don't even pick
up on that are circulating through old
memories that are in there that we're
not grabbing onto
all kinds of connections occur there's
something when
a human being looks through a window
something happens
something we can't measure something
people cannot understand out there
science doesn't understand and when we
look through a window and we see things
we see birds we see trees we see grass
we see buildings we see sidewalks
whatever it is we see cars when we look
through a window something happens a
connection is made and then the
emotional centers of the brain
starts to tick and starts to tick and
information starts to pour out of your
being and into the stones if it
shouldn't be there
a lot of people have experiences where
they look out windows because they were
depressed they had something happen in
their life maybe they had some kind of
disturbance maybe they had some kind of
abuse maybe they went through a hard
time maybe they had losses and it takes
us to the window and we look out the
window it takes us to the window in our
life how many times have we looked out
the window when the relationship breaks
at breakups with all kinds of
confrontations in life being bullied
whatever it is that's happened in our
life
we get kind of taken to the window
and we look out
and there's a reason for this lots of
reasons for that so the emotional
centers of the brain has all this
information
regarding when we actually look out
windows
it's important is important to know so
when you put the stones there by the
windowsill and you look out the window
the emotion centers of the brain are
connecting to our soul and so forth and
all that I'll talk about that more and
other things I'm making these banana oat
breakfast cookies as I showed you before
I got my raisins I got everything right
here two bananas first that's what we're
gonna do two bananas first
so
here we are let's get my little Mixing
Bowl here
this is what I felt like eating for
dinner tonight it was these have you
ever tried these have you ever made
these these that are out of cleanse to
heal
they're so good it's insane
Alfreda says we love this recipe so easy
do we ever I'm gonna Mash these bananas
Mash mash I'm gonna mash them
so what I'm gonna do
I put two it's two two medium bananas
just putting a little extra piece right
there
Uma says I think my favorite thing is to
read with my Stones I love to read with
my Stones too you guys don't mind I'm
just gonna give these a little bit of a
mash
I like this recipe because it's really
easy it tastes really good Gail Stewart
not says it looks like breakfast cookies
I've made them indeed it's breast
breakfast cookies and indeed and here's
the funny thing
the funny thing about this right
is it's breakfast but it's not breakfast
here
it's not break fast here
no it is not
it's dinner time
but it's it's perfect though feels good
right now processing a lot of emotions a
lot of emotions leaving the body
lots of Old Wounds
leaving the body leaving the soul
leaving
are being lots of wounds
felt like making a breakfast
you know what I like about this
breakfast it's a baked good we're baking
the funny thing about medical medium
information there's more baked goods and
medical medium information
it's insane it's like a whole website
you filled with them
crazy how much
anyway okay
all right
we're making these cookies really
excited about this
what I like about these cookies can I
just add this I know what's at the end
of the day it's evening for many of us
so it's a different kind of vibe a more
relaxed it's not that afternoon Vibe
right
so let me get two cups
of
some gluten-free oats let's get two cups
rolled oats
instant oats whatever you want to do
it's one cup let me get another cup what
I like about this there's no lard in
here
isn't that nice no lard
there's no pork fat
there's no bad oil in here there's no
corn oil there's no bad vegetable oil in
here either
all right
let's get some cinnamon in here
looking for my cinnamon hold on
we're live
we're actually live let's go with two
teaspoons
two teaspoons
boom right there
half cup of raisins skip that in there
let's get these baking
and then we can talk
how are my Stones doing are you guys
eating with your Stones I'm doing all my
meals with the stones I'm eating with my
stones
we got the cinnamon in here let's mix
that up
[Music]
we need a half cup of raisins
I'm gonna throw these in here just like
this
so there's no
there's no uh
swine in here
there's no pig fat in here
friend of mine makes
some baked goods and
puts anything in there
imagine he's still a friend of mine
I think the medical medium would say
you're not a friend of mine anymore
because of what you eat
but that's not how it rolls
that doesn't depict
if you're
a good Soul or not
so I'm just mixing this up we're pretty
much almost there I'm gonna make these
cookies
there we go
let's make sure these are moist enough
and I think it's the recipe was just
perfect right there
sometimes your bananas they might not be
as soft
or as ripe
these happen to be that perfect ripeness
when you're doing some baking
I just want to make sure these oats get
the attention they deserve
you guys how are you holding up how are
you doing through this transformation
day five of the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
there we go
I'm gonna make some cookies
I think so
you don't have to make them too big you
don't have to make them too small
you can make them any way you want
how about that
there isn't any big rules here
whatever feels good on this you can make
one I don't know I wouldn't do I
probably wouldn't make one big massive
cookie there we go just want to shake
the cookie up a little bit get another
pan here
there we go
nice
small cookies are fun
I like them a little bigger
here we go
whoa Tara says over there on YouTube I
feel better since I started this
meditation
this is like a meditation all on its own
right here just making these feels
really good
feels really nice
had a good day today
it's like you know what I'm gonna
bake some cookies tonight I mean I
actually do
like sometimes something just like this
at night
for dinner what about you guys
you know what I like about these cookies
here
I didn't have to put any eggs in here
because you know medical medium
information is the first that ever put
out that eggs feed pathogens
it was not known in the Health world or
medical world the pathogens ate anything
at all
but then you see people now saying it
even though science hasn't even proved
it yet or anything but you see people
saying it
where they get that info from oh
medical medium information
all right you guys we're day five
anyway I like doing baked goods without
eggs in them I'm not saying look I'm not
saying if you like eggs and that's what
you do it's fine but if you got chronic
illness if you're struggling in with
anything if you're dealing with anything
health-wise it's good to keep them out
and this is a great recipe
a great recipe
indeed indeed
all right so
I'm making these the size that I want
to make it smaller to make them bigger
there we go
so good so good with raisins
any of you guys raising fans
now day five
we have day six and we have day seven
I hear some of you guys don't want to
let your Stones go
already
or you're worried about letting them go
it's part of the process it's part of
the healing process it's part of the
exercise
letting them go
sending them back into nature
so nature can diffuse
the bomb
yeah
of emotions
of hurt of Old Wounds store deep inside
so nature can diffuse
IG
roanzin says Anthony I'm finally healed
from eczema and acne
that's what it's all about
that's why we do this
Deb says took my stones on my girl's
weekend
fantastic
the best news I ever heard as well
because you don't want to leave your
Stones behind you want to take them with
you you don't want to leave them behind
where they're just
all Left Behind
you're gonna be on your trip and you're
gonna be like well my stones are back
there
at
my house or back there at my apartment
back there at home
all right
I think this is really really worked out
we got a kind of a little bit of a
bigger cookie in the end I can go with
two smaller cookies I can go with a
little bit of a bigger cookie right here
we go
maybe it's the same size
are you guys singing to your Stones
that's what I wanted to ask
I got a few leftover raisins do you guys
mind if I place some of these raisins
on top of here I don't want to lose
these
there we go
boom
nice
you guys I'm gonna pop this in the oven
are you okay with that if I leave you
for a second my oven's over here can I
give you a little bit of a view over
there
so that's them
incredible if you guys just got here
gluten-free banana oat breakfast cookies
you can add dried wild blueberries or
chopped dates or cranberries those are
options cranberries make sure though the
cranberries have no added oils because
it might not be a good oil at all and
you don't need to have that
might be a canola oil or something which
we don't want to use so these are going
in the oven
for 350.
let's see what we can do
oven set for three
50.
nice
[Music]
let's do a little cleaning for a second
and then we're going to do a little
reading good to see you guys
can IG
sunlit says just put mine on the
windowsill it's Sunset perfect time to
do so
putting your stones on the windowsill
great time
people looked out the window and they
were at work
maybe at an office or some workplace
and they just stared out the window
you guys we are currently on day five of
the collecting Stones meditation Journey
you can sign up at Link at the link
right there in the profile and Link in
the bio Link in the description you can
sign up for all those in those
how many times have we looked out the
window
when we were just contemplating think
about that right there just
contemplating
have you ever looked out the window and
you're just contemplating
and you're looking out the window
how many times have you looked out the
window because you're having a bad day
you were having you were having a
stressful moment in your life a
stressful day
and something just took you over to the
window to look out the window how many
of you had that where you're looking out
the window because you're having a hard
day
how many people look out the window
because they want to see what's going on
outside no matter what and it's a part
of their routine so it's part of their
routine to look out the window look at
hummingbirds look at birds look at just
anything going on out there
look at the trees
how many people look out the window when
it rains you have a rainy day and
something kind of comes over you and you
feel
a little sad you just
you want to go to the window
Courtney says I feel trapped inside of
work
since he's just looking out
Tristan Marie says it's my daily routine
what happens when
pathways are accessed
that we don't normally have access to
so
basically a channel opens up
automatically emotional centers of the
brain connect to other areas of the
brain meaning the non-emotional areas
information is trans transferred
sometimes we get Nostalgia when we're
looking out windows sometimes we get big
ideas
great ideas sometimes we get
memories
but either way Windows play a big part
that's part of the whole windowsill
stones on the windowsill with you while
you're looking out the window
on day five
Boston says where can I find this P
would love to tell you it's cleansed to
heal if you don't have this book you're
missing out
by far one of the greatest medical
textbook out there for people to get
their lives back this book this book
I will commend this book
this book has healed so many people
around the world and saved so many lives
and very proud of this book soc's
information
going to page 450 I want to read just a
little bit just for fun
anywhere you open up the medical medium
books it's just people own away when
have you opened them up in a while have
you read
it's like you've never read it before
that's what's interesting too cookies
are baking
I feel like some big baking tonight
Jim says hi aw thanks for all you do for
us could you explain why I'm sensitive
to a heated oven I really miss baking
um beer on detective first of all are
you sensitive to Pete in general are you
sensitive to a really hot day because I
know some people they can't handle a 90
degree day they can't handle 85 degree
and humid they can't handle 78 degrees
anything above 75 degrees
oven heat is dry dry heat sensitive
nervous systems don't like super dry
heat
so sensitive nervous systems do not like
super dry heat sensitive sinus cavities
do not like super dry heat of course
real humid humid heat is a whole nother
you know
irritation for a lot of people on its
own but I'm talking about dry heat
coming out of the oven
when people are struggling they're
overheated internally overheated too
they might have a struggling stagnant
sluggish liver
and then info
now taken for granted around the world
about stagnant and sluggish livers about
why
if I don't mention that people be like
oh he must have got it from this person
he was got it from that person he must
have got it from this person no
originated from the medical me books
okay I want to read a little if you guys
are open to it
Charlotte career says I've been dealing
with awful heat sensitivity but it's
slowly getting better with mm info and
the reason why people have awful heat
sensitivity for the most part not
everybody most people have heat
sensitivity because of a sensitive
central nervous system sensitive central
nervous system and sensitive cranial
nerves that's a big one right there
sensitive cranial nerves
big one right there all the cranial
nerves
when people have those sensitive cranial
nerves what happens is insensitive vagus
nerve
sensitive vagus nerves the cranial
nerves
people have issues with that then they
get heat sensitive they're sensitive to
the heat outside they're sensitive to a
lot of sun sensitive to heat sensitive
to ovens they're sensitive to stoves
they're just sensitive to a lot of heat
that's a noise
Compton says where can I get the
information about the stone so what you
want to do is sign up to the collecting
Stones meditation Journey link is in
profile link is in description you can
get the original information which is
really important in medical medium
right here the meditation is in this
book if you don't have this book
that is also a bummer this book has
saved lives all around the world
countless lives
be kind to yourself tear Appleman says
heat sensitivity has been a huge
struggle for me finally been making
progress healing the symptom with
medical medium info
that is so amazing and it's been a hot
summer
Gail says I love listening to your audio
chapter
one from the revised book made me cry
share it with friends thank you for
sharing with Friends
bless you
[Music]
Sharon K over there on YouTube says my
stone found me it came out of nowhere
very interesting
profound actually
found
what experience that is
the idea of cutting out foods from your
diet even for the short space of a mini
cleanse just say
can be loaded
for women especially
societal messaging has attached shame to
food choices for far too long
I've always said that I'm not the food
police
medical meme information was the first
to bring back fruit
into the world of Health as we speak
even though there's still a battle
trying to stop fruit from being in any
of the health genres
fruit fear was the big one
so I spent 30 years trying to break
fruit fear because fruit was not allowed
in anybody's diet
that had anything to do with natural
health on any level
and he kind of cleanses any kind of
Natural Health
in any way fruit was not allowed and no
disrespect to all
frames of
of the health world everything from
naturopaths to acupuncturists and so far
so so forth like acupuncturist said
fruit gave you dampness you you're not
allowed to have it it can't have raw
fruit like everybody had their thing
naturopath said too much sugar feeds you
know Candida
see
to Sweet Jane over there
um I don't mess with any sugar except
wild blueberries
fruit today is all GMO despite being
organic too much sugar well fruit isn't
GMO
today I mean but but I'm glad you're
doing the wild blueberries and no
disrespect thank you for actually that
comment because that comment's very
interesting
so
if you're getting like the Honeycrisp
apple per se that's not GMO
if you're getting some pairs
some Bartlett pears that's not GMO so
bananas are grafted to start with the
corn that's not GM not corn corn
this whole thing the banana trees right
the corns
that's not GMO
so it's important to know
but but but but
in Hawaii
I would never eat a papaya there I mean
of course you can eat a papaya there
chances are they're GMO
or serious GMO contamination
because Hawaii is GMO capital
literally GMO Capital it's where they
grow all the medical corn
is a beautiful place
but
beauty also
another flip side of that there's some
hidden dark secrets
and so Hawaii
is literally the GMO
Ground Zero
including every Island
okay
but it's still a beautiful place let's
go a little bit here
so the idea of cutting out foods for
your diet even for the short space of a
mini cleanse is fully loaded a loaded
topic for women especially societal
messaging has attached shame to food
choices for far too long
I've always said that I'm not the food
police
and that will always be true
remember this when you see a medical
medium recommendation to limit or
temporarily cut out a certain food
that is never attached to judgment on
any level so there's no judgment
that's why I have friends
that just eat what they want
I did not defriend them
I did not say you are not my friend I am
the medical medium
and how dare you be a friend of mine if
you're eating an egg how dare you be a
friend of mine if you're eating whatever
far from the food police
so much so far from the food police
far
it's unbelievable talk about that
another time
Lilly says in IG my daughter back in
2015 was listening to you and you healed
and cleared out her skin explanation
points thank you so much aw you're
welcome
that's your service
I never judge anybody for what they're
eating
never will never have
I'll never judge them if they're eating
something in a store that was in a
package some kind of crazy cupcake with
some kind of like weird hard white icing
strip down the center of it I never
judge them if they're eating some kind
of crazy fudge cookie in a package
I never judge them if they're making
some pancakes and they throw all kinds
of crap in there and they got bacon on
the side or anything else like that I
never forever JoJo you know and that's
the thing and it's so important to know
because what happens is that
it wouldn't be
Fair
to anyone
it just wouldn't
it wouldn't it's a hard World we're
raised on certain foods a lot of us
don't know we don't have the education
and when we do it's still hard
Trisha Marie says my conventional doctor
had me afraid to drink juice or fruit
smoothies it was disappointing hearing
that he thought it was bad for the liver
medical medium information
was about breaking the fruit fear
putting the wild blueberries out there
the messaging the information being a
messenger about the power of the wild
blueberries it was about getting fruit
back into the diet done right
so people can heal it's not about being
fruitarian that's not it at all mm info
isn't about fruit only and only fruit
and nothing but fruit a mistake I've
seen out there where people talk about
quite the contrary
and then info brought in the leafy
greens not just the fruit people did not
eat real leafy greens nor did they treat
herbs like leafy greens
and medical medium
me
never ever shame someone for eating meat
quite the contrary I always said you can
heal while eating meat if you want to be
a meat eater
and you can still heal if you
want to learn the tools and the
information
the mm info shows you how to do it while
eating meat and you can still heal the
mm info shows you how to do it if you're
plant-based and never shamed anybody for
being plant-based ever
will never did
nor anybody who was a pescetarian or
anybody that was a vegetarian or anybody
who did anything
because it's not about that
a medical medium cleanse is never about
virtuousness virtuousness
versus shame it's about healings it's
never about being so virtuous
right
it's about healing
and from a medical perspective
shame is not healing
shame releases a harsh adrenaline blend
that's corrosive and abrasive to our
neurons our nervous system and can
weaken our immune system that's what
that adrenaline from shame is that's why
we're doing the collective Stones
meditation too some of our stones are
named shame I've noticed that people
name their Stone shame it's incredible
because what happens is all that stored
up the wounds and the soul and
everything based around shame starts to
funnel out into that stone and that
Stone's mineral composition is taking it
in and absorbing it it's eating up that
shame
Baghdad says as a nurse I remember the
first time reading your first book years
ago and going quote Oh my God this makes
so much sense so much more sense than
what I have been taught
over there on IG
my mm healing lifestyle and IG says my
Mom's doctor told her to have
half a banana only for breakfast
I'm Doctor
I'm not just so and so
I think the phone just I thought I heard
the phone ringing
I thought I heard the phone ring
if you set out with the very best
intentions
intentions for your health and then have
a terrible stressful day where
appointment after a appointment ends up
on your calendar and you get over hungry
and reach for a food that's outside the
cleanse because it's sitting right there
in the break room does that mean that
you should feel guilty
hi I'm Dr food shame
I got the food shame as I recommended
only eat a little tiny piece of banana
for breakfast
I only recommend
huh I'm not the food please
no no
why you hear that in social media about
the medical medium he's so bad he's
restricting everybody but I won't let my
patients have more than a little piece
of banana
for breakfast yes Dr food shavier a
nurse nurse did you just put off the
line
yes is this and no more than a little
piece of banana
that's all
Dr Fine many of the high protein gurus
can't even eat a banana without their
sugar spiking to 200 to 300 they created
their own insulin resistance
they did
correct
okay okay okay
wait wait
I'm gonna check my cookies
I have an oven mitt here
fantastic I'm just making sure they're
brown they got that nice toasty look
coming together nice
they need a couple more minutes
it's good it's good a couple more
minutes
I'm gonna keep this up
you guys are we having fun
is I'm having a blast
I'm trying not to crack myself up though
Chris Angela says just the laugh I
needed while on a break at work
whatever food choice you make at
whatever time it's not bad or shameful
it's only that a choice you made and the
next time you can make another choice
because food choices outside the
guidelines of any cleanse
does it mean you're a bad person doing
the best you can
when you eat a food that you know
doesn't take you closer to feeling
relief from your symptoms
self-punishment shouldn't come into the
picture we should not self-punish
ourselves we shouldn't
we shouldn't self-punish ourselves
it shouldn't come into the picture
should not
rather than enter that headspace try to
remind yourself gently that physically
the best choice you can make is to be
kind to yourself being kind to yourself
really important
healing
is not an easy process
we have to be good to ourselves while
while we're healing while we're going
through the process
while blueberry dreams on IG says yet I
healed my brain lesion using medical
medium info incredible
incredible
AKA Amy Kelly on IG celery juice
literally is still saving me thank you
mm credible info in all the books
I drink celery juice every day
I try to drink it every day
once in a blue moon I'll miss it or I
don't drink it in the morning I drink it
at the end of the day it just happens it
happens I'm not gonna punish myself I'm
not not gonna flog myself
I'm not gonna like
not gonna take a whip and or a strap and
whap my back
I'm not gonna do it
I'm not
be kind to yourself what does that
kindness look like it would seem like
the ultimate triumph over food shame
would be to eat anything you want at any
time I wish that were true
you can do that it's certainly an option
if your resource is allowed that will
take you down a route where you end up
sicker though
just a reality
self-compassion looks more like a pause
whenever you get the impulse to reach
for a food that isn't part of a cleanse
or part of what you're doing your
routine to heal
so I'm going to check those cookies one
more time
are we really talking about cookies
don't worry I'm still here
these cookies are just about done just
need a couple more minutes they're
looking really good
I can't wait to eat one of those cookies
I'm hungry hungry Linda Thomas says I'm
not a fan of bananas but I certainly
would make these cookies with banana and
enjoy them indeed
I am very excited about these cookies I
must say
Cellini says can we have the recipe for
the cookies please hey W yes you can
they're in cleanse to heal
the recipe is oats and banana
raisins they are on the medical medium
website for free go to medicalmedium.com
you don't have to go through a paywall
to look at all the recipes that are for
free
you do not have to do that there's no
subscription fees there and everything's
free we're in the middle of a seven day
incredible healing Journey for free
right now
don't be a hero can I read this for a
couple seconds
couple of minutes
rewatch this live once it's posted for
the recipe because that showed the
recipe already
another way to show compassion for
yourself is to think ahead taking into
account the fundamental truth that you
get to have an appetite
hunger is a sign of life
I love when Tick Tock shuts down my life
and kicks me off
you have nothing to prove by going all
morning without breakfast or skipping
lunch now here's something interesting
and something important to know right
mm info isn't about
intermittent fasting and not eating
anything all day long
until the very end of the night
it's not about that
that's the way you kill your adrenals
you destroy your adrenals
mm info the cleanses any or
the information in here is adrenal
protective it's all about protecting the
adrenals so these cleanses and these
books are Geared for protecting The
Originals you'll see misinformation out
there and you'll see somebody say oh
wait it's too tough on adrenals what are
you talking about it's actually for your
adrenals it's to protect them because
adrenals are destroyed with all these
other different diets and different
things and belief systems out there they
just get annihilated with so many people
they do good for a little while and then
boom they're hurting bad later they
don't know why
all it does is set you up to run on
adrenaline and get tired irritable
I'm gonna get these cookies out
take a look
I like my cookies with a little bit of
crispiness to it
I don't like them chewy and soft I like
them a little bit crisp crispy a little
brown
what happens is a lot of people don't
realize it but they run on adrenaline
and get tired and irritable and they get
over hungry and then they do
grab things they probably wouldn't have
grabbed because they starved themselves
the whole day
tree spennett says I'm in day three of
369 wish me luck haha amazing
so happy to hear that
healing with Holly 144 hunger is a sign
of life
quote
I think about this mm quote so often
it's so comforting
whenever you can plan ahead prep your
snacks and meals ahead of time on days
you'll be away from home or when you
know you'll get too busy to stop and
spend time in the kitchen midday think
about ordering cases of produce if you
need to so you have it like a you know a
backlog of it it's that it's it's what
you need
to have enough ingredients on hand
another thing too is a lot of people
don't have the ingredients they don't
have bananas on hand
they didn't grab a few extra bunches
they don't have potatoes on hand they
didn't grab an extra bag a five pound
bag of potatoes so they really don't
have much in stock
and they're grabbing little pieces here
and there and then end up going and
ordering something or they end up going
out and getting food out and in that
food out it's like
the fake olive oil mixed with canola oil
and all the MSG and in the food out and
everything even foods that are in like
seemingly healthy restaurants really
healthy restaurants loaded with MSG the
soy sauces that are all hidden in there
everything just lots of MSG
cookie time
put my Stones right here
yeah
boom
can I actually show you guys
there's a raisin that's running around I
saw a raisin running around
just that was crazy watch this video
afterwards find out how that reason was
cruising like that
all right
okay let me get these on a plate
but I'm gonna let them cool a little bit
did you ever burn your tongue because
you don't want to wait
this is a very hot cookie right here
right out of the oven
but I know I'm gonna burn my tongue or
burn my mouth
Gotta Wait I gotta have patience gotta
have some patience
boots McGee over there on YouTube
definitely as long as I'm eating every
90 minutes I make way better decisions
you also protect your adrenals
but since the light blasts I no longer
beat myself up when it isn't feasible
do not beat yourself up
and I'm so glad you don't anymore
mystere said pretty cookies over there
on YouTube
so we're talking about all kinds of
stuff I just want to give you guys a
reminder we are day five with collecting
Stones medication journey and it's a
profound Journey now
kind of downplay in it
I'm downplaying it because I'm getting a
little emotional about
day seven when we have to let our Stones
go
it's unbelievable what's happening it's
a phenomenon or or a hundred thousand
people doing this collecting Stones
meditation Journey with us all together
there are a hundred thousand people
doing this collecting Stones meditation
Journey as of right now
a hundred thousand people
so keep that in mind this is like a
collective this is a Powerhouse of
healing happening for all of us people
are feeling so comfortable with their
Stones they're able to talk to them and
not feel judged
that is incredible and mind-blowing and
very healing they don't feel like
they're being judged when they're
talking to their stones
they don't feel that way at all
there's Martinez says over there on
YouTube the light blast was my first one
I'm so grateful we had the opportunity
to do it it helped me I'm planning on
another one I don't know when but it's
going to be it's gonna be this year and
it's going to be sometime soon
I think that I'm trying to keep it kind
of low-key
but I'm beaming absolutely beaming
because I know the kind of healing
that's taking place
in every individual
and I'm
it's it's
extremely exciting
but I kind of got a little nervousness
right because the nervousness is
involved with I know
the time has to come to release and let
the stones go
I know it's coming soon
that's gonna be hard to let go of my
Stones I've actually really have grown
close to my Stones my stones have been
absorbing so much
of the things that have been inside me
that that I've experienced
being an underdog being um being bullied
my whole life all of it for hearing a
voice being taken advantage of being
taken taken for granted
people poaching all my info not citing
me
not having any respect for the fact that
there's so much contributed
from me in spirit to the health movement
in these last 35 years and how it would
not be like it is today
it would be literally a Barren desert
and all of that I can live with
but it's nice to get some of
this hurt that's been in there and get
that out into the stones and more than
35 years of the work I've done
to get information out there
healing From the Inside Out says hubby
and I have had these awful tense
conversations about a certain subject
day three we've literally broke into
Common Ground whoa it was no longer
emotional the Stones played a huge part
in that thank you
stones
we're kind of creating that channel
creating
that frequency
pulling in some of that old pain and
sorrow
kind of clearing the room all of it
that's what they can do
my cookies are cooling down
so is this pan
hands cooling down too
playing around
I don't know if you guys can see but I'm
playing around a little bit
hmm
a raisin
too good
here's my cookies
which one
you guys okay with it about this are you
ready I'm gonna take a break
take a break
am I alive
did we shut it all down
are we alive
we're not live anymore right okay
hmm
we're not live anymore
shoot with my mouth open and everything
oh my God we're live still
oh crap how embarrassing
Stacy Parker said which book did that
recipe come from
here
Amanda says an ID the stones help me
speak truth to my husband
when I couldn't connect
to it before astounding it's profound
I promise you this
satisfaction guaranteed
Something's Gonna Change
throughout this process of collecting
Stone's meditation Journey something is
going to change and I promise you this
it's gonna be life-altering
life-changing and I promise you this
when we toss those stones back in you're
never going to forget this meditation it
will never just be something that's in
the back your mind like I did that one
day
it's gonna be like
whoa
let's show you a quickly I brought
this is my dinner tonight
can I show you guys how's that on IG
over there on YouTube
these cookies are insane can I show you
the back of the cookie
dang my cookies are in the same
[Music]
do you ever meet anybody and they use
their fork and they point it at you
when they do this
they do this
breeding and they're so excited and it
tastes so good and they're just pointing
the pork and you're like
so good
that's how good this is you guys
Kelly Brook says what happens to the
stones and us when we release them
are you okay if I dip
[Music]
are you okay if I dip my delicious
cookie
into my Natalie tea with honey
freaking insane
I almost swore
Susan says YouTube hid this for me no
I'm censored on YouTube this way don't
we let a few people see
and then censored on YouTube for three
and a half years
I've been censored on Twitter
they only let a couple of people see
been sent her on Twitter
for seven years
Instagram and Facebook now is really bad
and Facebook centered me I think only
like 100 people
must be doing something right
you guys
it's an honor to be here
it's an honor
to hang out
and have cookies and have dinner with
you I'm having my dinner this isn't just
a cooking show
we're doing some baking we did some
baking tonight
right
we're doing some baking
what I love about medical meme
information you can bake all day long
all morning all afternoon all night
there is so many baked goods in the
medical medium recipe catalog it is
freaking insane
Catherine sweet
is this the medical medium mukbang
laugh out loud love it it is indeed and
let me give you the trick to mukbangs
are you guys okay with this
here's how they do it right of mukbangs
they put the food way up
can't do that it's not working
all right here's here's the trick
you think they're eating a lot during
their mukbangs right
yeah right they're not eating a lot nice
try nice try
all right
look at these dried cayenne peppers see
these dried cayenne peppers see them
back here
see how they're the regular size
you guess if you get a mukbang lesson
right see how it's regular size
what they do though is they
stick the peppers up here but they're
not eating peppers they're eating like
Fast Foods on mukbangs right
macaroni and cheese whatever it is they
stick it up here
like this so you think they're eating
the biggest mound of food possible
but they're not
they've been psyching people out for
years with those mukbangs on YouTube
Rhonda Johansen said the recipes are
always amazing they are indeed
these cookies are filling
they're they're freaking filling man
Isabella says I want to bake the metal
medium birthday cake for my baby's first
birthday whoa
hmm
foreign
truly honored be here with you guys I
said it before in this time in history
right now
think about how many people have been
healed around the world with mm info at
this point
we can all hang our hat on that
the medical medium info was so vast
there's something for everyone and it
could meet you wherever you are in your
healing process and you can customize it
to what you need to do got some mind if
I'm chewing with my mouth open
balanced self my on YouTube My Stones
which are teaching me patience helped me
paint some furniture today
I really like the sound of that
Michelle
on YouTube these cookies smell amazing I
made them alongside you
boom
dude
aren't they incredible
hands down these are freaking amazing
man 564 on
on YouTube I like the handle ma'am
excuse me ma'am
may I help you ma'am I no longer have
severe hip pain from arthritis that's
incredible
am I annoying you guys want to eat
dinner
and I'm trying to contain myself
and not be too silly
tomorrow's day six remember that please
still alive
because now I've been really oh God good
thing alive is over now I can really eat
these cookies real fast right now
I go cooking monster
wait oh crap we still are alive
I love you guys too you can't wait to
make them Glenda
it's good to hear I'm excited for you
I'm serious because I'm gonna make them
again
tonight
make another round just have them
so they're on hand for tomorrow
anyway
okay you guys at the end of the day
seven at the end of seven days there
will be a replay of all seven days of
collecting Stones meditation Journey
keep that in mind it will be available
for 48 hours if you missed any videos
that's your chance right there
available for free for 48 hours
for four eight hours
48 that's your chance to actually access
all the days if you miss them
but you must be signed up you have to be
signed up that I do know you have to be
signed up I love you guys all right
do you have corn to the hill do you have
medical medium New Edition make sure you
get those get them free at the library
or at amazon.com on a discount there's a
discounted on there amazing price
all right
God bless you guys
oh
I'm IG
Ria says
why do all heart specialists and other
doctors promoting a low carb diet
personally I'm sick of hearing about how
bad carbs are I'm grabbing an apple now
dear Lord
apples are incredible for the heart the
liver
apples are so good for the liver
and when the liver gets healthier it
helps the heart
and they say I'm the food police for
you you're not even allowed to eat an
apple
Susan says
I'm sorry upset I had to stop my stones
medication
wait a minute
Susan Fontes on IG
I'm sorry upset
I had to stop my Stones medication
because I had an extremely difficult and
stressful day
oh meditation but it turned out to a
typo to medication I was going to say
did you really have your stones on
medication
I thought the stones were on medication
I had an extremely difficult and
stressful day I'm really sorry to hear
that then I couldn't find my stones for
two days oh my God
but I couldn't reach at all
that's your heart
all right
I think hopefully I wasn't rude
um
listen we we get
I understand you know when we get
stressful days
and we can't even do we can't even do
what we need to do but that's okay
because your intention is there you have
it in the back your mind
so if you had a really stressful day and
you didn't you weren't able to do the
stone meditation for two days that's
okay
your Stones know this they know this so
keep on going if you can all the way to
the end you got still today tonight you
still got tomorrow you still got the
seventh day okay
all right I love you guys