[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello this is Anthony William the
medical Medium you're listening to the
medical medium radio show where each
week we bring the most advanced healing
information to date that's out there in
alternative and conventional medicine in
chronic illness in chronic illness and
and all the topics around it and
everything else we're talking about
Liver Rescue right now we're talking
about emotional liver emotional emotions
how it plays a role how it involves the
liver what's happening with the liver
how the liver can become emotional all
these different things that are going on
how when we become emotional what's
happening to the liver and what's
happening anyway all of this look you
don't no one has 10 years to throw away
and wait for answers no one has 15 years
but people do they throw away 10 they
have no choice there's no answers out
there it's misinformation
disinformation it's all of the stuff
that's out there on the internet and
books and everything else I hate to say
it but it's true and literally when
someone finds one piece of information
out of the hundreds and hundreds of
pieces the thousands of pieces of
information that I've I actually brought
into the health World okay literally if
they find one piece it benefits them
like for instance a celery juice
benefits them one Jewel and it benefits
them and so many other pieces that are
in the medical medium series books
talking about Liver Rescue today but you
should pick up a copy if you don't have
one you should totally do that if you
can't afford copies of the medical
medium books at the bookstore or
whatever it is I don't know if it's $15
or whatever it is just what if you can't
afford it go to the library get a book
get a book I don't care if the whole
world goes to the library how about that
I I just really don't care it's about
getting the information in your hands
and free information where wherever you
can I put it out in articles I put it
out the radio show I write articles
after the radio shows I put it on
Facebook I put it on Instagram
information information information
blogs M medical medium.com everything
free free free free free free it's not
an infomercial before this podcast where
I'm trying to sell something like a
$10,000 cleanse $2,000 worth of MLM
marketing whatever uh supplements or
blah blah blah whatever supplements of
alcohol in them that destroy the liver
whatever it is you know I'm not I'm not
doing any of that I'm not trying to sell
you a cleanse I'm not selling you
anything you can get the information
free you can go to the damn library and
get it for free it's critical that you
have the information to move forward and
heal so you can help your loved ones
your friends your neighbors whoever your
everyone your children and yourself in
any way possible and so if this the
first time tuning into the medical
medium podcast you should look and tune
in to the other ones and hear some of
the ones that have just done or just did
or whatever and and get from familiar
with how Health Works about the truth
about chronic illness the body doesn't
attack itself and so forth get get
thyroid healing the book thyroid healing
learn that the body doesn't tacket
itself learn the truth about causes at
least 100 different illnesses and
autoimmune conditions I have listed in
that book and it's important you have to
become an expert to protect yourself you
have to become an expert to protect
yourself that's what you have to do
information that comes from the medical
medium which is me is untampered with
it's clean it's pure it's not
regurgitated crap floating around over
and over again and over again and bogus
studies and so forth that keep people
sick so just just know that about me if
you don't know anything about me read
the first book read the first chapter
origins of the medical medium so you can
learn about me and know what I've done
my entire life since I was four years
old and how I just didn't step into this
yesterday okay I've worked on thousands
and thousands of people over the decades
and now the information from the medical
medium books is healing Millions across
the world globally just take one day at
a time and you can learn a little bit
about that but today we're talking about
emotional livers our emotional livers
you know I was talking to somebody in
there like that you know I was talking
to somebody in there're like that
doesn't seem like a great topic I'm like
it doesn't it
doesn't it is believe me wait till you
hear about it wait to hear about it
because and and they're like what do you
mean our emotional livers I go
depression and anxiety okay um mood
swings ups and
downs anger fear that that that people
live with every day trust issues
everything else that people live with
every day it's tied into the liver it's
tied into liver so it's not a it's what
it's not an important topic it's an
important topic even Seasonal effective
disorders sad has everything to do with
the liver I mean you name it and what
about chronic illness how that makes us
so upset when we have all all different
kinds of chronic illnesses diabetes you
know we have diabetes and and uh and
exmos soras and and sibo and gout and
whatever you could just name them a ton
of them has a lot to do with the liver I
mean everything does so our emotional
and our liers believe it or not have
they have feelings oh is that kind of
feel-good talk stupid talk huh is that
stupid talk someone probably just said
that now he's talking stupid our livers
have feelings they do that's they do
have
feelings do a liver transplant stick a
liver in someone you ever see that out
there I know that you're not going to
stick a liver in someone someone loses
their liver they get in line they're
blessed enough to get somebody's liver
thank God and they're blessed enough to
get somebody's liver and all of a sudden
they start acting differently they act
differently all the years have been in
the industry all the people I've talked
to that have had transplants you name it
including doctors including surgeons
that do transplants that I know
personally okay and all of the years of
all of this I'm just going to be
straightforward and tell you right here
okay that I've heard this over and over
again I've seen it the people change
with a new liver not a new liver but
somebody else's old liver they
change they act differently they think
differently they think differently as if
they had a brain
transplant a brain
transplant they think differently they
behave differently different emotions
different feelings different food
cravings different desires different
dreams and different
aspirations that is what I'm talking
about and I'm not even talking about
this with transplants I'm not just dis
mentioning that this is an
example of emotional liver and how our
livers become emotional are you
interested I'm interested I am I want to
cover this topic I do a section in the
book over it not a big section in the
book but there's a there's a chapter
called the emotional liver in the book
and it's a big deal absolutely the book
is so big it's so big I can't even I
can't even I mean even though it killed
me to write it it just killed me to
write it it's 200,000 words basically
it's a massive manuscript it's a it's
it's a big book it's a thick book and
it's a lot to read and it covers so many
illnesses it's unbelievable but the
point is is I needed room in this book
for the emotional liver and it's in here
so I'm going to talk about it that's
what I'm going to do so that's where
we're heading that's where uh we're
heading next that's the deal that's the
deal fasten your seat belts you might be
surprised like usual on the medical
medium radio show the liver's
unhappiness is the foundation of her em
emotional instability
the liver's
unhappiness is the foundation of our
emotional
instability just so you know I'm just
being straight up it's important to
know anxiety and depression can come on
when the liver gets viral just when the
liver gets viral if that's a new term to
you new understanding just know just so
you know everybody has viruses and
bacteria inside of the liver everybody
does I don't care who it is if you ever
had a cold sore before that virus that's
a simplex one it sits inside the liver
it sits inside the
liver that's just one example that's
just one example if you ever had Mono
before it's in the liver it's been in
the liver your whole
life didn't know you had Mono no you
probably didn't know you probably had a
sore throat in college for a week and
slept it off that was mono and it sits
inside the liver you know it's it's it's
amazing it's like the liver it gets
filled with viruses bacteria and then
there these viruses end up later on
causing Hashimoto thyroiditis causing
all these problems and you can protect
yourself just learn how to heal get
thyroid healing learn how to heal get
medical medium book one learn how to
heal make sure you protect yourself from
lime disease and everything else but the
liver gets filled with
viruses and these viruses start
releasing
neurotoxins because they eat food
viruses
feed they feed on food Foods they like
making you want eggs making you want
something to eat
cheese because that's what these viruses
feed off of them nobody in the industry
knows that by the way and if you heard
it somewhere it came from me first from
the books and everything nobody knows
that nobody knows that and it's
important to know that because you need
to know that because you're becoming
that expert right now so you just need
to know you're becoming an expert on
information that's Advanced that's how
it has to work if you're going to help
somebody become an expert like you guys
you got to at least know the
how advanced the information is so you
don't think it's just sitting out there
somewhere when you're telling somebody
and then if you hear it out there you
got to hear it straight and right or
you'll know that it's been skewed or
thrown off and that happens all the time
so always keep an eye out for
that so anxiety and depression that can
come on you know but that that can come
on and have everything to do with the
liver liver starts
releasing neurotoxins too because the
liver gets so filled up with neurotoxins
and dermatoxin
like for instance exam and psoriasis is
dermat toxins that's bugs in the liver
feeding off of copper and other toxins
DDT that's been in there you don't think
DDT is in us every eagle has DDT in it
right now every Eagle does what does an
eagle
eat um rodents
rabbits anything eagles eat chickens you
know they just fly right down in a c
grab a chicken fish they eat fish they
scavenge Eagles are like they scavenge
but why do eagles still have DDT why do
they still have
DDT in them there's not an eagle that
doesn't have DDT in it no there isn't
there's not a human that doesn't have
DDT in it in
them and that DDT sits inside the liver
gets passed on a generation passed on a
generation it's floating in the air
other countries are using
we're still selling it DDT companies are
still selling it just as if everything's
perfectly fine it's just you know when
it's floating around in every other
country
basically still in our country it's
everywhere it's in the
dirt it's unbelievable it's in houses
it's in the walls of houses it's
unbelievable I mean my
God anyway you know liver gets filled
with that pesticides everything else
gets it gets overloaded these things
feed V viruses prescription
drugs I mean everything antibiotics they
start releasing oxidized Metals so that
you know because antibiotics are filled
with metals are filled with petroleum
fills up the liver and all this stuff
goes to the brain short circuits the
brain short circuits neurotransmitter
activity can get somebody kind of
emotional even if it's not considered
depression even if it's not considered
anxiety just anxiousness even if it's
not considered your a diagnosis of
depression it's
still it's still causing problems goes
up to the brain can even cause
neurological issues these things I talk
about that in thyroid healing of course
and in Liver
Rescue so the emotions that even go with
seasonal effectivess disorder they go
with anything forget SE seasonal effect
disorder just your daily disorder like
your daily being affected by it becomes
you know disorder emotions are like that
emotions that go I mean we all have
emotions it it basically anger
frustration abandonment feeling crushed
forgotten or the like have to do with
your brain being affected by the true
story of what's occurring inside of your
liver and then if you have things that
happen on the outside of you it's like
somebody breaking your heart
relationships somebody stiffing you
somebody backstabbing you somebody
betraying you broken trust all this
stuff if you live on planet Earth long
enough you'll experience some of that
you'll experience some of that
absolutely
basically totally getting bleeped over
you know that happens to so many people
in so many ways and so that's not good
either and that that causes trouble too
because what that does is that causes
adrenaline surges and that's a whole
another section that we're going to go
into on the emotional liver adrenaline
surges surges from outside
sources adrenaline surges from you're
not going to hear this anywhere this
just not I have to repeat that in case
somebody new popped on to the podcast
out of nowhere and there you know you're
not going to hear any of this anywhere
adrenaline surges from being crushed
emotionally or being just
confrontational IED is that a word no
it's not a word that's not a word I just
made that word up
confrontation being you know pushed
around anything at work co-workers
friends anything going on any kind of up
and down that you have in your life any
kind of difficult situation that we all
face day in and day out or through life
or once a year or whatever it is
adrenaline gets released saturates the
liver injures the liver go the
adrenaline goes to the brain but it
definitely goes to the liver because the
liver has to absorb it up to stop it
from going to the heart and the Brain
the best it can but some gets there
anyway but the point is the liver is the
mop the sponge for adrenaline
related you know issues from outside
sources of being let down and so forth
and challenged and everything else
adrenaline
is an
issue it's very difficult so that's just
one thing that's just one thing and then
our own emotions that occur from a toxic
liver like I said anger frustration
abandonment you know that feeling of
being crushed forgotten or the like
having to do with everything being
affected by what's in occurring inside
the liver the liver's unhappiness is the
foundation of our emotional stability
I'm going to say it over again I'm going
to say it over again you
guys very important to know and then you
got Mercury inside the liver pathogens
feeding off of mercury creating more
toxins and these toxins being released
out of the liver and the liver holds as
many as it can until it gets sluggish
and stagnant and becomes
weak and that's the whole thing there
too electrical electrical impulses in
the brain can short circuit from all
these toxins that come from the liver
creating more emotional issues and
frustration and anger can arise from a
sluggish pref fatty or fatty liver so
basically your
liver is what I'm trying to say is your
liver getting fatty or pre fatty
emotions come from that they arise from
that they do and it's a difficult
situation the liver starts to lose its
strength as it's fighting for its life
on a daily basis
our livers fight for its own life on a
daily basis so what do we do we throw a
whole bunch of crappy food in there we
do we do all kinds of stuff I got people
complaining about celery juice they
can't drink celery juice 50-year-olds
can't drink celery juice they don't want
to drink it and they got babies on
Instagram toddlers drinking glasses of
celery juice is not complaining one bit
got 40y olds 25 year olds 30-y olds 28y
olds can't can't get any celery juice
down they feel like they're bloating or
they got something going on they just
don't like it because first of all it's
it's gets becomes
emotional
emotional it becomes emotional because
you're actually hitting the liver with
all that and you're cleansing the liver
it's yeah it could be
hard as you got these babies and are
just drinking down a big glass of celery
juice I swear to God it just blows me
off my seat and that's happening
worldwide it's happening around the
country and everything
else it's it's really funny it's funny
how things work I mean it's the best
thing I've ever seen you know I would
have never dreamed that I had over the
years um I've had moms give celery juice
their little ones over the years when I
was in practice you know year year after
year seven days a week all day sometimes
throughout the night depending on
emergencies and stuff like that and um
and um there's a lot of little kids and
a lot of kids that that drank celery
juice but when but that's before that
was before you can see it happening like
on the internet now you can see it so
when I see it it just blows me away it
blew me away a long time ago and it
blows me away still
today
so
anyway the liver can become
cranky on its
own and it can even feel disconnected on
its own it's not getting any love any
attention we really do abuse our livers
not because we want to I know you don't
want to I don't want to we don't want to
it happens from misinformation and
disinformation and everything else it
happens from a lot of that trendy stuff
too cleanses that are actually bad for
the liver cleans is just terrible
cleanse it's not like the 369 in Liver
Rescue you want to cleanse your liver
safely and learn why it's safe so you
actually know get get the Liver Rescue
book but
trendy misinformation out there the
disinformation is just horrendous
because it gets people in trouble you
eat a lot more fat you don't even know
you're eating all this protein fat
you're just killing your liver you're
aging yourself quickly sure might not
see it when you're exercising and
feeling pretty good at 25 years old and
you're trying to lower your carbs and
you're trying to stay off fast food sure
fine but everybody gets older you can't
escape it and and it's all catches up
the liver gets toxic bugs collect in it
you know relationships and all kinds of
things through life and bugs collect
that go into the liver whatever happens
you're eating in restaurants all the
time and whatever and you you can pick
up bugs and just what happens is the
liver gets filled up it's gets weak you
start getting bloated you get the hot
flashes you get the viral symptoms
everything else that everybody has the
type of thyroid that comes on later on
all these things you can't escape it
unless you do the right things and you
watch what you're
doing and you know what you're doing
that's the whole point so medical medium
series is teaching anybody that so they
can actually stay healthy and
young but the liver gets tired from
everything and it gets
emotional it actually gets
emotional and it's a really important
thing to
understand and we have to treat it with
some
respect when the liver gets toxic and
it's holding on to tremendous amounts of
poisons such as get this
radiation oh man the liver holds on to
radiation
trying to protect you number one plus we
get radiation exposure a lot pesticides
herbicides nanotechnology where can we
get nanotechnology it's coming out of
the
sky and I'm not trying to like claim
doomsday I'm just saying we just need to
cleanse our livers properly take care of
ourselves eat the right things and get
rid of our you know symptoms conditions
and learn how to protect ourselves and
learn how to you know help the emotional
liver so we don't become emotional I
mean all of this is this
important is it important I thought it
was really important I put it in the
book it's a little section in the book I
mean the book is so big it's got so many
other things in there to talk about but
I put this in
there you know spirit said to me we need
this I said all right okay all right
well then I said fine I mean I could
have said no but I said all right and I
get it we really really do need it you
know I I have to learn too when the
liver gets toxic and it's holding on to
a tremendous amount of poison such as
radiation pesticides herbicides nanot
technology materials that are on
clothing brand new clothing you name it
fungicides that are on
everything toxic heavy metals what's a
toxic heavy metal mercury lead arsenic
copper nickel
chromium Chrome whatever
anything the whole bit I said nickel
barium whatever um a whole bunch of
different
things you know bacteria viruses path
pathogenic waste matter like dermato
toxins like I said neurotoxins some of
these poisons can leech into the
bloodstream and intestinal tract as
you've read
before in thyroid healing and medical
medium book
one they can cause some of the issues
we've like looked at with everything I
talked about that before
adrenaline though is a really obnoxious
annoying
one because adrenaline get this get this
you
guys
adrenaline is released when we go
through a hard
time it's released with regular things
too or a good time but it's released
with hard
times it is when it's released with hard
times it has information in it
information stored in it because there's
over 56 blends of a adrenaline science
and research has no idea 56 Blends the
adrenal subtle Blends from being like
going through a hardship or a breakup or
whatever it is whatever it is whatever
hard time it is a
loss and that adrenaline has information
in it released at the time when a
certain time happened in your
life the liver Sops it all up absorbs it
all
up and takes on that information
and that that can build up over time if
a lot of stuff is intense and going
through your life and you're not
cleansing and take care in your liver
that's one of the things also adrenaline
scorches and weakens the liver but the
liver is doing that to protect your
brain your heart the whole bit the liver
is trying to protect your butt that's
trying to protect
you mind-blowing isn't it mind-blowing
information that's in Liver Rescue mind
blow it blows my mind it blew my
mind fasten your seat seat belts got
more to come it's really intense gets
actually pretty
crazy when that adrenaline gets trapped
in the liver the liver tries to trap it
in fat
cells yeah and when your liver gets
sluggish and lazy and it's been through
hell and you're eating high fat diets or
anything else the liver starts taking on
more fat adrenaline gets set not only
saturated in liver tissue can get
saturated in liver liver fat
cells
whether it's in liver fat cells or just
living liver tissue that adrenaline that
happened during a hard time or a loss or
a breakup or a divorce or a problem or a
stressful time in your
life when it needs to be released
because the liver decides to release
it you know like when you know breakups
betrayals being stabbed in the back this
information's in that adrenaline and
when it gets
released it goes through the
body and creates it's emotions that are
unexplainable you can't really tap into
it or touch it but it's there can get
somebody down depressed sad at the end
of the day without even realizing
it it's powerful stuff that
happens your liver wants to prevent you
from becoming Intoxicated by adrenaline
this is a steroid that races through
your bloodstream messes you up and
during these traumatic moments your
liver becomes so nervous and even scared
for your
life and get ready for
this it releases a hormone undiscovered
by research and science they'll Discover
it maybe in 50 years or 40 years
whatever it is I don't even know if I'm
if we're even lucky if I'm even lucky
they've already discovered some things
that I put out years
ago yeah heard it here first though
Discovery was here
first your liver becomes so nervous and
even scared for your life it releases a
hormone that's undiscovered like I said
by science and research that draws
excess adrenaline into the liver so the
organ can sop it up to protect you from
stroking out from neurotransmitters
being totally burned out from the
experience and even from Hemorrhage or
anything of the
sort the liver can soak up excess
adrenaline from the bloodstream during
bouns of intense stress and other
adrenal
triggers it's only a temporary solution
but still the liver is doing this over
time it must release its adrenaline
stores bit by bit because it has no
choice and even when you're cleansing
it'll release it which will make you
feel weird during your cleansing and
detoxing totally emotional can make you
feel really emotionally unstable when
you detox but people do different
cleanses and detoxes and water fasts and
whatever and Juice fasts they get
emotional because this is the stuff
that's coming out but nobody knows or
has a clue no one you're hearing it
first ever
here over time it releases this
adrenaline that's right bit by bit so
the kidneys and the intestinal tract can
try to be prepared to release a new bat
so you could be be prepared to get rid
of it as each new batch is coming in
even gets released out of your
armpits as the adrenaline leaves you'll
experience the information stored the
hurt the hurt
stored
nostalgic almost surreal in a
way even if the adrenaline was from a
month ago 6 months ago a year ago 5
years ago 10 years ago 15 years
ago you'll feel a little bit of loss
maybe some frustration maybe even a
crapload of anger
so this liver of ours tends to release
its storage bins of
adrenaline with even the change of the
seasons a little spurt here a little
spurt
there when your liver took this
adrenaline originally it released that
it was released during your emotional
trials and
tribulations it also took on and held to
your emotional experience that's what
I'm trying to tell you the liver took on
and held on to your emotional
experience experiences too experiences
too
okay that's really
important its release of this can
trigger the same painful experience and
feelings you had when the adrenaline was
first
released at a time of struggle because
it holds this emotional
Essence as the liver lets go you let
go so I
mean this is important
information and it's important because
you may be feeling lost when you feel
emotional not no but the irony is you go
to a you go to a psych and you go to
whatever and you go to a you go to a you
know whatever psychoanalyst psychologist
whatever it
is
psychiatrist and you know I mean they
just try their best but they won't know
that this is happening they just don't
so I mean it it's good that you know so
many people feel lost and they don't
even know why and the liver has
everything to do with it that's the
irony liver has everything to do with
it so the liver keeps a
record it's unbelievable it keeps a
record of what's
happening it keeps a record of
everything and you can feel extra
emotional as you get toward the end of a
calendar year too just as adrenaline
that's released on the liver schedule is
attached to emotions liver on a schedule
as well it's amazing how the liver works
the
adrenaline the adrenaline that's
attached to toxins that the liver is
forced to let go can bring out emotions
too so you can have adrenaline attached
to a
toxin any kind of toxin inside the
liver or you could have been at a
funeral at one time 8 years ago you ate
a ham sandwich to wash down your
Sorrows all this time your brain has
stored away the memory within its data
database and your liver is that database
and brain in this
situation your liver has stored the
emotional information along with the
cheap hams ammonia nitrates and other
preservatives that you ate at the
funeral and cheap fat or unhealthy fat
in the pork that it neutralized and took
on to protect you so your liver absorbed
it and took it on to protect you
I mean this is the power of the liver
what it does and the memory it has too
it's
incredible you can feel that when that
ham sandwich starts detoxing out of your
liver along with the adrenaline
too you can feel that sorrow again and
not even pinpoint where it's coming
from not even know where the grief is
coming from you can be consumed with
grief for a time and not even know why
as it traveling through your
bloodstream that's just one of hundreds
of examples of when that ham sand Sam
Sandwich starts to come out of that
liver with the experience this being at
a funeral as an example and eating that
ham
sandwich our bodies are complicated but
simple Simplicity meaning that if we
take care of them give them what they
need you wouldn't believe what they'll
do for you you wouldn't believe what
your body will do for you if you don't
know what it needs then we get in
trouble because if we don't know we
don't
know and that's the whole point of why I
wake up in the morning it's why when I
was age four and spirit started talking
to
me and I took spirit's information which
was just as advanced when I was 5 six
seven 8 years old as it is now it's all
the same Spirit would still tell me the
same didn't mean I had to understand it
but I can still I can still recite it as
if I was in a play in a play or
something trying to listen to my lines
or read my lines spirit was giving me
the lines to say didn't matter how
advanced it was about neurotoxins didn't
matter how advanced it was about 60
varieties of viruses it doesn't matter
how advanced it was i''d be 6 Seven 8
years old just talking just saying it
all as organized as the liver tries to
stay with different
compartments and store different toxins
in every place inside the liver because
the liver stores so many different
toxins in so many different areas it has
storage Banks and it and it's B do you
ever ever been to a
dump and you know scrap metal and all
this other stuff there I mean I don't
know if you've ever been to one you know
when I was a kid we lived near a dump
you know it was kind of close enough and
you know it wasn't good either because
you got all that mercury and you got all
that bad stuff just lead and everything
else just leaking from rain water just
leaking down into the Earth you know was
always concerned being kind of living
near that close enough but but the
bottom line is I remember going to the
dump and you know family would bring
some garbage go to the dump or something
like that and you I'd walk through and
back then it was it's not like now you
know as a kid literally walking through
like a dangerous area unbelievable and
and you can see like one pile had all
these wash machines and
dryers see you or something microwaves
wash machine dryers and all that
something like that one pile one pile
had all these like
bicycles you know bicycle frames and all
this other stuff one pile had all this
like toilets and sinks and all that you
know you know another another had like
bottles and crap just like it was all
that kind of stuff oh wa and another pot
would be like
couches it was crazy and know probably
would be like couches and mattresses
yeah I don't know if you've ever
experienced anything like
this yeah anyway you know I'd see all
that and I remember I'll never forget
Spirit saying to me I was 8 years old
and spirit said to me as I was standing
there waiting for my dad to you know do
his thing and drop off garbage or
whatever it is and spirit said to me
this is like your liver right here this
garbage dump I said my liver personally
Spirit Well your liver is not so bad cuz
we've been working on it you know Spirit
would always tell me how to eat a little
bit better and everything else at that
young age I do do the best at my
capacity then whatever was
available but spirit said no this is
this is the human liver right here
wow so it's like I was amazed because I
was getting it I was starting to
understand it more and more not just
hearing the information to be able to
tell somebody hey look you got you got
this thing in your liver and you got
these spots in your liver I see that
spirit's telling you about and that you
know all that and and you know and doing
the scan and all that that Spirit taught
me to do but it was I was sitting there
and it was like a revelation it was
almost like oh my God it was
serious and what it was what it was was
I had this realization I saw it this was
the liver it was starting to hit me wow
everybody's liver is polluted
and spirit said you see that pile of
scrap metal over there those are heavy
metals they're all in the liver of
somebody and the liver tries to actually
put them in compartments even separating
them if the liver can and it will it
will try because it'll do everything it
can and then spirit said you see those
piles of cans over there cans and and
all that and Bottles the bottle caps and
all that
and I said yeah all those cans and all
those different cans and all that
there's petrochemicals in those cans
those are all aerosol cans and solvents
inside of them and empty solvent cans of
you know of of oil degreasers and
carburetor cleaners and all these
different
things and those are all petrochemicals
and solvents and they go in a different
area of the liver a deep core of the
liver and in that pile you see m old gas
cans everywhere the metal ones some of
them still having a little bit of
gasoline at the bottom all piled up in a
big Heap ready just to ignite if
anything those old
dumps and spirit would say and you see
that pile over there and I said what and
spirit said and that pile over there the
furniture and the beds it's all from
Malahide that's all you know outgassing
materials and chemical Laden you know uh
uh Petri chemicals too and different
kinds of solvents different kind of
falah hdes and everything all sitting
there and I got it and I got it I
understood at age eight how the liver
works and how it stores everything and
how it stores
everything yeah and then spirit said
this which blew my mind as an
8-year-old and I didn't forget it I
didn't forget this
one and spirit said
these are all
possessions all these things you see in
here that are piled up bicycles the wash
Machines Car Parts all this kind of
stuff and they have emotions attached to
them people attach themselves to
possessions of course emotions are
combined into that it might be a bicycle
somebody first got as a gift for a first
birthday it might be or a birthday it
might be a couch that a husband bought a
wife for an
anniversary it could be
anything in the pile that was in there
could be wash machine a wash
machine that you know washed a whole
bunch of bedding from somebody that was
that passed
away it could be a mattress that you
know there was good times on the
mattress of of of a couple together
Partners husband and wife or whatever
and also could be bad times being sick
spirit said and having a stroke and
laying in the bed for a long
time there's emotions even in all of
this and spirit taught me then that the
liver is filled with emotions along with
toxins that even come from these
possessions
here if feel laid in a bed and there's
some faldh coming up which you can detox
and heal yourself from I mean it's all
good not trying to scare anybody you can
lay in your you lay in the bed and you
got these toxins coming
up and it happened during a
time yeah it stores in the liver and it
could get released and there could be an
emotional connection to
it it's that
intense it's that unbelievable the liver
is just an unbelievable mechanism of
some kind unbelievable organ gland and
whatever you want to call it whatever
science of research wants to call it I'm
cool with that science research thinks
it has 500 chemical functions try again
it's got over
2,000 it's got over 2,000 Spirit taught
me that
too did Spirit teach me all 2000 no my
head would blow up it would just explode
and I I can't go through that but I sure
as heck put hundreds of undiscovered
ones in this book live or
rescue hundreds of U undiscovered
chemical functions in Liver
Rescue but the bottom line
is is I was just completely blown away
as I stood there at 8 years old hearing
all this so the liver put compart has
compartments of these stored poisons of
all these different stored things that
we go through and memories and things
and bad and good and everything else
it's all piled in this heap of garbage
discarded
unbelievable
and so that blew my mind when I left the
dump that day with my dad with my father
I left the dump that day I was just
completely taken
back completely taken
back and you know what's really crazy
that day that happened I'm going to tell
you right now since I'm just being a
little bit
emotional me and my dad were walking out
of that dump and it was an old one had
kind of like a it was dirt road didn't
even have cement
and we were walking out of
there and I looked on the ground and
something shiny was on the ground and
yeah there's bottle cap shiny there's
flip tops there's all kinds of garbage
aluminum foil everywhere Just Junk I
looked down the
ground and there was a quarter on the
ground
1942 and it was silver so I didn't know
it was silver until spirit said it was
silver and I said well what do you mean
it's Silver Spirit said that's a silver
quarter that's not clad that's not you
know that's not
nickel it's not copper it's
silver and I picked it up it was
1942 and my dad said hey that's an old
coin I said wow was all beat up and
spirit said that's
silver Silver's anti
viral silver is a different kind of
metal
and silver kills
pathogens and sometimes Silver's you
know
sometimes sometimes I mean over the
years it's it's important to take a
little bit of the right kind not not not
the not the wrong kinds there's wrong
kinds out there but they remember being
blown
away by
that and spirit said not all metals are
bad not all metals are bad cuz Spirit
was teaching about all the toxic heavy
metals
and spirit said that there's going to be
some Silvers down the road where people
can actually take a little for a sore
throat take a
teaspoon for a sore throat to kill off
strep strep a cockus and I heard that at
8 years old walking out of the
dump unbelievable that just blows me
away I know it's off topic a little bit
but when you're dealing with viruses
strep and pathogens especially strep too
and eoli all that it sits inside the
liver it sits inside of Staff it sits
inside the Li liver SEI sits inside the
liver all these different bugs
everywhere funguses and everything else
bad funguses that it's all store inside
the liver and everything and then when
they come out or we get a bad sore
throat we get a tons lights viral
infection you know teaspoon of the right
kind of silver can really really move
people
forward take a little bit of that once
in a while but it just blew me away that
information at 8 years old
anyway it was a great day that day cuz I
had the window inside the liver and I
was able to tell people all the time
about the emotional end of it all it's
really
powerful you know you know the liver and
it's miscellaneous storage
area it just it it gets bombarded at the
same time with our high fat diet that's
what really bugs me and it's it's just
everywhere and the trend is just high
fat high protein which is high fat by
the way high protein don't get fooled by
that and it's just it's amazing what
happens it gets bombarded by Fats too
it's a whole another thing and do you
know what fats do and the reason why
have to tell you this the more fats you
eat in your diet the more adrenaline has
to be dispersed out of the adrenal
glands and more epinephrine more
adrenaline cortisols everywhere it's got
to actually be dispersed to try to thin
out the blood so the fats don't give you
a heart attack on a daily better daily a
daily level a daily level they got to
remember that so lowering your fats is
so important you can listen to the other
shows about the liver and everything
else and you'll hear about that how you
how to do that and all
that trying to take in and process all
these fats the best it can our liver it
will throw in
items like the
troublemakers from a funeral reception
the ham sandwich hairspray from a
prom that went bad you know air
freshener from a waiting room or you
were awaiting bad
news chemically treated fire pitted wood
and excess alcohol from a cookout where
your relationship broke up and even
little bits of
adrenaline the liver is not being sloppy
and throwing them all together it's
being efficient it throws all these
together and stores them inside the
liver and it releases them all together
out and when we bombard the liver with
high fat diets we trap it in
longer so and sometimes
sometimes the fat itself that gets
trapped in the liver absorbs all of this
and holds it on for a lifetime until you
start working it
out it's amazing how it
works basically the liver's goal is to
use chemical functions to sort out all
this miscellaneous pile that I talked
about at the dump
site sort it out and categ categorize it
can't say that word right
today most people aren't on track to
give the liver the break it needs most
all people are not on track to give it
the break it
needs we leave it to be alone like a
lone wolf a
worker a worker at the dump instead of
teaming up with it because we don't know
otherwise
and you know what when I was at that
dump when I was 8 years old there was a
whole bunch of people working it wasn't
one person it was like a whole bunch of
guys piling up garbage here driving a
truck over here dumping garbage here
pulling something out of here doing this
bringing things here another truckload
it was like a whole massive team of
people but guess what your liver's only
one one person your liver's only one
thing one Lone Wolf doing it alone
that's why we need to help it to help
our emotional
abilities so organizing this
miscellaneous pile is last on the
liver's to-do list and that's another
problem it often doesn't get to
it when it comes time to purge which
you'll know in liver 369 in this book so
you can get rid of the emotional
instability it's time to purge you make
room for
more it's this pile that gets emptied
out comes that ham sandwich that I
talked about at the funeral out comes
that miscellaneous
junk the the liver wants to toss out and
out goes Cravings along with sorrow
Cravings can happen too you can get you
start craving and that's it and you
won't be able to trace back to anything
you won't be able to trace back to
anything anytime you detox you guys
whether in a healthy way endorsed by the
liver which this book's about
out and this book's endorsed by the
liver when it's forced to empty some of
its miscellaneous storage bin I talked
about that dump site to make room for
anything else in the moment emotions can
come up as the toxins leave it happens
both during the liver's stress bomb time
that is the NeverEnding indulge in
Buffet basically what's happening is you
know the liver has emotions too it's
just doing the best it can to run the
whole show in there and it's by itself
just like we do the best we can when
we're sitting somewhere and we end up
eating things we're not supposed to eat
and we're stressed out and we're tired
and it's the only resources we got in
front of us and everything
else
unbelievable how it
works
Cravings are serious I mean you may
crave a honey baked ham double bacon
cheeseburger
I mean you may crave
pizza but your body's not telling you I
need protein and your liver is not
telling you I need protein and your
liver is not telling you I need iron and
protein no it's
not the best way to handle these
Cravings that even happen on emotional
level when when all this is going on the
best way is to not to give it to them
not to give into to them I mean sorry
about that not to give in to them and
instead we got to opt for that celery
juice opt for those steamed potatoes
without butter on them without fats on
them opt for sweet potatoes without oils
on them opt for and if you you know I
mean do the best you can opt for some
butternut squash steamed butter baked
butter not squash why not do baked
butter opt for bananas banana ice cream
opt for so many recipes that are in The
Liver Rescue book and so many other
books of mine you know opt for all these
other options
yeah yeah if you have to opt for a
little avocado sh if you have to opt for
something else sure I mean sure but try
to opt for some of these other ones some
of these other
things I know leafy greens aren't
comforting I know but they sure as heck
fix your liver I know celery juice isn't
comforting I know it's not I mean some
people say it is I mean I feel it is but
it fixes your
liver and it repairs emotional
damage and it just does wonders it's
like a
miracle the heavy metal detox smothie
may not be something anyone craves but
let me tell you something it's that good
for you it's
incredible but the emotional liver lives
inside of us and never forget it it's in
you the emotional liver is in you yeah
you got a liver you got that emotional
liver in there it lives inside of you
and the emotional liver lives inside of
me it lives inside of
us it has a
heart it has a heart your liver has
smarts it smarts your liver has
feelings it has
feelings know this in your heart for
certain we can live with it but we can't
live without
it we can live with the liver but we
can't live without it taking care of it
is the best way to get chronic illness
to just disappear and it's the best way
to stabilize taking care of the liver is
the best way to stabilize
emotions taking care of your liver is
the best way to stabilize your life to
stabilize your
life and don't forget it
deliver works for you it's working for
you it's not thinking about working for
itself it's actually working for you and
if it does work for itself it's for you
to keep it strong and keep it alive and
keep it
well next time you experience some
emotions think about your liver If you
experience some anger that's creeping up
think about your liver you experience
anything that's creeping up think about
your think about your liver if you're
getting triggered by somebody and it's
getting you pissed off and you're
getting hurt
think about your liver because that's
the adrenaline now that the liver has to
absorb and what does that mean it
doesn't mean you can't stop being hurt
and you can't stop thinking about the
whatever you went through and whatever
kind of breakup or relationship or
whatever it is it doesn't mean you you
don't have to you know avoid that it
just
means you just have to take care of
yourself a little bit in between it
somehow some way and get the willpower
and dig it up out and say I got to take
care of my liver a little bit I'm going
through crap in hard times I'm going
through struggles but I got to take my
care care of my liver a little bit I
don't want to store it in there forever
I want to make sure I take care of it I
want to eat a little bit better when I
can even if you have no appetite and you
can't eat at all for two weeks cuz
you're just miserable you just have to
think about the liver drink more lemon
water when you're going through a hard
time if it's all you can stomach and
stand drink more lemon water if you're
going through a hard time and if you're
really an athlete and you're into
adrenaline Sports remember the this you
might be happy doing the sport and
getting a high off of it but your
liver's taking a beating excuse me
it's taking a hard beating a crap
beating so we have to do things for the
liver too even as an athlete doing
sports we have to just take care of the
liver I love you guys one day at a time
bless your heart and uh I'll see you
next show okay that concludes this
episode and on to the next love you
byebye