day three heavy metal detox cleanse
challenge
this is a special time because when you
get rid of metals
you become lighter i think people
overall want to feel as if they're
lightened up like the load is taken off
them
loads not on their back they don't feel
a load on their
chest lightening the load that's what
happens when you get rid of toxic heavy
metals
because stress even reduces when you get
rid of toxic heavy metals
the more metal that leaves your brain
the less stress
you feel even when you're under stress
even when you're under stressful
situations
you actually feel lighter less
disgruntled
less flustered less miserable
less depressed less anxiety ridden
when you don't have an anxiety problem
anymore because you got the metals out
and they're gone things lighten up
you know you don't react so much you
don't get triggered so easy
metals are why you get triggered
that's one of the big ways we get
triggered it's metals
it's not you it's not because you're
someone that gets triggered
it's not because you're a difficult
person
and you know and and that's it
facebook's not working i hear so
it's like it's it's more than that
it's more than that it's not about
you being somebody that is just messed
up
that person's messed up no no person's
not messed up
medals do all kinds of stuff they make
it so we get triggered they make it so
we get emotional
metals can get us amped up metals can
take us to a place where we get
emotional easy
we get very emotional easy and then
metals can do even more
than that metals can take us to a place
of mania
like hysteria neurosis psychosis it
could take you even to that degree
metals can give you an eating disorder
do you know that metals cause bulimia
metals cause anorexia
metals cause all kinds of eating
disorders
metals cause all kinds of emotional
constant mental disorders metals
really do a lot of damage and think
about that
think about that think about somebody
with an eating disorder severe eating
disorder
one that's shaped their life for
difficult situations with their family
difficult situations with everybody that
loves them different difficult
situations with
with it with anybody around them
even like be feeling like they're
tortured and torturing others that kind
of feeling and
and meanwhile it's metals
short-circuiting the brain
and sending signals down the highway
the neurological highway you guys the
vagus nerve
sending signals to the vagus nerve
metals can send
signals down the vagus nerve boom and
get down to the gut right here
and create an eating disorder right
there metals
can set those signals down because
there's a short circuit happening up
here
i'm like up to here with neuroscience
talk
so many geniuses
so many geniuses in alternative health
i'm up to here with so much of that
so much i'm up to here with the whole
thing about you created your problems
like you created your problems
you did you just couldn't master your
thoughts right you couldn't mask i'm so
up to here about that
there's real reasons why people are
struggling and are struggling with their
thoughts and they're struggling with
their actions and they're struggling
with their pain and suffering
and their emotions and their anxiety and
their depression their personalization
their bipolar and everything else
there's real reasons medals are the big
reason
the big reason up to here
with oh it's because you can't master
your thoughts yeah we want to
we definitely want to think positive and
we definitely want to fight
we definitely want to fight for it and
we definitely want to better ourselves
emotionally we definitely want to better
ourselves with everything we can with
our meditations and everything else
absolutely we want to do those things we
need to be in the positive absolutely
but we can't beat the piss out of
ourselves
when we're struggling with anxiety and
that depression and everything else and
we can't
believe that we manifested our problems
and our emotional problems that we
manifested that because it's metals that
are speaking for you
not you not you being a bad person not
you causing the harm or causing the
trouble
it's metals that are speaking for you
and when we get those metals out and
they come out
then the wires work differently the
wires work like they should
we come into this world as a baby
saturated in metal we come into this
world
and then we get the medical crap going
on a medical system
boom as a baby saturating us with metals
right off the running that's what the
medical system does
that's right it hits you with metals
right off the running
and then you're doing the medications
hit you with more metals right off the
run
more medical more medical stuff hits you
with metals right off the running
yeah then you're a child there's a whole
bunch more metals
a whole bunch more metals and now you
got the adhd and you've got all these
other things and
and then the pesticides and and the
perfumes and clones and
and the carpet cleaning all the carpet
cleaning chemicals
the air fresheners more metals metals
metals the fabric softeners
right fabric softeners all the
fragrances and all the cleaning products
and household products
all the fragrances and then all the
fluoride treatments as your child is how
do you stand a chance
you're just saturated with metal and
more medical treatments and then boom
and then more of this
and then more of that metals metals
metals
and then all of a sudden a flip just
switches boom and you've got that eating
disorder all of a sudden a flip just
switches
boom you're triggered you get triggered
easy trigger real easy
and it's not your fault it's not your
fault
alexander says after one and a half
years following medical medium protocols
i feel again
what it's like to have clear thoughts in
mind amazing
amazing amazing
metal short circuit our brains that's
what
metals do short circular brain so we get
triggered real easy
real easy and when we're young we get
now we're crying in the corner when
we're kind of not supposed to or we're
in the store we get a blood sugar crash
and we're in the store as a child and we
get a blood sugar crash now we're
screaming and crying in the aisle
because metals what they do is they make
it so that when you get that blood sugar
crash
they get they make it so you can trigger
it easy
trigger it easy and then the focus and
concentration
focus and concentration that all the
children are going through that's metals
all of that focus and concentration
adults go through that's all metals too
that's all metals too
how it works learning disabilities
medals learning disabilities
medals dyslexia medals
autism adhd metals
metals metals metals neuroscience
geniuses let's do another neuroscience
genius talk
guys are so far off the mark they're so
far off the mark
but that's how it's supposed to be it's
supposed to be
it's supposed to be far off the mark
your professors in your universities
they're not supposed to know that you
guys you know that you guys went to
college
we went to university and went to dorm
rooms that the rooms were saturated
every single time you go away
you go away in december they sat they
spray the rooms
before you go in in the fall they spray
all the rooms
all the rooms and they spray it with
rodent killer
they spray it with roach killer they
spray it with insect killer
a worm killer whatever they can get and
they spray and they saturate the rooms
and then the kids
they just go to college breathe it all
in and then the weight gain hits it's
not just the food
if the weight gain hits and everybody's
battling their weight in college
it's like well i must be oh honey you
put on a lot of weight since the last
semester over and over again all that
pesticide
all those metals in the system
meanwhile you know what did the
professors know
i don't know anything about metals
this is the way it works karen says what
heavy metal causes dyslexia mercury
mercury mercury mercury the metals are
everywhere right we can't avoid them
they're everywhere
you know they're in the tattoo ink every
single person who has a tattoo
has metals leaching into their
bloodstream
every single vegan non-toxic so-called
ink that's used now saturated metals
because that's
that's the pop the light hits the
ink through the skin if they don't put
metal in it there won't be a reflection
and you won't get a pop from the ink
they're loaded with metal
doesn't matter how good or high gray
that
ink is how you know animal cruelty free
that ink is is the best vegan
animal cruelty free no it's loaded with
metals
so now we've got metals leaching in us
our whole life
our whole life and those metals leave
the ink and they blew they leave the
derma they go into the bloodstream and
it's a time release
release capsule capsules like taking a
time release capsule of metal
so we can run and we can run and we can
run but we can't hide
because metals are all around us so then
it makes the load heavy and it starts to
short-circuit the brain
and then you get older and that's it why
is alzheimer's on the
on the high why is it going up and up
and up and memory problems and
dementia and not even just that focused
concentration and brain fog and
everything under the sun depression and
anxiety
it's it's going up and up and up and up
in bipolar bipolar bipolar
it's because the metals the metals in
the brain they short get short-circuit
the brain
they get a short-circuited so
the heavy metal detox cleanse it's like
where it's really at
that's where it's really at really at
meanwhile all the other bs going around
and all turned medicines
it's a joke compared joke it's so sad
danielle the only info that has helped
me heal is mm
i know the combo of my daily lemon water
celery juice and heavy metal detox movie
has been the trio
the trifecta that has rescued me in my
health
the most thank god
i'm so proud of you i am i'm proud of
you
i am you know what's annoying i see
lately
people dabbling with the medical meme
information not citing it right
i know i said that but then adding like
the coffee enema thing
right if oh man also do your coffee
enemas
also do do your coffee enemas do your
bentonite clay
do your green tea and they just screw it
all
up and so people get a tidbit of that
medical medium but they can't really
heal if they're really sick
samantha says do you have any insight on
fulvic minerals of course i do
they're that that products useless to
waste money it's throwing money away
it's throwing money away i would spend
my money on those wild blueberries right
there right there
take that money for that that
that crappy product and you go and buy
some wild blueberries
take that money and you make sure you
buy extra celery
extra celery with that money each month
that's what you do that's what i
recommend
they won't remove toxic heavy metals
number one okay
you can get more minerals the body will
receive and enjoy
through that celery right there that's
that's right that
vulva fulvic acids been around fulvic
minerals have been around
been around it's just it died it died
they're just trying to amp it up now
they're trying to ride the medical
medium train
that's what they're doing but the whole
fulvic product thing just
went down the hill back 15 years ago but
there's a new generation of suckers
that i'm just giving you like it is what
do i have against fulvic if it was good
i'd tell you
i would i would thank you for asking no
it's important question because it might
have saved somebody some money in the
future
so yeah metals can cause schizophrenia
absolutely i saw that question 100
100 so getting the metals out of
critical so we're on day three the heavy
metal
cleanse right heavy metal detox cleanse
challenge
and getting battles out of your life is
like
that's where it's at that's where it's
at
but here's the problem you can't see the
metals so
are they really there you can't see the
metals
so is it really something i should do
and science research doesn't know what
connects to anxiety and depression and
depersonalization and neuroscientists
in neuro talking about neural pathways
don't even know about what causes
anxiety depression and depersonalization
focus concentration adhd alzheimer's and
they don't know so they're not saying
metals is unless they got it from mm
but they're not saying that also metals
aren't really there so i guess i don't
need to worry about them
right biofeedback is where it's at
oh nice try nice try watch
biofeedback people pour into my office
after
doing biofeedback and sure
you know you know what will make
biofeedback work is if someone's doing
their celery juice
doing their heavy metal detox smoothies
doing their medical meaning protocols
healing themselves and then getting
biofeedback and then you just say it was
the biofeedback that did it
because before medical medium everybody
was doing medical medium biofeedback
just left everybody sick
it's amazing what happens if and look
no disrespect to biofeedback
practitioners
no disrespect it's just that
if you don't say it like it is you can't
save
somebody's life if i'm gonna be all
like trying to be friends with every
single person i'm gonna be friends with
the biofeedback people i better be
friends with the green tea people i
better be friends with the coffee enema
people i better be friends with the
zeolite people
i better be friends with the water
ionizer people i just better be friends
and f everybody else if anybody who's
really sick
like through them it doesn't matter
because even though i know
what we need to do to get better let me
stay friends with everybody
so don't step on any toes
and then and then it's make or break you
know what it is it's break
that means somebody goes down when
they're really sick
really sick i've seen biofeedback take
them down
when they're really sick
i've seen rife machines
aggravate the heck out of someone's
nervous system
when they're that low and going down
all those things are for people who
aren't sick enough yet to know how bad
they are
all those things are people for you know
fulvic acid
fovic mineral supplements are for people
who aren't sick enough yet
to know what it's to to know what it's
like to be on the edge and then you do
one wrong move and then you're down
one wrong move and then you're screwed
and then you're down that's
that's what that stuff's for coffee
enemas are for people who don't know
what it's like
to be on that edge when people are
really sick that's when you can tell the
story
that's when you know what works or
doesn't work when people are on the edge
and all of a sudden they get the coffee
enema and boom it takes them down and
guess what no one hears about it
no one hears about it oh okay no one
knows what took that person down
that person's gone see you later just
forget about that person
that's how it works so it's just unless
when you're on that
that life or death you're really sick
and you start doing all the wrong stuff
oh you go down
quick but when you're not so sick or not
sick at all you can do give me another
coffee enema
and i'll even drink some coffee too give
me another coffee enema
and i'll drink some coffee and coffee as
well oh give me another bad supplement
sure and give me something else give me
some bio feedback as well
because i'm not sick enough yet to know
that that's not good not going to really
help
but when you're sick and you're on that
edge that's when your man or mouse
the stuff you're using is man or mouse
that's when the stuff you're using is
make or break
that's what it matters that's when oh my
god
when you're somebody really struggling
you got the mecfs
you already had too much blood taken
from you you've been to the lyme doctor
other doctors the other doctors and then
you do the wrong things and you go
downhill while your family's watching
you go downhill and you're going down
down down down
and one more coffee enema and you're
like done
a little bentonite clay diatomaceous
earth particles
a little zeolite a little whatever that
doesn't help you and you're down
down but when you're not sick you can
play in that game world
you got a little acne maybe your energy
is not that strong you're seeing
all your functional medicine doctors
okay i'll try coffee enema
okay you know i'll try this okay i'll
try that no i'm kind of okay not so bad
i'm trying to figure it out
if you're not if you're there you can
play in the game of that i'll still do
my green tea
i'll do my kombucha tea which turns your
blood into straight acid
i'll do my kombucha tea i can get away
with it i'm really not sick
i'm really not sick but i know i'm not
right but i'm really not sick i can do a
little list and i can do a little that
but man when you're sick you do that
baking soda you dump all that
sodium bicarbonate inside of you and you
have some some bentonite clay
and you dump some caffeine in you and
you go
down boom and you go down
and that's the difference
and you dump a whole bunch of oil in you
let me do that cleanse that's a whole
bunch of olive oil
let me do that and then you go down let
me do a whole sodium bicarbonate
thing now let me try that let me try a
bunch of neem oil and then do let me put
a whole bunch of essential oils
in and it actually ingests it
let me do oh i have an essential oil
person coming and they told me i can
swallow this
swallow this essential oil because it'll
really help me
and you're just gone because when you're
on the edge all it takes
is the stupid things yeah and it'll take
you out
what's wrong with bentonite clay tears
the crap and destroys the crap out of
your intestinal tract
it does rips it to shreds and scars it
not supposed to be consumed
exactly and zeolites
zeolites are bad because what's happened
is they unearth
the dangerous zeolites the the unedible
ones
and they're manufactured in the same
facilities they've been dusted
okay it wasn't like that years ago
but it's like that now so
you're not doing well all it takes is
a bad zeolite situation you're down i
don't care what company it is
because they're cross-contaminated now
they're cross-contaminated
but who cares
who cares if somebody goes down
like zeolite never even removes any
metals from the brain
or liver anyway
but who cares if somebody goes down see
you later
bye bye next sucker
next sucker
anyway let's talk about
electricity in the brain too a little
bit we'll talk about that we're going to
let's talk about the cleanse
for a couple of minutes let's do that
you guys were day three heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge
good to see you guys
i'm glad and if you're seasoned you'll
know what i'm talking about if you're
not seasoned
it's just a learning experience right
but but if your season you know what's
up
cleanse the heel right here incredible
book heavy metal detox cleanses in here
page 179 pick one up when you can okay
it's so inexpensive at amazon right now
this book specifically
that it costs more to print it so
there's there's no money to be made on
this this is costing more to print it
it's for people so they can heal bottom
line
so yeah someone who just asked what do
you think about fulvic acid just please
re-watch this from the beginning if
you're on facebook or youtube watch it
from the beginning i just talked about
it
definitely robinson says i'm seasoned i
think i'm sure you are
i'm sure you are um cheryl
i did the fish oil bentonite clay my god
diatomaceous earth oh my god apple cider
vinegar
zeolites l-carnitine coffee enemas
edta the mps chelation
and anal chelation for years thank god
you set me on the right path
it's a nightmare but that's how the
system's rigged it's rigged
it's rigged like that it's the saddest
thing i've ever seen out there
and they just wait for new suckers and
new suckers and new suckers and it
doesn't matter who got hurt by anything
who cares
who cares so
i totally understand i do and there's a
bigger list than that and i'm sure you
did it i'm sure you i bet you you forgot
a few things that are on that list
i bet you you forgot definitely so we're
talking about
the whole thing with depersonalization
by the way guys this toxic heavy metals
depersonalization
the personal toxic heavy metals
okay live in us rent free in our brain
courtesy of the industries
right the industries need us sheeple
they need us dumbed down metals are
ignored
by all the industries especially big
pharma because big pharma has all the
metals
in the pharmaceuticals it's
a way and technique to dumb people down
metals
aren't in pharmaceuticals by the way to
help us they don't have to be in a
pharmaceutical
they're in pharmaceuticals to hurt us
to keep us sheeple and dumb down there's
a bigger mission up there in the sky i'm
not talking about the doctors not
talking about the doctors that
go to medical school and don't know
what's happening and they just
they just they're there to help you
they're there to help you
they're there to put your bones back
together after bad car crash
they're they're they're there to help
you because we were taught to eat
wrong and we were taught to take care of
ourselves wrong so all of a sudden when
an organ that can be replaced by science
and research
that did a great job with our surgeons
and teaching our surgeons and our
surgeons learning along the way right
we can get something done we can get a
life-saving surgical technique
absolutely i know surgeons
and yeah definitely
right but they're trained in a system
that has
its limits so chronic illness is growing
exponentially
and it's a sick system and people are
getting sicker and sicker and sicker and
no one's trained in all that
so really we're all stuck we're stuck
there
and but oh don't worry we can rely on
all of our functional medicine doctors
and alternative medicine or for sure
we're gonna they're just gonna they'll
take more blood and more blood and more
blood and they'll bleed us to death
so we lose our immune systems
the system is is rigged
doctors are trained to keep you sick too
they
pull all that blood out of you pull all
that blood out of you
and then if you get a smart doctor an
alternative
you know movement they'll they'll put
you on a coffee animal routine
which is disastrous maybe they'll
recommend some diatomaceous earth some
bentonite clay
some fish oil right and some other
things too
taboo along with your vitamin d which is
good for you
along with your curcumin which is good
for you
and maybe they'll tell you to do some
celery and sorry juice to be keeping you
together
while there's all this bad stuff you're
being told to do and nobody will know
it's a celery juice keeping
keeping your ass together while all the
bad stuff is trying to take you down
and then when you do go down just blame
the celery juice
you guys check this out when you can
um 51 off amazon.com us 16.99
you won't be disappointed 75 recipes
over 200 symptoms and conditions the
heavy metal detox cleanses in here
go to the library if you want get it for
free
good good elaborating it won't make a
difference for me
get it for free at the library won't
make a difference for me it's it's it
costs more to print it
for what amazon's selling it for what
they're selling it for just just
just know it's a medical textbook it's
loaded with information
and you won't be disappointed heavy
metal detox cleanse is critical it's one
of the cleanses in here
chris good to see you michelle l good to
see you
all right let's do it let's work on the
cleanse a little bit we got stuff to
talk about you guys
lemon water why is lemon water so
important let me go find my knife
why is lemon water so important
i mean you guys know by now right
extremely alkaline that's one reason
another reason calcium that's
bioavailable
like no other is okay so this brings the
calcium back into your teeth
the calcium back into your bones
critical right
the other thing is it's antiviral
antibacterial that's a great one right
there
this is all good information right and
then
it's when it's in its raw state raw
state it's a cleanser it flushes the
liver cleanses
cleans the liver body of toxins
you can't do it hot you can't
do this in hot water you can have herbal
tea with lemon in it with hot water and
honey
at the end of the day or in the middle
of the day or any time you want right
but first thing in the morning you want
to flush it with living
living fluid that comes from here
barbara says i am allergic to lemon and
limes
now this is just to say you could be
your own detective
okay so a friend of mine said that one
time and
i asked my friend i said well what
happens when you
have lemon somehow do you like fresh
from a lemon like this a little water do
you swell up
does your throat close you can't breathe
do you need an epipen
do you get rushed to the hospital does
something funny happen
in your mouth you know what what happens
my friend was like no no i go because
that's an allergic reaction
and my friend was like no no i went to a
doctor they did food out food
sensitivity tests it was on the list
with 50 other things
i said well then you're not allergic
because those things are inaccurate and
they don't work
those tests don't work but if you're
having a reaction
then yeah you're allergic if you're
having a reaction so i always tell
people
be your own detective if you're having a
reaction you're allergic
but i told my friend if it was because
it was on a food sensitivity test
you're not allergic
lemon cleans out the bugs
cleans out the garbage but what the good
point the whole
the whole thing too if you get hives
from something you're doing that's
healthy
you're flushing the liver so if you're
doing if you get a hive because you
drink
lemon water oh you just flush that liver
of a lot of poison so it takes time
you do smaller dosages of things and
then the next thing you know you don't
get hives anymore and you flush out all
that poison flesh out all that stuff
that's something to think about too
meera says my son is allergic to cats
and dust mites i believe it
would i would i always recommend ask
your doctor what's right for you but i
always recommend when you start cleaning
up
get ready to get rid of the gluten get
rid of the eggs get rid of the dairy
when you get rid of those things right
and you clean that out at least you
start with that
what happens is all of a sudden the
animal allergies start to disappear
and the dust mite allergies start to
disappear
because the overload's not there
freely ashley says tests are bogus they
are lies my doctor told me i was
allergic to apples ridiculous
that's how those tests work those tests
are actually here here's the thing too
freely ashley check this out one thing
that
to to remember is this right
when all those food sensitivity tests
came about
it was done on the not knowing what
causes chronic illness
right not knowing what causes
hashimoto's rna
any kind of symptom condition migraines
depression anxiety whatever it is that
somebody has trigeminal neuralgia
tingles numbness vertigo dizziness
all kinds of stuff tremors whatever tick
spasms right aches and pains
fatigue problems with your feet problems
at your back because
all that mystery stuff is a mystery so
all of a sudden what food sensitivity
guys have the answer with all their food
sensitivities
they have the answer they don't even
know why anybody's sick they don't know
viruses cause all these things they
don't know what metals are doing they
don't even know metals what they'll hear
about metals now from
all the years and all the medical medium
books have gone around teaching people
about metals but
but they don't really know that it was
built on a system where we don't know
why anybody's sick so let's just try
this
it's like okay that's why they'll say
you're allergic to apples and you're not
so lorena good to see you see you guys
coming on
big health with liz is here too i'm
tick-tock
gene my skin tests for allergies
are accurate skin tests
so the other thing too is skin problems
right you know you mean skin tests when
these tests they did the test on your
skin
for allergies look i can tell you this
okay
allergies develop because of a toxic
stagnant sluggish liver
stagnant sluggish liver that's toxic
a liver filled with strep a liver filled
with
ebv a liver filled with all kinds of
metals the liver filled the pesticides
herbicides fungicides petrochemicals
liver filled the plastics liver filled
with all kinds of different toxic
chemicals
fragrances fill up in the liver lots of
fragrances when that liver just starts
to get overloaded overloaded man
you'll get all kinds of allergies and
they'll play they'll be playing allergy
games on skin tests
blood tests to the cows come home you'd
be like okay wait a minute
need my allergy shots now for this need
my allergy shots for that
meanwhile until that liver gets cleaned
up and things start getting out of your
system
and you start getting rid of some foods
that contribute to that whole
whole problem like the eggs and the
dairy products and all that and the
gluten you start getting all those and
you can make sure
they're gone gone you rid them then
you'll see the allergy problems go away
it's why you developed them
at some point to begin with because the
liver just got so
loaded up now children's livers are
loaded up right off the running
and metals are a big part of it bugs too
dr fun good to see you good to see you
so here we are we made some lemon water
why is lemon water important hydration
is critical we're at day three of the
heavy metal cleanse
heavy metal cleanse the metal detox
cleanse challenge we're day three and
it's important to
to be able to flush whatever is coming
out in the morning whenever it gets
baggaged up by your liver throughout the
night it's important to flush
and get that out of our system it's
critical to flush that and get it out of
our system you guys
so we're doing the lemon water to get
that to flush out that's how important
that is
the lemon water is hydrating on a level
that's different than other things this
is really hydrating
it's activated that's activated
bioavailable and activated
dino rubio good to see you you know so
this is important the lemon water is a
big part of how we do the cleanse so
let's go
15 to 30 minutes after the lemon water
we move on to some celery
juice so we'll run a little celery juice
really quick
i didn't have mine yet today so it would
be great to have some here
you don't want hot water for your lemon
like i said you'll kill the lemon
you'll kill the lemon you kill the lemon
and then
you ruin what it can do for you it has
to be alive
it has to be a lot of you guys on the
celery juice thing giving you
forewarning now
do not add anything to your celery
juice don't add anything to your celery
juice
important piece of information spread a
little celery real quick
can you freeze the lemon juice if you
have to
yes if you have no other choice yes
use it quickly don't let it defrost and
become yucky
and sit too long
but if you have to the good news citrus
has grown
in places around the world where you get
real bad frosts so
lemons the lemon tree has adapted
so that means if you freeze the lemon
juice
it's not totally foreign
16 to 32 ounces not in hot water
it could be in warm water if you really
want
warm water but room temp
it's fine could be cold water too if you
wanted to
it's all right if anybody just got on
right here
okay you guys if anybody just got on
here
we're we're day three of the heavy metal
detox plunge challenge we're talking
about
metals causing a lot of problems with
your brain
with our brains everybody's brain
metals live rent free in your in your
brain in your head
rent free courtesy of the industries
they're there to keep us dumbed down
the metals are purposely
put inside of us we get no education
about metals
why do you think it took the hundred
thousand
250 000 500
000 child and baby
to die from lead poisoning and paint
chips
for them to recognize lead being bad
because they don't want people knowing
metals are really bad
the industries don't want people to know
that
everybody's got mental problems they're
getting worse and worse and worse ocd
depersonalization
bipolar that's what's happening out
there
metals are causing it alzheimer's
dementia
[Music]
you wouldn't believe how many people who
are aging are losing
their minds you wouldn't believe
how many people that are aging are
losing their minds
you wouldn't believe it
[Music]
so much so it's it it's just
unbelievable
[Music]
[Applause]
losing their minds because of toxic
heavy metals
that's why cold white spring how are you
today
[Music]
so yeah
juicing a little celery just a couple
quick tips you guys know
there might be somebody new here right
don't mix celery juice with anything
don't add anything to it
watch out for hpp in the store learn
about hpp
hpp yeah everybody says it's fine it's
another
snare it's a new technique
to pasteurize drinks that's
foreign to the cells of whatever plant
food that's being
you know consumed or juiced
they're hp peeing celery and you buy it
on the shelf you think it's fresh you
think it's raw
but there's a date on that drink you're
drinking and the date is like
two weeks from now and how's that
possible if it's freshly done
i'll tell you how it's possible it's
been pasteurized it's called hpp
high pressure pasteurization you don't
want to buy celery juice that's been
through high
high pasteurized high pressure
pasteurization
celery juice is a complete electrolyte
cools down the brain helps to cool it
down a little bit really important thing
your brain runs on electrolytes yes runs
on electrolytes right
all right we're just talking some celery
juice fun right here
let's do a little straining of some
celery juice right now
austin what's up
we're day three the medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse challenge
are you lightening the load of the
metals inside your brain and body
you gotta strain the celery juice it's
an herbal
extraction so you have to strain it
if you're sensitive because you're so
toxic which can happen so so toxic do
less i always tell you guys that do less
do less that's okay that's okay
got a celery juice okay we did 16 to 32
ounces of lemon water upon waking
right now we're doing
15 minutes 15 minutes 30 minutes later
you can then work on your celery juice
and listen you can drag this out
throughout the morning if you need to
drag it out
and then we wait a little while we do
the heavy metal detox smoothie coming up
so we'll get that done but we go
before we do the heavy metal detox movie
we'll talk a little bit about what's
happening in our brains
let's get a brain out
the thing is with fluoride treatments
i've talked about this before um
uh susan elizabeth it's amazing how you
always get 16 ounces
no no 32 ounces
[Laughter]
32 ounces not 16 ounces
32 ounces i mean 16 ounces is okay
you can do 16 ounces if you'd like don't
worry i mean you can i'm not saying you
have to do 32 ounces right
so this is important to know fluoride
treatments are a direct main line to the
brain
that's aluminum byproducts a lot of
people have aluminum byproduct built up
in their brain
a lot of it a lot of it
so what happens is that those fluoride
treatments
direct to the brain direct
if you're somebody with who's sensitive
has a neurological condition and you're
sensitive or so forth
right and you get a fluoride treatment
it can keep you in bed for weeks that's
when you feel it when you're really on
the edge
so i'd say keep those fluoride
treatments away if you had fluoride
treatments in the past
it's not the past it's in the present
that fluoride's still in your brain
stuck in the present moment right now
so it's important how metals work they
actually sit and then
sit in us for years and years to come
and here's the problem with metals
right we end up going on our high fat
high fat diets
and our high fat diets oxidize the metal
quicker
this accelerates all of our diseases
that have everything to do with the
brain
it's the high fat diet right i'm not
sitting here scolding anybody
about you know almonds today or walnuts
or
hemp seeds or sunflower seeds healthy
fats right avocado healthy fat
if you're gonna eat fat those are the
fats to eat right hemp seeds and avocado
those are the fat those are the healthy
fats to eat
some walnuts right sunflower seeds yeah
sesame tahini
right those are those are the healthy
fats if you're going to eat fats right
but even then though if you want to heal
if you really want to heal and you want
to heal quicker you've got to be careful
on how many
healthy fats you eat you don't want the
bad fats ever
but you've got to be careful on how many
healthy fats you eat
because the fats accelerate
the metal fatty acid
fats are really acidic including chicken
turkey meat fish
those fats are really acidic too really
acidic
and what it does it accelerates the
metal
byproduct that's produced from the metal
oxidizing
so all these speckles of metal from your
fluoride treatments and the pesticides
you breathe in and
everything else that you've ever had
from the chemtrails coming out of the
sky
to the air fresheners and perfumes
colognes to the
cleaning products to the medical
treatments to everything that you've had
in your life that built up metals to sit
inside your brain
to give you anxiety depression
depersonalization
focus and concentration issues adhd
right autism okay memory loss dementia
alzheimer's parkinson's wilson's disease
right
and even even without all that let's
just say just
emotionally triggered really easy right
emotionally triggered all of that medals
eating disorders bulimia
anorexia other eating disorders that
aren't as severe
and still severe okay
that's the metals and then all the fats
in our diet
what it does is it rots the metal quick
it starts to oxidize it so it rusts
fats rust the metals in the brain
so your condition worsens as time goes
on
and then the short circuit the
electrical panel gets short-circuited
and that's when that electrical panel
gets
zonked bonked out electricity is running
through the brain your brain's made of
electricity
all the thoughts and everything all that
electricity surging through the brain
and it's hitting all these metal
deposits and byproduct that's oxidized
it's hitting it and then that's what's
happening
some people it's so bad if they go into
mania manic moments
some people they're up and down they're
all over the place some people got the
bipolar going some people just have the
continual brain fog going
some people have all the the above some
people just have a little bit of it
some people have some adhd some people
just have a hard time focusing
some people have migraines from it but
whatever it is it all
happens it's all because those metals
live in there rent free
and is that electricity circulating
electricity circulating i showed you
guys this right
i showed you guys this so that
electricity is circulating right
okay and that pencil is a neuron inside
the brain i showed you that right
yesterday it's a neuron
inside the brain right and you got metal
in the middle of that neuron so when
that electrical impulse comes down like
here's the electrical impulse it's
coming down
that's your electricity because you're
thinking of thought you're like hey you
know what i gotta focus on this
paperwork right now
i can't my brain fog so bad i can't
focus or i'm getting really emotional i
can't explain it like i'm so emotional
right now i just i can't
it's like a sadness or i'm just i want
to scream i don't know what it is
well that neuro that that electrical
impulse has come down
and it's hitting the metal if you if
it's ocd
it's bouncing off the metal that means
the deposit is in a spot in the brain
where it's a larger deposit
and that electrical impulse is coming
down it's hitting the metal and bouncing
back up
and slamming into another another
electrical impulse
and that's ocd but you can have a
combination of ocd and also
also everything else too metal all
through the brain
savannah says so why someone will go
bipolar
some other autism what else affect the
manifestation of disorder
so as far as manifestation goes i'm not
sure exactly what you mean by the
manifestation but
but as far as like how it works for some
people i'll give you a little bit
of a tidbit here okay this is the
midline canal right
there's a little there's a little canal
that goes in the center of the brain
right
left hemisphere right hemisphere that
fills up with metal when you're a child
so all those medical treatments when
we're a child that children are forced
into to go to school and stuff all the
medical treatments
fills up that canal with all that
mercury
fills up the canal with all that
aluminum and mercury right there
so we get right off the running when
we're children another thing too utero
utero
sperm and utero when we're a baby
we get all that mercury in us too right
here
right then especially when pregnant
women are
pushed into medical treatments while
they're pregnant right
and so so then the baby's
already developing with metal in the
brain all this determines whether it's
going to be autism to some degree or a
larger degree how much mercury how much
aluminum
what's happening there how much adhd
what's the difference between something
that's going to be
mania to something that's going to be
different that something's just going to
be depression
something is just going to be focused
and concentration but we got a
fighting spirit when we're young we got
a fighting will because we're trying to
thrive so what happens human nature is
when you're a child you have this you
have this automatic
bodies the body is programmed to thrive
so you can grow as fast as possible and
as healthy as possible
so it's overriding a lot of what the
metal causes
but sometimes it doesn't override it
enough
and this is just some of the ways we get
heavy metals and we get them in every
way
i said like the carpets carpet cleaning
services that come in
saturate us with toxic heavy metals
perfumes colognes every time you smell
perfume you got metal
inside your body that's why the heavy
metal detox smoothie is so important
that's why the heavy metal cleanse is so
important once in a while to do
because we're just surrounded by metal
you go into a store you're breathing an
air freshener plus cologne plus perfume
plus scented candles
you go down the aisle in the grocery
store that has all the conventional
cleaning products
believe it or not you go down the aisle
in the non-conventional cleaning product
the more natural stuff
that stuff's saturated metal too in many
ways
you get it in the water you get it in
the air you get at the coffee shop you
get it at your coffee house
the mosquito spray coming down i talked
about that the other day
the mosquito spray coming down right now
there
there's a deal with the mosquito spray
companies
and the governments
just spray everybody dump it out of the
sky
it's never gotten rid of one mosquito
it never kills off the mosquitoes
but they but so what's happening is like
our governments pay the chemical
companies
to slowly exterminate us
that's what they do and they use their
tax money
that's what they do so they fill up all
their planes with mosquito spray
from from you know courtesy of the
chemical companies
our tax dollars pay and they
dump mosquito spray dangerous lethal
mosquito spray on us they never kill off
the mosquitoes
mosquitoes are always there they can go
by and dump all that spray
to exterminate us but the mosquitoes
will still be there flying around
you'll still be like mosquito
so the industries are wired into
that right now right now they're dumping
mosquito spray everywhere in the united
states all over
every single town and city they're just
dumping it dumping it dumping it
right now all over dumping it nobody's
permission don't bring it on your
children your babies dumping on
everybody
they won't kill a single mosquito with
it but they're just dumping and dumping
and dumping it
to make money and and and
courtesy extermination services for
human people
for humans i don't know about aliens
walking around
from other planets and other solar
systems and galaxies
maybe they're not affected by it if you
believe in that or not i mean i don't
know if you guys believe in that or not
maybe you maybe don't it's another
discussion someday
i know some of you guys are like i know
that's happening well maybe we can talk
about it someday and we can find out
but then the conditions and symptoms
happen the asthma really happens the
asthma gets really bad
other problems or children's asthma gets
really bad other people's conditions get
really bad
you can when that mosquito spray comes
down on everybody your neurosis
psychosis ocd can get worse and worse
and worse
everything can get worse and worse and
worse they do it every year
they dump it on everybody and that's all
metal and metal and
metal and neurotoxic methyl metal
conditions and symptoms depend on where
the metal is in the brain is the metal
in the frontal lobe
is the metal sitting on the optic nerve
it's the metal in the pituitary area
it's the metal in the hypothalamus it's
the metal in the brain stem
is the metal where's the metal how much
metal and where and how much
and what kind of metal is it mercury's
aluminum is a little bit of arsenic
is it a little bit of lead what kind of
metal is going on and they mix
and they mix and then electricity hits
the metal left and right hits the metal
left and right
they just michelle l said they just
sprayed here last week a lot of people
90 michelle 99 99
of all people don't know they're even
being sprayed on have no idea
don't have a clue they don't even know
what's happening they're just being
sprayed on when they're doing their
cookouts at night
they're sprayed on during the fourth of
july especially sprayed on then they're
just sprayed spray spray spray spray
and the symptoms get worse someone's be
like you manifested it
you manifested that symptom it must be
something you're doing wrong
because your neurologist says you're
fine right
so depending on where the metal is by
the way if you guys just got on here do
you have cleans the heel
you guys should have it it should be in
your own personal
reading room in your apartment in your
house
it should be there it's a medical
textbook
it's got incredible information it's 51
off amazon.com us get it to bookstore
somewhere else book depository
overseas i know we got a lot of people
that are everywhere around the world
right now
yeah so yeah and
i mean check it out check it out follow
me on me we by the way
and subscribe here on youtube subscribe
if you can
give me a thumbs up if you like it if
you hate it
give me a thumbs up anyway
if you hate it give me a thumbs down
i'll take a thumbs down
i'll take a thumbs down i'm used to it
it's all right
it won't hurt my feelings but i'm glad
you're here anyway
all right electricity runs down that
neuron
hits the metal deposit and now
you're in ocd land ocd
that ocd can get rough i read incredible
comment on youtube
i think it's marie maria is it maria
right on youtube
and she talked about her ocd
i mean it's real it's real
so you guys are incredible so we're oh
you guys are incredible so we're here
let's make the heavy metal detox
smoothie we're talking about a lot of
cool stuff
you could have mild ocd you can have
severe ocd you could have some really
crazy ocd
it could be debilitating in such a way
and god bless people for surviving it
because it's really harsh
it's really really harsh but
heartbreaking really
it's it's heartbreaking to me people go
through what they go
through there's also mild ocd which is
brutal mild ocd is brutal
you can have the mild disorders there's
a lot of different rights that's soci
let's do mild depersonalization people
are numb
numbed out checked out you know why is
my husband so checked out all the time
you know why is my friend so checked out
all the time
what's with the checkout how come when i
talk to my friend my friend doesn't hear
me really and i have to repeat myself it
over and over again and how come when i
talk to my husband
my husband has my husband doesn't hear
me i have to repeat myself over and over
again
i don't even know if he understands me
or she understands me i don't know if my
wife understands me my husband
understands i don't my girlfriend
understands me i don't know if my
boyfriend understands me
metal's really getting away
so i got some wild blueberries right
here i'm going to put two cups in here
let's get some wild blueberries in here
i'm gonna put this over here
did you guys notice that the wild
blueberry is so
powerful that it just
it'll stain anything and everything it's
ruined a lot of my clothes
with stains everywhere right the wild
blueberry
the wild blueberry is is so potent right
it's so important it'll it'll really do
some serious stuff you know
it's it's crazy
so i just put the frozen wild
blueberries in here i'm also going to
put the wild blueberry juice right this
is the wyman's wild blueberry juice
if you don't have frozen wild
blueberries just get the juice
do two to four ounces of the juice
i'm loving the cleanse amazing
the heavy metal detox smoothie gives me
headaches why
i would be your own detective that's the
only time you've ever had a headache
or are you coming down with the flu
you're coming down with something
at the same time you start at the
cleanse
did you already have headaches nothing
else gives you a headache you can eat a
vegan pizza not have a headache but you
have a heavy metal detox smoothie and it
gives you a headache
i just want you to be a detective your
own detective right
if for some reason you are experiencing
that from
the heavy metal detox smoothie lower the
dose
make a tiny one or put tiny amounts of
everything in it
and see how it is if you're that toxic
super toxic but the heavy metal detox
smoothie
removes toxins without shaking them up
so it doesn't give people headaches
because it removes the toxins it doesn't
shake up the toxins
but what you can do is
you can do smaller smaller smaller
amount you can try that
i mean it's amazing you're trying to do
it you're doing it so i support you in
any way you're doing it you've got to
use a tiny amount
you can always try and that's what i
would say
i've i've told uh i've told people who
also
are sensitive in general that they start
with a little bit of everything is fine
and that there's nothing wrong with a
lot of people are afraid to do stuff too
because they're sensitive you're like
afraid to try something you think oh
do just a little bit and then you'll
build up the confidence as you go along
right
that's the uh vimergy wild blueberry
powder
if you don't have another thing too like
what creates headaches
well bananas and wild blueberries aren't
going to create headaches
but but uh metals do
viruses do caffeine does chocolate does
so chocolate so that's the person who
says well i get headaches we've been
doing that well did you have chocolate
the night before do you do caffeine at
all do you do green tea at all do you do
kombucha tea which has caffeine in it
you're doing caffeine caffeines give
people headache and withdrawal from
caffeine gives your head so if you're
starting the heavy metal detox cleanse
and you just quit caffeine without
realizing it
you might be getting withdrawal too
these are all the things in case you're
in
you know in case you haven't looked at
everything
um i'm going to put the if you don't
have the frozen wild blueberries
you can just do the vimergy wild
blueberry powder
if you have to and just throw that in
you just do a little bit and just do a
tablespoon
and you go that route right tablespoon
or a little more if you want that's
bimrgy.com via
victor i am as mary e r g dot com
what i love about vimergy you guys know
it's one of not just the quality and
everything else they're the only
supplement company
supplement company right
that refuses to allow manufacturing
to put in a small percentage of
something nobody knows they're getting
in every other supplement so if you're
you're if you're you like the fulvic
acid or fulvic mineral supplement
there's a small percentage of something
in there you don't know
shouldn't be in there if you like a
zeolite product
there's a small percentage of something
in there shouldn't be in there if you
like
a diatomaceous earth product if you like
that then there's a certain thing that
nobody knows if you like a bentonite
clay
there's a certain percentage of
something that shouldn't be in there if
you like some other kind of vitamin or
v complex out there there's a certain
something that shouldn't be in there
i'm just saying and some of those
products i would never touch with a
1000 foot pole diatomaceous earth
particles chlorella i wouldn't touch
i wouldn't touch corel you guys saw what
happened yesterday when i was the
when i was the wild blueberry like
removing heavy metals and then i was
chlorella
and i knocked over the blender and
everything just fell apart
but vimergy doesn't have those hidden
things
hidden sinisterly
hidden away they refuse to do it they're
like it's not gonna happen they're like
nope
not gonna happen not for us every other
stuff every supplement company in the
world
they got they got a certain amount of
something in there you guys don't know
about that's in there it's not listed on
the ingredients
and vemma just said we're not doing it
we're not doing it no way
no way that's a big deal i'm not
sponsored by these guys it's just great
stuff
see i'm friends with the guys i know
these guys i make i try to make friends
with any supplement company i can that
puts out good stuff because if i make
friends with them
then i could kind of like be in touch
and be like
did you guys change something
and that's why i ditched the pacific the
the specific spirulina i ditched it
i like the imagery stuff pacific
spirulina they never contacted me back
i tried to become friends with them
because
i was seeing problems and they never
contacted me back
so i like making friends with any
supplement company can that's putting
out good stuff so i can be like
dude is something changing because i
need my people to be okay
and vimergy you know
you know they're like they're really
special people
anyway you guys know i'm working with
wyman's though i'm not sponsored by them
but i'm working with wyman's and they're
they're amazing people too
and they call me back
that's how that's what happened you know
like it's like if you're gonna like
if you're gonna like make sure stuff is
right
and not changing and stuff is incredible
you want
you want communication and then
friendships develop through that
communication and it's good because it's
like okay
keep everything at the top grade at the
top notch the highest quality possible
and hey
it even should be like this and all
right so
i put some spirulina in here let's talk
about spirulina a little bit spirulina
is light years from chlorella
chlorella disastrous
disastrous just letting you know
chlorella doesn't remove toxic heavy
metals and
if it does it will drop it and and and
basically drag it
that means if it ever does unloot so
here's how it works
so if you're told by your practitioner
your naturopath your chiropractor
you're told by your influencer who's
saying i'm taking chlorella because i'm
getting metals out
metals they only know about now because
of medical medium information for 35
years
and if you some influence or if some
chiropractor or some nd
or some functional medicine doctor says
here's a chlorella product or
you find a chlorella product out there
somewhere right
and you're like it's and you read about
it's like yeah chlorella takes out
metals
yeah if it ever did take out metal
here's what happens with chlorella
it drags the metal and worsens the
disease or condition
it drags it and drops it that's what
chlorella does
drags it and drops what would i have
against chlorella what would i
if it worked i'd be like chlorella
chlorella i'd be like everybody should
be on chlorella if it worked i'd be like
chlorella
here for the thousandth time i'm gonna
show you chlorella you guys
like i show you everything else what
would what would i have against it it
doesn't work
it doesn't work it's disastrous
but that's not why i hate chlorella the
most
in fact that it drags the metal if it
does pick it up
and worsens the disease or condition or
symptom like anxiety or depression or
anything
right that's not that's one but that's
not the worst reason why
the worst reason why is because bacteria
that's
bad thrives in chlorella
spirulina is antibacterial
antibacterial chlorella
is bacterial
that's why many people have been like
and attached to their toilet for weeks
because of getting poisoned by chlorella
because it's not even tested properly
because it's a magnet for bad bacteria
that means it feeds the bad stuff inside
you let me take my chlorella and feed
every bad bacteria and bug i got inside
of me
and make sure i get sicker down the road
that's chlorella
you know what sucks you guys check this
out
you know what really really you know
it's really hard
and i understand i sympathize i really
do
just hear me out if you got a minute if
you just got one second okay
if i was a doctor
and i was and i spent 10 years pushing
chlorella
you think i would want to be told i'm
wrong
or that i've been giving my patients
for 10 years no i'm going to fight for
it
and i'm going to stand my ground because
i am not going to be mud
if i was a healer or naturopathic doctor
out there
or chiropractor
if i was an influencer
that was pushing something for a few
years
and i told my whole crowd this is what
gets chlorella chlorella chlorella
even if i learn the truth it's hard to
be like
oh i was wrong
it's hard to just chalk it up and be
like
a chiropractor that's like uh i've been
giving you chlorella
all these years telling you what's good
um
i'm probably wrong i'm hearing and i'm
wrong i'm not gonna
admit it here's chlorella here you go
here you go here's clarella here you go
same thing with anything same thing with
all the different stuff if you're
been pushing coffee enemas for 20 years
in your practice
coffee enemas are absolutely disastrous
disastrous
they just kill the the nervous system
weaken the immune system
destroy the nervous system coffee enemas
are a tragedy
right and if i was a practitioner and
i'm telling people to eat coffee animals
for 10 years
you think i'm gonna stop and say i was
wrong
no way meaning like
a lot won't maybe some will
is coffee enema bad too horrible
horrible
and i simplify i do i do if i was wrong
i would say it i screwed up i'm wrong
but i'm lucky because i'm not the one
calling the shots
i'm not that doctor that's hearing
misinformation and then giving you some
coffee enema and saying it's good for
you
i got my source my source is not
a man my source is not meaning men
on the planet a human being on the
planet my source is not
my source is not a human being who makes
mistakes
and then says yeah you can do chlorella
yeah you can do
you know mercury fillings in the 1920s
30s 40s 50s 60s 70s and 80s
90s 2000s you can do mercury fillings
my source isn't that so so that's the
difference
but i get it when you don't have that
source
where i get the information from since i
was age four if you don't have that
source
you can make the mistakes and you could
be giving out coffee
enemas for years and then if you're even
if you're even told hey that's really
bad because
your stomach buffers the caffeine to at
least protect you a little bit but when
you get coffee the other end like the
coffee animal the other end up
that you have nothing to buffer it and
it goes straight to your nervous system
and it starts to annihilate your vagus
nerve so when you do coffee enemas
you're doing vagus nerve damage
and then that chiropractor that doctor's
gonna be like i'm not gonna
i can't stop i just i just spent 15
years invested in coffee enemas giving
all my patients coffee enemas
and i can't tell them to stop i can't
say i can't admit i was wrong
i wrote a an e-book about coffee enemas
how could i admit i'm wrong no you fight
for it
who cares about the people i get it
okay let's make the smoothie let's get
two bananas in there you guys
but there are some good doctors that say
you know what i heard that coffee enemas
are bad
i'm gonna stop doing that i heard
that diatomaceous diatomaceous earth
particles are bad i heard that chlorella
is not the best spirulina's better
i heard pacific spirulina
is garbage
and i'm gonna tell my patients there's
some incredible doctors that do do that
don't get me wrong
but no one's held accountable for all
the mistakes in alternative medicine
ever
i got cilantro in here we're trying to
make the smoothie and i i'm talking
yours off i feel really bad now
you know
when you're really sick coffee enema
will break you you won't heal from it
it will break you it will break you
it'll get you
high if you're strong enough to handle
the high that the caffeine gives you
thinking that you did something good for
yourself but if you're not strong enough
to handle that high
and you're weaker because you're injured
and sick and you're sick you're viral
and you're sick your nervous system
that coffee enema will send you down
to an early grave cilantro
poisons the heart and brain puts it into
shock cilantro
goes into the brain and helps to remove
toxicated metals it's got phytochemical
compounds attached
to the mineral salts trace mineral salts
when you combine that with the wild
blueberry and you've got the spirulina
in there
and that's the demergie spirulina by the
way right you got the spirulina in there
um if you don't like the taste of that
cilantro that's because you've got a lot
of metals
got a lot of metals in you let's put
some orange in here
get a little orange in here you guys
some oh it's a juicy orange
whoa it's a juicy orange
guys we're day three of the heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge
i hope you guys are having a little fun
and hope
what about the deworming fad going
around you called it
it's a fad goes around and around again
the deworming fad around and around
and around again 1980
deworming worried about warming 1990
it's worms that are making us sick it's
worms
that's why you have fatigue night 2000
oh the worm cleanses again goes round
and round let's hear some products
try to get worms out 2010 the worm thing
again here we go
here we go the warm thing again 2020 the
worm thing again
meanwhile that's not why you have ra
hashimoto's thyroiditis that's not why
you're sick with fatigue and
see it and that's not why you're sick
with all kinds of problems that's why
you don't have
that's why you have it's not why you
have pcos and endometriosis it's not why
you have eczema psoriasis it's not why
you're sick with migraines
it's not why you're sick with anything
it's a money-making scam comes around
and around and around and all the poor
saps that got neurological lyme
and multiple sclerosis and ra and lupus
and all these headaches and problems and
fatigue all get totally got this
parasitical worm thing and let's just do
a worm cleanse now
and they get screwed over once again and
they're still sick and they stay sick
do the parasite thing too all on its own
just like oh it's now the parasite
thing over and over again have you guys
been seasoned enough to see this
1980 oh maybe it's a parasite 1990 oh
it's a parasite
oh night 2 000 is a parasite actually
not in the 80s is parasite
actually no the parasite thing came off
of medical medium talking about people
having bugs in them
back in the mid 80s so teaching you know
in early 80s when i was like
like full throttle teaching people every
day about
about um people having bugs and people
having viruses and everybody's like what
little parasites no parasite
thing came out of dysentery the amoeba
that's in bad
water that's where the parasite thing
developed but then it took off after the
whole viral thing i was talking about
and then by the
early 2000s it was like we keep on
hearing about viruses for medical medium
but isn't it a parasite that we need to
be talking about and then worms
and then there you go again back to the
warm thing everybody's trying to bank
bank get you on a worm protocol
it doesn't fix your hashimoto's it won't
fix your other problems it won't fix
your hyperthyroids it won't fix your
brain fog won't fix anything
chrissy said to clarify i work in a
prison and don't have access to a
blender i need to make it at
zero three three zero how long can it
sit
in the fridge before i need to
drink it how long can it sit in the
fridge i can sit in the fridge for a
while you might need a spoon
for the smoothie because it congeals
because of the wild blueberry pectin
it couldn't it congeals right so you you
can
you can see you know you can have it in
the fridge definitely
24 well 12 hours
i probably wouldn't let it go past 12
hours i probably wouldn't let it go past
that
right these are popsicles i actually
made these popsicles
so i made some popsicles right these are
they're frozen great for kids
that's the heavy metal detox smoothie
popsicles right
love those those are just awesome okay a
little popsicle container here
and um if you check out my directory it
might have one up there
here if you want to look metameme.com
smoothies in here i got the orange in
there cilantro in there wild blueberry
spirulina barley grass juice powder
i don't think i put that in so the
emergency barley grass is better don't
do barley grass
it's gotta be coffee grass powder
removes toxic heavy metals
even if you don't do all this and you
just do a little bit of barley grass
juice powder every day
you're gonna be moving yourself forward
right the right kind right
spirulina same thing you know if people
if you don't have
the the means or the capacity to have
all the things you need
susan renee cilantro powder or juice
would be convenient
if it's still as effective as a natural
kind
cilantro in its holy form is what you
want
raw fresh in its holy form if you it is
best
not even juiced but in its holy form
when it comes down to cilantro right
you got to have the living water in
there as much as possible
to when you're about to drink it so you
keep it in the whole leaf so that one
matters when it comes down to the herb
but but you do the best you can i mean
you just do whatever you can do right
whatever you can do all right
do a little blend here
blending we're blending you guys
we're day three by the way okay just
came on here
so on tick tock i personally feel like
i've been scammed
and fell for a lot of
laugh out loud thank you for this i'm
honored you're here
a monitor here
the scamming is unreal unreal out there
um so i was just showing you the
popsicles they're for kids i mentioned
earlier
right for kids popsicles
um you can get popsicle holders like
this this is really cool
the scamming is insane out there there's
a new type of scam going on now though
it's scan medical medium information
because no one
no one in alternative medicine has like
information like if you read the medical
books if you read
the the medical books right the medical
media medical books if you read these
you'll see how much information is in
here right so what's happening is the
new scam is to take
data from these books not cite it back
to medical medium
write posts about it post it and then
they get a bunch of people commenting
like oh my god i didn't know that
and meanwhile the practitioner or the
influencer isn't even even
isn't even mentioning medical medium but
they look like a hero
because they're they're talking about
stuff you can never get anywhere else
right
and then they recommend stuff that's bad
for you
that's the new scam we're
seeing it every minute right now out
there and then the person can't heal
because they don't really know
where they're supposed to go and what
they really need and
so sad
so we got heavy metal detox smoothie
right here awesome
thing is i need a huge team of people to
keep up with it and they're just
you know
it's really hard i mean i'm writing a
book right now i'm trying to finish up a
book and hand in the manuscript to the
publisher it's already two months late
it's like i'm working till three o'clock
in the morning four o'clock in the
morning i wake up at six in the morning
i'm trying to get the book done it's
just too much going on
and you can't keep track of all the of
all the
you know the shenanigans that are
happening out there
you know anyway apples
try to do a couple apples before noon
keep the radical fats out before noon
try to keep them out try
try the best if you're somebody that
still wants to have your avocado toast
and your heavy metal detox smoothie
i welcome that but but if you want the
best out of it
what you if you want to really kick some
serious butt and get metals out quicker
do the heavy metal detox cleanse without
having anything any any fat at all in
the morning
try to be fat free where you're just
doing the smoothie you're doing your
lemon water of course you know the
rhythm and then your celery juice and
then the smoothie
and you got that the problem is with the
fats is it thickens up the blood so it
makes it harder to get metals out
even though you can still get some out
each day if that's what you do but try
to do
fats at the end of the day this way you
can get metals out all morning and
afternoon and then the fats at the end
of the day so you could do your avocado
your nuts or seeds if that's what you
live off of that's what you like
you do all that stuff then and your
olive oil whatever it is that you like
and your chicken your meat this is an
anti-animal protein or anti-plant-based
that's not what we're about you guys
know that here so everybody's
everybody's welcome this is the only
place
in the alternative health movement that
isn't on one side or the other
okay now you'll start hearing like
mimickers
imitators say that now i heard a podcast
doctor someone told me about said that
recently it's like oh my god
you were always on one side and now
you're not all of a sudden
i get it just you know taking mm info
but the point is is this is the only
place that's never been on one side or
the other
okay it's all about getting everybody
better and how to do it so if you eat
animal protein there's a way if you eat
plant-based there's a way if your
plant-based stay plant-based if you're
animal protein that's where your heart
is
stay there we can still work on it but
don't do the radical fats in the morning
have the apples before noon maybe even
if you want you don't have to cram all
that in in the morning
you can you can stretch it out have your
apples in the afternoon have your heavy
metal detox smoothie later
in the in the in the morning you know
you can stretch it out if you need to
and then at night have your meal that
you're you're eating whether you're
animal protein or your plant-based and
that's the meal you're eating
maybe even go a little further and do
one of the recipes
or two of the recipes here at night for
dinner and then be fat free
and then oh my god how much metal can
you get out then
get a lot of heavy metal out
you guys heading off to ig
heading off to ig tick-tock i'm heading
off to ig
but tick-tock i'm turning you back on
clubhouse i'm going to turn you back
on right facebook and youtube i'll see
you guys
again give me a thumbs up or whatever
you do for facebook likes or whatever
or the thumbs up and subscribe
if you can if you like the video thumbs
up
if you hate me and hate the video give
me a thumbs up anyway i don't know