I bought this right here and I looked at
it I was like you're spindly you're
skinny and spindly and small why would
you say that reason why I got the celery
juice out there all these decades is
because for chronic illness it's an
integral part of helping people recover
this machine cold press masticating
juicer with a triple auger gets the
nutrients out without damaging or
scorching the vegetable or in this case
the herb what you're making right here
is herbal medicine
the mm-1500 100 off right now you guys
know I work with the mega and everything
it is the medicine maker the reason why
is because it extracts to such a degree
and what happens with other juicers like
the basket juicers that everybody gets
suckered into is it's deficient juice
because it's not extracting enough of
the nutrients the mm 1500 extracts such
a large quantity of critical nutrients
literally leaves dust behind to that
degree almost
you're looking at really dry pulp
because of the compression how sick is
that this isn't wet and sloppy pull
people don't juice like the medical
medium Community juices people don't put
wear and tear on their juicers like the
medical medium Community does the other
juicers out there will never stand up
for that it can't handle that intensity
it's not possible that's why the mm-1500
is here it's here to handle that that's
a celery juice right there boom boom
boom
boom boom fresh off the press
[Music]
thank you