[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William the
medical Medium you're listening to the
medical medium radio show where each
week we bring the most advanced healing
information out there so you can work on
healing so you can get the things you
need so you're not trapped in all the
trendy misinformation and disinformation
that's out there that confuses everybody
and it keeps you sick for years does it
work does it not work is it working
don't know staying sick am I getting
better whatever and the whole thing
keeps on going on and on and on it's a
difficult world when it comes down to
chronic illness science and research is
behind the times with chronic illness
it's ahead of the times with so many
awesome things it really is and
including in medicine life-saving
medicine without a doubt we're we're way
ahead to where we were before but not in
chronic illness not in chronic
illness and Today's Show is about
sluggish liver sluggish liver is a term
that I've actually been using all these
decades in and and working with people
and everything sluggish liver is is
that's that's where it's derived from
this isn't fatty liver this isn't fatty
liver this is sluggish liver someone
said to me wait a minute never heard
sluggish liver yeah because that that's
that's the thing that I've been actually
trying to teach people along the way so
they know what's going on so you can
kind of see the symptoms and everything
and what's scary about sluggish liver
about the liver being stagnant and
sluggish what's spooky about that well
you can get all kinds of different
things all kinds of different illnesses
and diseases and everything else and
that's what we have to avoid our liver
gets filled up with all kinds of toxins
and poisons I'm going to go into it but
I'm also going to show you the signs so
you actually know what they are so you
could be like oh my God I have to start
taking care of my liver this is really
an important show this is one of those
shows where look if you're dealing with
a condition now this will help you if
you're not deal dealing with a condition
this will help you if you're you know if
you have a symptom or two this is going
to help everything is going to help when
it comes down to the liver with getting
rid of a sluggish liver and and a
sluggish liver isn't just about having
weight gain you can have no weight
coming on and have a sluggish liver I'm
going to talk about this this is really
an important episode without a doubt so
I want you to be uh I want you to be
comfortable get some herbal tea whatever
you need sit back and and just you know
let me let me throw it all at you so you
can say okay okay and you could sit back
and everything else let me do the work
here let me do the work and then you sit
back relax and uh let's go for the ride
fasten your seat belts though cuz this
isn't going to be a pretty this isn't
going to be a pretty show this isn't
going to be a pretty one you know the
funny thing is the symptoms and
conditions that result from a
compromised liver aren't only the ones
you would expect not the ones you would
expect so you have to always know that
the liver gives us all these different
symptoms that we're not aware of and
conditions that we're not aware of so we
have to think about that for a minute
okay so contrary to popular belief Xmen
sasis isn't a a like autoimmune
condition where the body's attacking
itself that's not what causes ecos
psoriasis see that's just one condition
that is a liver problem see the liver is
why someone has examon psoriasis it's
their liver and it's not their body
attacking the liver their body is not
attacking the liver at all but that is
one prime example that research and
science has no idea about has no idea
that xasis is literally just a liver
problem and with Xmen psoriasis it's
copper in the liver coupled with a viral
um a viral load so a lowgrade chronic
viral infection that sits in the liver
for for could be for decades starting
from childhood sitting in the liver and
what it does it feeds off a copper
releases a
dermatoxin um that dermatoxin floats to
the surface of the skin creates XML or
psoriasis or rosacea and so forth so
that's that one but see you know science
of research isn't there yet so example
so here's the deal like an overloaded
liver can cause acne too nobody knows
that part science and research is still
kind of hung up on the whole hormone
thing like it must be hormonal something
must be going on but that's not it at
all sure you can get acne breakouts
during hormonal period times in your
life whether it's puberty or menstration
or anything like that
because because the immune system drops
during anything anything happening
hormonally including a bad experience
including high stress where your
adrenals are pumping and all those
hormones are flooding through your body
from your adrenal glands you can then
get acne a week later nobody knows you
can't connect the dots that happens all
the time so it's all about the IM immune
system from dropping because of
experiences that are hormonal that lower
the immune system research and science
doesn't know that part so but a sluggish
liver leads to acne so that's a whole
another thing you know and and and just
I could go on and on and on and I think
I will and I think I will we're told
it's only hormonal like I said for skin
related but that's not true it's a sign
that that that basically there the the
liver is under some type of duress some
type of duress and with with acne when
the immune system lowers strep which
sits inside the liver and sits inside
the lymphatic vessels and everywhere
else in the body can kind of rise up and
strep causes what you know causes the
body to build up sebum oil and then you
got the acne and the whole bit and then
you got the cystic acne which is Strep
related that's why when doctors used
antibiotics in the old days and a long
time ago for the first acne cases they
were just like whoa It's Working For A
Minute exactly and then it created new
antibiotics and new antibiotics and the
strep gets resistant new antibiotics and
hey you know keep people on antibiotics
for years try to keep their strep down
they don't know it's strep they don't
know what's happening that's what I was
saying this is Advanced information so
you can be like armed so you can be
protected so you can have armor so you
can have your Shield so you can be an
expert there's nothing better than being
an expert there's nothing better than
being an expert and that's what you are
when you get all this information and
that's it you can kind of you can hold
that sword hold that Shield in the whole
bit it's important to to protect
yourself when it comes down to health
being an expert in health is really
important so so we're talking about this
mystery high blood pressure mystery high
blood pressure how about that one okay
mystery high blood pressure means they
they don't really see a big old clog
somewhere they don't see a big old clog
like in the artery like tons of plaque
buildup and and you know and even people
with plaque buildup and all that they
don't have have to have high blood
pressure at all and they don't see a
heart problem a direct heart problem so
they're thinking like you know hey wait
well you got high blood pressure it's
just probably genetic or it's just you
know maybe your father had it maybe
whatever and this is what happens or
your you know your mom had it or
whatever it is and so they go by things
like that but unless they see a direct
like clog somewhere you know that's some
arteries that are really being clogged
up and the passageways are getting more
narrow for blood flow and then the blood
pressure can go up because of that but
even with that it doesn't mean blood
pressure is up with a lot of people that
have artery and plaques and plaque
inside their their you know inside the
arteries arterial plaque so what happens
is that it's the liver that has
everything to do with high blood
pressure sluggish liver sluggish
stagnant liver mystery heart
palpitations once again sluggish
stagnant liver but in that case that
case it has a lot to do with something
viral inside the liver creating a
jelly-like substance that's the Epstein
bar virus that jelly-like substance gets
sucked out of the liver pushed up the
highway right up to the heart collects
in the valves creates heart palpitations
rhythmia ectopic heartbeat and so forth
so science of research doesn't know any
of that either and at all including the
high blood pressure thing I just said
you medical communities are unaware of
any of this so you're getting really
Advanced information out of Liver Rescue
right here if you don't have a copy of
Liver Rescue you should get a copy of a
rescue if you can't afford a copy go to
the library I see it all the time I know
I sound like a broken record but that's
how bad I want you to have the book I
want you to be able to help yourself so
we have um and in a book if you don't
have I don't know what it is if you can
get I $15 $20 but if you can get a book
get a book if you can whatever you can
do or at the library so the har
reputations Diabetes Type 2 diabetes see
what happens is science and research
thinks type two diabetes has everything
to do with nothing but sugar consumption
and you know insulin resistance from
sugar consumption they're thinking you
know pancreas gets weak A1C goes up got
type 2
diabetes um everything's wrong again
wrong wrong wrong what happens is it has
everything to do with the liver you
change your diet the liver gets better
okay you start eating better the liver
starts getting better your numbers go
down that's how it works if you keep on
eating all this bad food all this bad
food that's filled with fat and sugar
combined toiv gets burdened the liver
gets burdened the liver gets burdened
gets sluggish sluggish sluggish type two
diabetes is a sluggish liver you get
your liver a little bit better you you
lose the type two diabetes or the or the
the blood sugar issues that's sluggish
liver right there so think about that
and I mean I'm I'm going through all
these different conditions right here
which is kind of cool you know I didn't
expect that on the show I didn't expect
it I was going to go about I was going
to talk about other things about the
liver being sluggish how it works and
everything but it's I guess it's good to
actually connect the dots right here of
the conditions that sluggish liver
brings I think that that's the best way
to do it I mean I just realized it just
now I was just going to give you this
whole bunch of stuff about sluggish
liver which we're going to do which
we're still going to do but this is
really cool um I'm excited about this so
in Liver Rescue I talk all about this I
have whole section in the book on
sluggish liver it's important to know
all this stuff and I can't scratch the
surface of what Liver Rescue has in this
radio show I I know some some of you are
probably listen to radio show well I
don't need to get the book I got his
radio shows actually actually the book
is massive and the the word count is
huge and I can't even scratch a surface
it's not even possible but this is fun
so we got um we got the type 2 diabetes
so what happens with diabetes is and
I'll give you the quick rendition of it
because we'll probably do another
diabetes show down the road the quick
rendition is with type 2 diabetes is the
liver gets sluggish toxic and it's from
the high fat diet all high fat diet it
just so happens people usually eat a lot
of bad sugar with their High fats so
what does that mean bad sugar where your
hide fats it's ice cream it's fat sugar
that's just an example right there you
know milk lactose fat that's milk I mean
it's you know cheese fat sugar that's
that's what that is cheese you have
cheese to just you have fat and sugar
what that does is it creates a real
sluggish liver creates a real sluggish
liver it puts lots of fat in the
bloodstream puts poor quality sugars in
the bloodstream at the same
time and but but really you can do that
you can put you can put ice cream into
people and young people and they're not
getting type 2 diabetes they're not
getting insulin resistance because their
liver isn't sluggish yet you see how it
goes your liver starts getting sluggish
from all the junk in it from all the
garbage in it from high fat diet for
many years
you know a teenager is not on a high fat
diet for many years but when you start
getting in your 20s and you're getting
in your 30s you're still doing high fat
diets and now we're told to eat high fat
diets high protein high fat diets now
but minus the sugar as if that's the
answer if that's actually the answer
which it's not it's not in Liver Rescue
I explain the whole thing it's not the
answer I have a whole section of the
book talking about the high fat Trend
and where it came from how it started
and why it's not right and what's right
and what isn't what's wrong what's not
whatever just so you got the right
information
just so you don't waste time I mean I
don't know life is precious and when I
think about it when I think about how
precious life is and um every day is
precious every hour is precious I mean
come on face it I mean right and when I
think about wasting time on information
that that is isn't correct or doesn't
get you anywhere or you think it is but
in the end it tricks you and it's like
falls through your hand like sand and
then it doesn't get you anywhere down
the road it's really disappointing
because how much time was invested how
much money is invested whatever it is
it's really sad and and life here on
Earth is precious we need every minute
we can get so getting the real
information is the key and the one thing
you'll you'll you'll get if you're brand
new to the show is like is okay is he
selling something no I'm not selling
anything is he selling something what's
he selling is he selling a $5,000
cleanse what's he doing what's his gig
is he selling zillions of supplements no
I'm not selling anything I'm not selling
anything when I'm saying the
information's correct and it's right
information for you and everything else
what you'll find there's no there's no
marketing MLM marketing or you can buy
into a cleanse or whatever it is and get
you know I'm you know whatever it is
whatever that people are doing out there
now it's crazy it's like infomercials on
every podcast they almost can't even
stand it so when you're getting the
right information it's key it can
protect you from diabetes it can protect
you from exom and psoriasis it can
protect you from the from high blood
pressure but more than that protect you
from acne protect more than that it
doesn't waste your time it doesn't waste
your time and that's the key right here
so what happens is when somebody's
younger and they're and they're not
getting that kind of they're sluggish
they're not getting that sluggish liver
yet and let me tell you something young
people get sluggish liver too and
they're not getting that sluggish so
many are are younger they're not getting
the sluggish liver quite yet what
happens right there is they're not going
to show signs of A1C Rising they're not
going to show signs of diabetes 2
they're not going to show signs of any
of that they might see you might see
some hypoglycemia I've seen a lot of
teenagers with hypoglycemia without a
doubt without a doubt not hyper so much
but always hypo so that's a sluggish
liver starting right there all on its
own but the point is it's not you know
not not not the most normal thing it's
just yeah there there are teenagers
going through that and then people in
their 20s go through it more people in
the 30s go through it even more sluggish
liver gets worse and worse and worse you
got the fat and the sugar combinations
you fat and sugar combinations fin liver
is just like oh my God I can't take this
anymore I can't handle this anymore the
liver can think I can think it can
function it has over 2,000 chemical
functions undiscovered by research and
Science and in those 2,000 chemical
functions it it it's it's at a place
it's at a place where it you know it has
to think for you it actually has to
think for you if it doesn't think for
you it can't protect you it can't do the
best it can to give you that longer life
and we just trash our livers and that's
the whole thing
we do trash or livers I mean it's it's
that's how it works here do we do it on
purpose I I don't know if anybody really
does it on purpose even if someone
drinks I don't know if they're trashing
the liver on purpose even if someone
drinks so it's just a really really
strange situation on that whole thing
but so but basically we do trash your
livers maybe it's by default maybe it's
by just being here but either way so
that sluggish sluggish liver what
happens is it starts to get so clogged
up with
fat and it loses its glucose
reserves on top of that that's that's
what happens then the pancreas starts to
give away a little bit starts to give
away a little bit weaken a little bit
too it's really the sluggish liver that
gets you into the diabetes the type 2
diabetes but what happens is someone
starts exercising and they start shaking
up their liver and they start changing
their diet and they start taking out the
sugar and they still keep their high fat
diet but they take out the sugar their
A1C goes down and the doctor's like look
you're already getting better but
doesn't mean your liver's not sluggish
as heck and diabetes can't come back in
the drop of a hat when you eat a little
sugar what you really need to do is drop
the fat and bring healthy carbohydrates
in healthy sugars and that's how you
beat it and that's how you get rid of
your sluggish liver but that's just
diabetes that's was just a quick a quick
rendition of that real quick you know
another thing right here Seasonal
effective disorder
sad so Seasonal effective disorder
that's from a sluggish liver it's
amazing you know the in the 1980s early
1980s Seasonal effective disorder a
whole bunch of experts got together and
they crowned they got their like Crown
Glory they got their names behind
Seasonal effective disorder as if they
discovered something Seasonal effective
sorder I have a whole chapter in here
it's it's actually a joke it's like it's
it's it's not about the
seasons it's about how sick your liver
is and yeah for a lot of people and you
know in the summertime it you know their
liver does a little better you know why
they're walking a little bit more
they're eating a little bit better maybe
they ate a couple of pieces of fresh
fruit maybe they had some
berries um yeah they're getting a little
sun which helps your liver and talk
about that all the time helps your liver
and Liver Rescue I talk about it I mean
they get a little more sun but they're
helping their liver and then what about
all those people that don't have
Seasonal effective disorder their liver
is not as bad yet so they kind of tend
to do okay in the winter
but everybody you know everybody in the
winter months you know does doesn't do
that great unless they're you know
exercising and they're in the gyms and
everything else and they're taking care
of the liver a little bit and they're
eating still a little bit better and
then they can kind of but seasonal
effectives order like it was a big
Discovery unbelievable I think it's a
group of I don't know a group of doctors
or group of experts have their name on
seasonal effectiv disorder from back in
the 80s it's like oh my God yawn my God
because it's it's like when you think
about it you can't even scratch the
surface to what it really is or even get
to it not to men you get all the people
with chronic illness meaning a chronic
fatigue syndrome where it gets worse in
the winter or it even gets worse in the
summer because their nerves are inflamed
and that's the whole thing seasonal
effect disorder went to Summertime
because it was getting so kind of like
shady where it wasn't the winter there
all these people they're exhibiting
symptoms and it's summertime too and
they're exhibiting symptoms in the
spring and exhibiting symptoms in the
fall it's kind of was ridiculous what
was happening because do people have
viruses in their liver they got chronic
illness they got Epstein bar inside
their liver they got chronic fatigue
syndrome on and off they got all kinds
of different things going on and it all
reflects on you know how their nerves
feel and if they can't handle the heat
they swell up with the humidity and in
the winter time they hurt and they're
sore and they're achy and is it sad no
it's so many other
things and that's the joke about
Seasonal effective disorder but if you
take seasonal effect disorder you know
serious for what it you know for the
name or whatever it is you look at it's
a liver problem and it's all these other
problems with the liver it's all these
other problems with the liver so can set
you up dark circles under the eyes
that's a sluggish liver because the
blood's getting filled with so many
toxins so the blood's getting filled
with so many toxins unless you haven't
slept unless you don't
sleep I'll get a few dark circles under
my I'll get a few days of it without a
doubt because I'm working on the books
and I don't want to stop sometimes you
get on a roll and you just you just
don't want to stop and spirit's giving
you the information you don't want to
stop you just don't want to say oh no I
I I can't do this right now you just
want to just take that medical
information from Spirit you want to put
it in you want to put it in you want to
write it write it write and so if that
means three days of being up mostly and
sleeping on and off on the
couch for a few hours or whatever it is
yeah I'll get some dark circles but if
you have dark circles and you're getting
all the
sleep you're getting all the sleep I
mean you're getting 8 hours a night 7
hours a night whatever 6 hours a night
you're getting your sleep you got some
dark circles that's the sluggish liver
and those are toxins in the blood blood
toxins floating around floating around
those blood toxins are floating around
and they surface to this thin skin the
under your eyes you got your thinnest
skin that's your thinnest skin under
your eyes I don't I mean the under your
armpits and under your eyes it's your
thinnest skin especially under the eyes
and so you'll see you know you see the
dark circles because that's actually
blood that's toxic
blood that means you got a sluggish
liver so that's how it works all these
things and this you know something
chronic
dehydration you know chronic dehydration
that's sluggish liver too people don't
know they're chronically dehydrated they
have no idea walking around chronically
dehydrated it's unbelievable I just
grabbed some water just now when I was
when I was seeing that and saying that I
just grabbed some water so I'm going to
sip a little bit
so H yeah it's good water very good so
chronic
dehydration is something that people
walk around with all the time and don't
even know it but the problem is with
that is then your liver the liver just
gets sluggish and stagnant it can't
flush out the poison on a daily basis it
can't do a job you're you're you're not
drinking in a flute you're not getting
your lemon water you're not getting your
celery juice every single day you're not
getting your celery juice not getting
your lemon water you're not getting your
coconut water you're not eating some
fresh fruit you're not eating fresh
salads you're doing all cooked food or
you're doing all animal protein and all
cooked food and maybe you're doing some
salads and a green juice once in a while
but you just get
dehydrated and how dehydrated were you
were years before you started eating
better how dehydrated were you were
years before how dehydrated were you you
know were you
sorry how dehydrated 10 years ago 15
years ago 20 years ago
and consistently dehydrated from when
you were
little I remember I remember being in
daycare remember being in
daycare okay and I was so thirsty I was
so thirsty unbelievable like dying of
thirst in daycare I remember there was a
like Dixie Cups they give out Dixie cups
with a thimble of apple juice in it I
mean I'm sure it's changed I'm sure it's
changed but there's like you know D like
Dixie cup with Thimbles of like a
thimble of apple juice in it I mean
unbelievable I remember being so thirsty
it's like you know like your your
babyhood you could be dehydrated you're
you're three years old four years old
you could be dehydrated
and then you know catch a flu and a
fever and forget it exactly I mean
because you're just you can it's easy to
be chronically dehydrated from the very
beginning without a doubt and then if
you got a sluggish liver all the way a
sluggish liver I mean all the way
through your life for all kinds of
reasons filled with poisons and toxins
we inherit them we inherit a ton of
toxins and poisons I mean ton yeah okay
that's not the right phrase but we a
substantial amount old DDT pesticides oh
my God everything Mercury heavy metals
all kinds of metals lead cadmium nickel
uh arsenic yeah arsenic absolutely
traces traces arsenic in there as a
child traces of arsenic in there without
a doubt sitting inside the liver do you
think it burdens it yeah it does and
then there's all the other stuff we're
exposed to
unbelievable so varicose veins
what about that one I know I'm covering
a few conditions right here this just a
few ones just just a few for fun
vericast veins that's a sluggish liver I
mean I've heard for years when I was
working with people this women being
like I I got all these varic coose veins
I'm getting them removed I don't know
what to do whatever or um how do you do
how do you address it that's sluggish
liver your whole life that's what that
is spider veins it's all sluggish liver
liver you know the liver's burdened
toxin strugg struggling strained and I
talk about in Liver Rescue how it all
works these conditions I'm not even I'm
not even like scratching the surface of
any of this stuff that I'm even talking
about that's in Liver Rescue but I'm
just going over like sluggish liver it's
it's amazing what is there and how much
is there it's incredible so you got the
varic coast veins wak gain okay let's
talk about wak gain for a little bit
total sluggish liver all the
way all the way because that's the whole
point
that's the whole point the weight gain
has everything to do with the liver and
it's not even just a fatty liver
sluggish liver will lead to a fatty
liver sluggish liver is kind of like you
know a little bit before fatty liver
then the fat fat comes on to the liver
comes onto the liver you can you can
look like you don't have a scrap of fat
on your
body and your liver be fatty waiting for
you to put fat back on the body it's
unbelievable how it works with the liver
unless you take care of that liver
really work on that liver look okay what
do I mean how hard do you have to work
on well there's a little cleanse in the
book that's so easy to work with that
actually can get the weight off and gets
your liver back in into action and
everything else but it's not even just
about that it's about doing the celery
juice just Basics Basics lemon water
having a fat-free morning what's a
fat-free morning no overt fats in the
morning if you're into animal protein no
animal protein in the morning if you're
if you're if you're vegan and you're
you're not into animal whatever no
avocados in the morning no nut Butters
no oils in the morning that's how you
avoid a sluggish liver just just the
mornings
alone so and I haven't gotone in you
know I haven't gone into so much we got
so much to cover we we still got a
little time so with the weight gain when
that liver gets burdened with all the
poisons and toxins over the years
including medications Pharmaceuticals
everything else we're exposed to and
there's a lot of things we're exposed to
they could all Zapped up and saturate
into the liver including stress related
hormones like adrenaline sucking into
the liver and damaging it little Scar
Tissue occurring in the liver the liver
getting sluggish over time viruses
inside the liver you got the hhv6 is
sitting inside everybody's liver you got
the Epstein bar sitting inside
everybody's liver sometimes people have
three Epstein bars three varieties it's
just sitting inside the liver because
there's over 60 varieties of EBV because
they you know and then some people have
you know shingles two varieties of
shingles sitting inside the liver and
CTO megga virus and bacteria and all
kinds of things sits in the liver and it
could be sitting in there not doing much
but it bogs the liver down and weight
gain occurs get the hot flashes you get
the weight gain you get the heart
palpitations you can get palpitations
you can get everything could it can all
come bloating can come so it's just you
know sluggish liver can lead to anything
and what happens is what happens when
the liver gets sluggish talk about that
a little bit long longer before I go
into more symptoms and conditions when
the liver gets sluggish bio
reserves break down they break down bio
production weakens so bio production
weakens why is bio so important you guys
because it goes up into your gut goes up
drops into your intestinal tract drops
into your dadum drops down in there and
it's there to disperse fats so it's
there to disp disperse fats and if it
doesn't disperse fats and we keep on
bombarding our we keep on bombarding
ourselves with these high fat diets
including the healthy ones right now all
that bile got to be produced wearing
down the liver let's wear out the liver
let's wear it wear it down so it's got
to produce all its bio reserves and wear
it down and break it down no one even
talks about this stuff they don't even
know not even the experts out there
so-called experts you know I talked to
some of those experts out there also
writing books or whatever in health and
everything and it's almost like I I
can't talk to them because they they
they they think you're talking Chinese
when you talk about because they've
never heard this information before they
don't understand it they don't know that
sluggish liver means bio reserves break
down then then fats can't disperse from
the high fat healthy diet and then the
fats have to go somewhere and you know
where it goes It goes on the lining of
your intestinal tract grows ran it and
feeds bacteria and they look at you they
don't know they don't understand it's
crazy they'll just say um well you know
it's it's good to get rid of sugar and
carbohydrates and um and healthy fats
are good for you and they're good for
your brain I that's where it stops it's
actually unbelievable and then they say
oh and stay away from grains you got to
stay away from grains this is where it
stops and I'm like oh my God am I am I
talking to who am I talking to and
they're just like well you need your
protein and you got to get rid of your
car carbohydrates and you got to get rid
of your grains Okay okay you get to rid
of gluten you got to worry about your
lectins oh okay sure sure and you got to
get rid of this and then you know and
and this way you know you're you don't
get the insulin resistance you get rid
of your sugars out of your diet got to
exercise it's almost like oh my God I
just got stupider I just got stupider
it's unbelievable to me
really and you know and so the bottom
line is what happens is if your bile
breaks down because of the high fat diet
you've been on for so many years meaning
the poor fats you've been eating then
the good fats whatever all the same to
deliver eventually in the end you got to
just lower them you don't just you can
have fats and I'm not saying some fats
aren't good for you that's not it but
the liver it gets so beaten down so
burdened down so then the bile can't
actually break down any fats anymore
what this happens is with your sluggish
liver it also causes your stomach to
lose its hydrochloric acid so that
breaks down down so you can't break down
your proteins good anymore and then you
get gut rot and then you get diagnosed
with sibo strep with strepa cacus that
doctors don't even know either and I was
talking to another expert and I was like
well what what what kind of bacteria do
you think's in there and they're like um
it's just bacteria you know it's an
overgrowth of bacteria I go what kind of
bacteria I'm like well we don't know
nobody knows what bacteria it is I go
yeah of course it's strep that's what it
is people are loaded with it from their
mouth down to their butt and they loaded
with it it's in their throat deep in
their tonsils just sitting there it's
coming out in acne
everywhere yeah it's just chronic
illness is not advanced in all I mean
even if you talk to these you best
functional people right now they just
they kind of don't know instead they go
into oh biome and bofilm and they'll go
into you know that kind of thing go into
lime and but but a cluel less though
even about lime and it's hard so and I'm
saying this only because if you if you
want to be an expert you just you got to
have the information you got to I mean I
teach a lot of uh doctors too and I give
them the information a lot of them are
open to and they're like oh my God
that's the thank God for telling me this
and my patients are getting better and
my patients are getting better and you
know I that I go through that all the
time but it's amazing with some of the
trendy guys and gals some of the trendy
ones where they're just like I don't
even they don't even know just get rid
of your get rid of your gluten your
lectins and make sure you you know stay
away from all fruit the very thing that
actually keeps you alive the longest in
this world the very thing that gives you
10 15 20 more years in your life is
fruit the
antioxidants the minerals to trace
minerals in the antioxidants the very
thing that stops you you from dying
that's an antioxidant comes from fruit
it doesn't come from a whole lot of else
even vegetables don't have a lot of
antioxidants it comes from fruit comes
from berries but not just berries it
comes from everything but p mango and
everything else and you know what those
antioxidants do stop sluggish liver you
know what else those antioxidants do
stop you from dying it's called
oxidizing we oxidize that's how we die
that's how we die on the planet we
oxidize and when we get disease we
oxidize faster and
faster so you talk to these trendy guys
and they'll just be like I'm not talking
about a lot of the brilliant gu there's
a lot of brilliant doctors and
practitioners out there and functional
doctors too there's a lot of brilliant
ones out there and they're working on
some amazing stuff I mean you won
believe and I have some good
conversations with them it's
unbelievable and they take my
information and they apply it in their
practice and they like and they contact
me and saying oh my God this is this is
really helping out my practice and it's
putting it together with what I do and
blah blah blah and it's great but you
talk to these other trendy guys and it's
like they're just like no no you got to
keep the fats going you got to do the
keto thing you got to just you know you
got to avoid this avoid fruit you got to
avoid all the fruit you can fruit's bad
for you it's bad for the liver oh my God
dear Lord I'm going to tell you now that
that's what it's like out there it's
that's exactly what it's like out there
I am not exaggerating here and I'm not
just I'm not yeah I'm not just saying
this the whole bit so when it comes down
to weight gain you got the sluggish
liver the bio reserves break down so
then your fats that are in your gut
they're going in there that's why the
weight is coming on so fast for so many
people the bile can't break it down
disperse it into the bloodstream and
even if it does break it down disperse
it into the bloodstream you still got
all this fat in the bloodstream causing
problems and going back up into the
liver again that's a whole another
problem but that's why you got to lower
the fats in the diet for the for the
sluggish liver but weight gain has a lot
to do with that sure people lose weight
when they go on like they when they go
on they go off of all sugar they go on a
radical change of their diet their body
goes into shock they start exercising an
hour a day and they start losing weight
they're just eating you know some some
protein and which is fat some protein
and fat and some vegetables and they've
changed everything they stopped eating
the pizza their body goes in the shock
but their liver still stays sluggish
they still have a high-fat diet and
they're still prone to heart attacks all
the time I've seen people in the best
shape with sluggish livers get heart
attacks just heart attacks I I see it so
I mean it's so unbelievable out there 39
years old heart attacks 38 years old 42
44 whatever even exercising taking care
of themselves I'm not talking about
people that aren't taking care of
themselves at all because what it is is
you got this liver completely stagnant
and sluggish no one's doing anything
about the liver they're still on a diet
that's not that's not helping the liver
it's hurting the liver they've gotten
weight off they've shifted things
they're exercising but it's not enough
we have to do more we have to do more if
everybody thinks if anybody thinks
they're just you know
protected I mean you know no no you have
to do things for yourself and the live a
rescue that's what I talk about here so
so with the weight gain all that F it's
rants it sits on the Linings it's built
up on the Linings of the intestinal
tract the walls everywhere it gets
rancid starts getting hard gets in the
bloodstream too much it gets in the
liver starts getting hard it gets in the
liver sits there gets stagnant sluggish
liver gets like that hydrochloric acid
starts to break down in the stomach
because the liver is breaking down the
liver is weakening so HCL has to
overproduce until it burns out so your
gastric acid built Burns Out you start
bloating you get weight gained and
you're bloating the whole thing can go
wrong and this is just I'm just
scratching A A Touch of this I mean I
could do a we're going to do a whole
show on all this stuff chemical
sensitivities chemical
sensitivities that's one right there
that's a sluggish liver a liver filled
with a lot of poisons and toxins in the
body reacting as these toxins are
actually leaving the liver not only that
they're in the liver stored and then you
can't do any it can't store anymore more
so then the chemicals anything anything
you're exposed to you name it sits
around in your system longer and longer
and longer it can't even be vacuumed up
into the
liver I mean once again that's a real
stagnant sluggish sluggish liver and
I've seen people with a lot of weight on
them with chemical sensitivities a lot
of weight on them with the worst
chemical sensitivities just really
sluggish lymphatic system the liver
sluggish a lot of weight on them the
whole bit and I've seen people skinny as
rails so skinny with chemical
sensitivities and you still can have a
dysfunctional fatty sluggish liver
that's how how it works too you can have
both things with different people
easily easily with different people and
for different reasons but that's how it
works and then I've seen people they're
really skinny but then they gain all the
weight later so they chemical
sensitivity is really skinny and they
gain all this weight later after their
adrenals start to really burn out but
the adrenaline is actually keeping
keeping their weight off I've seen
people go 10 15 years really thin really
thin not eating good not eating great
really thin no carbohydrates I mean the
healthy carbohydrates all on fat and
protein thin in a bad way meaning like
where where everybody's
worried and then and then what happens
is eventually catches up the adrenaline
stops the whole thing what happens it's
what when you're on the fat high fat
diets when you're on the high fat diets
whether we're talking about chemical
sensitivities for a second but let's
just go up when you're on these high fat
diets it it it it burns the adrenals out
because when you put fat when you eat
too much fat over fat of any kind your
adrenals have to flood the body with
adrenaline to keep the blood as thin as
possible it just wears the adrenals out
too breaks it down totally kills them
that's another example and I was
explaining that to one guy and I was
like look I said you have to understand
the more fat you're putting in every day
the more your adrenals have to keep on
flooding and and you'll get a little
high off of it but your adrenals are
just going to be going and going and
going how long can that last before all
this weight comes back on before all
this weight comes back on cuz that's
what
happens I was talking to a couple of you
know trendy experts that got like books
out and stuff and they're like yeah but
and and I realized they they haven't
been really doing it that long they
might be doctors but they were doctors
different field of medicine and they
were doing conventional medicine and
they decided to go alternative you know
in The Last 5 Years so they don't even
have a track record of seeing people
sick for 20 30 years and heal for 2030
years and going through all the
different things and that's another
thing I'm seeing now but they put out
all this data and everybody bites it's
amazing it's amazing and I'm saying this
because you got to protect yourself and
not be afraid of fruit you got to
protect yourself and lower your fats I
can teach you how to do it we'll do it
in every show we it's it's doable you
can do it so chemical sensitivities
that's the blood being toxic with a lot
of different poisons but also it means
you're viral so with chemical
sensitivities you have to be viral there
has to be a virus inside the liver
feeding off of all kinds of different
poisons and releasing different
varieties of toxins not just dermat
toxins and and and uh neurotoxins that
these viruses are
releasing including bacteria but
releasing other forms of toxins the body
gets allergic to and sensitive to so
this way you become hyper sensitive to
whatever exposure out there because you
have exposure internally that's all
sluggish liver begin with it's viral
sluggish liver but it's sluggish liver
but it's viral sluggish
liver I mean we can go we can go on here
and on bloating low hydrochloric acid
because of a sluggish liver low gastric
acid because of a sluggish liver low bio
reserves it just just talked about that
that's bloating that means the liver got
sluggish a long time ago and you can do
something about it we can fix all this
we can fix all of this so you know if
anybody's just you know cluing on to the
show or just got on to the show I'm
talking about Liver Rescue I'm talking
about rescuing our liver sluggish liver
is what I'm talking about it's very
important constipation once again
sluggish liver filled the bacteria
though constipation has a lot to do with
bacteria sometimes viruses inside the
liver
a lot of toxins and poisons is another
thing
so it's amazing and I got to tell you
something it's completely unknown that
these and more originate at the liver so
it's completely unknown that these
symptoms and conditions and more a lot
more that I even that I talk about in
this book too are related to the
liver and that's how it
works that's how it works it's just
incredible how it works so it's not just
sluggish liver I say or anything like
that I say stagnant liver that's what I
say and you can say that too that's fine
um but but there's so much to learn
about this so let's talk a little bit
more too about all of
this you know it it's it's when you take
when you take a walk every single day
what are you doing you're saying well
I'm glad I'm walking I'm glad I'm taking
a walk when you take a walk every day
I'm glad I'm you know people I talk to
people and they're like well I took a
walk today was good and I was doing this
I was doing that I was really
active and and it's incredible because
someone's thinking about I was eating
really good today I've said people tell
me hey aw I'm eating really good today
I'm actually I'm actually you should see
it you should see what I'm doing and
it's
incredible and everything we do for
ourselves we have to think about what am
I doing for my liver is this helping my
liver and and eating better can help
your liver everything I'm doing can help
the
liver and so that's important I want to
talk about bugs inside the liver for a
couple of minutes
too I really do and we'll go into this
so there's all these unwanted bugs and
poisons in our liver that are actually
that are our liver is dealing with and
our liver has its own immune system to
help kill off these bugs so we want to
support the liver's immune system so
helping sluggish liver by supporting the
liver's immune system is another way of
getting it out of sluggishness because
you're killing off the bugs that are
inside of the liver and that's really
important
and the thing is it takes a lot of
nutrients inside the liver in order to
battle anything so that's why foods are
so important in taking care of ourselves
that's why we need to lower all the fats
and we got to get all these other
nutrients in there it's incredible the
last thing a liver needs is fat the last
thing if you ever hear that glucose
sugar of any kind healthy sugar I mean
hurts the liver is bad for the liver you
have just heard the most negligent and
disappointing
and unbelievable pieces of
misinformation there is in the
industries if you hear that out there
see that on the internet you just heard
the worst of it because because what
what happens out there is when you hear
that then you don't know what to do the
fat doesn't the fat isn't good for the
liver doesn't want any fat going into it
it doesn't want to deal with any fats so
you have to remember that so when it's
overburdened with having to deal with
fat because it's overburden with Epstein
bar bacteria heavy metals old DDT
aluminum exposure it's pesticides and
all the different cousins of pesticides
insecticides everything like that you
know I remember I
remember when I got an apartment it was
laced it was laced with insecticide when
I got an
apartment it was laced you can smell it
I you to talk to a landlord landlord's
like well yeah we did you know we we we
do and we do an insect spray you know
they come in here and they got the
little you know they get the little
machine and they're just got a little
backpack and they're just spraying every
corner of every wall and you know we're
they they're spraying for this and
spraying for that and it's just it's
unbelievable where did all that go when
I was standing there inhaling all that
or living in it where did it all go when
inside the
liver it it just does even carpet
cleaning chemicals just goes inside the
liver everything goes in there so you
got all these different
things our livers are meant to purify
and filter and hold on to the
good so hold on to the good stuff so
it's it they our livers become hoarders
they hold on to the good things but they
also have to hold on to the bad things
the more bad things we get in the liver
the less ability it can hold on to the
good things and that's how it
goes so we have to always remember that
the more bad things the liver fills up
creates a sluggish liver the more it can
hold on to the good things the liver is
filled with vitamins and nutrients going
all the way back all the way back since
the beginning including inherited
meaning inherited meaning like literally
from the family l nutrients from Mom and
and and and her mom there are some
nutrients that get passed along to our
lier it has to have nutrients it holds
on to a whole whole bunch of nutrients
like unbelievable how many and then it's
conversion the conversion ability cuz
the liver converts everything it plays
with things it moves things around it
converts it I mean this is it's
unbelievable about what the liver does
and it releases
nutrients and minerals and hormones all
into the bloodstream and that's its job
but yet its other job is to actually
filter out all those poisons I just
talked about and all those toxins that
make it sluggish what happens is when
those toxins are going up up up up up
and up and they're climbing and they're
climbing and climbing all the ability
for the SL all the ability for that
liver to actually being sending it to
send out the right hormones the right
conversions of nutrients methyl ating
everything cuz the liver methylates
virtually
everything so all of that going on the
liver can't do that anymore so you can
get people who are mineral deficient or
deficient or going to going to doctors
or whatever it is and they're going to
all these different doctors and they're
getting all these different blood work
all the profile and everything it's like
you're deficient in this this this this
this that's because of a liver problem
and nobody even knows that and then
they'll give you the wrong diet that
will still keep your liver sluggish and
keep it harmed that's the irony they'll
take you off of you make sure you're not
doing any fruit they'll make sure you're
doing high protein which is high fat and
they'll whatever including even if
you're vegan or plant-based this isn't
about animal protein people you're vegan
or plant-based there just put lots of
lots of fats and you could be hardly
doing any fruit or leafy greens really
just being doing lots of fats and so
what happens is you got all these
deficiencies it's all showing up
everywhere and that's the liver
that's how it
works so I mean it goes goes on and on
and on
basically basically it's good to know
that there's warnings that happen here's
how it works with the liver too the
liver neutralizes so it
neutralizes it has to neutralize poison
all the time it has to stop
poisons and neutralize them so that you
know what happens is when it's
neutralizing I'll say it over and over
again it's that important of a word for
this that's why it's that
important what that means is it's
stopping the toxin from being as harmful
as it really is so that when it leaves
the liver it doesn't hurt you as much
that's the power of the liver and what
the liver can do it's it's
extraordinary and so it's doing that so
it has over 2,000 chemical functions
that involve detoxification neutralizing
poisons and everything else and what
happens when your liver gets sluggish
from all the different poisons that are
already in the liver and then you're
bombarding it with high fat diets and
everything else what
happens it loses it neutralizing
capability that's how you age fast down
the road sure you might not be looking
like you're aging when you're in your
20s you might not be looking like you're
aging when you're in your
30s but you know you start aging too
fast when you get or people do you know
they start aging too fast and that can
happen that's a neutralizing ability is
lost because of a sluggish
liver the liver also has an anti-s
sluggish emergency alarm response it's a
chemical induced response that brings in
new vital energy to break up stagnancy
the response is a liver spasm this spasm
can result in A tingle a twitch a slight
ache a warmth a heat a pulling bloating
a prickly feeling A Stitch in the
side that's what this
is it's incredible but you even lose
that opportunity when the liver gets too
sluggish and it starts breaking down you
even lose that opportunity and that's
the sad sad thing there are five
varieties of sluggish liver so five
varieties of sluggish liver I'll give
you that real
quick there's the middle of the liver
that's one variety of sluggish liver so
the middle of the liver can get
sluggish science of research has no clue
that's like 30 40 50 years from
now maybe I mean that's if we're
lucky it's not even about the liver
itself as a whole becoming sluggish it's
different sections of the liver that
become sluggish and I'm just going to
give you this rundown really quick see
if you see if you see if this matters to
you how cool this is cuz when I got this
information I was blown off my seat so
the middle of the liver that's the
deepest part of the liver and that's
when you can get hot flashes night
sweats pre-diabetes swelling flute
retention body temperature fluctuations
low energy weight gain brain fog dark
circles under the eyes hypoglycemia
fatigue rashes anger frustration
irritability a sense of loneliness
depression anxiety anxiousness poor skin
tone skin pigment issues Reena that's
all sluggish liver in the middle of the
liver the bottom of the
liver what happens is when the sluggish
liver is in the bottom of the liver a
sluggish liver can make you toss and
turn when it's in the bottom of the
liver you toss and turn at night result
in sleep disturbances insomnia
constipation feeling of unease s a
sensation of hot and cold all that's
from the bottom of the liver being
sluggish think about that how cool is
that to even know that
the top of your liver being sluggish
let's talk about that for a second
that's acid reflux that's bloating
gastritis pressure in the abdomen I'm
just giving you a little bit of this
that's that's in Liver Rescue about
sluggish liver the left side of the
liver when you're sluggish on the left
side of the
liver okay that's that's when you have
feelings of weakness in the in the left
leg or arm nausea anxiousness lack of
hunger insatiable hunger
this is
information you can use and I haven't
even touched upon it that you could use
to learn about your sluggish liver and
learn how to heal it or learn how to
move forward I there's so many symptoms
I'm just scratching the surface of some
of these symptoms of what sluggish liver
is about about if it's in the middle the
top the bottom the left side so
forth and there's five varieties of
sluggish liver someone can walk around
with two of them somebody walk around
with three VAR is a sluggish liver mean
three areas because it's it's of of the
liver being
sluggish some people are just walking
around with one and it's hasn't started
yet it's just starting a little bit
think about that and we can stop it we
can stop it we can do something about it
we
can I mean we can and I lay it out in
Liver Rescue I lay it out so I'm I'm
doing everything I can to make sure you
have everything you need to heal in
every way possible that's all I care
about that's all I care about are you
healing are you getting better do you
have the information you need do you
have the tools you need do you have the
golden ticket in your hand do you have
what it takes and that means the
information okay the information is what
it takes the rest is just applying it
and applying it in the most Gentle Way
basic way in any way even if it's just a
celery juice that we brought to the
world that spirit and I brought to the
world the plain straight celery juice
that didn't exist until us even if it's
just that golden ticket to help you with
your sluggish liver
anything but I stand behind you I love
you guys dearly you take one day A Time
thank you for being on this this show
with me this was amazing and uh hey just
know I believe in you and just know I
care know I love you guys bless your
heart bless your soul take one day at a
time things will be all right okay
bye-bye