[Music]
hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else in is decades
ahead of what's out there now in fact
Today's show is that very thing we're
going to talk about Epstein bar we're
going to talk about everything about it
information it doesn't exist anywhere
else and you're not going to hear it
anywhere else it's not in any books it's
not on the internet you're not going to
hear it from any other person or expert
and that's what we're doing today we
need information that's 10 20 30 years
ahead of the times in order to get
better because who has 10 years to wait
you know for answers we don't really I
mean I know people have gone through
where their their grandmother has gone
through all these different waves of
illness and chronic illness no answers
at all ever just living with it and then
you know and then it goes down to the
mother having it and then the daughter
having it and then even even farther
back great-grandmother and you know we
don't have just this kind of time to
throw away life is precious and it means
everything and our health means
everything and this is a big show today
and this means a lot what we got to
cover today today's show is about
Epstein bar virus revealed meet Epstein
bar virus one of the biggest mystery
illnesses causing millions of people to
suffer today Epstein bars secretly
behind debilitating conditions such as
fibromyalgia chronic fatigue syndrome
all the different varieties of chronic F
fatigue syndrome that we have multiple
sclerosis rheumatoid
arthritis thyroid disorders such as
Hashimoto and much more join me today
don't miss this show if you just tuned
in stay with it because I'm going to
reveal the historic truth about Epstein
bar virus in this episode and I and I
say that historic truth that no one
knows it's that important today a little
bit about me since the age of four woke
up one morning heard a voice and it was
what I call Spirit this voice has been
with me my whole life at age 4 diagnosed
my grandmother of lung cancer and uh
weeks later they brought her in and she
had lung cancer so the gift started
there and for the rest of my life I've
dedicated everything to getting people
answered ERS so they knew what was going
on I've helped tens of thousands of
people recover their health reclaim
their health understand their
illnesses and re and gain control and
move forward and heal it's been my
life's purpose It's My Life journey I
know everybody has a life purpose and
journey we all do magical special things
every single day in our lives and so I
support your gift thank you for
supporting Mine by being here and
listening to the show it's it's just so
important
um so let's get started um you can see
I'm you know I'm trying to get through
things that the you know at the
beginning is quick as I can almost
because I want to make sure we get
everything we can out of this show and
this is so important
um let's take a look here and see what's
happening what you're going to hear
today about Epstein bar it could be even
shocking and it could be more than just
shocking in this sense because it could
be it's real it's revelational it is you
know it can really wake up the mind and
wake up the body unlike other because if
you're dealing with symptoms and you're
dealing with illness and you're dealing
with conditions and you're not getting
answers and you got fatigue and all
these different things hearing the truth
about what's going on could be pretty
heavy and so with that I want you to
just relax get a cup of tea get a cup of
herbal tea of course
and relax and listen to the show you
know if you got a notepad or whatever
take notes but what what I recommend is
going back to the show in the archives
because we're going to cover a lot of
information I'm going to drop a lot of
information down on everybody and so you
might want to go back to this archive
for sure and because we're going to run
over a lot of things you may miss
something and and you want to get every
bit of it it's that important so I'm
preparing you
um so when it comes down to Healing
especially healing with Epstein bar
knowing the truth knowing the cause is
half the battle to Healing it's why
people don't heal so easily it's why so
many people have chronic illness and
don't have answers and basically what
happens
is that if we don't have answers if we
don't know what's going on how is the
healing going to start start see that's
half the battle that's half of how it
happens the other half is knowing what
to do having answers on what to do what
to address how to address for example
Epstein bar and we're going to cover
that so it's about knowing what's wrong
that's half the battle knowing what to
do to fix it to heal to move forward
this is a big part of it all and that's
why also why we're doing the show so to
understand EP steam bar virus we have to
hop into our time machine and set it for
1890 yeah I I said it 1890 that's what
year we're going to so let's let's get
ready and you know put the seat bels on
for this at this time in history a
harmless virus that was herpetic in
nature so herpetic meaning like herpes
herpetic in nature was redefining itself
due to antibiotic experimentation
this is antibiotic use before 1928 did
you hear about the 1928 thing where
penicillin was born that's when it was
discovered and it was a huge Discovery
penicillin it saved a lot of lives it
was definitely an amazing it's an
amazing Discovery in health history till
today and so but right prior that there
was also other types of antibiotics
being used yes you won't see that on the
internet you can look you may not find
that different forms of
antibiotics and this is the earlier
Renditions of penicillin being used to
treat various
bacteria this was an amazing Discovery
like I said before and it's helped so
many other people but at the same time
this harmless common herpetic natured
virus which we named later epsteen bar
was developing an intelligence and
learning how to cope and maneuver around
pre-
antibiotics pre-time
antibiotics and it began to use this
early source of antibiotics as a food
source now this wouldn't have been a big
concern really or a big deal if there
wasn't another Factor contributing
another Factor occurring at the same
time in the same era back in the late
1800s and this was early pesticide
herbicide and fungicide use and
development and you may say you may be
someone that knows about pesticides and
say well Anthony that's not true because
pesticides really started in the late
30s and you know during the War Machine
during you know that World War II where
all the chemicals were made and all the
pesticides were made and the
DDT but there were pesticides before
this time period before this time period
and they were being developed in the
late 1800s early 19 1900s they were made
up of Arsenic and Lead what they were
were arsenic sprays arsenic water
arsenic spray Arsenic and Lead Vapor
okay and this was fairly a fairly new
exposure in our day and AG to us and our
immune systems and it was on our food
supply everywhere so you know how you go
and get organic food cuz you don't want
the pesticides today all the synthetic
pesticides and everything well back then
back before in the 1890s and right
around 1900 there were sprays on
everybody's food and nobody really even
knew anything but the difference between
organic or conventional because
synthetic sprays weren't even invented
yet to differentiate that this is
serious this is something to understand
here it's important factor what we're
going through what we're talking about
so instead there was these arsenic
sprays and it was on everything it was
laced down all this food and everyone
had a big container a big container of
it at home with a hand pump you know
those antique you know bug killer pumps
on and it would spray a vapor of Arsenic
and Lead misted okay all of your plants
all your garden plants all the fields
that were you growing produce had this
stuff the stuff was also being you know
sprayed in all kinds of different ways
this common herpetic virus we call
Epstein bar now this common docile
easygoing virus learned how to use toxic
heavy metals such as Arsenic and Lead as
its
fuel it became fuel for this virus
basically the Industrial
Revolution was fueling and creating
Epstein bar virus the Redevelopment of
Epstein bar virus what I'm trying to say
is Epstein bar was beginning to redefine
itself and mutate by thriving on these
toxic heavy metals including early
antibiotics that were even pre-1 1928
the penicillin age which also had heavy
metals in them to begin
with and that's how things were
established so so we have to know this
so by
1900 Epstein bar had established itself
and had a hunger for arsenic lead and
some Mercury and at this time our food
supply was covered like I said in early
PES side use of this compromised with
all this comprised of all this Arsenic
and Lead so when we would eat our food
the Arsenic and Lead would quickly
absorb get ready get ready for this it
would quickly absorb into our
thyroids into our thyroids so as you
would eat this food that was everything
was laced in Arsenic at this time period
understand this this is serious stuff
when it would enter your mouth the
Arsenic would absorb into your cells of
your mouth and travel so when you
swallowing it would absorb right into
your throat as you were swallowing and
it would then absorb into your thyroid
and your thyroid will fill up with
Arsenic and lead and even some
Mercury the Epstein bar virus would
adapt and start to search for its food
and travel when I mean be food Epstein
bar would feed off of Arsenic and
remember that it would travel and start
to adapt and learn how to adapt in the
body and it started mutating back in
that day it would travel for that
Arsenic and that lead and guess where it
would find its way guess where it would
go to are you guessing what I'm thinking
you are the
thyroid and invading the thyroid causing
you know what I'm talking about
Hashimoto's
thyroiditis Hashimoto thyroiditis now
this label this condition of Hashimoto
thyroiditis was discovered meaning the
label was dis was created in
1912 1912 see no one knew what caused
Hashimoto thyroiditis they still don't
know today I've spent decades trying to
teach people that it's caused by epeen
bar virus and it's just starting to
surface now out there and any place you
hear it or see it it originally sources
from me I'm just being straightforward
about that one that's the bottom line
cuz I'm the one that only knew that
because of spirit for decades now and
been trying to get that information out
there so now when Epstein bar virus when
the Epstein bar gets into the thyroid
this is stage three of Epstein bar so
you have to understand this this is
stage three of Epstein bar so that means
when it entered into somebody's thyroid
in
1912 in the early
1900s this was stage three of having
Epstein bar now we're going to talk
about Epstein bar stages Epstein bar has
four
stages stage one of Epstein bar is when
the virus is in the body but it's in a
dormancy incubation period it's
incubating it's waiting for an
opportunity like when we get really run
down or we get deficient or we got
stressed out or we're
intoxicated with some kind of poisons or
whatever it may be or we have emotional
hardships
and then boom romatic fever occurs yes
romatic fever guess what romatic fever
is no one realizes it's in the medical
industry romatic fever is Epstein bar
it's
mononucleosis it's a variety of
mononucleosis and now it's diagnosis
mononucleosis used to be diagnosis
romatic fever and it's also diagnosed as
glandular fever in fact all the way back
back in those days when Epstein bar
would hit stage two and turn into
mononucleosis it was called glandular
fever it's still called glandular fever
in different parts of the
world the infamous kissing disease were
taught about is called glandular fever
romatic you know romatic fever and
mononucleosis and so this is important
to know the virus
um once again after that period goes and
waits into a dorcy period this could
take a month this could take years this
could take decades depending on what's
going on in the
person and it's and this happens before
it goes to stage three remember I told
you I jumped ahead earlier because I had
to because 1912 they discovered
thyroiditis Hashimoto thyroiditis is
stage three so when the virus comes out
of dorcy again which could take a month
or a year or a decade or more or two
decades or even longer it can turn into
hashimotos thyroiditis or
hypothyroidism and it depends on so many
variables the person's immune system
what is happening in their lives I've
seen children get mono at age five or
six or seven years old and then they get
Hashim Modas at 16 years of age 17 years
of age or 18 years of age it kashimoto
that early that means they had Mono
before that this is not understood on
any level in our medical field right now
so what you're hearing is groundbreaking
information that doesn't exist out
there but back in the old days in the
early 1900s we going back now it
normally took longer before there were
only because there were only a few
varieties of Epstein bar what I mean is
it took longer for Hashimoto thought
thyroiditis it took longer for the next
phase or the next stage of Epstein bar
because there were only a few varieties
of epin bar in that time which leads me
to the next bit of information to
understand is there are over 60
varieties of Epstein bar today our
medical model has no clue about this
some are doile some are timid so some
varieties of Epstein bar doile some
varieties of Epstein bar are timid and
some are more
aggressive so going back to the old days
early to mid 1900s it took most people
especially women to get to the age of 40
get to the age of 45 get to the age of
50 before they experienced a set of
symptoms that eluded the medical world
even up to
today understand the importance of this
this is this is amazing if you got
Epstein bar and you were born around the
time of 1900 or 1890 or 1895 or
1903 and right around the age
40 the virus would go into the next set
of phases right around 40 45 50 years
old every person was different because
of different circumstances and different
situations but at that time there
weren't a lot of varieties of Epstein
bar so they were all similar there only
were a few at that time that mutated at
that early time so there was a whole
like crowd a whole vast sea of women
that experienced epine bar symptoms out
of
nowhere turn on the turn of around 1950
right around 1945 to
1950 and it stormed the medical world
these symptoms that all the women were
faced with and these might be familiar
okay so you know match them up TI yours
if you want to that's you know it's
important to know this is important but
the symptoms were the next phase of
epine bar which is called stage four
Epstein bar that's what this is so that
that's what all these symptoms were
about to go into it's stage four Epstein
bar so it took a long time for these few
varieties of Epstein bar for women to
get you know that were born at 1900 or
like I said 1895 and by the time they
turned 40 45 50 years old they had
tingles and numbness do you know about
the tingles and numbness
they had aches and pains joint
swelling vertigo and
dizziness tentis ringing in the ears
buzzing in the ears hot flashes yeah hot
flashes that's important to understand
because we're about to cover that next
heart palpitations are you getting heart
palpitations night
sweats brain
fog
depression
anxiety burning feelings burning you
know pins and needles or burning in
various parts of the body which we call
neuropathy now which is another kind of
like hey we don't know what's wrong with
anybody but let's put another label to
it blurry eyes migraines loss of
libido head pains in the back of the
neck back of the
head weight gain unexplained weight gain
edema swelling and edema lymph Pema
swelling ankles unexplained swelling
knees when you get hit the knees get hit
and they swell too long and they stay
swollen for years vibrating feelings
inside the body
confusion roving and moving body pain
see by 1950 women were feeling the first
round of stage four Epstein bar symptoms
ever in
history ever in history and no one's
talking about it no one's talking about
about it but right here at this show and
this is why you have to stay tuned in to
these show shows because I got to pour
my heart out I to give you everything I
got so you have a chance to take the
information heal you know spread the
information around because it's so
critical to
know and women were told at that in this
time period that it was all in their
heads and they were told they were crazy
this was the moment in time right around
the 1945 1950 period when this wave of
symptoms from Epstein bar crashed the
scene women were told by every single
Medical Institution there was that they
were lazy that their fatigue was because
they were lazy because they were bored
because they were crazy they even
entered it into some medical medical
books where they called it crazy women's
syndrome that's how they dealt with it
and that lasted that's still kind of
floating around a little bit it's it's
died out cuz we put labels now on sets
of symptoms so the so before these
labels all these new labels came about
before that started happening in the in
the 19 late 1980s yes in the late 1980s
it took that long in the 1990s before we
started getting actually names for these
conditions you were just insane that's
what happened when you had all the
symptoms I mentioned when you were
fatigued had tingles and numbness
vertigo dizziness ringing in the ears
hot flashes heart potations brain fog
depression anxiety burning in various
parts of the body blurry eyes migraines
aches and pain swelling these are all
stage four symptoms of Epstein bar and
we were told we were insane at that time
period okay the the push back occurred
women had enough at that point hitting
in the mid-50s after five to seven years
to the late 50s women had enough and the
push back was just
enormous and basically what happened
after that these symptoms of the medical
field that they all the symptoms that
women were experiencing the medical
field put a big blame on one thing you
know what I'm talking about someone out
there knows what I'm talking about that
was the birth of the hormone movement
that was when it was all hormonal it's
actually hormones and they were still
saying you're still crazy to have these
symptoms because there's nothing wrong
with you know everybody they were
looking at so when they were doing you
know physical exams they're like who
nothing wrong with you we don't know why
you have tingles and numbness so you're
either crazy or it's hormonal we still
get that today where we're told it's
hormonal now to and that's what's
happening and so hormones the hormone
movement their hormone replacement era
was born in the late 50s because of
stage four Epstein
bar women didn't suffer from the
symptoms ever before in the past ever
anytime they hit menopause ever in
history were they suffering from these
symptoms it wasn't n it was never there
because it was never was never hormonal
see it was abstein bar stage four now
decades later women of all ages get the
symptoms get all the symptoms I just
mentioned so when they're younger
they're not told it's
hormones they but they're starting to
now because still to this day people
don't know why we're getting these
symptomss so they're still kind of
saying well now you're 30 years old
maybe you have hormonal problems and
maybe that's creating all these symptoms
of fatigue all these symptoms of brain
fog blurry eyes you know everything uh
heart palpitations tingles and numbness
so even younger women and men some men
are being told it's it's a hormone
problem and if that's not good enough
then it's off to the Lyme disease doctor
you can listen to my lyme disease show
if you want a little taste of the whole
lime
truth and so that's what's happening to
today now we'll go back a little bit now
now now back by
1964 two brilliant biologists discovered
a virus that was responsible for
mononucleosis romatic fever but
mononucleosis glandular fever and they
singled it out and named it Epstein bar
virus after the doctors and that was an
amazing Discovery it really was and that
goes to show you what we can do with the
doctors that are out there the problem
is the funding dropped and that was the
bottom line funding was over it's a dead
topic see you later and that's what
happens in chronic illness though that's
the whole point that's what happens all
the time now what medical research and
science has done to acknowledge Epstein
bar symptoms meaning without knowing
Epstein bar causes any of these symptoms
is they put labels now on these sets of
symptoms so the medical world doesn't
realize that this is Epstein bar related
but they put names on sets of symptoms
now that everybody has and that's
fibromyalgia what what causes it h
nobody
knows but it's Epstein bar that's stage
four Epstein bar multiple sceris still
don't know the cause it's a mystery
illness Epstein bar different varieties
of Epstein bar cause cause and mass now
there's over 60 varieties like I said
chronic fatigue syndrome which has
various names now such as and me CFS
okay also systemic exertion intolerance
disease these are still just a way of
saying yes you're tiredness is real so
thank God we have labels at least to say
hey your symptoms are real but we're
nowhere closer to understanding what's
causing this and knowing that it's over
60 varieties of epsteam bar causing
these sets of these labels these sets of
symptoms
so and it goes on past then ra RTI
arthritis that's another one so you know
when children get ra it's stage 4 fste
bar but early
on early on in their lives because
there's different varieties they've
mutated and they become a little bit
more aggressive and kids get different
stages early on doesn't mean everybody
can't heal anyone can heal and there's
ways of doing about it we're going to
get to that don't worry we're going to
get to that menopause that's a label see
menopause really is just supposed to be
menstration stopping the cycle stopping
that's all it's supposed to be in fact
before 1950 women felt great after their
cycle stopped they felt great it was
looked forward to in history meaning in
P in the past women look forward to that
stopping it meant they felt better more
energy than ever before no symptoms
would
occur and but now we label your set of
symptoms everybody sets of symptoms as
menopause
depression we use that label too when
we're depressed instead of knowing the
root cause of someone's depression we
throw label anxiety lupus that's caused
by Epstein bar and that's another one
and of course many cases of Lyme disease
these labeled conditions plus many more
are caused by over 60 varieties of
Epstein bar and in different stages of
the virus including Hashimoto
thyroiditis like we talked about before
he hepatitus C is not a hepatitis virus
it's a condition of the liver caused by
a variety of Epstein bar there they
still don't know this and medical
history Medical Research Medical Science
isn't even caught up to that you know I
always say I'm going to die come back in
another lifetime they're still not going
to know die One More Time come back in
another lifetime and it's possible they
still won't know you know and it's it's
nobody's fault it's nobody's fault but
that's the slowness of it all that's the
slowness of of everything so hepatitis C
is caused by Epstein bar that's
different than Hepatitis B hepatitis C
is is Epstein bar
glaucoma you know the eye illness the
eye condition glaucoma that's caused by
a variety of epine bar and certain
cancer specifically breast cancer is
caused by ep bar
viruses so all this is important to know
this is part of the epid mic we live in
today now it it does matter to know this
information it's not because you know
knowing it makes things more scary
that's not it at all you gain control
knowing the truth you don't want the
truth avoided or you don't want it
hidden away you don't want it being a
mystery because that's when all this
stuff is tougher on us is when it's a
mystery and nobody knows and we're never
getting validation and we're going to Dr
doctor you get 50 doctors going to
different people and you're traveling
across country you're spending hundreds
of thousands of dollars that's more
damaging than knowing the truth and
knowing how to recover and heal you see
that's that's how it
works see you don't have to there's a
couple of things to know you don't have
to remember having mono in order to have
Epstein bar in the system some people
have bad cases of mononucleosis so they
remember it specifically but some people
have had a sore throat and a scratchy
throat for a week and that's all they
had and it went away it went into a
dormancy so let talk about Epstein bar
testing when you go to the doctor and
you get tested for Epstein bar they only
care about present infection which is
mononucleosis they only care about
present
infection now what the medical research
and medical science and doctors don't
know right now is that past infection
Epstein bar meaning knowing that you had
it in the past still means it could be
doing something and creating your
symptoms so it's completely ignored so
when you go to the doctor and you say I
got this problem and I got this and I
you know I got tingles and I got
twitches and I got all these you know
different things going on and I got um
you know and I got fatigue and I can't
function and they do a test and they say
everything looks okay it looks like you
had Epstein bar but that shouldn't be
your problem because you don't have it
now that's not true they haven't
developed the proper testing to see that
it's in the organs and then it's also
affecting the nervous system they don't
have this technology yet we still don't
have a lot of technology in chronic
illness how do I know that there's 200
million sick people in the US alone with
symptoms that are mystery illness that's
how I know that we don't have the
technology or the understanding yet you
know this is you know I'm passionate
about this because this is about
everything about you getting better it
means the world so when you have stage
four Epstein bar and all the symptoms
around it the doctor can't find Epstein
bar actively in the bloodstream so they
dismiss it it's one of the mistakes this
is one of the greatest medical blunders
of our
time we'll talk about some of the
symptoms of Epstein bar Epstein bar is
herpetic so it's in the herpes family
this is the one family the only family
of bugs that release a
neurotoxin that aggravates the nervous
system causing tingles and numbness see
the neurotoxin is basically an excrement
that comes out of the virus after the
virus feeds off of heavy metals feeds
off of foods like eggs like I talk about
if you're if you're someone who's not
feeling good and you got all kinds of
different symptoms make sure you're not
eating eggs because eggs will feed a bug
like Epstein
bar so this neurotoxin can create a lot
of different symptoms can create tingles
and numbness and many other different
symptoms around that brain fog can
create um aches and pains and so this
neurotoxin also creates food allergies
people say well how can I have a food
allergy now how could that have happened
I never had it before why am I
developing food allergy I went to the
doctor to the you know the integrative
doctor I went to the functional medicine
doctor I got all these food allergies
and sensitivities now that's from having
a higher debris of this byproduct these
neurotoxins from Epstein bar it creates
chemical sensitivity
it creates food at food sensitivities
epine bar creates a lot of byproduct and
debris and garbage and this builds up in
the liver causes a stagnant sluggish
liver and gets the heart to even have a
heart palpitation because all that
byproduct from the liver goes up to the
heart and trips up the mitro valve
creating heart palpitations these These
are the mystery H heart palps that no
one understands out there and it's the
sticky residue that builds up in the
mitro valve this is from the byproduct
EBV Epstein bar raises inflammation
markers with this byproduct it produces
it raises inflammation markers causing
the CRP so when you get the CRP C
reactive protein test and it's showing
that you you got an elevation no one
realizes it it's from byproduct from
Epstein bar same thing with the
anti-nuclear antigen test the Ana test
this is inflammation
levels that rise
because of toxins released in
neurotoxins and byproduct from Epstein
bar so guess what you end up getting a
lupus diagnosis that's how far off we
are we're that far off in
medicine we're that far off so we get
the whole lupus thing and and that's
because someone's getting sensitive and
they're getting the chemical
sensitivities and they're getting all
the symptoms based around it this
byproduct raises homocysteine levels
were you told you have an MTHFR gene
mutation at all so when you go to the
practitioner and you're told you know
you're having that gene mutation some
people have three mutations some people
have you know four mutations two M
mutations right so when you that's
because of epine bar byproduct it's from
having Epstein bar in the system for a
long time in your life and it builds up
a tremendous amount of byproduct and
excrement releases all these toxins
including neurotoxins so it raises
homine levels and it sets off the faulty
MTHFR gene mutation
test and creates a but it does create a
true methylation issue at the same time
so there is a methylation issue that
that does occur from having Epstein bar
so there's like they're almost there
with that one Epstein bar can make a
liver really sluggish causing weak
digestion and breaking down hydrochloric
acid and Epstein bar can can trigger off
false positives on a lime test that's
when your lime test comes back
borderline why is it borderline you
either have lime or you don't you can go
you can listen to the lime show on that
for sure cuz I can't go into lime like
crazy into lime right now and deep into
it but it can trigger off your lime
tighters for everything it could
literally mask as bartella babesia
bellia that's what Epstein has the power
to do not in everybody depending on how
long you've had it what variety you have
so it's important to understand these
things and and anyone listening to this
I'm not saying Bella doesn't exist I'm
not saying lime you know bacteria such
as B you know bellia you know babesia
parasite babesia doesn't exist I'm not
saying that so you you know don't get
thrown by this right now if you if this
the first time hearing one of my shows
but evv upsteam bar is responsible for
hundreds of thousands of people's
tonsils coming out you know the whole
tonsil thing when they're plucking them
like apples forever back in the ' 50s
and the' 60s the 70s and we're still
plucking them out that's from mono
undiagnosed mono because mono is elusive
you can have mononucleosis Epstein bar
is elusive you can have it once early on
in your childhood they won't rediagnosis
it's another thing it does so they're
just pulling tonsils out for decades
without realizing what's creating
tonsilitis see how important the show is
this episode I mean it's really that
important
and you know fste bar tends to create
problems with soreness aches and pains
fatigue after the body gets jolted so I
you know lots of people they get into
small car accidents or they have a they
have some trauma and they and and their
body is physically fine after or they
recover from the trauma part but yet
they have new aches and pains that are
unexplainable by doctors and in by
medical research and Science and you
start getting fibromyalgia and you start
getting inflamed this is from Epstein
bar ttis ringing in the ears is caused
by the Labyrinth of the inside of the
ear getting inflamed by epine bars
neurotoxins you go to an ear nose and
throat doctor they're not going to
figure that one out that's going to take
30 years from now it's caused by a
neurotoxin That's What Causes That
ringing in the air unless you damage
your nerve your nerve in the ear by
listening to you know concerts rock
concerts your whole life or something
crazy like that you worked in a machine
shop or something and that's a little
different but this is this is the common
ringing in the ears caused by Epstein
bar I was saying previously dizziness
vertigo that's the Vagas nerve that runs
through the chest that makes the chest
feel tight that Vagas nerve gets
inflamed by neurotoxins from Epstein bar
causing vertigo bouts of vertigo bed
spins head head spins dizziness balance
issues that are unexplainable by the
medical world when you go to the doctor
this is caused by Epstein Barb then
there's headaches back of the head neck
AES back of the neck caused by frenic
nerves frenic nerves that run up through
the chest up through the neck they get
inflamed from the neurotoxin Epstein
bar epin bar has a friend in crime
called strep acacus it's a bacteria
strep that's when you get strep throat
that that's when you have strep that's
when women are about to have a baby so
the doctor checks for vaginal strep the
strep is everywhere in our bodies it's a
co-actor to Epstein bar causes a lot of
the bladder problems strep aacle is
responsible for intercal cystitis which
is technically kind of caused by Epstein
bar because it's its co-actor so that
that alone has to be uncovered someday
and you're only going to hear it here
at this show at the medical Medium
show so and that could lead to you know
bladder leaking burning without a proper
diagnosis and and many other kinds of
things bladder spasms so basically the
bottom line is we're going to get
through the show today we're I know I'm
going a little fast that's why you have
to you have to go to the archives on
this but you have to listen to the show
again look a big part of all of this is
so you can you can know what's bugging
you causing your pain and gaining
control over it in healing and moving
forward it's about knocking the viral
load slowly down and restoring your
nervous system restoring your health
breaking down that viral load so you can
gain control over your health this is
what it's
about if you had symptoms for years in
your life it may take a little while you
got to be patient it's three steps up
two steps back three steps up two steps
back that's how it is you start feeling
better a month later and you start
feeling a little better better another
month later and you keep on climbing
that ladder and climbing that ladder
until you look back a year or whatever
it is depending on how long you've been
sick with all these different symptoms
you look back and you see how much
better you are I've watched a lot of
people get their lives back I've helped
them get their lives back with Epstein
bar and so you can recover let's talk
about Foods let's talk about um what
kind of foods are great wild blueberries
flushes out the neurotoxin right out of
the liver wild blueberries incredible
for Epstein bar you have them in every
day celery remember the celery juice
thing strengthens the hydrochloric acid
provides mineral salts at the same time
builds up that HCL provides mineral
salts for the brain helps with brain fog
helps recover you from Epstein bar
Sprouts they strengthen you from Epstein
bar too Sprouts are actually antivirus
with Epstein bar asparagus strengthens
everything cleanses the liver pulls
Epstein bar toxins out that you know but
how many people eat eat enough asparagus
spinach helps remove Epstein bar how
does it do that it cleanses out the
Epstein bar toxins the overload of
Epstein bar toxins cleanses the colon
too apricots another great one for
rebuilding the nervous system cilantro
removes heavy m
which feed Epstein bar so you want
cilantro in all the time you have to
remember hey look if if it's been a week
since you've had cilantro that's not
going to help that's not going to help
so you have to know that this you have
to at least do some of these things you
know you don't have to do all of them
it's life is overwhelming there's a lot
going on you just get some of them in
cilantro is one of it one of the things
we need in it grabs on the heavy metals
which robs food away from Epstein bar
that's how you heal parsley that's
another one that robs metal from Epstein
bar it does remove some metal but it
also pushes out Epstein bar toxins
raspberries helps restore the nervous
system which is a result of Epstein bar
fennel that's another one fennel juice
you take the bulbs and you juice them
that helps clean up clean epine bar of
the system Ginger is another one
supplements to kill off and lower the
load knock the viral load over time
silver hydrol so silver hydrol you know
you get the best one on the market and
you take a little bit a little bit at a
time that's a great one zinc having
enough zinc the reason why Epstein bar
has done so much damage to begin with is
because most of us have a severe zinc
deficiency there's no zinc left barely
left in food anymore it's been like this
for a century and this is another reason
why Epstein bar is kind of grabbing a
whole hold you build your zinc reserves
reserves up long term and you're going
to be in a better place B12 especially
the one I talk about the adino silk
balamin that B12 restores nervous
systems so you lose your symptoms
resulted from Epstein bar lemon bomb
incredible EBV killer Epstein bar killer
builds up the immune system knocks EBV
EBV out selenium protects the nervous
system sparina helps pull Metals away
from Epstein bar and it's
antiviral red Marine algae that's a
powerful antiviral too kills off EBV
Epstein bar monol Lauren breaks down
Epstein bar breaks it down pushes it out
of the body very important
Eline Eline someone may say well I've
taken Eline before now you have to take
it you have to take a decent amount of
it what I suggest is you you know you
you take the supplements I'm talking
about meaning you take them to your
practitioner you take them to your
doctor I take everything I'm saying you
can take it to your practitioner you can
take it to your healer you can take it
to your doctor and say you know I want
to take this or that and you have your
you have your your doctor your your
naturopath or your functional medicine
doctor plug plug the wires in and put
the light bulb on top and just and get
get active with you and start helping
because if you're on enough Li scene the
differences occur licorice root licorice
root tea or highquality licorice root
products in incredible for knocking down
Epstein bar but a lot of people are
afraid of uh licorice because of certain
things you know there's meaning because
of rumors or something it's another
thing too is is losing fear over some of
the things some of the rumors or the
myths or the the fads and trends that
kind of go in the wrong direction 5 mthf
methylfolate that one's a great one for
Epstein bar and vitamin C vitamin C
every sing single day you know the
highest quality vitamin C you can find
can talk to your practitioner you know
that's important or you know or or just
you may have a vitamin C you already
you're already comfortable with and you
use it it just breaks apart Epstein bar
and pushes it out of the system now some
people say well wait a minute can
Epstein bar really go away can we do
something about it does it go away it
can can we heal can you kill off epine
bar you can kill off 90% of it and
regain your life and leave some in and
this is interesting you don't want it
all gone you want a little bit left it
prevents you from getting another
variety of Epstein bar it prevents you
from Catching another variety of
mononucleosis caused by a different
variety of Epstein bar so having a
little bit of your own in is not a bad
thing it is a good thing but you want to
knock down as much as you can and you
gain your life and you gain control and
you get your life back and you can with
Epstein bar I've watched it I've seen it
I've seen hundreds do it I have people
here lived 30 years now completely free
from every symptom I mentioned and
they're in their their 70s they're in
their 80s I have people in that
condition where they're like gardening
every day they're exercising they do
what they want and they were tragically
sick 30 years ago so yes the hope is
there you keep the faith you can heal
you can move forward everybody deserves
to heal you have a god-given right to
heal that's your right you own that
right it exists and you can heal and you
can move forward and you have to
understand this is not your fault that
you even have symptoms it's not your
fault that you've even been ill or had
these conditions or struggled with it
you didn't create it it's not your fault
you're a good person you know you didn't
do this not Karma this isn't Karma and
you didn't deserve to be sick in this
lifetime right now you didn't create
this problem that you have right now
with Epstein bar this is a virus that's
been around this is a virus that's been
around it's not being acknowledged it's
been here in Family Lines our family
lines can you know have it this is this
is serious I mean our great-grandparents
have it our grandparents and it gets
passed on down the line and there's
things you can do about it and heal and
when you know about it and you
understand about it it weakens it see
see knowing the
truth that's how you win and it breaks
down and it cleans up and you can push
it out of your life and push it out of
your system when it's mysterious and
nobody knows what's going on and you're
just sitting there with symptoms and
you're going to doctor to doctor it's
harder to get through it it's harder to
heal but the but the tide has changed
now it's changed this is your time to
move forward with this and all the
symptoms you've had this is your time
and your life right now and everything
that you've suffered from is valuable
and not wasted if you've suffered for
years it's valuable it's worth its
weight and gold Liquid Gold because it's
information you've learned it's
experiences you've experienced it's
pushed you to different levels of of
spiritual levels it's pushed you into
different areas of your life that you
wouldn't achieved different achievements
that you would have never done so when
we get challenged by this it's it's a
good thing it's not a bad thing we just
don't want to have it anymore we don't
want to have the symptoms anymore we
want to heal we don't want that you
severe fatigue and all the symptoms that
I mentioned before we can move forward
you're a good person and you have every
right to heal so you need to understand
that it's it's more than it's more than
time for you right now