hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 or 20 or 30 years
to wait to answers to their illnesses
someone said to me the other day they
said you know I had to wait 20 years to
figure out what caused my Hashimoto
thyroiditis 20 years and and the person
said to me well you know I was told it
was my body attacking itself so I was
convinced my body was working against me
all those years and it was something I
never forgot every morning I woke up
this person said to me every morning
they woke up they felt well oh my God
how further how much further did my body
go to attack itself like is there more
damage being done um is something being
done about it and it was just nothing
but but fear and worry for 20 years and
I felt terrible I felt terrible that
this person had to go through this and
not know Advanced information I couldn't
find it and they couldn't find it
anywhere else they said there was no one
talking about it no one ever said the
real cause of Hashimoto thyroiditis
anywhere nobody talked about it wasn't
written anywhere wasn't in any books and
this person was you know an ADV you know
Health person where you know lots of
lots of books you know had like you know
200 different Health books and you know
read all kinds of Articles was up to
date with the the newest information
from you know from doctors that are
putting out information that are well
known you name it and just had no idea
that the body doesn't attack itself so
so when I mean 10 20 30 years ahead of
what's B basically what's out there and
do you have 10 20 30 years to wait to
have answers I'm serious Spirit serious
about this now it's no joke when someone
actually has to go through through that
have you gone through that at all
because a lot of people are so this
person was like you know I'm relieved to
know that my body is actually defending
itself it's defending itself against a
pathogen called Epstein bar that's what
enters into the thyroid causing
Hashimoto's thyroiditis and this
person's like thank God I know now and
now I can do something about it I could
take care of myself I could knock out
the Epstein bar I could work on healing
I can move forward I can get past this I
can get off a thyroid medication I could
move past all of this and and and most
importantly I know that my body is not
attacking itself that was just told to
me because no one had answers so the
blame had to go on the person's body
that's how Medical Research Medical
Science works so as I said before do you
have 10 years to to learn this no you
know you have to learn this you have to
know this now if you just logged on and
this is your first show you know pick up
my book learn about it now um you know
get the answers and uh and and and yeah
it's important it's important people
have spent thousands thousands of
dollars I mean tens of thousands of
dollars sometimes hundreds of thousands
of dollars trying to get answers going
to Clinic to Clinic traveling around
just pick up a $16 book and find the
answers so you can just at least give
yourself some relief and know where
you're going and um and it's really
important and my new book actually
coming out life-changing Foods I and I'm
going to talk about a little later TI
I'm going to give you some information
out of of the book I thought it's like
so you knew what was going to be in
there something really cool and uh cuz
we're talking about Eye Health and I
want to talk about different things
about that so make sure you look into
that and um and everything but we don't
have to wait this long for all these
answers we can get this information now
there's no time to spare you know life
is precious we need to get that
information we we need to start the
healing now and move forward Today's
Show is about unmasking eye health
condition conditions do you have an eye
problem at all or eye health issues well
eye health problems like blurriness and
sty and cataracts and glaucoma and
falters and optic nerve issues and
burning and dryness and more are
extremely common their true causes are
still largely unknown until these
conditions are properly understood
healing will be limited you know today I
will reveal the truth behind common a
lot of common ey health issues I don't
know how many I'm going to be able to
cover but I'm going to cover as many as
I can we're always going to do another
show on every topic I do that's that's
the plan we're going to make sure we
cover all kinds of aspects of things
that you know I wasn't able to cover
during different shows so remember to go
to my website medicalmedium.com I offer
the free healing path um we put hundreds
of hours I put over 100 hours into it
making sure we was perfected and right
and we are giving it away for free so
that you don't have to pay for it so you
can get going with your health and it's
packed if you've ever listened to the
healing path don't think you just heard
everything by listening to it once
because even when I listen to it again I
go oh my god I didn't even know I can't
even believe I said that meaning I
didn't even know that I forgot or I
missed I missed it I can't believe I put
that in there cuz I was getting
information from Spirit putting it in
into the recordings so when I hear it
back I'm like whoa and and so make sure
that you listen to it a couple of times
take your time you know maybe over the
summer or something try to listen to a
couple of the recordings the audios and
um and and because you're going to start
you know ingesting and digesting
different things that you you didn't
hear or you might have missed or or you
need it to hear again I mean it's it's
it's a great resource and it's it's
really supportive um I've dedicated my
life to helping people and I'm here to
help you guys we're talking about we're
talking about Eye Health today so you
know when it comes down to eyes it
really comes down to antioxidants that's
where that word matters antioxidants
what's an antioxidant really it's a
phytochemical a group of phytochemicals
that actually stop you from dying that's
what they do they stop you from dying
they stop you from
aging they stop you from from
deteriorating that's what antioxidants
do think about that you know because
what do we do we oxidize we oxidize like
things do like things
oxidize like metal
oxidizes like a car gets Rusty well
right now cars are made out of plastic I
don't know what else they're made out of
now I think they're made out of plastic
and they're made out of what
fiberglass um you know paper mâché I
don't know what they're made out of Now
cars but it used to be made out out of
actual metal and you get a ding and then
it would start rusting uh I don't know
if you guys remember that does that date
me or
something bring me back too far but um
so so that oxidizing so right when water
would touch that open exposed metal or
that carbon steel or whatever it is you
know bam you know oxidizing would happen
rust well we rust we actually rust we
oxidize we fall apart we dissolve and
that's what happens here when we're
exposed to free radicals millions of
free radicals pesticides pollutants
chemicals there's crap falling out of
the sky right now I mean and I'm not
trying to put us into fear it's it's
it's why I wrote the life-changing Foods
book of that book The the subtitle to
that book is save yourself and the ones
you love with the hidden healing powers
of fruits vegetables orb spices and wild
Foods there's a reason for that because
we can use our food to stop stop us from
from oxidizing regardless of what kind
of crap is floating out of the sky
regardless of radiation that's still
floating out of the sky from World War
II you know from Hiroshima literally not
even a fraction of radiation has fallen
out of the sky from hoshima it's still
floating up there we haven't even it the
Fallout hasn't even happened never mind
Fukushima hasn't even happened yet it's
just starting to rain on it so so what
can we do we can totally battle that we
can totally adapt to that we can totally
rise above that and that's what I
explain in life-changing Foods never
been done before the information I put
in there from Spirit to actually protect
us and our families and our children
with Foods information about Foods never
talked about ever before I made sure are
in that book I didn't care what it took
to write that book I didn't care what it
took how many hours I had to stay up
late how much sleep I lost I didn't care
how crappy I felt I didn't care that
book had to get done because I need
everybody to have that and so when we
talk about antioxidants that's a big
part of what's in the book too when we
talk about antibi
antioxidants okay I was going to say
something antibiotics actually really
oxidize us they really oxidize us I was
jumping ahead I was going to talk about
that a little later so we take
antibiotics for different things that
quickens the oxidizing phase our organs
start to oxidize our liver oxidizes so
if we had antibiotics in us going all
the way back we need a lot of
antioxidants a lot of antioxidants more
antibiotics you've used the more
antioxidants you need on every way shape
and form and and so that that's that's
what matters and I talk about in
previous shows about the 80,000 meals if
you've had 40,000 crappy meals or 40,000
not healthy meals or 40,000 uh you
nonuse full
meals um if you've had that you know
then we need to make up we need make up
time because or if you've had 20,000
meals in your lifetime depending on how
old you are now we need to make up all
that and take this serious and get some
good meals in us and we can do it we're
going to talk about different foods
today um as well so when it comes down
to Eye Health eyes are affected by
oxidizing by things oxidizing in our
body heavy metals oxidizing in our body
pesticides oxidizing our body stuff
falling out of the sky you name it
coming out of there and um and just just
sprinkles on down literally just every
day and that's okay we can adapt above
it we can totally live in it without it
affecting us if we protect ourselves Eye
Health matters a lot because if we have
any kind of eye issues um it's related
to deficiencies it's related to
antioxidants it's related to weight too
many free radicals basically just
poisons floating around in the body
having their day and so we're going to
cover different aspects of our health so
that we can protect our eyes so it's a
big deal when it comes down fruits
vegetables herbs you know spices wild
Foods this is what we need for our eyes
that's what matters you know we always
talk about the color of our eyes right
isn't that what it's all about what's on
your driver's license is say eye color
on there you got brown color eyes you
got blue you got green um so yeah it
it's all about eye color and then you
meet somebody and you're like oh my God
look at your eyes look how look how
amazing the color of your eyes are and
it's all about eye color and when it
comes down to um when it comes down to
that very like term you know what's the
color of your eyes we need to flip it to
what's the color of your food what's the
color of of your food that's what we
need to do what's what kind of what food
are you eating that has color in it of
any kind and this is one of the most
important aspects of Eye Health is
what's what kind of colors are you
actually eating and we know that we know
colors that's already been going out
that that round that information is is
not specifically new um so but but
colors matter so it's those pigments
it's it's that it's that color in the
food that lines up to the eyes in a lot
of ways because what's in that color
lots of antioxidants so the blue skin of
a
blueberry that blue skin in that
blueberry that's packed with
antioxidants and that is incredible for
the eyes right there that's a big deal
so that's the antioxidants we need now
if it's a wild blueberry it's blue all
the way through blue all the way through
if it's a weak cultivated blueberry it's
white and clear in the center with a
blue skin so now that's fine if you it's
all you got so if that's all you got is
that clamshell that little pint-sized
clamshell that you find at the uh the
health food store or the protu section
and it's the cultivated blueberry It's a
larger blueberry and it's kind of white
and clear inside and that's all you got
it's still good for you it's still going
to help it's still going to help in some
ways with your eyes but you want to look
for that wild blueberry
you know people say to me you just love
the wild blueberry I go how can I not
love the most powerful food on the
planet that literally can stop any
disease and symptom that's going on in
our lives how can I am I supposed to
stop talking about the wild
blueberry am am I I'm supposed to be
done okay I talked about it one time
that's it no it's that
important and it's blue all the way
through all the way through purple and
blue all the way through and so that's
what I'm talking about when it comes
down to Eye Health right there that
example Alone um in life-changing Foods
I really Lay It lay it out about what
the wild blueberry does for our bodies
and what it does for our soul and
everything and the power of it and um
because it's it's a lot to talk about in
in just one show it literally could take
over one show the wild blueberry so it
comes down to Colors just like we're
always focused on the color of our eyes
hey you got green eyes wao they're so
pretty or you got you know blue eyes
look at that or whatever it is it's it
should be like hey wow that food has
that color who look at the color of that
food and and that matters because that's
antioxidants and it matters now okay
fine now there's there's something else
you have to understand the inside of
food that doesn't have a lot of color we
don't want to negate that on any level
so the inside of a radish is white
but that doesn't mean something else
special isn't in there okay so that
doesn't mean that something else isn't
really special in there so always
remember that so foods that have white
to them or clear to them still have
something in them they have minerals
they have minerals that's the other
aspect of your eyes color Okay color
matters with the food that's one thing
that we got to connect to the eyes
that's critical and the other one is you
know is that the mineral composition so
it's antioxidants with color and then
it's the mineral composition these are
the two things that we have to use for
our eyes and this is critical we're
going to talk about different facets of
what's going on people's eyes we're
going to get into that we're going to
get into the nitty-gritty there um so
because what happens is when you get
inside of food when you get inside of
food you got chromium in there you got
selenium in there you got manganese in
there you got M mbum you got in there
you got uh you got you know a little bit
of zinc zinc is a hard one it's hard to
get zinc and food no matter where we
really search but there's still traces
left in some foods so either way it's
the mineral composition too in these
foods that are so important so
understand that remember that
um so let's talk about like some eye
symptoms and eye conditions you guys
ready for that I figure someone out
there has an eye problem in some way
some shape or some
form let's talk about
blurriness blurriness of the eyes now
here's here's the deal with blurriness
it's complicated it's complicated
because everybody's blurriness is
different it's different someone else's
blurry eyes isn't someone else's blurry
eyes that it's entirely a different
thing going on there's other there a
whole bunch of reasons why we have
blurry eyes and let's explore some of it
uh eyes are so complicated we're just
going to get what we can get done so for
example one person could have blurry
eyes caused by macular
degeneration okay so macular
degeneration you guys know that one did
you go to the eye doctor and like hey I
the eye doctors like I see some
degeneration in here we get we got some
problems um so maybe you're one that's
been going through that or you you've
been through that see now macular
degeneration is first of all is an
antioxidant deficiency and a mineral
deficiency it's an antioxidant
deficiency and a mineral deficiency you
have to know that about Immaculate
degeneration it's it's it's not
technically like uh it's not like other
things that go wrong with eyes it's
really just for the first 10 years of
your life you had just food that had
really nothing in it first 20 years of
your life you might have food that's had
nothing in it first 30 years of your
life um I always kid around and say you
know people eat fruit when it's on their
Strawberry Shortcake so they have
strawberries when it's on Strawberry
Shortcake they eat blueberries when it's
in a pancake they eat blueberries when
it's in a muffin you know I remember um
years ago a friend of mine was like look
I eat a lot of blueberries I was like
well where are you getting them and my
friend says well I have a blueberry
muffin every morning I I I couldn't
believe it yeah first of all I laughed
you know I had a good laugh which is
probably maybe that's not the the best
thing that that I could have done for
support but it was the first thing I did
anyway I couldn't help it I I do tend to
laugh a lot but the point is is that you
know he really thought that all the all
the blueberries and a blueberry muffin
were going to cut it and I said well
where's your blueberry muffin where did
you get it and what you know what are
they using and then they're using fake
blueberries on top of
it so sorry about that you guys so
they're using fake blueberries on top of
it was it even real blueberries in the
blueberry muffin they're fake
blueberries there's actually fake
blueberries they're actually fake
they're made out of some kind of like uh
jelly and some kind of um um some kind
of gelatinous stuff that's dyed blue and
flavored blue so anyway so he was
getting lots of blueberries and um you
know and then some people you know they
have you know they get their apple and
apple pie some people get their bananas
and banana you know Sundays or whatever
you call those at the ice cream parlor
and um Banana Splits or whatever you
know in different places you can get
them and and then you know every now and
then someone has you know like a slice
of Mandarin or something like that in
like in like some kind of holiday thing
or they have a piece of fruit cake piece
of fruit cake with dried sulfured fruit
in it in the holidays look you guys
might be getting pissed off at me right
now cuz that might be that's might be
what you're doing you might be doing
something like that and now you're
getting mad at me but look the deal is
is that um um you we can go through a
hunk of our life without getting enough
antioxidants we can go through a hunk of
our life without getting what we need
and it can pass by so we got makeup time
to do we got makeup time to do just
fasten your seat bels you know I haven't
said that in a while we just got to do
it we're going to have to fastet our
seat belts for this because we got we
got we got respons responsibilities
today we got responsibilities we got to
start eating better and all right and
look some of you guys out there are
killing it right now you guys are eating
you guys are just eating really good I
mean you're you're eating probably
better than me I mean seriously I've
seen people out there that are eating so
good that I'm like whoa and a mind blown
from it because they're doing nothing
but their smoothies and they're doing
lots and lots of wild blueberries and
I'm like wo I didn't even have my wild
blueberries today and so I'm really
proud of every but I'm proud of
everything everybody I'm proud of
everybody because you know we all got
different circumstances and we got to
just do the best we can and eat when we
can and eat what we can get what we can
I I I understand the whole situation um
so blurriness of the eyes so say we got
Mac degeneration that's like a
historic piece of your life that's
that's missing something or or basically
it's history in your life with all these
missing pieces and these Miss missing
pieces are antioxidants at all these
different times in your lives and
minerals minerals from foods that you
know they're mineral
rich and that comes from fruits
vegetables herb
spices uh and wild Foods that's where it
comes from it comes from there so we're
going to you know and and that's the
whole thing that's that's where it comes
from and um and like I talk about
life-changing Foods I talk about every
disease and illness literally a fruit or
a vegetable herb spice can help
reverse um all right so immaculate
degeneration it's about antioxidants
what do we need to do we're going to
talk about foods to help that a little
later on we're going to talk about
supplements to help that a little later
on but that's one form of blurriness you
guys that's one form of
blurriness and then what about another
form of blurry vision that's different
that that isn't the same thing and you
know the doctor's look you go to the
doctor the eye doctor you say hey look
you know I got these blurry eyes I don't
know what's going on here is it my
prescription do I need
glasses and the eye doctor looks and the
eye doctor says say you have
prescriptions anyway the eye doctor says
well your prescriptions are fine they ly
up um you have no macular degeneration
you got no glaucoma you got nothing else
going on I don't know why you have
blurry eyes the mystery blurry eyes okay
that's neurological that's neurological
that's central nervous system so mystery
blur eyes is a central nervous system
and if anybody dealing with it's going
to they're going to know that it gets a
little better in the morning okay so
when they wake up the morning they might
be a little blurry at first for a few
minutes but when they Shake It Off and
and get out of their tiredness and
everything else their eyes are more
clear and then towards the end of the
day they just get more blurry by night
time they get blurry blurry and they're
just totally blurry and that's ner
that's the central nervous system that's
the kind of blurriness that gets in the
way of people driving you have a
sensitive central nervous system that's
that blurriness is usually from um other
things happening like a blood toxicity a
liver condition um heavy metals in the
liver uh viral issues like an Epstein
bar in the liver so maybe you guys have
noticed that with some of your Epstein
bar issues that you're learning now here
at the show and you're learning with
with the different you know Facebook
groups and everything that we're
teaching the information about epsteen
bar that your blurry eyes really really
can be that low-grade uh viral thing
because the FD bar releases poisons and
toxins and the liver gets filled with
toxins the blood gets toxic and you get
the blurry eyes it affects the central
nervous system it then that's what
happens it's one form of blurry eyes
right there and
then there's another type of blurry eyes
cuz blurry eyes are the most popular
issue actually one of the most popular
issues so I'm really hitting that hard
now there's another type of blurry eyes
and this blury eye is about blood sugar
it's about blood sugar so blood sugar
issues hypoglycemia
hypoglycemia mostly hypo um and uh
inconsistent blood blood sugar issues uh
glucose
deficiencies um you know that all that
sporadic blood sugar you know high high
A1C whatever and that you know those
blood sugar disorders whatever someone
has even on a mild level will give you
blurry eyes that could easily give you
blurry eyes and a lot of the different
type 2 diabetes pre- diabetes high
A1C um um uh hypoglycemia all that is is
is adrenals and liver adrenals and liver
adrenals and liver so once again we're
back to the liver we're back to
adrenals and um that's a big part of
that all on its own so that's another
form of blurry vision so that means that
look protect your adrenals if you're in
that form of blurry vision it's time to
protect your adrenals it's time to eat
every hour and a half can't let your
blood sugar drop uh lower the animal
protein um you know the more animal
protein you eat with hypoglycemia you'll
feel like it balances out but the worse
it'll get and turn into pre-diabetes so
it means you have to lower the animal
protein I'm not against animal protein
I'm just saying if you're dealing with
hypoglycemia you're dealing with blurry
eyes because of blood sugar issu you got
to lower the animal protein could maybe
eat it once a day and the rest has to be
more fruits and vegetables and salads
and and um different things like that
that we always talk about and you'll see
you can get a little bit better but you
have to eat every hour hour and a half
if you're dealing with that kind of
blurry eye and that's a big deal so you
want to support your adrenals and
strengthen your adrenals clean up your
liver and um and then maybe down the
road you can bring in more animal
protein if you want you know once you
get it under control and get it in a
better place and and don't set yourself
in the in in the stage for pre-diabetes
and diabetes um and so that's that and
as long you just have to have a healthy
diet too around it all but that's one
type of blurry eyes that we're talking
about and so um and then there's other
things too let's let's leave blurry eyes
for a little bit let's go into other
areas too people talk about glasses they
say well if you need glasses you got
some you know you got a health problem
or you got eye problems not necessarily
with glasses that's not how it works um
if a child needs glasses early this is
this is mercury inherited from the
family this is mercury passed down from
the family line Mercury causes people to
need
glasses not entirely every reason why
people need to to have glasses but it is
responsible for people needing glasses
Mercury is is um disorient disorientates
the eye it basically it basically throws
off the eyes the eye muscles it throws
off the eyes responses it throws off the
um even some of the nerves behind the
eye Mercury does a whole bunch of things
and if it's systemic if Mercury is
systemic and it comes from a family line
or you picked up new Mercury you know
you know children will have will need
glasses and they will need them soon
literally it can happen overnight and
that's what happens with Mercury and the
Mercury's effect on as far as everything
to do with Eye Health so it's a big part
of it right there so um some people
collect little bit a little bit of
mounts of mercury throughout their whole
life they have a little bit of inherited
and then they um collect it over you
know all through their life and all
through their life and then their eyes
start going at they start kneading
glasses at age 40 age 42 age 44 this is
just your normal average buildup of
heavy metal toxicity forcing you know
glasses to be needed um this is a big
part of it and so when it comes down to
glasses it's really just you know higher
levels of mercury in the body um and but
we're not allowed to talk about Mercury
ever
instead we have to completely avoid it
like it doesn't exist um in
life-changing Foods I really Let it
Loose about the things that are taking
us down as a culture as a society and
really harming us and one of those is
Mercury and um but hey everybody wants
to blame it on our jeans because no one
wants to go there no one wants to go
there no one wants to know what's really
causing our problems and how you know we
have this Mercury that's being passed
from generation to generation it's
ruining our eyes it's causing all kinds
of trouble but hey no blame it on our
jeans it's always the easy way out it's
the best way out because it's your fault
that means it's your fault I love that I
love how it's always blamed on us
autoimmune it's your fault genetics it's
your fault um you know you're just a
pain in the ass it's your fault how
about that so that's just not how it
works it's how it should work and and we
need to change that tide and it's
important and that's what that's that's
the whole point so we have to be honest
about the Mercury that we have that
we're inherited and we get uh you know
affected by now and collect throughout a
lifetime and it has to come out that's
why the heavy metal detoxes are
important so what I'm saying is if
you're somebody dealing with eyeglasses
needing eyeg glasses it's heavy metal
detox is what you have to do is what you
need to do someone said to me recently
you know you you wear glasses Anthony
and I said do you know my
story do you know my story because if
you don't know my story let me give you
a little uh a little basis a little
Foundation of my story
you know I live my life 34 blind because
I see nothing but white from spirit's
light because I do readings non-stop my
entire life so everybody you know people
if you're not blind for other reasons or
handicapped or blind for other reasons
um and um and you're not blind and you
have you have you know your regular
eyesight you get to see you know your
whole life your whole there's no three
quarters missing I have three quarters
missing my life because it goes white
and I talk about that and I I've talked
about this before in different places
it's a it's a light blindness that comes
when Spirit does readings or I look
inside the body of
somebody and the um and and the light
that happens you know that's why I have
to need an assistant when I go on an
airplane because I just lose my eyesight
in the airport instantly because I'm
doing all the readings Spirit sending
light down I'm looking at everybody I'm
doing reads it's it's Unstoppable I
can't stop it's been happening since Age
4 and so what I did was um and I went to
the eye doctor uh and in myself and I
said you know what I'm going go to an
eye doctor I'm going to have my I'm
going to talk about my gift and how it
blinds out my light and take wipes it
all out and you know and I can't see so
the eye doctor looked at my eyes and
said well you got the perfect 2020
Vision so you don't have an eye problem
so you don't need glasses and I told him
about what was going on he said you know
what though we could probably throw on
some glasses so that when you go in
front of crowds and you do things that
you can see farther away with all the
haze of light that you got to live with
maybe it'll improve You by by um 1% or
something and it has it actually it
actually helps so when I'm doing events
or anything else it helps get through
the smoke and fog of that bright light
that Spirit sends down so that's why I
wear glasses but um but you know when I
do wear them and then but the point is
is that when we have to wear glasses
though in life and everything we we have
we're dealing with a Mercury issue we're
dealing with the heavy metal that we
have to deal with and that has to be
that has to be cleaned up and your eyes
will get better your eyes will get
better I lots of people I know that have
done the heavy metal
detox have um have they've gotten rid of
their glasses and they've been able to
toss them and throw them out um you know
don't do that yet make sure that you're
taking care making sure that you're
taking care of yourself um you know
meaning use your glasses for a while
until you start adjusting and then you
start adjusting and then you start
adjusting get the heavy metals out build
yourself up get the antioxidants in get
the minerals in with all the foods that
we're going to talk about a little later
and you can be one of those people that
actually doesn't need their glasses as
much anymore or in different or they you
your in eyesight improves enough where
you only need them partially or whatever
it is so um but as far as children
needing glasses at age six or age4 age8
that's from large deposits of mercury
that are that are that are p on Down the
Line plus new collections of it so let's
keep that in mind and um so let's talk
about some different things as well
glaucoma glaucoma that's an interesting
one eye pressure inflammation blood
vessels eye pressure the whole bit
that's from Epstein bar that's the
culprit for glaucoma there's an Epstein
bar virus of variety that causes
glaucoma and I've seen this variety not
do much of anything besides give
somebody a little fatigue until they
become 80 years old and they get the
glaucoma or they get a little fatigue at
age 60 70 doesn't really do much but the
variety of Epstein bar I'm talking about
ends up causing glaucoma so that's
that's actually one of the variety of of
varieties of Epstein bar and so you when
if you're dealing with glaucoma you got
to deal with antivirals antivirals
antivirals antivirals which leads me to
something to tell you that most I
conditions are viral and that's that's a
whole different that's a whole another
thing so let's talk about some different
eye conditions here we got glaucoma
which is viral that's Epstein bar
related so you want to do an anti-
Epstein bar protocols including diets
and all the different things to knock
that out and and and improve that so
your eye pressure comes down and I've
seen people's eye pressures drop from
getting the right things in them
including getting zinc in them and
getting the right Foods you know getting
rid of the eggs the dairy products um
doing some antivirals olive leaf you
know I've seen people's people get
better with that now lots of vitamin C
also helps get rid of glaucoma too over
time and drops the pressure down
now there's other things associated with
viral issues like burning eye burning
you know I've had people come to me o
over the years the worst eye burning and
it's hell and it and it completely
disables them and they can't function
they can't work they can't do anything
they got burning around their eyes they
got burning under their eyes they got
burning above their eyes they're running
around they think it's mold and it's not
mold and they go to you know 100
different doctors the neurologist you
name it and they get MRIs CAT scans at
the brain and the eye burning is
Relentless and that's really you know
that that kills me when I see somebody
going through that because um because
it's just it's it's horrible and so what
happens with that that's usually the
shingles that does the eye burning um
I've seen Epstein bar Edge onto it
sometimes or hedg it but the shingles
tend to do a lot of eye burning you
don't need a rash to have the eye
burning although some people they break
out shingles on the shoulder they break
out shingles on the shoulder um the
shoulder blade back uh you know uh neck
torso what they break out with a
shingles and then it goes away 5 years
later they have burning eyes that's
that's later stage shingles without the
rash so um and you don't even have to
have the rash in order to have that so
the burning eyes is is a lot of shingle
stuff so what you do is um you know we
work on the shingles protocols uh very
important uh so that's that's critical
but it's good good to know what's
causing it tickling tingling Sensations
on the side of the face causing eye
issues you know temple on the temple
causing eyes to squint causing eyes to
feel weak causing eyes to burn a little
bit that's all shingles it's all viral
too floaters floaters white spots black
spots unexplained you're at the eye
doctor don't know what the hell it is
that's that's Epstein bar that's Epstein
BR that's 100% viral it's a lot of
neurotoxin floating around in the body
um and short circuits the it actually
short circuits currents and electrical
currents that go to the eye and causes
floaters it causes all kinds of
different things now I'm not talking
about detach retina and you see
something because you got to detach
retina and you're seeing you know a dark
spot or you're seeing something else I'm
talking about floaters that are
unexplained that's all Epstein bar 100%
um and it gets us every time the
floaters are really annoying that's
that's that's something that's really
annoying that's why I'm doing the life
changing Foods book I put it out there
because I have that symptom showing what
foods to deal with that symptom you
focus on that symptom take the foods out
of the book focus on just those foods
and you get better you start moving
forward and you start going past things
um so floaters is a big one there uh
trigeminal neuralgia trigeminal
neuralgia is caused by shingles that's
something that goes up the neck it goes
in the jaw it goes in you know you get
told you have TMJ sometimes you don't
get told you have TMJ but you just have
that pain that tends to run to the eye
causing eye pain so eye pain unexplained
eye pain is the nerves caused by
trigeminal neuralgia caused by shingles
that's a whole another one too so let me
just simplify you got eye pain it's
unexplainable it's the shingles
simplified okay if we want to complicate
it yes it's trigeminal neuralgia it's
from the neurotoxin from shingles
inflaming the nerve the trigeminal nerve
when that nerve gets inflamed it'll give
you eye pain that's a little bit more
the complicated version so um and it
gets you know and and there's just more
to it than that too so that that's
another example migrains I Rel Rel ated
migraines okay yep I related
migraines um ocular migraines different
kinds of migraines um all then affect
eyes going to the eyes once again viral
and heavy metals too though so that's a
whole combination of viral and heavy
metals shingles virus is one of them
I've even seen you know I mean the
Epstein bar too I've even seen other
things like hhv6 throw that into the the
mix um you know some people have really
high versions of you know CMV uh ceglar
virus and I've seen that kind of amp up
the anti a little bit as far as creating
poisons but understand this migraines
yes viral eye problems from migraines so
that's a whole another angle a lot of
people with migraines go to the eye
doctor all the time eye issues all the
time they're wondering what's going on
getting checked all the time so that's
another example let's talk about
something else I just I know I always
run us out a time but we got time we
still got time hang in there is the seat
belt still on are you guys hanging in
there cuz I'm hoping
so um um sty who gets a sty out there
who gets chronic sty they're awful
that's strepa cacus that's strep in the
system that's strep in the sinuses that
sit there dormant comes out it causes a
sty your immune system breaks down um so
that's that you can even you can even
put you know e sty are are also from
fresh strep so strep that you've you
know you grabbed a door knob in a really
kind a greasy door knob in kind of a
really dirty place and then you just had
your finger in your eye for like 10
minutes because you decided to rub your
eye um then you know that that's an easy
sty coming also I've seen people get the
flu virus and or colder flu and it it
directly it dropped the immune system um
the congestion actually feeds any kind
of ongoing strepa cacus issue that's
happening and that sty can break out
just from the strep so we have a lot of
strep in our system I'm doing a whole
show on strep so you know all the
different ins and outs of it as much as
I can give you on on you know in a show
and I'm doing that coming up pretty soon
so hang in there for that but sty are
are mostly strep
related and um and so that's something
that we got to keep our immune system um
up zinc got to have your vitamin C you
know all that has to be there for your
immune system let's talk about some
other things too optic nerve issues 100%
viral 100% viral optic nerve issues
optic neuritis optic neuritis there's
all kinds of different nerve issues with
the optic nerve so when you go to the
eye doctor and they look and they look
deep into the nerve they do a test they
say hey your optic nerves look healthy
and um if they don't look healthy that's
a viral infection uh right there Epstein
bar it's one of the varieties of Epstein
bar that causes op optic neuritis and
also different kinds of op optic nerve
issues um you know you start you know
start getting problematic issues with an
eye or one eye or two eyes uh usually
just one eye with optic nerve issue
that's viral so we got to go antiviral
um another reason why the fruits the
vegetables herb spices the wild foods
are antiviral it matters so much I'm
going to blame viral because it's the
truth of what things are instead of
blaming you and your body and your
health so your body being autoimmune
your body attacking itself I'm not going
to go that direction I'll never go that
Direction ever because it's not accurate
it's completely incorrect I'm going to
blame the viral issue so you may as well
learn and know these viral issues and um
I'm proud of you guys for just being
here being here and wanting to know the
truth um so so
cataracts cataracts is another good one
that that's pesticide exposure that's
pesticides building up um if you're
someone that's had to eat conventional
food your entire life uh without any
organic food coming in most likely
you're heading to heading into some
cataracts um that's that's an in the
cataracts believe it or not is also old
DDT that's in our system from you know
from uh four fathers and four moms and
four dads and and uh and um our
great-grandparents and so forth so you
know DDT sits in us and it just sits in
us and sits in us and it gets past the
generation past the generation it takes
it might take a hundred generations to
get DDT out of US unless you adapt or
know how to get rid of it in
life-changing Foods book I talk about
DDT being one of the big culprits still
today um you know not just the heavy
metals but that too DDT and other
pesticides and herbicides cataracts is
pesticide herbicide and old DDT that's
what it is in your system um so you know
that's something to to understand so
it's about taking out it's about taking
out all the uh pesticides all the
herbicides we can out of the body with
the right kind of foods you know and
that matters too so
a lot of eye problems in general you
know are um are fixable fixable fixable
a lot of eye injuries um tend to not be
as easy to fix but we can still support
the eye we have left or both eyes if
they're
injured um so dryness ey dryness welcome
to adrenal issues welcome to adrenal
issues with dry eyes dry minus and stuff
that's a big piece of it big piece of it
um adrenals have a big role it's not the
entire reason some people get dry eyes
because they get blockages in the Ducks
um you know these these blockages are
from low-grade bacterial infections such
as strep and even staff staff's actually
another one that gets in the eye that
can cause a sty too it's not just 100%
strep but it's close but sty actually
you know can be can be staffed too I
forgot to tell you guys that olizee and
um so dry eyes got to get your adrenal
strong without a doubt see it's all
about adrenal Health look you know maybe
listen to the older uh adrenal Health
show we're doing another adrenal Health
show eventually so we support the
adrenals for that let's talk about Foods
let's talk about supplements for the
eyes bringing eyes back let's do that
while we have a little time left wild
blueberries yes wild blueberries most
powerful number one eye food there is in
the world nothing else can touch it
nothing nothing nothing there's no weed
in the jungle I'm just sorry to say
there's nothing in the rainforest that
can touch the wild blueberry there's a
there's powerful stuff in the rainforest
there's amazing things in the jungle
absolutely but nothing can touch the
strength of the wild blueberry it's the
most powerful food on planet Earth today
I have to make sure you know that in
this time why I'm here on this planet
you know before I leave I have to make
sure you know what the most powerful
food is on the planet I do a whole
section in life-changing Foods about
that that's a good food uh mango is a
good food is a good food that's a great
one for eyes let me tell you though you
know um Spirit has has given me
information of what mango does for all
kinds of illnesses and diseases I put it
in the life-changing Foods book let me
give you an example mangoes are
incredible for acid reflux incredible
for
ADHD um help mango top reverse
Alzheimer's disease dementia ulcers skin
cancers insomnia stomach cancer renal
failure peptic ulcers diabetes
Parkinson's disease kidney stones
epilepsy hypoglycemia Cron's disease
post-traumatic stress
disorder okay urinary tract infections
depression
personal issues associated with anxiety
mangoes can help you with anx anxiety
Eating Disorders they help with eating
disorders they help with adrenal fatigue
chronic fatigue syndrome caused by
Epstein bar cognitive issues colitis
Cushing syndrome fibroids fatty liver
mystery infertility that's what mangoes
do that's an example of what's in
life-changing Foods book by the way I'm
using some of that content right now and
symptoms trouble sleeping mood swings
snoring are you snoring sunburn fatigue
slug isness um muscle fatigue muscle
pain muscle cramps anxiousness cognitive
issues brain fog memory loss Melancholy
listlessness abdominal pressure candida
overgrowth Bells Ball Z mango helps with
every bit of that and and I don't mean
just like a little piece of mango it
means one day you just have to say
mangoes are in season or hey like look I
found some great mangoes at the
supermarket I'm going to eat two a day
every day for a while and you're going
to start heading getting in the
direction to start reversing things and
that's that's that specific information
of what the mango does not just in I
health and ey Health too but all these
other things is what I have listed
specifically in the life-changing Foods
book along with hundreds and hundreds of
other things going on in that book so
just letting you know and also what it
does emotionally to support us mangoes
actually help us when we've been let
down they help us Lift us up when we've
been let down or we're changing our
direct we need to change our Direction
they help us change our Direction they
help us connect to Destiny they help us
feel better when we've been cut off or
we're lonely or even
abandoned so mangoes give us emotional
support and so do other fruits
vegetables wild herbs and spices and
wild Foods I list in this book about
what it does in an emotional level and
spiritual level I don't have time to go
into the spiritual level but even on a
spiritual level asparagus are great for
Eyes by the way incredible food orange
is great for the eyes great avocado
parsley celery juice once again I've had
people tell me their eyes are getting
better from doing celery juice okay even
a little touch of saffron is really good
for like cataracts and good for other
things little touch of saffron um
fennel spinach winter squash even
carrots if you're a carrot person let's
do some carrots
um you know they are okay for the eyes
absolutely sweet potatoes really good
for the eyes spirulina that one barly
grass juice powder amazing to keep your
your nerves healthy in the eyes to help
pull heavy metals out of the brain and
body actually out of the body wild
blueberries pull heavy metals out of the
brain wild blueberries pull DDT and
toxins out of the body so these Foods
matter every last bit of them matter
elderberry tea pick up some elderberry
tea
ibrite there's an herb called ibrite
it's not good for your eye because it's
called I bright it's good for your eye
because it's antiviral it helps knock
down a lot of different viruses it helps
lower down bacteria like strep to help
your eyes get better with whatever eye
issue you're dealing with Ginko Boba
that's actually good for your eyes
nettle Leaf get a cup of nettle Leaf
going once a day and I talk about these
Foods in detail what they do on
spiritual levels emotional level
sickness illness in the book too and
life-changing Foods eser C crank up the
vitamin C you run across somebody with
eye issues you crank up the vitamin C
you know you you assist people
definitely do that assisting assist them
get them on some vitamin C get yourself
on vitamin C zinc that's a big one big
one for stopping viral issues and
selenium so see how important it is to
to eat all these different foods and hey
look you know I'm with you I'm with you
on this and I'm staying with you on this
we're going to do this together so you
know eyes mean a lot because it's how we
see although there are people out there
with perfect eyesight but they're
completely blind to what's happening out
there in the world but not you guys not
you guys you guys see everything you
guys are seeing everything you guys are
intuitive you guys are there you guys
are awake you guys are on on you guys
are in it you guys are investing you
guys are you guys are investing in your
health you're investing in your being
you're investing in everything and it's
incredible and I have to tell you I am
blown away 100% And just know I care and
you're unbelievable mark your calendar
for next week's show where I'll be
talking about Mysteries of the thyroid
Mysteries of the thyroid next week's
show millions of people deal with
mysterious weight gain hair loss are you
dealing with hair loss fatigue brain fog
hot flashes dry skin restless legs
insomnia impaired memory depression
menopause symptoms anxiety dizziness and
more sound familiar well guess what it's
related to the thyroid and we're going
to explain why you can't miss that show
it's too cool and um remember to go to
my website medical medium.com um the
healing path that's another thing too
and if you haven't locked down a copy of
the lifechanging foods book check it out
uh it's out there check it out it's on
Amazon everything else just look for it
and um it's packed jammed packed with
how to protect ourselves how to protect
our children how to protect the future
you know of the earth what we need to do
how we can heal from all different
diseases illnesses how we can adapt how
we can protect ourselves and what food
really does for us for the first time
ever and not to mention there's 50
recipes in there that are geared from
Spirit just know that we love you I
believe in you I stand behind you um you
did notate your illness okay um and
you're a good person you pat yourself on
the back know that I care know that I
love you take one day at a time have
compassion for yourself pat yourself on
the back you're a good person and we
love you over here dearly bless your
heart you know have a you know have a
good week I'm behind you one day at a
time just know I love you bless you
byebye take care take care