[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show we're talking about fearing celery
juice all the fears the the fear that's
created out there you know goes along
with myths and rumors and rumors and
fears and you know it's unbelievable
what happens out there so that's what
we're talking about really important
Advanced information have science and
research that's what medical medium
shows are about medical medium books
medical medium Liver Rescue and the rest
of the books and medical medium celery
juice that book too make sure you have
it it's really a critical one and it's
really important actually for so many
reasons I mean I can't touch what's in
that book and through these radio shows
always remember that I know that some
people one person said to me hey I could
just listen to your radio show I don't
need to get your book I'm like okay if
that's what you want to do but there's
there's the radio shows they can't touch
what's in the book tremendous amounts of
information Way Beyond what I can do
here on the radio shows and um but we're
talking about the fears that are created
and what that is like what does that
mean you'll just hear them over and over
again all different kinds out there
and I'm just going to cover some because
the book has so many of them in there of
what you got to look out for what you're
hearing out there and all that there's
so much of that but I could only cover
some and I'm going to cover them right
now let's do it let's go straight into
it
oxalates so what you might see on social
media or other places is like acceler
juices has oxalates oxalates worry about
the oxalate thing oh wo there's so many
problems with that one all on its own
there is so many issues with that all on
its own do not be concerned about
oxalate oxyc acid in celery juice the
myth that certain leafy green vegetables
and herbs such as celery are high in
oxalates and therefore harmful is
completely misguided when I mean
completely misguided oxalates not even
barely exist in celery juice this is so
important this myth prevents so many
people from getting the powerful healing
they need it the nutrients the healing
properties that foods have and it you
know it could provide them with so many
nutrients and hearing a myth or a rumor
or a fear that really doesn't exist is
unbelievable might be well hey wait a
minute I'm sensitive to oxalates is it
are you you sure you sure that's what
you're sensitive when you eat something
because it's incredible what happens
I've had people tell me that and then
they eat something that doesn't have
oxalates in it or so-called doesn't have
oxalates in it and they're reacting on
those but they're not blaming oxalates
they're just they're not even blaming
the food but they're having bad
reactions a bad day a bad day with their
Foods a bad problem and this is just a
prime example right here oxalates are
not the concerned they are even believed
to be and that's a whole another issue
all and its own now I respect if you're
scared about oxalates or you believe
because you were told that that's
probably why you're having an issue I
respect that I totally do and look I'll
Stand By Your Side if you need me to do
that the one thing I will do is I'll
stand with you okay I will and you know
I will be a friend about that 100% but
don't worry about it in celery juice
whatever you do that's one place you
should not you you should not worry
about it do oxalates exist yeah they
exist but they're not what they're made
out to be or believe to be you got to
remember you guys that chronic illness
had this whole succession of De decades
before now okay and the Decades of
succession were people not knowing what
causes disease illness chronic symptoms
all the different mystery chronic
fatigue all the mystery f moralia
everything else you you name it they
still don't even know outside of the
medical medium books that puts the
information out there so you can learn
about that but because nobody knew why
everybody was sick all these theories
popped up over the decades candida
candida it's candida meanwhile candida
these people are viral and viral sick
really bad and I would tell different
doctors what are you talking about
candida that people are sick like really
sick with things like real things real
things going on like like other things
like strep in their gut eating away at
their Linings real things going on and
and I talk about all that and this what
I mean this is an example oxalates
oxalates you pull that out of a hat that
rabbit out of your hat because you you
know I was going to say rabbit out of
something else because you pull that out
because you don't know what's caus the
Epstein bar that's wreaking havoc giving
everybody fatigue and giving everybody
neurological problems and and and
depression and anxiety and everything
else these are the things these are the
fears that have cropped up over the
years lectin isn't lectin is another one
another one that's cropped up that
cropped up because still no one knows
what's wrong what creates hashimotos
thyroiditis and all these other
illnesses and everything like this you
see what I'm saying
this is serious stuff so oxalates is
another one just thrown in there okay
let's fear oxalates now oh and let's be
somebody on social media and say oh
oxalates and celerate Juice don't drink
it you just basically could have ruined
somebody life somebody's life by doing
that because what if that person avoids
celery juice when it's the one thing
that could literally take them out of
hell and bring them to Heaven what about
that okay take them out of hell and
bring them to Paradise how about that
bring them to a place where wo you mean
I'm actually getting better for the
first time in 5 years and I could have
listened to that jerk that said there's
oxalates in there think about that it
it's incredible how it works there are
oxalates in every single fruit vegetable
on the planet did you know that there's
more oxalates in more in every single
fruit and vegetable than celery
juice but also on the planet there's
oxalates on in everything there's
oxalates in animal proteins because the
animals are eating
they're eating plant
food so there's oxalates in all the
chicken there's o oxalates in all the
the the meat there's oxalates in Lamb
there's oxalates in all of it because
because the oxalates that's in the grass
if it's grass-fed the oxalates that are
in
everything there's oxalates filled in
Meats there's oxalates
everywhere but of course a piece of
fruit's going to be blamed for something
of course missing information fruit fear
stopping people from living longer
that's real great and let's just throw
celery in the mix celery juice Now
Incredible incred I can't say enough
about this one oxalates in a plum for
example are much different from those in
a piece of
cheese okay but there's oxalates in them
all this is an underfunded area to begin
with the medical research and science
cuz guess what there really isn't any
medical research and science on the
oxalate the
that's the whole point you guys that's
the whole point and research and science
is a theory that can only be funded for
a possible outcome always manipulated so
the investors of the theory are
happy over and over do I have to say
this and teach people it's incredible
how it works and you're not going to
hear this from anybody not one single
podcast out there not one single podcast
in health is going to say all the things
things that I say or different things
that I say none of them this is an under
underfunded area of medical research and
science no so medical communities don't
truly know how different forms of
oxalates even react react in the body or
accum accumulate in the body because
there's no way to ever know there's no
science in research claims that oxalates
should you know create be a problem in
celery juice or unproven and OB unstand
un
unsubstantiated they're
unproven and unsubstantiated that's the
whole point in reality these Foods Do no
harm it's incredible how it works you
know rather they provide us with
critical healing phytochemicals minerals
vitamins and more the vast array of
nutrients in
socalled spinach meaning High oxalate
leafy greens such as spinach are
incredible for
you Cel are some of the most beneficial
to us now if someone says wait a minute
Anthony you're wrong because I react
when I have spinach or I react when I
have something I react in my mouth I
feel the oxyc acid causing a problem
that's not the oxyc acid you're feeling
causing the problem that's an
alkaloid that's an
alkaloid okay that's what that is not
oxyc acid oxyc acid that's false okay
true is it's an
alkaloid a lot of leafy greens certain
types of spinach not all types of
spinach will have a higher level of
alkaloids something that's not studied
something that's completely nobody even
knows about really and alkaloids are so
detoxifying I mean literally
detoxifying and and and and could
stimulate the salivary glands all of
that and cause a little bit of a stir
and people can react a little bit but
don't do the spinach then that's okay if
you're actually feeling that but if
you're not feeling that with things then
you should have it regardless oxalates
or not whatever it is that's how it
works I I know a lot of people lambs
quarters I I remember I remember
foraging for wild lambs quarters okay
and I'm out there I'm looking for wild
Lamb's quarters I'm eating them I always
did good with Wild Lamb's quarters
always did good the alkaloid is really
potent but it never bothered me because
it's a wild green a lot of
spinaches are almost on the Wild Side
yes are on the Wild Side practically
they are there's a lot of varieties
right on the edge of The Wildside
they'll have a little higher alkaloid
content
and I'd be foraging for Lamb's quarters
and sea plantain sea plantain is
something grows on the shore North
America okay and it's kind of like it's
kind of like it's uh lot of M
muc in it you know I can't say the word
right now for some reason but it's it's
very like milky when you pluck it at the
bottom like milkweed all right and I
could eat I could eat the sea plantain
that alkaloids off the
chart then I went to my friend's Garden
who grew lamb quarters grew lamb
quarters they weren't wild but it was a
different species and basically wild
because they were a cultivated lamb
quarters but you can't really they were
too close to the wild but it eat but it
had a stronger alkaloid for some reason
it's just the way it works could have
been the soil could have been everything
in his garden you name it had a stronger
alkaloid that thing bit me that thing
bit my butt when I ate it I felt it in
the mouth and in the throat I was like
oh my God I'm having some kind of
reaction to this to this lamb quarters
when I could eat all the lamb quarters I
want you know and the reason what it
what it was was the alkaloids were off
the chart on that baby not oxyc acid not
oxalate but see nobody knows any of this
information but that's the whole point
nobody knows anything in the alternative
movement practically it's all hit Miss
guess folklore crap this fake science
pseudo science you name it is what it
all is you got to remember that most of
it so it It's Tricky the whole thing's
tricky so you got to be careful what you
get sucked into you can get sucked down
the road remember I don't work for
anybody you always have to remember that
I don't work for anybody except for
guess what guess who guess who not
myself all right yeah I try to survive
so I can give you guys as much as I
can but I work for you
guys it's a difference between working
for yourself and everything's about
yourself yourself yourself yourself
yourself and you just glean up grab onto
any information that you can make money
off of make money off of make money
whatever it is or you work for the
people and so you deliver them
information that's real for the first
time and that's what I do all the time
that's how it works so the vast array of
of nutrients in so-called High oxalate
leafy
greens and celery which isn't a high and
celery is not a high oxalate anything
it's not on a high oxalate of anything
they're some of the most beneficial
available to us barely there's barely
oxalates in so but there's oxalates in
everything remember that but barely
medical research and science have not
yet discovered that fruits and
vegetables and leafy greens and herbs
contain anti oxalates get this anti
oxalates that prevent oxalates from even
ever causing an issue
whatsoever like the current Trend says
that oxalates cause problems because
it's never oxalates that are causing the
problem it's an alkaloid that's causing
the
problem it's an
alkaloid tobacco is so high in Al alids
those tobacco leaves so high in
alkaloids really is you got smoke it
smoke it smoke it smoke it but you eat
that tobacco leaf that alkaloid is going
to bite you like NE like no other and
it's not going to be
oxalates so if you go you go to a place
where they grow that they grow that
poison where they grow that tobacco leaf
and you go there and you pluck a piece
and you put that in your mouth you're
going to be
like what is this reaction I'm having I
could smoke the stuff I could smoke
three packs of cigarettes a day but I
can't this stuff is hard in my mou
what's in this my throat it's an
alkaloid
attack that's what's happening little
bit of an alkaloid
reaction so yeah I mean Isn't it nice to
have some clear information for
once oxalates are wides spread whether
we like it or
not you know so understand that but so
are antidotes to oxalates they're
naturally in the the fruits and
vegetables what they're not naturally in
there's no antidotes in meat chicken
animal products and people still aren't
reacting to those oxalates and there's
not even anti oxalates in
there that's how harmless oxalates are
there's not even antioxidantes built
into a piece of meat into an animal's
body like there is in all the fruits and
vegetables that the animals are eating
there's no antioxidants they don't
they're not in oxalates in an animal's
body meat when you when you're cooking
that meat and all that there's no you
see but yet those oxalates still aren't
bothering anybody when they're eating it
they're like okay this CH piece
chicken's fine and whatever you see the
common belief is that foods high in
oxalates produce kidney stones and golf
Stones unbelievable protein causes
kidney stones and call
Stones protein causes kidney stones and
gall stones I I could say it again but I
think you got it not an oxalate in
fruits and vegetables so oxalates in
fruits and vegetables will give you a
kidney stone celery juice dissolves
kidney stones lemon water dissolves
kidney kidney stones um I can go on and
on and on leafy greens stop the
production of kidney stones I could go
on and on and and
on this is
unbelievable don't toss out valuable
healing tools like spinach and celery
and things like that and celery juice
for mistaken
theories for mistaken theories it's so
important everything I'm talking about
celan let's go into celan look you might
you might pronounce celan differently p
s o r a l
NS I call them selian sorians you know
you can call them different things um
sorians with an S and not even pronounce
the P or however you want to do borans
but the bottom line is these right here
this is going to be this is a constitute
fear but this is a fear
Creator that's what this one is so let's
go into that a little bit it it's an
ultimate fear tactic that might come out
that probably already is it's used to
it's used to deter people from consuming
celery
juice sorians are phytochemical
compounds which reside in almost every
single fruit and vegetable and Herb how
do you like that sorians are helpful for
the immune system and for healing our
bodies we need that chemical compound
it's actually critical for us to heal
yeah any sorians present in celery is
harmless it's in fact great critical
that it's even in
there they do not create Sun
sensitivities or dermatitis celery juice
rids
dermatitis so this fear this fear tactic
is just amazing to me absolutely amazing
instead sorians help and rid people of
these skin
conditions you got to think about that
right there how can some of the worst
cases of eximus psoriasis and it's not
just recently I I've been doing this for
decades promoting that celery juice
since I was a kid 1975 since I was a
little kid in
1975 Spirit gave me that
information I've watched people get
their lives turned around because of it
my whole life when I was a stock boy in
the grocery store 13 years old 14 years
old 12 13 14 years old I was actually
juicing I talk about in the book juicing
celery there at the store bringing it
out to people walking around out there
bringing you know pushing their
carriages and stuff bringing it out when
I knew there was a condition and problem
and everything like that I've seen skin
conditions better and get better and
better I've seen that it's it's not it's
it's it's not something you can't get a
in Sun sensitivity that's ridiculous
from from celery juice okay sure you're
not going to get it from celery juice so
these are some of the fear tactics that
you'll see out there if I don't prepare
you you can't then spread the word
either
because I'm only one little guy that's
it I mean your voice is is what
matters that's what matters just knowing
the truth and I know so many people with
chronic illness they're quiet they're
quiet they're reserved they're laidback
and then you got the naysayers out there
that are just instigating purposely
they're loud they're squeaky they're
scratchy they're abrasive they're
abusive is what they are and you got
people who are literally trying to live
their lives they're trying to work dayto
day or not work work on their health to
try to get to work someday and they're
they're you know taking care of
themselves they're killing themselves to
take care of themselves of course
they're working hard at it and they
don't have time to be squeaky wheels on
social media and stuff and spread the
good word and all this kind of thing
they don't and they stay kind of
reserved and stay kind ofly back and
then you there are some people that
battling chronic illness that are
Fighters for out there spreading the
word and if you guys are one of them you
know spread the word about these very
things get the book and and read and
just become an expert get the soues book
become an expert is really important
because you'll save lives you don't
think you'll save lives you'll save
lives you don't think that matters you
know saving lives you don't think it
matters it does it does it matters it
matters when we're here the good works
we do matter when we're here we're only
here for so long
it matters when we're here it truly does
every little bit counts let's go to the
next one so that's
suran um hey look and prove me wrong
pronounce it differently and just say
you could laugh at me I could be totally
pronouncing it wrong and it's kind of
funny it's actually really funny you
know I mean I I'm not an English major
and I'm certainly not the smartest guy
in the world my information is smart
because it comes from Spirit you know I
don't have any training you guys know
that
it comes from Spirits and was a little
kid it's Advanced Medical information
filled in these books and it's original
information because it's no one else's
there's no citations in the books for a
reason it's all from Spirit so for a guy
that's not too smart and writing all
that down right from just sitting at the
desk why Spirit talks to me you know
it's pretty interesting don't you think
so sorens so that's another way you can
say it is
sorens so that's a whole another way
way and so hey look there you go let's
go into salici acid
Sol you know that's a good one okay all
right that's a good one salicylic acid
you know everybody's got a different way
of saying it I think that's the way to
say that one there tricky words some of
them you know it doesn't mean hey it it
doesn't mean if you can't say the word
right does it mean you don't know what
you're talking about so always know that
when you're saying the word somewhere
it's okay but you know salicylic acid is
is something that is always been a
tongue twister and you know basically
it's got other it's also known as other
things you know salicylate acid is
another myth and fear tactic that deters
people from experiencing the healing
benefits of celery
juice so this is another one the theory
that individuals are sensitive to this
acid from fruits and vegetables has not
even been proven by medical research and
science here's another one here's
another oxyc acid thing this is another
mess up in the system how would you even
know that's what makes you sensitive how
would you even know in in God's name how
would you even it would it even be
possible or in the higher power or in
the heavens or in the light how would
you even know no if it was even possible
that that's what you're reacting to that
chemical compound in a fruit or
vegetable is what you're even reacting
to it's incredible and so they'll throw
that one at you with the celery juice
too why not try to stop you from
drinking celery juice with that one you
know that's it that's a whole another
one and so you got to be careful since
celery is not a vegetable it shouldn't
even be grouped in this Theory anyway
this is a vegetable Theory you guys
salic cylic acid is a vegetable Theory
it's an actual vegetable Theory it's not
a herb Theory it's not even an herb
Theory celery is an
herb I mean the amount of bull bleep
that we got to sift through here it's
daunting and it shows you how even the
top so-called experts out there know
nothing about celery juice nor People's
Health in general it's actually kind of
like sad and scary at the same time when
you really think about
it it's
incredible so since celery isn't even a
vegetable it's not even it shouldn't
even be grouped in this Theory anyway
celery juice is in herbal medicine that
helps reverse chemical food
sensitivities that many people develop
from gluten dairy corn eggs and soy
celery juice is an herbal medicine that
helps
reverse ready chemical food
sensitivities chemical food
sensitivities that many people develop
because of eating all this gluten all
this Dairy all this corn all this eggs
and all these soy and all the soy that
feeds
pathogens that feed Epstein bar virus
seg virus hhv6 virus simplex one virus
Simplex 2 virus all the different
mutations of all these viruses hhv7 many
other ones strep staff ciff MCA boom
whatever all these things and then some
just more bacteria than that just tons
of bacteria all of this
well eggs feed that they feed all those
little bugs eat your eggs eat your eggs
happy happy feed the bugs eat you know
and that's what it is well celery juice
helps combat not only the pathogens that
cause food sensitivities and all these
other issues in everything
else
but it's it's it's anti all this it's
it's incredible okay let's go
into
sodium let's hit sodium this is a fun
one this one is is my favorite is
actually my
favorite the same okay you got to get
ready for
this the same dietitians nutritionist
so-called experts blah blah blah
everybody else the same ones will
literally tell you there's too much salt
and celery juice but they'll advise all
their patients clients all their people
all their whatever it is they're writing
or doing they'll advise them to stick
salt in water and drink it that's what
they'll
do irony I irony is not even a word I
could use for this because you have to
attach irony with stupidity with with
just plain old something with plain old
ignorance with something else with
something else with something else and
you have to lump them all together so
irony can't work I can't use irony for
this one because I know for a
fact that virtually probably almost
every single naysayer against the sodium
and celery juice almost every single
naysayer
allows a little pinch of sea salt in
your water because it's another once
again no science behind it no anything
behind it no nothing behind it once
again it became law and where did it
come from who the hell knows and it's
junk what it does is the salt in celery
juice hydrates
you the salt thrown in a glass of water
dehydrates
you dehydrates
you so that's the
difference the salt in celery
are are subgroups of
sodium ones that go to the
brain to restore damaged
neurotransmitter chemicals to fire up
electrical
impulses to help you heal on almost
every
level those are the salts that your body
craves the mineral salts that your body
craves that's your bloodstream craves
it's your organs
crave sea salt can dehydrate you you
have to be careful it's not the same
thing from an
herb that's from the
ocean that's not from an herbal
food now if you can excuse me if you can
walk up to the ocean right up to the
beach and you can just you know drink of
that salt water right there just scoop
and just drink it and that would be fine
and I would start to believe you or
believe them the
naysayers the reason why guys died at
Sea was because they drank that salt
water the other reason why they died at
C they had no vitamin C cuz vitamin C
stops you from
dying guess what's in celery
juice an unbelievable variety of vitamin
C undiscovered by research and
science that's what's in celery juice
we're going to talk about that another
day we're going to go
into the whole salt thing now we're not
a low salt Society we're a high salt
Society I'm okay with a little pinch of
salt if you want it on some food to
flavor it a really good sea salt a
really good Himalayan rock salt I'm not
anti I mean I'm not anti a little flavor
in somebody's life here and there
okay but I'm anti someone ripping a hole
in celery over its
sodium when if guys that see that were
out of water were drinking celery juice
that whole trip they'd be not only in a
incredible condition the sodium would
never dehydrate them it would do the
opposite it would keep them hydrated on
a deep
level and that's what we're talking
about that's the differences but
remember the naysayers has too much salt
in it and they pass out that information
out there the so-called professionals I
mean can you believe it I don't want
listen I have respect for anybody with
credentials I do because it's not who
they are as a
person okay and I'm proud of anyone who
goes to school I'm proud of anybody who
goes to school and they get all the
different letters behind their name I'm
actually proud of them I feel like it's
a serious accomplishment I'm proud of
people I'm also proud of people who
don't do that because they're doing
other things in their
life you see you see but I notice though
you know you can have all the letters
behind your name you want all the
letters but if you're sitting there
saying there's too much salt and celery
juice so and look out and you're you're
advising your people
that you know those letters they just
become they're they're empty they're
empty and you want your letters to
matter at the end of your you know at
the end of your name if that's what you
seek in life so anyone who's got
credentials which I'm a big time Big
Time respect for all doctors and friends
I have and everybody else all the
different credentials that people have
make them
count make the make those letters at the
end of your name count and not tell
somebody hey avoid celery because you
know because it's got salt in it you
know that's that's that's that's just
not going to work
because if you keep on doing things like
that your letters they just become like
they're hollowed out make them Rich make
those letters after your name rich like
the work you did to get them so and
doing that is taking information that's
powerful that can change lives and
reverse people's conditions and and
change your lives and don't make them
fear fear fear fear fear celery juice
unbelievable but yet make sure they
throw pinches of sea salt in their water
all the time after they did a workout
out which is utterly
ridiculous you want celery juice after a
workout so we're going we're in sodium
this sodium one's that important that's
why I'm going into
this so look we're inundated with salt
in our daily life we just are you can't
run from it while there are people who
are mindful about it they're a minority
the people who are actually mind that
are mindful about this their salt
consumption is a really it's a minority
it's you guys got to know how small it
is it's such a small crew of people it's
ridiculous even the people that are
mindful about it doesn't mean they even
like it hear
it so the majority of restaurants rely
on salt because if they don't I mean the
the majority you know what all
restaurants rely on salt they just do
I'm sorry I mean you could ask for salt
not to put salt in something at a
restaurant whether it's vegan
plant-based kop keto whatever kind of
restaurant that pops up out of the
garden the point is is would it relies
on salt because it's never going to get
a repeat customer if it serves bland
food unless this minority who truly
wants to be salt-free and they know the
flavors are tasting without the salt you
know walks through the door but that's
not going to keep a restaurant alive I
don't know who that one person is that's
going to walk into a restaurant and keep
that restaurant alive because it's
rare the the majority of restaurants
they're all on salt for a reason if you
like if you had never eaten food with
added salt then went out to eat or tried
a package snack you would be staggered
by the overpowering nature of of the
salt itself we put in food so if you
were born and you were raised and your
mom and your dad your mother and father
they were like hey we're just going to
keep salt out of the diet we're just
going to do celery juice and this and
that and and spinach spinach is salty
spinach is very salty in a healthy way
too and there's all these other lemon
has sodium in it lemon so and you're
getting all these salts from all these
other foods and then you go out and eat
you know you're now a teenager and you
eat in a restaurant for the first time
in your life you would literally be
blown off your seat and probably
consider it's
poison probably consider it's
poison but we're trained we're
brainwashed and trained to consume
sodium and then our senses our senses
okay in our brain they adapt to it and
then they require it or not required for
a healthy reason but for
happiness and that's how it works I mean
that's just a part of
it so where does all the salt we eat go
does it just go flow right out of our
body so easily as it's entered no it
doesn't some of it
does even the most premium salt from a
jar of organic salsa or the healthiest
kitschiest dehydrated
crackers or salted nut mix stores even
those even those okay a salted nut mix
that's really
healthy that salt will store itself in
cells deep inside the organs and
crystallize there it'll crystallize we
slowly salt ourselves to death
culture and this crystallization of salt
builds up inside
organs until they're pickled until
they're preserved in a bad
way I mean it takes decades but it
happens and your skin starts getting
weird and you start getting
older and then somebody say well I don't
know why I'm I'm I'm aging too fast with
my skin and everything else someone's
going to say you need
collagen you need you need collagen
unbelievable and that's not what it is
it's because someone has a lifetime of
salt crystallization build up in their
liver and other
organs and they're literally getting
dehydrated on levels you can't even
speak
about look the bottom line is salt
particularly in beds itself inside your
liver because your liver tries to gather
it up from your bloodstream to protect
you from falling ill because we overuse
the overuse of salt which is part of
nearly everyone's everyday
life okay there in the liver salt sticks
around for years sound it like salt
sticks is there you know like a salt
like a salt stick salt sticks around in
the liver for years and becomes
toxic that's how it works if we're not
cleansing it out someone who worried
about their salt and celery should
instead be worried about the onslaught
of salt they've had throughout their
whole life and in package food and
everything packaged healthy food and in
restaurants and dishes and everything
else you know that's what they should be
worried about the sodium and celery
juice is a reprieve from all that and it
does even one thing nobody even knows
about this is a huge thing and I talk
about it in medical medium celery juice
you guys need to know how important this
is it provides sodium that not only
doesn't harm us but it helps us when
people are concerned about celery juice
and sodium what they are really saying
is they don't understand celery or
celery
juice so think about that one it's a
blind absum a blind absum with no
research in science to back it up when
they say that in truth the sodium in
celery juice helps loosen up and break
apart toxic old sodium deposits that are
crystallized in the liver and elsewhere
in the body and freeing you from
possible problems down the road because
the sodium and celery is different
celery juices sodium contains sodium
cluster salts subgroup of sodium it's
the only thing that does it helps Drive
toxic sodium deposits out of the body by
attaching themselves to the toxic sodium
and carrying it
out further the sodium and celery juice
is what our blood needs the most and can
use the most the most neurotransmitters
in our brain thrive on this variety of
sodium which has just the right minerals
and trace minerals attached to
it rather than contains neurotransmitter
chemical building block box you see
see here's how it works okay let me
clarify that last part that might sound
confusing and if you're if this is a a
live podcast meaning that you're
listening to like live right now in the
moment with me afterwards try to do the
replay or whatever down the road in case
right on this part this is important
so what celer juuse does is it doesn't
contain the building blocks to
neurotransmitters it does better than
that you see somebody's vitamin water
with electrolytes somebody's electrolyte
thing somebody's even incredible water
they're drinking like the water I like
and stuff that I drink that you guys
prob maybe see me with here and there
like all these different things you know
I'm not sponsored by any companies or
anything or nothing like that and I
still say Brands all the time to you
guys but the thing is is with water
there could be these amazing
electrolytes naturally occurring in
there but they're just building
blocks you get some from there some from
the salad you just ate some from the
other uh fruit that you ate some from
the Apple you just ate some from all
these different things that you're doing
in your life you get all these pieces of
electroly building blocks all these
pieces of neurotransmitter chemical
building
blocks there's only one thing on the
planet that gives you the full
thing that's why people have Clarity get
the rid of their brain fog all these
other things start happening their life
starts changing anxiety starts dropping
their depression starts getting better I
talk about this in medical medium celery
juice you got to get the book you have
to get the
book you have
to and the thing is this is what I'm
trying to tell you is the celery juice
has the complete electroly like complete
so the neurotransmitter chemical can
revive itself not just a building block
like a little bit in this water a little
bit in this thing you eat a little bit
in this then you're going through the de
day and you're trying to collect pieces
you're trying to collect them minerals
that find their way to neurons by chance
when you're just collecting them like
that they're just minerals that are
finding their way to neurons by chance
depending on what someone's eating or
drinking what water they're drinking
what what they're eating what they're
doing think about that celery juice is
the only food on the planet to offer
complete activated
electrolytes even with coconut water you
don't get complete see that's what I'm
trying to say if you had coconut water
last week you got a couple of the
building blocks to your neurotransmitter
chemicals and if you had some good high
quality water like Fiji or something you
got you know there you go you got
another one when you're out there or if
you did this or whatever and you get the
building blocks but coconut water isn't
a complete it's not a complete it's just
pieces of them celery juice is complete
that's why you have to drink it every
single day it offers a complete
neurotransmitter chemical that are
already bonded together to reignite
weaken
neurotransmitters
after and and and it offers the ultimate
neuron relief our neurons in our brain
this gives our them our you know
ultimate neuron relief
when electricity flows it can flow more
freely through a
neuron with neurotransmitter chemicals
restored by the complete
neurotransmitter chemical option that's
in celery
juice celery juices naturally occurring
beneficial sodium is a part of this you
can't get this in SE salt Himalayan rock
salt or something else remember science
and research is so behind with with
chronic illness you guys have to know
this every time I'm interviewed now I
say the same thing you ready I didn't
know everybody was better I didn't know
science and research got everybody
better that's what I tell every
interviewer now and then they just go
and write smack about me and put and try
to publish it because they're irritated
I say it every time I didn't know the
science of research you keep on throwing
at me that doesn't support celery or
support me or something like that I
didn't know science of research had
everybody better I didn't know there was
wasn't like two billion sick people with
symptoms on this planet may actually
more than that with symptoms way more
than that I didn't know I thought oh so
you mean they're not all fixed or wait
they're all fixed everybody's better
that's what I'm trying to say with the
science of research you know about
anybody with chronic
illness when it was just a decade ago
they told women to just go and get go
and get a job if you are lazy and
tired you're bored you're making it up
think about that
unbelievable
look as I say all water is not the same
and all sugar is not the same we'll add
this to the list not all salts the
same how about that let's go in the
water this is a good
one let's hit the water one on the
subject of water if anyone tells you
that drinking celery juice is the same
as drinking water know this they are far
from the same what you hear from
dieticians nutritionists health coaches
or whoever or
trainers there's some like trainer guy
out there socalled he's he's known or
something which I beg to differ he's
like he's sitting here telling me
there's no stomach glands meaning he's
he's saying it on social media he's not
telling me he's probably trying to tell
me there's no such thing as stomach
glands and he posted
that I there's no sto there's no such
thing as stomach glands what are you
talking about of course there is they
create gastric they gastric juices
gastric
acids correct I mean it's correct they
they actually you know create all kinds
of
HCL hydrochloric acid and that's a
stomach glands but let's go into water a
little bit you'll get these same
professionals out there that are just
quick to just try to deter people from
doing anything good for themselves cuz
they think they want to own their space
and they want to be The Authority so
they just knock down powerful
information they'll try to like celery
juice and they'll say it's all water oh
that's interesting okay well every
single person that I've ever talked to
that had a chronic illness or every
single person that's ever had a
symptom I you know water didn't fix it
sure someone could be
dehydrated and they could be getting one
of those lowgrade headaches or something
and they up their water and it impr
proves them but people with
hashimotos people with thyroid disorders
hyperthyroid people with rheid arthritis
people with multiple sclerosis Lyme
disease people with trigeminal neuralgia
water doesn't fix people with eczema
sasis dermatitis rosacea water doesn't
fix people with lyan sclerosis water
doesn't fix Vitiligo water doesn't
fix people with severe chronic fatigue
neurological fatigue or even fatigue
that's just mild but still always there
water never fixes
ever people with headaches migraines
severe migraines back in the neck pain
body pain back pain feet pain Mort
Norton's Morton's neuroma plant
fasciitis
digitises in fix I'm going to go on a
little more people with diabetes water
doesn't fix but celery juice actually
reverses diabetes what else I mean we
can go on and on and on and on and on if
you actually want to insult The Chronic
ill really insult them tell them they're
getting better or they think they're
getting better with a placebo effect
possibly because there's water in celery
juice and they happen to just be you
know kneading a little extra water
because they're not drinking enough
water during the day ever so because now
they're juicing celery juice that's
what's giving them a better feeling
let's just insult The Chronic Le by
saying that well that's what the
dietitians are saying they're saying In
Articles they say it out there they're
talking about that places that's where
you know naysayers are saying
nutritionists whoever and I'm not
against dietitians or anything like
there's really some amazing ones that
actually are drinking celery juice and
promoting celery juice talking about the
naysayers anywhere naysayer doctors the
naysayers the naysayer people
whatever so that's what's happening here
when sources say that the only reason
chronically ill are getting their lives
back from celery juice is because it
offers water it's almost incon conable
I'm sorry but it's almost inconceivable
it shows confusion and a lack of
experience and understanding of what
people have gone through and suffered
with I've seen it I know it I've been
there with people side by side I've been
by their bedsides why they've been
suffering I've seen it all and this
means they don't know anything about it
or what they've been through and what
they've tried it shows confusion and
lack of experience I swear to God and an
lack of understanding people with
symptoms and
illnesses and and what they need to do
to just be on a daily basis to survive
yes celery juice has more water content
than other
sources but it doesn't have more water
content than a cucumber juice it doesn't
have meaning like you C juice cucumbers
and you got a whole thing of cucumber
juice or you just something it's it it's
still not as much as that celery juice
has more water yes but it's hydrob
bioactive water it's benefit beneficial
yeah is that my word that's my word
where's it from Spirit anybody who's
ever listened to my shows or just tuning
in here wondering where this information
comes I hope I don't burst your bubble
and get you to run the other way but it
comes from Spirit since I was age
four it's hydrob bioactive you don't
trust my
information well then how come I'm the
actually first one that said Epstein bar
causes Hashim modus thyroiditis and I've
been saying it for decades and now
science of research they're worried and
so now they're putting out papers saying
they think it's linked to it because
they don't want me to be the so-called
hero of that
Discovery and that's from Spirit since I
was a kid so and lemon water flushing
the liver that's mine for decades now
but yet it's like law out there now so
it is what it is it's not a simple
matter of water content that's getting
people
better if it were if it were ever
everyone who had tried increasing their
water intake would have already gotten
better it's unbelievable on the subject
of water if anyone tells you that
drinking celery juice is the same as
drinking water know this they are far
from the same water does have naturally
occurring electrolytes and especially if
it's high quality water like say like
fij or something still those
electrolytes provide entirely different
benefits from nose and celery juice this
is not even comparing apples to oranges
it's like comparing apples to beef water
and celery juice are two completely
different substances on all levels only
the herb celery contains the sodium
cluster salts the special vitamin C I
talk about all the different
antioxidants I talk about in the celery
juice book all the different
phytochemical compounds that are
undiscovered I talk about in the celery
juice special enzymes trace minerals
that make celery juice what it is is
it's suspended it's thick as for putting
a pinch of salt in a glass of water
thinking that that's the same or better
this is even more misguided you
dehydrating yourself I promise you
that's what you're doing celery juice on
the other hand is hydrating on a deep
level celery juices salt
water are two different
worlds so celery juice versus salt water
are two different worlds they're just
salt water is an entirely different
Beast the bottom
line so you have to know that mixing
celery juice with water is not a good
move don't do it because they're so
different they clash and you stop
getting your celery juice to work if
celery juice was all water and that's
how it helped you why would mixing water
harm it it kills it literally dilutes it
and kills it and destroys it cuz it's
not water they got to remember that
there's friction between them you can't
add you it's like oil and water you
can't there's friction or whatever you
say adding water to celery juice dilutes
the sodium cluster salts and deactivates
them while also interferes with trace
minerals enzymes some of the most
powerful aspects of celery juice that
helps us heal adding ice cubes to celery
juice same thing bad it destroys the
ability of the celer juice to heal the
body here's another point to keep in
mind when it comes to celery juice some
sources say that people only feel better
from celery juice because they're
getting hydrated by its water
content these sources say it has nothing
to do with celery juice itself this is
an inadvertent insult to the chronically
Hill remember that I told you that
earlier it's like telling people who
have been sick for months or years who
have looked for everything tried
everything you name it to drink more
water that'll fix your
problem staying hydrated
is the first advice that any doctor ever
offers anybody in health and wellness
when they're
sick and people carry their water
bottles everywhere feverishly with them
because of it and remind themselves to
drink more water it doesn't get
everybody out of chronic illness I'm
sorry it just doesn't these are people
who have been in the weeds tried
everything for years water isn't doing
it but I don't want you to stop drinking
water because you need the water yes but
it doesn't pull people out of the depths
of Despair like celery juice and medical
medium information
has and if you're dealing with an
illness you're going to get results on
on celery juice but you want to get full
results if you're dealing with some
serious stuff going on you get the
medical meeting books you learn how to
do the rest like the celery juice book
and all these other ones and you move
forward with your life I love you guys
thank you for hanging in there on this
show because this was an intense one and
I know I've been I know I was ranting
but it's all in the name of making sure
I got your back take care I'll see you
next radio show I can't wait