rumble youtube facebook tick tock
we're talking about how to incorporate
foods healing foods into your life
a lot of people have a lot of trouble
doing it completely understand okay
because it's not easy
but what's happening
is people are eating
fillers
i'm not talking about fillers that are
stuck in bad supplementation
not talking about fillers that are stuck
in bed supps supplements right like i'm
not talking about fillers that are in
packaged
foods that's bad enough as it is right
fillers and packaged foods
i'm talking about fillers in the diet
everywhere so where do you slip in the
healing food
where do you get the healing food in
when there's a whole bunch of other
things that we're filling with where do
you get the healing food it's good to
see you guys we're live right now a
little surprise live right now today
great to see you guys coming up tara
appleman good to see you you're here
today incredible
so it that's what happens we go into
these fillers so what are these fillers
let's go into that
fillers
are foods
that may be okay to eat
but
they're not healing us
they're not healing our body
they're not healing our organs
right
because that's what happens
no i'm eating good i'm eating clean i'm
eating a great keto diet oh no i'm good
i'm eating a great paleo diet i don't
know i'm eating a good vegan diet
i mean a good plant-based diet maybe
right but it doesn't mean you ain't got
all these fillers in there because it's
easy to get all these fillers in there
now you got some corn chips that's a
filler
no but these corn chips are healthy
they're healthy what says on the package
here it says
whole organic corn
and
avocado oil
so i'm gonna be able to eat all these
corn chips i want
it's a filler
the whole thing is a filler
right
now i mean gonna mean good i i'm having
i was just getting some chinese food and
i picked the healthy options in there i
got some sesame oil and all this rice
and i got this pork and it's a filler
all of it's a filler
i mean pretty healthy i'm eating this
vegan pizza it's a gluten-free crust
it's a filler
where's the healing foods oh the healing
food was on my vegan pizza
i had a couple little tomatoes on there
i saw something green on there probably
a little bit of basil
but it's a filler
there's so much filler going on
that's what people
don't understand
is there so much
filler going on out there and that's
where does the healing food come in how
do we incorporate the healing foods
how do we bring in
the healing foods
so we can
bypass all the fillers
right
potatoes potatoes that's a filler no
no
potatoes aren't a filler
potatoes aren't
potatoes are a medicinal food
they're a medicinal food it's not a
filler
too many beans
are a filler
doesn't mean they're bad
doesn't mean beans are bad
ah no it's just that it's a lot of
filler you see how it works you guys
where's all the leafy greens where's all
the leafy green herbs i want to show you
guys where's all the asparagus right you
guys where's all the kombucha squash
right
where's all the kale
i got some avocados over here
you eat too many avocados and you got a
filler you could wolf those avocados
down you can wolf those down you can
just tank avocados down it's easy to eat
a lot of avocado
avocados healing
but when we're sick and we're
chronically ill we need more of the more
healing foods avocado can become a
filler but it's still it's it's in this
list over here because it's still
healing
avocados more healing
than a piece of chicken
chicken is a filler
not the worst thing to eat if you're a
chicken eater
meaning like if that's what you eat i'm
not gonna shame you
the one thing you won't get out of
medical medium is you won't get the
shaming
i'm not gonna judge you
no way you come on this channel
you come on this channel
and you're an animal eater
i'm just gonna say no
uh it's okay if you do that no i'm not
going to judge you no way i'm not going
to shame you
no way
if you're a butter eater
i'm not going to shame you i'm not going
to judge you i'm just gonna say that
butter that butter will kill you in the
end sure
that'll clog up your heart that's the
heart attack butter
the heart attack that's it butter is
that's heart attack and a stick
that's the that's not that's what i'll
tell friends i'll be like oh you're
having a heart attack in a stand on a
stick
heart attacking a stick
you're having a heart attack stick
right that's what you're doing no i'm
only how this is organic butter it's
grass-fed butter i'm only going to have
a little here i'm going to spread it on
this if you're just having your heart
attack stick
not going to judge you though no way
ever
right
salmon
it's a filler
you want to eat salmon that's okay
you're sick you're taking space
away from other things that will heal
you
you love your salmon
but it's a filler
there isn't fillers in it
you can get wild caught salmon there's
no fillers in it but it's a filler
itself you see how it works you guys
that's how it works this is important to
know
salmon
is not anti-viral anti-bacterial
anti-fungal anti-mold anti-yeast see
it's a filler
right you can have grass-fed beef if
you're somebody that loves grass-fed
beef because medical medium is an
anti-animal protein medical medium is an
anti-plant
diet
medical medium's not anti-vegan diet
anti-vegetarian diet anti-animal protein
diet now but keep in mind
if you're gonna be eating your meat it's
not anti-viral anti-bacterial
anti-fungal anti-yeast anti-whatever
anti-whatever it's not
it's not
it's a filler
it doesn't mean
the meat
is going to
feed everything bad inside of you i
never said that someone wants the animal
protein i would say lower the amount
but it's
a filler
the lower says what's a filler
these are fillers that take up space
very good question dolores thank you
very good question these are fillers
that take up space in our diet and stop
us from making room for what making room
for what
making room for more leafy greens more
asparagus more brussels sprouts more
kale
more squash more papayas right there
more bananas right there more oranges
right there more zucchinis more
everything
right these are just some things
i got right here
so we take seaweed hero exactly less
filling we take up space
right you want your chicken you want
your chicken
okay people want their chicken they want
to eat it too they want to eat the cake
too they want their chicken and eat it
too they want their meat they want to
eat it too they want their fish they
want to eat it too they want their
butter they want to eat the butter's
different that's just a heart attack on
a stick that feeds bugs
let's talk about plant-based for a
second talking about vegans and
plant-based for a second so this is
important i just want to say uh to kim
kim on
rumble hi kim marie
right
and um i could see your comments
on rumble too
plant-based you could be plant-based and
still have fillers everywhere guess what
you can be plant-based and have too many
avocados
and yes they're healthier
they offer more than other fillers
avocados offer more than meat filler
avocado offers more than salmon
if you're wondering how that lemon stays
on there like that's because it's
obviously a prop piece of salmon
avocados
have more in them as a filler than
chicken but you can still play the
filler game with too much avocado and
too much nuts and seeds
you can eat as a plant-based person lots
of nuts lots of seeds you hear this guys
listen lots of nuts lots of nut butters
lots of seeds and yeah there's some
healing properties in nuts and there's
some healing properties in seeds but it
still takes too much space and can still
make it so a vegan person a plant-based
person can't heal
because it becomes a filler it becomes a
filler
and you can be a vegan and eat too many
beans too much rice
because those are fillers
oatmeal
oatmeal for both the animal protein
people and the plant-based people i'm
just telling you now or the vegans and
the animal protein people oatmeal
is a safe grain to eat
but it's a filler
this is such an important topic
it's a filler you guys
that's what it is
you can tank on some oatmeal every day
but it's not enough healing properties
in oatmeal oatmeal is not antiviral
antibacterial anti-fungal anti-yeast
anti-everything that's making you sick
oatmeal doesn't cleanse the poisons and
toxins out of your liver and body
meat
is not antiviral
antibacterial anti fungal anti yeast and
meat can't cleanse metals and stuff
that's inside your liver and your body
it can't cleanse it out
salmon is not antiviral anti and
antifungal anti yeast antibacterial and
it can't cleanse the poison out of your
body it can't pull the poison out of
your body you see how it goes
it can't
aj good to see you
right
okay
cara del sol high on rumble
it's good to see everybody coming on
here
you see the difference
this is what i'm talking about where's
the room for this right here
where's the room for this
when you take on too much filler whether
you're plant-based animal this isn't an
animal attack
this isn't an animal protein attack
we don't do that here
i know that so many people who come onto
this channel like what is he is he vegan
plant-based okay he's against animal
okay i'm gone bye see you later medical
medium because
or same thing the plant-based people
coming on here they're like what is he
is he pro animal cause i'm out of here
boom
but where's it's not it where's the room
for this for whoever whatever side of
the aisle you're on what side of the
aisle are you guys on
are you plant-based are you vegan
you could be are you animal protein you
could be
where's the room for some of this see
even more of this where's the room for
this
that's what it is where's the room for
that dinosaur kale
darlene says what can you eat for
breakfast that's not a filler
if you want something dense
you can have a potato potatoes not a
failure you know why potato is
anti-viral antibacterial anti-yeast
anti-mold anti-fungal and it allows the
body to cleanse
that's a potato right you can learn
about these different recipes
so darlene always get a cleanse to heal
liverescue's 53 off right now amazon.com
us
51 off right here
you can do the potato skillet how to
cleanse the heel
right here medical medium books
right you can do that
so
you got those options
so what can we do it's a really good
question potatoes look there's all kinds
of recipes right here medical medium
book one the potato skillets in that one
that's what i remember
the bottom line is
we can eat different things you could do
your smoothies in the morning what would
you replace for oatmeal and it's not
like you're not a loud oatmeal so ann
weston it's not like you're not allowed
oatmeal it's just that it could be
there's so many things already in your
diet oatmeal is one of them that could
be a filler
so what can you do bananas antiviral
antibacterial maybe put some extra
bananas in your oatmeal see guys i want
to help i want to help in any way i can
because what i see out there is people
eating so much filler then like that
person's not going to heal if they get
sick well that person's not going to get
healed if they're sick
they're not
if you have some oatmeal and oatmeal is
what you love chop up a lot more banana
make that oatmeal more banana than
oatmeal and you just switched the game
you just turned over the game right
there you guys you hear that on tick
tock you just switched the game
you chopped up some bananas
and you threw them in your oatmeal and
now your oatmeal is not all big oatmeal
your oatmeal some oatmeal and a lot of
bananas and you just got the antiviral
antibacterial anti-fungal anti-yeast
thrive
thrive said thrive with said i love
potatoes
do the heavy metal detox movie
do the heavy metal detox smoothie in the
morning
do something right that takes place of
the fillers but does something for you
don't you want it working for you don't
you want what you're doing working for
you you guys
don't you want what you're eating to
work for you like you want it working
for you
and so when everybody's doing too much
filler doesn't mean you're not allowed a
piece of meat if you're an animal
protein person doesn't mean you're not
allowed a piece of salmon if you're an
animal protein person or a piece of
chicken it doesn't mean you're not
allowed doesn't mean as as a plant-based
person you're not allowed all those nuts
and seeds you're not allowed some
avocados you're not allowed all that it
just means
you gotta work
with the miracles that the planet has
and offers
i recommend holding off those animal
proteins till the end of the day till
dinner time if you're an animal protein
person you wait to the end of the day so
you don't take up your day with too many
fillers and then at night if you do your
animal protein at night that's when you
did a filler
and i recommend if you're anna if you're
plant-based if you're vegan and you're
plant-based i recommend
you hold off on a lot of the grains and
a lot of the oatmeal a little bit maybe
you do those two to the end of the day
but you you replaced it in the morning
with
with your smoothies and you got your
banana smoothies you got all that in
there
saying hi to
gabriel on rumble
glad you guys are on here in rumble
so we're live on youtube we're live on
rumble we're live on facebook we're
loving tick tock
it's live in telegram
so gabrielle potato waffles
are really awesome potato waffles are
really awesome everyone rumble
so
you can do things like a potato waffle
because that isn't a filler a potato is
not a filler
but avocado toast is a filler i'm not
saying you can't have avocado toast on
gluten-free toast you guys i'm not
seeing you
i'm not saying that angela says liver
rescue smoothies live a rescue
incredible book
right here
it's an incredible book
you guys need you need a book christmas
the holidays a whole bit these are
incredible books liver rescue you got
cleanse to heal you got the medical
medium book right there
the problem is
i'm not telling you no
you can't have that piece of meat
i'm not telling you no you can't have
your oatmeal this is um uh this is you
know
bad
i'm telling you guys
you gotta kind of adjust it to make room
for the foods that are going to heal and
help you and turn your life around and
not get caught up in too many of the
fillers because if you get caught up in
too many into too many of the fillers
you pay the price down the road either
you don't heal or you never heal
completely or you get sicker in some way
and that's what happens and no one
really understands this
this isn't the channel of oh it's either
animal protein or plant-based
no this is the channel of
reason this is the channel of making
sure you have every opportunity to heal
in any way possible and taking advantage
of the opportunities here on the planet
because you gotta eat
you gotta eat so we can do things
we can do things with our foods
that can change our lives we get into
these habits i'm not telling you no
no no no i'm telling you you can have
some grass-fed beef if that's what you
eat
you can have
amazon you can have um
food that you order from amazon that's
packaged or something like a good pasta
you can you can get something like that
you can have beans
you can have grassed beef you can have
salmon
right you can go into the grocery store
into whole foods or another grocery
store and you can go and buy a can of
beans if that's what you wanted you can
go buy a package of lentils you can go
buy a package of oatmeal you can go into
whole foods and grab some grass-fed beef
you can go online to one of the stores
wherever it is
and order something
i'm not saying no no no no no what i am
saying is
we have to start thinking about where is
your medicine where's your medicine
where is it
where's your medicine
is what i'm saying
where is
the medicine
because
i'm just saying
if we're going to eat we want to heal we
do
saying hi to selfie sage out there
yeah on rumble
and drum cat on rumble
so
you guys i'm glad you're here we're live
right now we're talking about fillers
and we're not talking about fillers and
supplements we're not talking about
fillers in packaged food we're not
talking about fillers you know what i
mean the bad stuff additives and fillers
we're talking about fillers that you're
adding into your diet every day that's
stopping you from healing stopping you
from changing your life stopping you
from reversing the conditions and the
symptoms and stopping you from cleansing
and healing cleansing and healing the
body
beverly grafts hubert said i found out
fillers dry me out morning lemon water
celery juice heavy metal detox smoothie
makes such a difference in the morning i
didn't realize i was so dehydrated
beverly it's easy i'm so glad you're
here thank you for the comment it's easy
to fill up on fillers
so easy
eggs in the morning filler an egg's not
going to reverse a condition an egg is
not going to heal you you guys have to
understand this an egg doesn't heal you
th this is critical information for
people out there that are trying to heal
and get their lives back an egg doesn't
heal you
at all
and red onion helps you heal an egg
helps you get sick it doesn't heal you
i'd rather have you eat avocados than
eggs any day but like i said if you're
plant-based you could be eating way too
much avocado then it becomes a filler
because avocado does have healing
properties so i like it better than a
lot of things
but when you dominate your diet with
avocados all the time it doesn't mean
we're going to be actually reversing a
condition so when we have our avocado
toast on gluten-free bread that's great
and there's some healthy things in
avocado but it's not enough to reverse
our condition and turn our lives around
it becomes a filler
becomes a filler
an orange is not a filler you make room
for some oranges you're making room the
minute you take away all those fillers
the minute you take away those right
there
you just open the door
for something to come in
that can turn your life around you just
open the door to the magic of healing
you just open the door to the angelic
healing powers that are around you
angels wanting you to heal
however
universe wanting you to heal whatever
you believe
whatever it is
that you have around you
you open the door
for healing to happen
when you push back the fillers a little
bit just push them back a little bit you
don't have to push them all the way back
you're just pushing back a little and
everything starts to change
it's incredible
tara said
look on his website the recipe is there
on his page so lots of recipes on
medicalmedium.com
if you're too busy eating pork
so that's a filler right there pork's a
big filler
just letting everybody know right now
when you eat pork
you really hamper your pancreas you hurt
your liver
but it's not just that
you have it's a filler
ham pork chops
pulled pork
bacon
bacon is one of those fillers that takes
up your diet
doesn't give you anything back you get
nothing back
it takes away you get nothing back but
it's one of those fillers
so it's something where if you get rid
of the bacon
you get rid of the ham you just open the
door you bring in those steamed potatoes
you bring in that bring in that kabocha
squash you bring in that butternut
squash you bring in that deli delicata
squash you bring in that red curry
squash
you can just bring in bring in the
spaghetti squash
but you can bring in different options
bring in the steamed vegetables bring in
the steamed broccoli the steamed
asparagus the steamed brussels sprouts
you bring these things in
so
jaylon rumble says or ask is egg white
as bad as a yolk it is
it's bad in a different way the yolk has
more fat in it
right
yolk has more fat in it
okay
all right so that's that's why the yolk
is is pretty bad
but
but regardless of
whether the egg white or the yolk
it's all bad because it feeds the bugs
so let me just show you right here
because i have to show you
okay
so when you eat an egg
it becomes food for these guys in you
yeast mold fungus
viruses
bacteria
feeds
on eggs when you eat the eggs when egg
particles are floating around your body
all the bugs
that make you have lupus fibromyalgia
rheumatoid arthritis hashimoto's
thyroiditis neurological lyme
acne eczema psoriasis dizziness vertigo
tinnitus aches and pains
it's these bugs
that feed off of foods like eggs that's
why i don't like eggs as a filler i
don't like eggs i'd rather have you eat
oatmeal any day if if you were to tell
me i'm going to either eat eggs or
oatmeal
and uh and pick and choose the filler
i'd be like filler filler
lots of oatmeal
doesn't matter if it's a filler
at least the oatmeal won't feed the bugs
because oatmeal won't feed the viruses
and the bacteria in the fungus and the
yeast of the mold
oatmeal won't feed that but the eggs
will
that's why i don't like eggs as a filler
eggs is a bad filler that's a bad filler
that's a bad one
the funny thing is is all the vegan
people and the plant-based people the
minute they get a symptom or they get
sick they run back to eggs first
and then they're just eating eggs and
they have no idea why they're sick
that's why they're eating eggs and they
have no idea eggs feed
the very viruses and bacteria that are
making them sick and the yeast in the
fungus and mold but they don't they
don't know
so all the vegan people and plant-based
people just run back to eggs as fast
they can that's why they don't it's why
they don't really attack eggs i don't
know if you know this
but the vegan world and the plant-based
world they'll attack meat meat eaters
and
they don't really like to say something
about eggs too much because guess what
every month they're having an egg or two
not all of them
so
i'm rumble compassion nco good to see
you
love your mm liver rescue it helped me
heal my migraines i've suffered for 30
years
wow
wow right on rumble
i'm glad you're here it's an honor
what kind of fillers are you guys on i
just want to ask rebecca says why are
people with ic intolerant
to so many good
to so many good free good good for you
fruits and veggies
i have i see
and struggle to get enough to eat
does not cause a flare
will these intolerances go away as i
heal
well the thing is with ic it's it's like
this okay
i see worsens from foods that you don't
feel any discomfort from
because i see
right
is caused by pathogens so that's what i
see is caused with right interstitial
status is caused by pathogens
so these pathogens
they make a home in the bladder the the
urethra uti right the trap the the
urinary tract and they make a home and
that home gets really
patched up and rough
gets beat up in there and so
what happens is that you eat things like
eggs and
your you think your ic is under control
and you eat things like
some meat and you think it's under
control but
it's okay to eat some meat but it
becomes a filler in your life it's not
opening up the door for something that's
going to heal your ic
what happens is
fruits and that's the question right
there you said fruits why is fruits but
why do fruits bother healthy fruits
bother some people with ic
it bothers them
because they're raw inside
they're raw inside that urinary tract
they're raw because they got the in
long-term infections of streptococcus
they got the
long-term infections of epstein-barr
they got the long-term infections of
bacteria and so it's raw to the bone so
when you put astringency on it when you
start putting something astringent on it
like some buries
you're you're eating and the berries go
down or some oranges you're going down
right and then that those berries and
those oranges are detoxing the body and
all that acid that's sitting inside
people's bodies starts to come out along
with the astringent power of some
healing fruits you're going to feel
something with i see but yet that's how
you heal i see
so i tell people with intracellulitis i
tell them to take it easy that you do
some bananas that does not
bother at all you do papaya
tell them you do papaya
right there for instastitus
right there papaya
it still gets the acids out you're still
going to have some of that acid burned
from
from all that poison in the body
but that's one thing you can do
so today i just wanted to run by you
guys a few things
i want to run by
what fillers are you eating
and how can we
slowly move some of those fillers
to a lower level in the diet so we can
get something else in there
how many zucchinis are eating are you
doing steamed zucchinis you can do
steamed zucchinis you can do steamed
asparagus every day what does i see it's
interstitial cystitis
uh hopefully that's the ic that
they're asking about
maybe you know maybe it's someone can
also make a mistake and and do i see for
incontinence or something or something
else
but it should be that
so you create brown rice
i see that what are you guys eating
if eggs are cooked properly wouldn't it
be
wouldn't it be dead to the virus
no it's it's it's
thresa it's the it's what's in the egg
that the virus feeds on dead or alive
when you eat the egg
it's the undeveloped proteins
in the eggs
undeveloped proteins whether they're
cooked or the raw the undeveloped
protein because the chicken hasn't been
formed yet so when you eat the chicken
the chicken
won't feed a virus
a chicken is not anti-viral
anti-bacterial anti-anything no it's
it's not a healing food you can eat it
it's a filler it's a filler but it's not
a healer
chicken
is not a healer
right
eggs the undeveloped protein in eggs
feeds all the
bugs it feeds all the bugs
that that's what happened so when you
eat the egg whether it's alive or cooked
your the bugs in your body are going
whoa whoa food food food now let's get a
flare up of lupus down the road let's
get a flare up of fibro down the road
let's get the neurological lime moving
up a notch
let's get every other problem multiple
sclerosis worse
steve manson says
i have my lemon water first then celery
juice then heavy metal detox then
oatmeal that's my morning okay let's
let's cover that for a minute first of
all it's amazing you're having to learn
lemon water first okay so steve
incredible
right
you're moving on to your celery juice
now
boom
you're moving on to your celery juice
that's incredible you're already doing
things that fillers would have replaced
what if you decided just to have your
oatmeal all morning and that was it you
just did a filler in the morning but
what you did you had your filler later
on
the oatmeal which is not antiviral not
not anti-bacterial
oatmeal is not anti
yeast and mold
but you at least got some powerhouses in
in the morning then you had your filler
that's okay
but what if you
you got a few powerhouses you got the
heavy metal detox then the oatmeal so
you got you got a few weapons in there
of healing and then you did the then you
did the filler later that's what it is
that's your morning that's great but can
you imagine
if you did that
right
and then you did potatoes maybe for
lunch like some steamed potatoes because
potatoes aren't filler they're antiviral
still they're anti-bacterial they're the
anti-yeast and the anti-anti-mold what
if you did avocados with one of the
medical medium recipes what if you did
it with some cilantro what if you did
with any avocados potatoes what if you
did your potatoes with cilantro what if
you did your potatoes spirit cracked at
me that time spirit of compassion
corrected me
what if you did
some kale
would have did some leafy greens right
and then you did the oatmeal later on in
the end of the day or later on in the
afternoon you just did more more healing
foods more healing foods and then you
did your filler even later
and later
and what if
at dinner time you did steamed asparagus
steamed brussels sprouts more greens
some tomatoes
all of that
and maybe threw a half an avocado on
there too
which is the best of all the fillers
maybe you had some winter squash
and you did all that and then you didn't
do your oatmeal
literally you just avoided a whole day
of fillers
but i'm not saying everybody has to do
that
okay
so on tick tock i'm asked where do we
get our protein
check out the brainwashed
okay by protein on rumble check it out
right protein
that's a head scratcher for me so let's
talk about protein a little bit because
that's that's gonna that's gonna have
everybody thinking
where you gotta check out that protein
episode on rumble you gotta check that
out you guys the one i did
protein
does not heal right it's not an
antiviral thing it's not an
antibacterial thing protein doesn't heal
the body
you know i'm scratching my head if
protein means everything and protein
heals everything
why is the whole world sick and they're
all on protein they're just they're
cranked with protein you guys on
tick-tock they're loaded with
everybody's eating protein protein is it
is everywhere everybody's diet's loaded
with protein you can have bacon every
morning all that protein
you can have
pork chops and bacon and meat you can
eat anything eggs you can have protein
all day long
but the hospitals are filled the
hospitals are filled everybody's getting
sick protein doesn't stop people from
getting sick proteins not saving
everybody's life
everybody's eating protein but
everybody's sick protein doesn't have
antioxidants it doesn't have glucose it
doesn't have trace mineral salts doesn't
have phytochemical compounds doesn't
have antiviral compounds doesn't have
antibacterial compounds doesn't have
anthocyanins it doesn't have
doesn't have anything
so
how come protein doesn't michelle l that
word triggers you protein
juan says if we are into building muscle
what else can we eat with medical medium
i want to heal but not lose so much
muscle
one
what keeps your muscles on is calories
calories
that's what keeps your muscles on
it's calories and trace mineral salts
that's what keeps muscle on
if you take away your carbohydrates
if you you should check out frogman on
instagram
juan check out frogman on instagram
he builds muscle
you can build muscle with fruits
vegetables herbs leafy greens potatoes
all that it's it's about mineral salts
and calories that's how we build our
muscle
protein doesn't build our muscle
i told the story on rumble you got to
see the rumble on protein honestly
watch the rumble episode about protein
you're minorly blown i talk about
a study they did
on people
that murdered a hundred people
it murdered a hundred people they
couldn't get out of the study
and they had to sit there and starve to
death and die
because all they fed them
was protein isolated protein they took
the calorie out they took the
carbohydrate out
they took the fat out
and because there wasn't even fat in
there and they separated the protein
from the fat they separated the protein
from the calories they separated the
protein from the carbohydrate they
separated the protein from everything
everybody sat in there for a couple of
months
until they died
they wasted away as if they were in a
concentration camp and they couldn't
back out because the study was years ago
right now you can back out of a study
now if you become part of a test study
of some kind now there is a clause in
the contract that says if you start
getting really ill or start falling
apart or something happens to you you
can leave
but back then
60 years ago
okay
60 years ago 70 years ago you couldn't
leave the study you signed your life
away
and then 100 people watched each other
die and some of them started eating
other people some people died in there
and others were actually eating
other people in there
and that's what happens when you feed
somebody just protein and you take out
the carbohydrate because the
carbohydrate is how the muscle stays
stay strong
take all carbohydrates away from a
bodybuilder take them all away
what do you think bulking and cutting is
bulking and cutting they end up eating
all this carbohydrate with fat but they
end up eating all this carbohydrate all
this carbohydrate and they bulk up and
they bulk up and they're doing the
weights and they're bulking up bulking
up and then they have to cut their
calories back again it hopes to lose the
fat but keep the muscle it's a game they
try to survive with it's bulking and
cutting bulk up eat more carbohydrate
eat more carbohydrate eat more
carbohydrate and then you're bulking up
you're bulking up you're bulking up and
then you're really fat because you ate
carbohydrates with fats combined so
you've got fat and muscly so then they
go well i don't like the way i look i
look too fat even though i got lots of
muscle so i better i better now cut my
calories down cut my calories down and
then they try to shed the fat but keep
the muscle it's a game it's called
bulking and cutting but what they don't
understand is you don't do the fat so
much you bulk up on the carbohydrates
and you work out and boom you got
muscles and you're not as fat
look
you can be an animal protein person you
can be a plant-based person
and i'm not telling you no
you can't eat that meat no you can't eat
that salmon no you can't eat that
chicken if you're plant-based no you
can't eat those nuts and seeds no no no
i'm not saying that
what i'm saying is
where's your medicine
because it ain't chicken
and it ain't a whole bunch of nuts and
seeds and nut butters and oils
that's not medicine
it's not medicine enough
your medicine is not bacon
your medicine's not eggs
your medicine isn't sunflower seeds
where's your medicine
like the real stuff the stuff that's
going to help you cleanse the stuff
that's going to help save your life if
you're ever down on your hands and knees
begging for god to help
you know the whole thing is
i've run into so many people over the
years and i've helped
tens and tens of thousands of people
throughout the years right 35 years
of helping people get their lives back
and then the medical medium book series
right here if you don't have liver
rescue take advantage of the 53 off or
get it free at the library if you have
to get it free at the library i don't
care
right now it's not going to help me if
you buy liver rescue because it costs
more to print it
but the point is
as you go to if you have these books you
can arm yourself with information and
the point i'm trying to say is
right
out of
all the years
and the people that i've watched that
have been just
sick and so sick i've seen people that
weren't religious
weren't religious on any level
i didn't even believe in god which is
fine you can believe in god you don't
believe in god it doesn't matter to me
i don't judge anybody for anything
but
i've seen people that not religious at
all
that no way god exists and then they get
really sick and they're on their hands
and knees and now they're praying to god
first time in their life they're on
their hands and knees they're so sick
that they even they're even praying to
god now because they're so sick they
can't believe how sick they are and they
don't know how to get out of it because
they went through the 50th doctor and
50th specialist you guys are so sad they
went to their 50th specialist
and they've been so sick
and now they weren't even a religious
person and now they're down on their
hands and knees and they're praying to
god
god help me god help me
and i've seen people religious that
don't believe in jesus christ they're
religion that's fine you do whatever you
want we i've seen people who are
religious that don't believe in jesus
christ and they get sick and they get so
sick and now they're on their hands and
knees saying jesus christ save me jesus
come help me jesus that's what they're
saying and they never believed in jesus
they're religious that had a religion
and now all of a sudden they're just
praying to god to send jesus christ to
help them
i've seen people that don't believe in
angels
the kids said oh no one can convince him
an angel exists no one can convince them
and then they get sick and they're down
on their hands and knees and down on
their hands and knees and they're like
angels just please i need an angel to
save my life i need an angel here now
and it's just because that's how hard it
is when we get sick and we're struggling
that's how hard it is
and i've watched this over and over
again and i feel so bad for people i'm
like well where's where's your medicine
where's your medicine
you know like where is it
like where's the medicine
where's the answers where's the
information where is it and then when
people find the information i've had
people talk to me for years like oh my
god i didn't know
jeannette says all my cysts have cleared
up for medical medium cleanses
incredible
the information in the books is here for
people
a cleanse to heal if you don't have
cleanse to heal or live a rescue or
medical medium
ana says they used to have coffee with
milk and bread for breakfast filler
bread for breakfast to fill it right
milkshake filler
and now i replaced it with 32 ounces of
lemon water 32 ounces of celery juice
and heavy metal detox smoothie for many
years now you have you have rid your
morning anna anna amigos you have read
your morning
of
fillers
well look that information is all in
this book right there
anna that you know that of course
obviously you have cleanse to heal so
that information for everybody else is
all in the books
right
it's important to know
i've seen people that didn't believe in
anything
people that just think we float on a
rock
this they just no we're on a rock you
die then you're nothing
you float on your you float on this rock
you die you're nothing
evolution's why we're here we were a
monkey
we were a snail and then the snail
crawled up the shore and we became a
lizard
then the lizard was on the edge of the
shore and the lizard grew into a possum
and then the possum
possum grew into uh
a bear
and then the bear grew into a monkey
and then a monkey grew into a giraffe
then a drew draft grew into a tiger and
then finally we became i don't know
tiger became a gorilla and then the
grill and all of a sudden we became
human and now we say well where'd the
other
what happened to the other gorillas
what happened to the other monkeys
because i'm confused about that one
i've seen people who don't
who don't who actually just think we
just we just live on a rock we die
we don't have a soul in the end it just
disappears we die i've seen them when
they get sick
on their hands and knees like
i know i'm more than this and they're on
their hands and knees i know more this i
need help i want answers
you know and all of a sudden god god
help me
that's what when we get sick
that's what can happen right
daisy says what about emergency food
supplies what do you recommend that's
okay if it's fillers
emergency food supplies
well i'll give you a couple rundowns
right now you know what i'll do a rumble
on it too sometime a whole rumble on it
okay
but emergency food supplies
first of all
freezer stuff is important
that's important
right meaning like you know you run out
of food food shortage there's no food
you want at least enough in the freezer
so keep that in mind so you can freeze
fruit you can freeze bananas i got a lot
of bananas in my freezer a lot of frozen
bananas
that's something you can do right
and one day i'll talk about a whole list
i'll do a rumble with a whole list of
different stuff
or do an amazon live or something
you know and we'll do that okay we'll do
maybe we'll do an amazon live and
because we can make stuff too and
everything else will be fun right
but anyway just want to let you guys
know about that book though it's 51 off
amazon.com us
right
question on rumble why do they say if
you have a cold or fluid chicken soup
because it's soup it's lighter
it's lighter
they don't tell you to eat it
thanksgiving dinner because somewhere
along the line somebody figured it out
that if you eat too much when you're
sick with the flu and you can't eat
anything you just vomited you got
diarrhea you got a high fever the last
thing you need is a big old turkey wedge
sub or a big old meatball grinder or a
big old philly cheesesteak sandwich or
when you got the flu you don't need a
pizza when you got the flu because when
you got the flu and you go eat a big old
pizza pie your butt's going to be
probably cranking that fever higher than
it was to begin with it was 102 fever
it's going to be 104 by the night's over
so what they found out was you eat light
you eat light when you have the flu and
since people can't give up chicken who
love chicken it's better to just have a
little chicken in the soup and then
you're sipping all the vegetables
what's healing about your chicken soup
i know this is gonna piss off somebody i
can't do a show without pissing off
somebody's not gonna piss you off that
asks a question i'm sure but this is
gonna piss off somebody i'll have the
chicken soup people on me
i have so many people on you guys you
don't even know you should see what half
my day is lately you have no idea what i
gotta do i have so many people i got so
many people making up fake crap fake
stories doing this doing that i got so
many industries that are putting all
kinds of trolls out there i got so many
people out there trying to chip me away
at every different angle you guys have
no idea the apple cider vinegar
the earth particle you know crew the
charcoal crew everybody in the sun and
they got bucks they got millions and
millions of bucks man and they send
people out to put out fake stories fake
this fake that do this bad media you
name it
because i put the truth out there
you know what my holidays is my holidays
is trying to navigate you want to know
my christmas is my holidays are
navigating the amount of tax i have
behind the scenes that nobody even knows
about
that's my life outside of writing the
books
here's the deal
chicken soup is healing because of the
broth because of the onion
it's onion
onion
in your chicken soup it's the carrot
it's the onion
that's what's healing in your chicken
soup you got the flu you got the onion
and garlic i got relatives that make
chicken soup
but they because they can't they can't
let go of their chickens and they make
the chicken soup they've got garlic in
there they've got onions in there i
always say nana nana
i'm like nana
right nana you got to put garlic in
there nana you've got to put
nana you got to put onion in there
you got and what happens is that
that it's it's those things in the
chicken soup when you go eat a roasted
chicken you got the flu you eat a
roasted chicken
your butt's going to be sick when you
got the flu and you eat a half of a
roasted chicken say you're somebody
that's used to eating a whole bunch of
chicken drumsticks a whole bunch of
chicken thighs
and you go and do that rotisserie
chicken when you got yourself 102
temperature and you go do that you'd be
so sick that night you'll have 104
temperature you'll be in the hospital
now wondering if you've got some other
kind of thing
chickens okay if you want to eat it but
it's a filler
i never said meat you can't eat meat
when did i ever say that
when did i ever say that you know what's
funny about medical medium information
it's the number one
selling books in health for six and a
half years running out of any health
author out there in the world
right worldwide you see the gold emblem
there
no one has that
and
what's incredible is i still got all the
vegans pissed off at me i still got the
animal protein people pissed off at me i
still got the keto people pissed off at
me
everybody takes personally oh no
he's anti meat
because he doesn't have a meat recipe
that's not true i'm not anti beef oh
he's anti he's anti vegans no i'm not
if you're a plant-based person and you
do all raw stay all raw cause i love it
if you're a vegan person and you're not
all raw and you're doing cook stay stay
that way and keep your cooked in there
if you're a vegetarian and you like to
do this you can stay that way if you're
an animal protein person you can stay
that way but learn how to heal learn how
to cleanse and heal cleanse and heal
cleanse and heal
so let's talk about a few healing foods
let's go
i got a few things in front of me right
here asparagus
if you can get asparagus in you
every single day you're going to move
the needle
you're going to start moving the needle
that's a liver cleanser that's a liver
cleanser right here
right there guys on tick tock you can
see it a little bit yeah you see it
telegram liver cleanser right there
telegraph
send that down the wire asparagus you
cleanse the liver you got skin issues
you need asparagus you got eczema
psoriasis you need asparagus you got you
got vitiligo you need a spirit you want
an anti-ager you need asparagus
anti-ager
asparagus anti-ager i'm backwards on
this right
asparagus that's what i love doing live
stuff you just don't know what's going
to go wrong
right
i got a phone call coming in
i got a phone call coming in by the way
i had
i got a friend calling
so i just got you know it's incredible
where's your medicine where's the
medicinal food where is it
hello
yeah i'm
having dinner
yeah i told you i'm doing asparagus she
told me to do asparagus so i'm doing it
how many
one
yeah
yeah one
huh
what do you mean
yeah yeah yeah i'm having salmon
uh-huh
i'm having i'm having surf and turf
surfing turf i'm having salmon
and i'm having chicken
yeah
well i have i have a i have asparagus in
here
yeah
i have
well i was at the restaurant you know
when i was at the fancy restaurant
last week
what they gave me was they gave me
salmon
sauteed and they gave me
two asparagus so i'm just having two
asparagus
yeah
yeah no is my
pea get a smell
yeah i don't like asparagus because my
pee smells
yeah
and then my roommate doesn't like the
smell when my roommate goes in the
bathroom
yeah
what happened last week when i went in a
restaurant and i had more than one piece
i had a piece and a half and then i came
home and i went to the bathroom and i
smelled up the bathroom and my roommate
said that he
yeah my roommate said he wants to move
out
so i'm just gonna have one you know what
i'm just gonna have one tonight yeah one
asparagus
all right i gotta go
you get a bunch of asparagus
right
and and you eat a bunch a day but it
what it does is it replaces the fillers
is what i'm trying to tell you guys you
eat a bunch of asparagus
a half a bunch you eat a half a bunch of
asparagus that's what today's about i
forgot what today was about
i'm talking about everything under the
sunshine i think i forgot
let's just not go into the time change
thing yet because i'm going to do a
whole show on the time change
that we're going to go into the real
nitty-gritty about the time change i
hope you guys stay tuned into all my
videos on rumble on telegram right uh
right here on youtube right right here
on tick tock i got so much to say
and it's not because i know anything
it's because of my source my source
knows a heck of a lot
half a bunch of asparagus
do that
do do a half a bunch
right maybe a half a bunch do that a day
and and then you're taking place of
fillers but you're doing something where
there's the medicine you know what kind
of
anti-anti-disease fighting compounds are
in asparagus
oh whoa
you start doing that
right
and what about herb leafy greens
leafy greens that are herbs
cilantro
i'm not talking about like this you
ready
let's talk about this
so
i'm gonna put a little bit of cilantro
on my salmon
you know medical medium says cilantro is
really good
now i'm gonna
i'm gonna put a little cilantro on my
salmon right there
that's not going to get you anywhere
that's not good i love it i love you
know cooking shows out there like famous
chefs and all that stuff or whatever
do they think they they think they you
know they got it so down because they
put a little bit of that parsley chopped
up on there they want that green through
they put a scallion like a little bit of
a chive on there they put a little bit
on this meanwhile the whole plate is
filler
this isn't going to be enough
so what you do is you have
like the heavy metal detox smoothie and
you put some cilantro in there you have
cilantro as a salad okay okay okay okay
i know you guys all love avocado
right
fine
let's eat avocados let's eat avocados
okay
let's eat avocados let's have avocados
all right
let's have avocados okay i'm gonna eat
some avocados
but let's put them on a nice old big old
bed of leafy green herb
let's do that
let's put them on a big old bed of leafy
green herbs let's do that okay
how does that sound
let's do that remember what i taught you
guys about avocado on all the videos now
you guys remember right
remember that get rid of that right
there boom
that little heart is a rock stem
get rid of that you bite onto that
you're in trouble fall to the guacamole
but let's eat avocados
i'm not anti-avocado
but let's have avocado you want to eat
all the avocados you want
but let's eat it let's chop up all that
avocado on top of a lot of herb
and i'm not talking about this herb
not talking about that herb
okay is that everything
that's not a good thing
i'm not a fan of it
i'm not judging you
i'm not making funny i'm not judging you
or nothing i love you being here you do
what you want in your life
okay
but there
but keep in mind
if you want to do avocado you have it on
a bed of herb
you could do a lot of cilantro you can
do a lot of parsley you can do you can
do chop up a whole bunch maybe some
lettuce too if you want maybe some kale
and then you throw all that avocado on
there and then you chop up a tomato you
want it a little juicy you chop up a
tomato you put one of these babies in
there a little bit if you if you can
handle some heat you pop in one of those
maybe you put some red bell pepper maybe
you put a little onion but what you do
is you have your avocado salad but you
just made a medicine
ball
you just made a medicine ball
in your salad
a medicine ball that's what you did
that's what you did
you made a medicine ball
right
so keep that in mind
so let's go into a little bit of kale
right
you love your avocado
put a little bit in your kale then
but get your leafy greens in you now if
you want to heal and you got a serious
condition there's ways to heal and you
keep the avocado out and you keep the
meat out and you keep whatever out and
that's a good question right now let's
talk about that let's talk about meat
okay
you love your chicken
put a little bit of chicken
on a bed of herb
a bed of herb
you love your chicken
make sure you're eating enough herb with
it
have that at the end of the day you love
your meat or salmon
make sure you have it with a lot of herb
throw some radishes in there
get the medicine in because you gotta
balance the filler
now when it comes to healing though
healing deep seeded stuff that's still
gonna get in the way the avocado still
can get in the way if there's too much
in your diet
but the point is is you're balancing
the filler you're actually you're
actually tipping the scale the better
direction
you want to have your grass-fed beef
pieces in a salad you put them on top of
some parsley and some cilantro and some
kale and you get that green in you so
that it can help to kind of
mediate the filler
the filler
and that's the way to do it
you can do so much with steamed
vegetables on greens you can take
asparagus brussels sprouts you can take
squash you can take these beautiful
kabocha squashes right here look at that
you can take these
and you can steam these up
and it's unbelievable and you chop all
that up and all these steamed vegetables
and you put the kombucha squash on top
of your greens and that's not a filler
that's medicine your squashes are
anti-viral anti-pathogen anti-bug
anti-this anti-that they're
anti-everything that's bad for you and
that's what these squashes are and that
that when you think about that whoa
whoa
you feel like you want to have a coffee
get a bunch of oranges out cut them up
squeeze the juice out of them get a nice
fresh orange juice down
replace that coffee one time see what
happens see what clicks in see what
happens
right
carlene says i can't get organic veggies
are conventional really bad
no they're not really bad
if you can't get organic you get
conventional now i'm gonna get the crap
eat out of me for that by somebody
because someone's that's when they all
get mad everybody gets mad and they say
no medical medium tells everybody to eat
the dirty dozen medical medium tells
everybody to eat the bad pesticides
medical medium no you can definitely do
that i would do that in a second you
think you think that the fruits and
vegetables i'm eating every day are all
organic
you think so no
because you know why
because the medicine in the fruits and
vegetables you just gotta wash them good
the medicine in them outweigh they
detoxify what's in that vegetable or
fruit that's conventional it detoxifies
it
every single
crop in the conventional world
gets sprayed three times a week
the organic world
they spray three times a week
they spray msg they spray caffeine they
spray nicotine
organic doesn't mean you're free of
spray
they use nicotine and all the organic
sprays
that's why i say wash your fruits and
vegetables you you there's nicotine all
over organic produce there's nicotine
all over everything it's a good
that i mean i'm just telling you there's
msg all over organic produce there's
nicotine all over all those organic
croppers man they're spraying
they're spraying all that produce all
that produce they even spray it with
copper and stuff stuff that's bad
there's copper all over everything in
the in the conventional world of produce
there's copper in that spray too there's
pesticides they got all that all that's
in there too
and all animal products
all the animal products animals that eat
all the green grass still has all the
toxins on grass grass-fed beef
animals are also eating all these all
these other foods
right all the grain and everything else
right
people still go into restaurants i have
people there like i'm a grass-fed guy
only and they're in a restaurant eating
just regular farm-raised chicken eating
regular meat
you know everybody's eating something
see you use a lot of conventional too
look you can do conventional produce
lorraine uh lauren casey says why spray
with nicotine to kill the bugs nicotine
is a neurotoxin
nicotine and msg is a neurotoxin
msg kills insects
doesn't kill viruses inside of us it
just kills like flying insects you know
like innocent flying insects that are
flying around the nicotine and the ms
chiefs hits them and it just kills them
it kills their nervous system
so
you guys you guys i'm going to be on
amazon live
at 3 p.m eastern 12 o'clock 12 o'clock
pacific on wednesday
okay and i'm gonna be doing that every
week so i'm just letting you guys know
every single wednesday
i'm gonna be on amazon live doing the
cooking show the medical mean cooking
show and doing all the cooking tips
at three o'clock
eastern 12 o'clock pacific
just letting you know and i'm gonna be
on amazon live on sundays too it's every
sunday
it's every sunday at three o'clock
right
probably three o'clock
uh pacific three um three o'clock sorry
eastern 12 o'clock pacific just letting
you guys know
and we're going to be doing some holiday
cooking ideas we're going to be cooking
stuff we're going to be doing tips we're
going to be talking about stuff that i
use all of this
you love those squashes too
frugivore bear
how are you you love the
medical medium regular schedule
trisha marie thanks for being here amy
tang thanks for being here
and you guys i'm doing the exclusive
messages on telegram make sure you make
sure you guys subscribe to my telegram
and i'm doing exclusive videos on rumble
make sure you subscribe there cool white
spring good to see you kimberly miller
you guys
and on tick tock it's great to have you
guys here i hope we picked up some
goodies i hope you guys picked up some
goodies
today because that's what i want to do i
want to make sure you guys have the
information when you get a chance pick
up a cleanse to heal all right liver
rescue get it free at the library or
your bookstore amazon's got a killer
sale on this book right here and liver
rescue
anyway i love you guys proud of all you
guys and uh
i'll see you soon
amazon live is what we're gonna do on
wednesday i hope to see you guys there