oh
thank god you called thank god you
called
yeah they're doing it again this year
yep they're blowing off fireworks
it's not even the fourth of july yet
yeah
i know right like two two doors down
they're blowing them off they sound like
bombs
yep i know my dog
yeah my dog is in the closet right now
shaking
uh-huh i i don't know what to do i
called the vet
three times i i did the dog went into a
seizure
yeah the dog went into a seizure
i know i don't know what to do my yeah
my
my grandparents oh they're sick over it
over by their house they're laying in
their bed
yeah they're sick they're sick over it
they they're
scared to death of the fourth of july
coming like the net yeah coming
i know they usually blow fireworks until
one o'clock in the morning in people's
yards
yeah this isn't the city or the town
this is just people
people being just total
yeah disrespectful no integrity
they don't care about other people yeah
and you know and maybe some people are
good people doing it and they just
they're just that stupid they just don't
know
that they're harming they're
harming animals i i know i know i i got
the vet
i know the vet's going to be calling in
a minute yep
yep yeah
i think what happens is that oh my god
there they go again yeah they're just
blowing them off
they're two two doors down it's not even
the fourth of july
i know i know it's just so screwed up
and they don't care about newborn did
you know that in the neighborhood
there's a newborn baby
yeah yeah one month old baby
one month old baby can you imagine
all these like quarter sticks of
dynamite being thrown in the air
you know shot into the air and blowing
off do you think quarter stick
sticks of dynamite blowing off like
bombs do you think a one month
one month old baby you don't think
that's gonna affect
the future yeah there they go again
they're blowing them off
it's just i don't even
know what to say
i know i know
and the thing is is that what people
don't realize
yeah you know what it is just people who
aren't sick they've never been
chronically sick they've never been
chronically ill
they don't know what it's like to be a
mattress island they don't know it's
like when they have sensitive nervous
system
they don't know what it's like when they
have like
yeah they don't understand what that's
like to have fibromyalgia and sensitive
nervous system
yeah they just don't know they don't
care
they don't care they don't have any clue
what it's like when you're sick and and
you need to sleep there's so many people
with their sensitive nervous system they
could hardly sleep anyway
and the fact that they're just gonna be
hearing these bombs blow off past
midnight
some neighborhoods they just blow them
up cops don't do anything nobody does
anything about it
yeah yeah i mean the fireworks
just before this should be just for the
park
that has it and then everybody goes
there it should be for the beach or
something and everybody goes there
whatever
i know i know i know i don't know what
to say all i know is i have one dog in
the closet shaking
already had a seizure yeah and
so far so far this fella is hanging in
there but it's
he's traumatized he's traumatized yeah
so one dog in the closet having a
seizure but this this dog's hanging in
there but
i don't think i think that over time it
gets worse
and then next year it's gonna be worse
and then at other times of the year
yeah i know i i think it's just a
disrespect for
wildlife too like what about all the
birds that are trying to sleep
and they're just blowing these things
off everywhere in everybody's yard
and everybody's apartment home it's just
blowing them up everywhere
what about all the wildlife and the
birds yeah
what about all the different dogs and
cats what about other types of animals
too because i have a guinea pig
the guinea pig doesn't want to hear this
i know i know
i think that yeah
yeah no i i understand
i i we just gotta we'll get through this
year but
it's so sad it really is all right i'm
gonna let you go
you go my poor pup is miserable during
fireworks
i worry about seizures every july
i completely understand it it's it's
gotten really bad though
really bad i hate fireworks my dogs get
so scared karen appel chelsea thanks for
saying
they get so scared exactly what i think
people don't realize
too is that it's far worse than it ever
was
courtney may i'd be pissed if my baby
had to have bombs next to her ears and
it happens
every day you guys you guys it happens
every day
i mean they're blowing them off
everywhere and they're just starting now
starting to blow them off but it's
really devastating you got to think
about it you got a little baby right
so you got neighborhoods with all these
little newborn babies right
cheryl my dog is a seizure dog and when
she goes into seizure i lay down
and hold her and pat her and talk nice
till it's over
it's unbelievable right how it works
i mean what they're doing out there
fireworks need to be banished they
really do
they do selena they do um you know if
you want to do them at this one place
park where everybody
rolls in and you want to just one place
you know and it's it's
it's it's a lot easier unless you live
next to that park but
bev says should stopped should stop
cause the
uh vietnam vets yeah shell shock yeah
they jump under things i have to tell
you i've had so many vets that i helped
out throughout the years you guys
that are tortured by the the
by the four fourth of july but it's not
just the fourth of july that's not it
they're tortured by
neighborhoods blowing them up in their
driveways
and in their yards all across the
country so it's neighborhoods it's
in the driveway a driveway next to a
house with pets
right there or elderly people that
you know that what about without people
that are like having difficult
problems they're breathing they're on
oxygen tanks what about people that
that are um you know elderly people that
had strokes
and they're you know they're home thank
god and they're at least alive and then
they're just blowing these bombs off
i've seen it
all for years but here's the thing it
got
really really bad last
year the last couple of years it got
really really bad
and it's gonna be the worst probably
this year because the whole thing with
covet and everything
right it's made this whole thing even a
little bit more complex
people just they kind of went insane
from being locked in their homes and all
their stuff just people
bought a lot of fireworks it's probably
way worse this year right
and it's really really it's
sad it's that and you know and no one
no one gets it a man in my neighbor lost
her dog he jumped the fence and was hit
by a car
because of the fireworks right scared
the dog over the fence
and they blow them they blow them off
they blow them off
all through the night everywhere and
it's not like anybody's
like stopping it or you know anything's
happening like that
it doesn't it doesn't work like that
it's just
it's just it's just terrible and i think
that
i think it's it's important to say
something about it this fourth of july
it's gotten so bad last few years i've
always seen it bad
yeah late night too they'll do it late
night as well so you know i mean
i've always been asked what do you do
what do you do and i say look i i know
that
lemon balm tea can't fix it right can't
fix people blowing these bombs off
non-stop
everywhere and it happens all night long
right
and but but i always recommend lemon
balm tea just lots of lemon balm tea i
got lemon balm tea now i recommend that
you know
there's the vimergy lemon balm tincture
right there the cleanest stuff out there
in the world
and then i tell friends and family just
totally
just just down it you know four five six
dropper fulls at a time that's what i
tell family and that's the vimergy
lemon balm if you guys want something to
help
in some way so especially with so many
people with crippling anxiety problems
too
these fireworks are really out of hand i
cannot take it they release toxins in
the air and i want to talk about that
that's one thing i want to talk about
we get anxious causes anxiety my cats
get scared too adrina i totally
understand
you guys on tick tock how you guys doing
thanks for coming on we're talking about
the firework
problem lorena good see everybody's
coming on and
and i think that you know uh the toxic
part okay so let's go into that part
right
fireworks are manufactured right
without eyeballs on them i want you to
know so there's no eyeballs on the
manufacturing of
of fireworks right and even if i
eyeballs were on them
in the industry they'd still be toxic
but they're
severely toxic fireworks aren't gun
powder
alone they're a brew of chemical toxins
and they just and and so when
everybody's blowing them off the stuff's
drifting and floating through the air
really bad for people with asthma bad
for people with all kinds of
sensitivities
and chemical sensitivities right all
that kind of stuff
and so this stuff just drifts and drips
and it's a chemical soup it's not
gun powder gun powder is just one aspect
of it
it's a chemical soup like literally a
chemical soup is what it is
and and so no one's even like
no one even is monitoring that no one
cares
about that no one cares whatsoever
i got nervous about people hurting
themselves too i mean that's just
one aspect exactly michelle that's one
aspect of it right there's always a
child that gets their
like hand blown off her fingers blown
off every single year
not one there's always like a good 100
children that get injured from it being
shot one way or shot the other and then
and then
you know causing a severe injury to kids
right
so there's that too and then that's
scary that's terrifying really
but it's it's terrifying
that it's all encompassed children's
injuries
babies getting like a form of shell
shock
in their life so here's how it works so
when the bombs are blowing up and you
got your little baby
and your little baby's hearing these
explosions
what happens is you don't know it but it
affects situations years later down the
road
in the child's life so it affects it and
even into adult
adulthood so people don't realize that
the shapes
it causes problems like it causes
problems
down the road and that's another thing
too i'm just sad about it all
conrad i once witnessed how a drunken
young man
blew off half of his thumb by holding on
to a big firecracker
in his hand without throwing it away
absolutely i mean there's hands blown
off there's
feet burned and toes blowing off there's
there's all that stuff for sure and
there's head injuries and deaths
there's deaths there's lots of those
every single year catherine elizabeth
espanol years ago we know a child that
died
from a mortar blowing up in his face
absolutely and catherine
i i know stories of that children that
died
from it going to the face and just
blowing the child's face
off i mean literally
i know one tastes horrifying i don't
know anything worse than that actually
there's nothing worse than that on the
planet right
and so um
yeah so anyway i was talking about like
the lemon balm and stuff for people see
if you guys got the anxiety
um you can't get a hold of emergency
lemon balm maybe get a hold of
uh a traditional medicinals right
get a hold of their tea do a whole bunch
of lemon balm tea
i'm not sponsored by vimergy i'm not
sponsored by
traditional medicinals just so you know
okay
but that's the vimergy lemon balm
vimergy magnesium glycinate i recommend
that all the time for this and
the vimergy gaba the vimergy gaba i
recommend to
war vets who live through wars and
there's lots of them
there's lots of them and they live
through wars you know
and they watch their friends die in wars
and
and uh but check you know check with
your doctor and what's right for you of
course you know
check with your doctors what's right for
you but that's what i recommend friends
and family
um i think that i think one of the
things to consider really with it all is
that
is that it's a compilation of all of it
right you've got the elderly
people okay lots of them out there
right and lots of them are sick now so
we've got elderly people that are sick
and then we got young people that are
sick now two struggling with their
central nervous system struggling with
severe fatigue struggling with all kinds
of problems they got ocd
they got bipolar they got ptsd from
being sick
they got migraines they got all these
different issues right
and you guys know that and these bombs
blowing up it's just
downright torture just downright torture
it's heartbreaking
and and then you've got the wildfires
that happen from it like nobody cares
about that
does anybody realize after every fourth
of july
there's a serious fire in california
that starts
up like a new one and a really bad one
so let's just make the connection there
okay because every fourth of july
in california we have the fires
and they start up and then before they
become
raging which is like a week later two
weeks later
but they start it during the fourth and
it and they caught on and no one really
found out about it until late or a
little bit like a week later as it's
already blue
but you know everyone should be aware
they should bring awareness about this
stuff people should start voicing about
it
you know everybody's about them here's
the thing here's the thing that bothers
me the most right
is not bothers me the most but just one
of these things that bothers me right
hey paige hall crystal how you doing
exactly right and the fire's raging
and yeah now so here's here's something
to consider okay it's like isn't
everybody about this awareness thing
everybody's so aware and so spiritual
and so together and
and i know listen i know people have
their
thoughts uh about like certain groups of
people are more apt to blow off
fireworks i i don't believe that
it's everybody it's east west coast
it's it's everywhere in between it's
south
north it's you know
it's north it's south it's east it's
west it's everywhere
and so it's not about hey you know
everybody's like well you know
everybody's so spiritual everybody has
so much awareness
and i just wonder about that because i
scratch my head on that one i'm like i'm
scratching my head on that one
and what about kindness everybody's got
that whole kindness thing going on like
everybody's pulling that whole kindness
thing behind this i
just wonder um i think that
um you know so it's kind of stuff i
wanted to talk about for a couple of
minutes with you guys
and adriana says it's everywhere yes
yeah it is you know firework negatives
don't
outweigh the positives firework you know
sorry firework positives don't
they don't outweigh the negatives
gotta flip that one around yeah and uh
that's what happens when you're working
on the book all practically all night
and then you get three hours of sleep
and then you want to let everybody know
about fireworks jewel
you know i think the butt and we're live
we're live we don't do the editing
editing cutting editing cutting make
sure everything's right i sent every
sentence editing cutting
cutting editing cutting whatever we
don't do that i want to make sure you
guys it's
raw to the bone it's live
it's here um i think i think the bottom
line is
is when you look at all the different
pieces of it it's
it i think it's just tragic tragic i do
guys give the video a thumbs up if you
get a chance i never ask you guys
subscribe if you haven't subscribed
all right if you haven't we're live on
tick tock live clubhouse live on
facebook live on
youtube um i think okay so you know the
thing my dog ran away
last year because he was trying oh my
god because of the fireworks oh my god
if my dog ran away and
and you know i couldn't get my dog back
and my dog ran away because the
fireworks i just
i don't know what to even say i think
these things matter i mean don't they
these things matter so much so much
and and then there's like i said the
fires right
it's like we get these california fires
we get them everywhere too we get them
in other places because the fourth
fourth of july are around this time of
year but we get these california fires
really crank up
right around the fourth right because
it's it it's like
it's it's really irresponsible for so
many ways but
then you get all this wildlife that's
just wiped out
wiped out 500 acres wildlife wiped out 2
acres wildlife just wiped out like over
some fireworks
right i don't know sick
i think seaweed hero good to see you
yeah there's catastrophic wildfires that
have happened
i'm heading off to ig and
i'm gonna put tick-tock back on i'll put
clubhouse back on you guys and over to
ig now
i know i just think you know think about
it you know give it give it some thought
you guys if you haven't thought about it
before i know you guys know what's going
on you guys in the medical meme
community you always know what's going
on
there's so many other ways to celebrate
the fourth of july
i'm not saying that all fireworks have
to be completely banned
it's not what it is it's like what has
to be done is
i don't think we should be allowed to
go and buy because quarter stick of
dynamite half stick of dynamite
these blockbusters right they're all
blockbusters they're m80s
m60s blockbusters their quarter stick of
dynamites have sticker dynamites they
get propelled in the air
through a rocket right and um i just
i just don't think that the cool that
those big bomb
blasts should be a part of it i think
that those big bomb blasts i think
curfews on on on fireworks too
i just don't think your neighbor should
be allowed to go get a half a stick of
dynamite and propel it in their driveway
while you got a one month baby one month
old baby
two dogs that might be seizuring cat
that might be seizuring
a war vet home whether a female or a
male warbuck
man or woman and uh at home
and i i just think i just think that
that shouldn't be
part of everything you know i think we
just should be mindful
and then the chronic illness and then
the elderly and then and then
i i know situations where you know you
got
an elderly person who's hypersensitive
been through enough in their life
they're older
sick and then they also have a pet and
they
can't even get the pet in the closet to
try to stop the seizures you know
because they're just too sick they're
going around in a walker
and they're trying to get their pets you
know
and war vets they had to serve the
country
they lived through the wars they they've
been through all that they've had
explosives blow up and around them and
close by they're damaged
emotionally uh spiritually
ptsd right you know
and when you think about that i just
don't think we should be blowing off
these bombs right next to the war vets
that could be you know
nearby got to have some respect i mean
they went to war to hear those bombs
right they didn't want to hear it in
their backyard while sitting in a chair
in the backyard or they don't want to
hear it
when they're trying to go to sleep at 10
o'clock at night 11 12 o'clock at night
i don't know it's all it's everything
it's everything
right now a lot of people with
trigeminal neuralgia by the way
trigeminal neuralgia really have a hard
time in the migraines in the
in the trigeminal neuralgia
i mean seriously that's really rough
really rough so i keep that in mind
then i keep keep in mind too about the
homeless you know
the homeless because there's millions of
homeless people now in the u.s
millions right and millions of homeless
people in the u.s right now
and they're living on the streets
they're living in tent cities right
and they're they're not well they're
hanging in there by a threat and they
have no
not even a house or an apartment or
anything like that to protect them
um ellie says i agree that you shouldn't
be able to buy fireworks in australia
you can
only you can only do it if you have a
license too many get hurt in the past
it's incredible really
anyway guys i'm heading off to ig and
i'm gonna turn
tick tock back on clubhouse back on
you know so okay um and heading off to
ig