[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
Decades of ahead head of what's out
there now and I've recently been seeing
that it's been upsetting a few
professionals out there the fact that
the information's advanced and the
information is ahead of the time and it
makes certain people feel uncomfortable
it's the last thing I want to happen or
um to get anybody stirred up that's not
it although stirring the pot gets people
to think and it gets people to move
forward in different ways but still at
the same time you know when
practitioners and healers and doctors
doctors especially doctors and they go
whether it's alternative or conventional
they go to medical school they go in
because they want to save the world they
want to save people they want to
discover something they want to know
what's causing cancer they want to know
what's causing a disease what's causing
an illness and that means it's so much
it's incredible what you know and they
go in with compassion and they go in
because they in their heart and soul
they want to help someone and they want
to have those answers and that's what's
amazing about the health field and the
most incredible part of it of the
journey in and and in people's souls and
in their hearts and so you know I mean
over the years I've run across some some
amazing Professionals in the health
realm that that want to hear the
information I have to offer they want to
hear it because they they know they've
been around the block long enough they
they've been there long enough whether
they struggled with their own illness
and couldn't find an answer or theyve
they just want answers no matter what or
where or how the source is they want to
know what's going on for their patients
and then have come across you know some
some different professionals that hey if
it's not in a textbook somewhere they
don't want to hear it they don't want to
know and that's too bad it's really sad
because you got to keep an open mind you
got to keep you know belief systems you
know on what I call like neutral the
best you can because the information
that comes from Spirit that that I've
been given the gift to offer is
information to consider and truly
consider you know and and I'm not saying
hey it's the end all or anything someone
said to me well you got all the answers
you got all the answers Mr bigshot and
that's not it at all I don't have any
answers it's Spirit giving me the
information I'm the messenger I'm the
voice also for people who have struggled
and suffered offered for years and
decades with no answers in no direction
and that's frightening right there not
having the right answers or having a
diagnosis that's you know not even the
right diagnosis or a label that isn't
even correct or an understanding I mean
you guys know if you listen to the show
you've heard enough shows to know
there's so much going on underneath
these labels and these mystery illnesses
and chronic and mystery illness is so
out of control it's getting out of
control more and more rapidly and
rampantly so for a professional to or
professionals to you know put a blind
eye to information or think it's not a
credible source is really a disservice
to patients and other people like I said
I know so many doctors and professionals
that want information and they don't
care they want to hear it they want to
understand it they want to know and they
want to they want to level that against
the information they've learned and they
want to equate it or equalize it or
neutralize it so they can find answers
because when it comes to Healing The
Miraculous healing process of the human
body no one really has their finger on
that part because the because it it has
a lot to do with God it has a lot to do
with human nature it has a lot to do
with so many different facets and so
basically what I'm trying to say is yes
the information is ahead of the time on
the show and it is
much of it's not found anywhere else but
if you are a professional and you just
logged on and this is the first time
just sit back hey if you want to giggle
giggle if you want to say aha that's an
aha moment say an aha moment but sit
back relax enjoy the show get as much
information as you can for your patience
and so forth and and and move on forward
from there and look and the show I've
always said the show is and everything I
do is for the person who's not even a
practitioner it's a for the person to
become their own expert it's for the
person to become an expert and know more
also than no more than many people or
many practitioners out there so it's
about making sure everybody's armed and
everybody's armed with the power of
information The Shield of information
the armor of information from a source
that was given to me since age four and
um and someone said how is it possible
you have so much information you put it
out on blogs you write articles
constantly you have it in your books
it's never ending and it's and it's all
it's like brand new coming off the shelf
and never been anywhere else the only
way that's possible and and someone also
said well it how do you store all that
in your head I don't it comes streaming
through from Spirit and that's the gift
and that's why the books are coming out
and they're going to keep on coming out
and that's why I'm doing what I'm doing
but the deal is for you to be that
expert okay so I'm a voice and a
messenger from Spirit giving you know
giving that those messages to you so you
can become that expert so you can heal
and I'm also the voice for the people
who have never been hurt who suffered
their whole lives with no answers 30
years going by with fatigue and multiple
sclerosis and and and God knows what
else is they they've been labeled or
dealing with in neurological problems
and everything else depression anxiety
that never goes away I've been the voice
for people so they get answers so they
can get help and so you can be that
voice too and we can join together and
really and really make a difference in
the world I'm honored to be here I'm
honored to be here during the show
today's show is about food poisoning
food poisoning have you ever had food
poisoning have you had that before I
have I've had it before when I was a
child one time I talked about a little
bit I talked about a couple of lines
about it in my my first book medical
medium but food poisoning is rampant yes
it's out there it's everywhere and we
have to be careful there's a lot you can
understand to avoid it why would you
want to avoid food poisoning because it
has killed a lot of people it has ended
a lot of lives for a lot of people and
also injured and wounded a lot of people
as well along the way where they've been
wounded and injured permanently
permanently so yes we want to be careful
we want to look out with food poisoning
so today's show is about you know arming
yourself with the truth about food
poisoning in all kinds of different ways
that's what we're going to cover today
check out the life-changing Foods book
since we're talking about
Foods check out the lifechanging foods
book okay um you know it's packed with
information that one is packed with
information you know I did everything I
could to make sure that thing was just
Lock Stock and Barrel packs so please
please check it out it's if you can um
healing path download the healing path
as well go to Medical medium.com you can
download the healing path for free what
is the healing path it's the healing
path is like a 19 episode course thing
that's for free free
free it's it's audios of me walking you
through all kinds of aspects of health
so you can heal I mean I talk about
freedom in there I talk about creativity
in there I talk about you know um
everything that can help you and Aid in
your healing I talk about Foods just
just get it for free there's no gimmicks
with it just download it and you got it
and start listening start listening and
um and take it seriously just because
it's free doesn't mean you don't take it
seriously because it's serious it's real
serious so make sure you do that so
let's go into the show let's let's hit
it let's get right into it food
poisoning um you know there's a lot of
people all you have to do is just
mention the word food poisoning and
they'll be like oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I I kind of aware of that and they
might be one of the wounded soldiers
along the way that have been injured
from food poisoning are really hit hard
from it so what what can we do to
prevent it we're going to hit all
aspects first of all it's important to
understand that I'm not going to make
fun of any diet belief system in this
episode but I am going to talk a little
bit more about meat eating and chicken
eating and turkey eating and pork eating
not in the negative way like hey you
should well you shouldn't eat pork that
that part I'll definitely say just no
one should be eating pork I don't care
who it is just saying there's no healthy
bacon now I realized that one of the
listeners out there two or three or 10
of them for all I know could be raising
their own their own pigs and and and
raising them in the best way and that's
amazing so if you are going to have if
you are going to have bacon and it's
your own Pig you're raising and that's
the and that's what you do I I support
it okay I do it just don't eat a lot of
it don't eat a lot of it don't have it
every day keep it in the freezer or
something you know uh longer term
stretch it out more just so you don't
you know burden down the liver and the
pancreas and everything else because no
matter what pork is still high fat even
though the white meat of pork so okay so
back on to this I'm not going to be
ripping in to you know a belief system
if you like animal products I support
you and I'm going to support you on how
to protect yourself how to protect
yourself that's what I'm going to do and
if you're a vegetarian or a vegan or
whatever just eat fish I'm going to
support you to protect yourself because
you have to be protected there too when
it comes down to food poisoning believe
it or not because we go into restaurants
if you're a vegan or a vegetarian you go
into a restaurant you can go into a
restaurant and and uh what happens is in
that
restaurant um you could be having a
salad or something or or or so forth and
that salad could have been contaminated
it could have been you know that salad
could have been um um cont
cross-contaminated with something else
in there in in in the restaurant in the
kitchen the restaurant I'm going to go
deep into that in a little bit so so
let's let's rip into this let's do this
so on meats and chickens and Fishes
that's where we have to worry pretty
much the most is how we're preparing
meat and chicken you know this if you
eat chicken that's raw what can happen
you can die yeah you can die not just
get sick but but die lose a life you
know there's so many people who
undercook a turkey for Thanksgiving the
hospitals are filled with sick people
that have had underdone turkey in during
Thanksgiving there are hundreds and
hundreds actually thousands of food
poisoning turkey dinner cases in the
hospitals and ERS across the country
during Thanksgiving so so what we have
to understand is why is that how is that
happening what's going on with that what
what makes that happen well so so so we
need to be safe bottom line bottom line
so you know I talk to doctors a lot and
and over the years and have a lot of
doctor friends and and they've seen
people die from food poisoning like it's
no joke when you talk to a a doctor
who's been who seen it or is aware of it
he or she will have a look on their face
and say it's it's it's almost like the
most most sad death because it could a
could have been avoided maybe B there's
so many other things we can die from
that food poisoning really it shouldn't
be on the list because this is food
safety this is food this is food we're
eating this is our lives this is what
we're
doing so okay so what do we do when
we're making food at home and we're
going to hit restaurants too this is
important so what what are we doing when
we're making food at home well first of
all you have to make sure that your
hands and you will probably already know
this many of you if you're taking
chicken out of a package touching the
package itself is already a problem
right there that means when you touch
that package your hands already have
bacteria on it and I'm not just talking
about salola in the packag is in the
grocery store chicken and meat of all
kinds there's SEI and some sorry there's
SEI and Mera all over the outside of
pack packages at the grocery store
that's number one right there so there's
bacteria loaded on the outside of every
one of those wrapped packages so when
you're just grabbing the package and
you're like oh honey hey and you take it
out of the refrigerator we're going to
have chicken tonight and you put it down
you put it down on the counter now your
hand is a weapon that can actually
injure your children right there right
there so you have to go and wash your
hands right there right after you touch
that package or after you opened it up
you got to make sure you always have a
clean hand when you touch your knife the
handle of your knife or your handle will
have bacteria from when it was dirty so
if you take a package out of the
refrigerator honey would you like
chicken tonight then what do the kids
want and you put that chicken on the
counter okay and now you grab the knife
to open up the package to cut the
package open your hand now after
touching the package touch the handle of
the knife and you Put The Knife Down you
open up the package and whether you wash
your hands or not your handle on your
knife could have the bacteria on it now
is this being more is this being phobic
is this is that what it is no it's not
trust me it's not it's being big time
safe Big Time safe I've seen a lot of
food poisoning cases in my day in the 30
plus years and more and even before that
and so so that's one thing to always be
con concerned about so what do you do
you can do a couple things you can
purchase those night trial gloves those
blue n trial gloves you know the ones
you see um at different places and stuff
you know the ones where they pat you
down at the uh or you see you see not
they pat you down at the airport if you
don't want to go through the scanner or
they have the night trial gloves at the
airport everybody's wearing them when
they're looking at your ID when you're
walking through whatever it is those
night Tri gloves and you see them at the
dentist's office you see them everywhere
now so so you can wear those until your
chicken is out into wherever you're
going to be start preparing it or making
it and then tear tear the gloves off and
you got instant Clean Hands you that's
one way of doing it you can you know
change your knife if you know your knife
was contaminated in different ways the
handle of the knife was contaminated but
this is just the tip of the iceberg okay
rinsing off your chicken in the in the
sink is a common thing we do the problem
is with that is you just rinsed all this
dangerous bacteria in the sink and it's
just sitting there right off the chicken
and and what happens is then you go
watch washing an orange or washing a
some lettuce in the sink and the lettuce
Falls in or touches the side of the sink
and you
forget and that lettuce touching the
side of the sink could have picked up
some of that bacteria from rinsing the
chicken off first so there's so many
things to be concerned about and to be
worried about and we have to be careful
and here's the other thing if you put
chicken in a plate that's raw and you
didn't cook it yet and it's in a plate
that's raw that plate that Plate's done
after you start frying that chicken or
start boiling that chicken or start
doing what you want to do if that
chicken was raw in a plate that Plate's
done that means that plate goes
somewhere it goes in the dishwasher it
goes in the sink wherever it goes but it
goes
somewhere because you can't put that
cooked chicken once that chicken's
cooked I've seen people put that cooked
chicken right on top of that same plate
where the raw chicken sat same thing
with Meats I've seen people have the raw
steak the steak on a plate they go to
the barbecue in the back or the grill in
the back okay they you know lift that
steak off that plate there's raw juices
on that plate throw that steak on the
burner on the grill whatever it is in
the backyard they're cooking that steak
and then when when that steak's done
they throw it right back on the plate
with the
juices bam instant food poisoning
possibilities and it's a it's a luck of
the draw it's Russian Roulette Russian
roulette with your lives so hey that's
that that once that steak was on that
plate that that's done that's over with
right there once that's you know once
that's been on there that's over with so
you move that over over so so and you
get a new plate and you put that cook
steak on that new plate but that's not
where it all stops barbecuing with the
sauces you got the brush sticking in the
sauces and then you're you're you're
glazing the raw meat with that
sauce so you got the sauce brush and
you're glazing your ribs you're glazing
your steak you're glazing whatever it is
your pork chops whatever it is you got
cooking you're glazing with some kind of
sauce well as that brush is rubbing on
that raw meat raw pork raw chicken
whatever it may be it's just pulling
bacteria off right into that sauce and
you put it right back in your big your
big dish of fresh sauce over there and
the problem is with that is a lot of
people stick their finger in the sauce
they they taste it after that boom food
poisoning also another thing happens
what they do is right after after it's
been cooked right after the pork's been
cooked the meat's been cooked the
chicken's been cooked they stick more
sauce on it at the end which isn't
getting cooked now because it's going on
top it's glazing on top after it already
did on the raw meat chicken or pork
beforehand see you know you see how it
works so food poisoning is really easy
to get and what can food poisoning do
well it's a lot of different strains of
ecoli rip right through your guts break
into your gallbladder explode it people
lose their gallbladders all the time run
down to the appendix get you an appendix
operation a lot of confusion happens at
the doctor's off or at the ER they don't
know what's wrong um they don't know if
it's food poisoning or not while you're
in agony and vomiting and diarrhea they
don't know they just wait you just wait
it out and the problem is that the ER is
not a lot they can do but just stick an
IV in you to keep you from dying from
dehydration and hopes that your vomiting
eases off and the diarrhea eases off and
because I know for a fact by by knowing
so many professionals and so many
doctors and being friends with many good
doctors over the years I know for a fact
that and ER doctors emergency room
doctors hospital doctors I know for a
fact that when people have food
poisoning it's a matter of time and
chance and luck and doctors know that
when you're sitting your butt in a
hospital in a hospital hospital bed and
you've just vomited for two straight
days and had diarrhea for two straight
days including maybe some blood involved
or maybe none of that just
pain and you're in the hospital for two
days on an IV they all wait it out and
they all look at each other like is this
person going to make it or
not that's how serious food poisoning is
so at the same time you know you can
heal and you can get past that as well
at the same time there's things you
could do that we're going to talk about
that up your game so you don't end up in
trouble so you don't end up in that
waiting game so if you do get food
poisoning no big deal you vomit for a
bit have diarrhea for a bit but it's not
going to take you out because we're
going to prepare you with some options
to make sure that you're not in that
situation where you're in a hospital and
doctors looking at each other after
you've been sitting there for 5 days on
IV with no ability of putting food down
or water down the pike and so we're
going to make sure that we we prepare
you the best you can best we can in any
way possible so that it's you get food
poisoning it doesn't take you out and
maybe maybe you throw up a couple times
and that's it maybe you know whatever it
is but we're going to we're going to
help you in every way so to to look out
for your family your friends it's not
about fear it's not about scaring you
it's about protecting you it matters
I've protected a lot of people over the
years and it mattered and it Protected
Their Lives when they got food poisoning
they weren't scared because they knew
options they knew how to handle it they
knew how to deal with it they knew what
to do and so all the
matters um so okay let's go let's go
back into contamination a little bit so
I have to worry about that
cross-contamination putting that steak
back on that plate that there's juices
in that plate you know using that big
fork that went and put the steak on off
the plate onto the grill and then when
the steak was done taking that fork
jamming it into that steak and and and
and running new bacteria in it and
putting it back on that plate all these
things we have to consider every last
bit of it now I know this makes it hard
and not enjoyable as much so when you're
cooking hamburgers on a grill you might
be like well you know Anthony scared the
bedin out of me so much it's not I'm
taking the enjoyment out of my fourth of
July cookout that's you that's not what
I'm trying to do but it it could it
could spook you a little bit but once
again it's important to understand how
all of this works
so contamination chicken in the kitchen
yeah we want to make sure that you clean
your surfaces The Cutting Board Factor
happens all the time people put raw
chicken right on The Cutting Board and
they're they're slicing it or cutting it
there or filling it or whatever I mean
opening it up and doing some kind of
stuffed stuffed um breast and they're
they're preparing it on the cutting
board and all that raw chickens Over The
Cutting Board you got to make sure that
you wash that cutting board off good you
can't can't just throw it in the in the
sink and give it a quick rinse I would
have another cutting board nearby so if
you you're pretty much done with that
cutting board I just move it you know
move it over make sure it's nowhere to
be found make sure it's in the in the
you know on a different counter or
something like that put a new cutting
board down so that if you know whatever
you're doing whether it's plates or
whatever I mean remember if chicken
juices are on the counter or on a
cutting board and you put a clean plate
on top of that cutting board or that
counter the bottom of the plate has
possibility of of some dangerous
bacteria at the bottom of the plate so
even when you put that cooked food that
cooked chicken right off the right off
the pan right on top of that new plate
and then you stick your hand underneath
that plate to serve someone you got now
that raw chicken on your hand it's so
easy in so many ways to get this stuff
around so okay if you're not perfect at
any of this fine fine but at least
you're more aware of it maybe and that's
the key too you got to be more aware of
it make sure oh wait did I just use that
fork in this raw chicken and I forgot
and I put it to the side and now I'm
giving one of my guests that fork at the
table you know it's everything
everything matters why does it matter
because the animal products can kill us
they can kill us now I know there's a
lot of um there's a lot of vegan doctors
out there and stuff that say yeah well
it can kill us cuz it can clag your
arteries and it could it can uh you know
it could do this it can do that it can
give you heart attacks it can make your
cholesterol go up and sure sure sure
sure I'm talking about it can kill you
it can kill you you eat raw chicken you
can die you eat raw turkey you can die
and you know you eat raw steak you can
die never do raw steak tartar never do
anything tartar never do anything raw
don't even do raw fish whatever you do
make sure it's cooked you like fish you
cook it you cook it you know I worked on
a boat a long long time ago for fun and
uh to get some fresh air and go out a go
on go out on a fishing boat and I I you
know did that to help out a friend and
and so forth and everything and when I
was out there I saw a
worm that that came out of a fish that
came out of a fish the worm stretched
six feet long six feet long
this worm and that worm used to be a
tiny egg inside the fish you don't want
and this is a wild fish you don't want
and and you and and I pul I I grabbed
that worm and I stretched it out it was
six feet long and it was alive and it
was
squiring and it was a worm that was
inside a fish you know when the fish was
cut open the worm popped out and so you
don't want to eat raw fish if you're big
into Sushi I just I'm just I just would
say no I would say first of all you're
not supposed to be doing tuna anyway
tuna is really not a good thing maybe
you could do salmon sushi but still you
always have the possibility of getting a
couple of eggs in you from you know from
some
worms but you want your salmon cooked
you want your fish cooked and you want
to apply similar laws where you don't
want
cross-contamination where you want to be
careful with that
cross-contamination you want to you fish
juices that are on the counter on the
plate whatever it may be it's important
now look grass-fed beef Freer range
chicken has less bacterial
possibilities than Factory farmed meat
and chicken and turkey and so forth and
we know that you guys know that I'm sure
you do that's what's
amazing about you know grass-fed beef
and everything else that it is
especially from small sources small
farms but even small farms have to ship
they have to ship their
cattle to a small Factory and the small
Factory could have different things
running through it and so forth I don't
think in a lot of States it's legal for
a very small farm you know doing their
grass-fed beef and growing their growing
their cows and and slaughtering on
slaughtering them on site um I don't
think that's allowed in a lot of places
they have to ship them I mean they have
to send them to the old factory so even
though they raised them in it's high
quality grass-fed beef they have to ship
them to a factory and that factory could
be more wholesome more free range more
grass-fed in the sense of its nature of
the factory and everything around it but
I've seen situations where the factories
weren't really like that and they're
running through a lot of different
business and okay sure here's the
grass-fed beef stuff coming in but what
was before that was grain fed and so
there's possibilities for
cross-contamination even in the best
circumstances of grass-fed and free
range now once again once again just so
no one's angered no one's upset doesn't
mean I don't support anybody who's who
thinks that meat's good or doesn't or a
belief system or they love grass-fed
beef whatever it doesn't mean I don't
support all that that's not about it
that's about making sure that you're
protected that's that's what I care
about no matter what um and it covers
every part of the aspects that we talk
about in all that different episodes so
but there is less contamination with
grass-fed beef free range chicken
there's less possibilities for Dangerous
strains of salmonella dangerous strains
of eoli and so forth so all the
different you know bugs and varieties of
bugs that we worry about and and so that
matters but it doesn't mean it's not
still dangerous and the possibilities
aren't still dangerous so we have to
understand that conventional eggs the
outside of conventional eggs are loaded
with bacteria loaded salmonella on the
outside of conventional eggs you know
unconventional eggs free range eggs they
don't have that on the outside of the
eggs it's rare to none so that's an
example of of of how much better it can
get just you know I always say don't eat
the eggs if you're viral you get
neurological problems if you got been
diagnosed with any kind of autoimmune
whatever it is I always say don't do the
eggs anyway we know that
so all
right so we're getting out of the
kitchen tricks the whole bit and and
kitchen tricks meaning being cautious
the way you're plating things that the
knives you're sticking in food making
sure that that wasn't the knife going
into raw meat and then sitting there and
being used again you name it we're being
cautious on all of that so let's go into
restaurants let's go into restaurants
this is important this is really
important restaurants it's it's it's
hell in those kitchens I'm just going to
tell you right now what I mean by hell
in those kitchens the pressure is is uh
insurmountable in kitchens for on the
cooks and the chefs the pressure is
unbelievable the pressure and I've
talked about this with Epstein bars and
stuff a lot of chefs cut their fingers
daily in kitchens whether it's a slight
cut a mild cut or an old cut that's
still bleeding on and off from being
banged around with pots and pans the
cuts happen all the time
there's a lot of Band-Aids on Chefs in
the kitchens they do throw gloves on
when they get cut okay but then you know
that glove after a day they take the
glove off the Cut's still kind of there
it's still seeping that happens all the
time and with when regards to Epstein
bar that's an easy way to catch Epstein
bar or a new Epstein bar or someone's
Epstein bar so I'm going to talk about
what to do to protect yourself on that
level but food poisoning my God that one
right there for kitchens is really what
we need need to look at is the most
important of all because in kitchens
they wash all that lettuce in the sinks
they wash chicken I mean it's
unbelievable what happens countertops
surfaces are never washed good enough
there's all kinds of things
interchanging constantly you can be
getting a vegetarian dish that's in a
chicken restaurant or a meat serving
restaurant and you can be getting a
vegetarian dish because you you want
vegetarian and that pan
could literally have been splashed by
chicken going into the pan next to it
raw chicken going into the pan next to
it for somebody else's dinner here's
what I
recommend I recommend that if first of
all if you're a meat eater chicken eater
whatever in the whole bit Animal product
eater and you know it doesn't matter
what restaurant you eat in in a sense
okay well unless it's a fast food
restaurant with fried food and
everything else that's ridiculous you
know what I mean getting in a good
restaurant a a decent restaurant if
you're a vegan that vegetarian you know
plant-based person don't ever eat in an
animal product serving restaurant then
you can really protect yourself but okay
say you have no choice as a plant-based
person and you have to go out with
family and friends and they also serve
chicken and whatever there so and fish
so never eat
raw ever in a restaurant as a
plant-based person that's serving
chicken
or meat or anything else this is
critical to know because you're going to
get your raw salad but your raw salad
was made by somebody with bare hands
that just held a chicken because they're
under so much pressure there's no rules
it is literally like it's like Mad Max
it's like there's no rules it's like
Escape From New York or whatever you
know we're talking about it's you know
the old movies there's no rules in those
kitchens when when stuff's fly and
everything and maybe there are a couple
kitchens that have it down pat but
there's a couple of kitchens sure but
there's hundreds and hundreds of
kitchens where it's all about get this
ready get this done people want this now
um short staffed high pressure you name
it so if you're plant-based you never
eat a salad or anything raw in a Animal
product restaurant unless you ordered a
avocado but they didn't cut it open you
cut it open at your table you cut it
open say do you have an avocado here
bring me an avocado bring me a couple of
avocados and you cut them open right
there and you scoop them out on top of
your plate that's just an example that's
one way of eating out there but hey
that's no fun I get it so what you do is
you order cooked so if you're
plant-based for example if you're
plant-based and vegetarian so forth you
want to order cooked there's no question
it has to be cooked but that's not all
it has to come hot has to come hot you
can order a cooked dish they might have
a couscous dish or something or quinoa
dish in a restaurant fancy restaurant
that's also serving all kinds of animal
products but that quinoa dish has been
cold sitting in the refrigerator it was
already pre-made a day before okay and
they say oh this this num skull wants uh
this num skull is a plant-based person
and they want they want now the quino
dish they're picking let's we can't make
fresh quinoa right now let's pull the
the pre-made quinoa dish out of the
fridge it was sitting right next to all
the chickens and and raw chickens and
raw meats let's just warm it up really
quick in the microwave or we'll warm it
up in the pan really quick and it's
it'ss right there on the pan and a lot
of times it doesn't get heated all the
way through then in restaurants they
have sauces lots of sauces and squeezy
bottles there's so much
cross-contamination in all the squeezy
bottles in restaurants high quality
restaurants of all kinds of levels of
salmonella and bacteria E coli sitting
in those squeezy bottles because the
sauces are prepared around raw chicken
and raw meats all the time and people's
hands are dirty and they're just they're
just you know putting it all in those
containers The Squeeze bottles and you
get your quinoa dish right out right
even if it came out hot in that moment
after you heated it up or she heated it
up the chef did then they squirt cold or
lukewarm unheated sauce right on top of
that and bring it to you so here's the
deal you know tell them you want no
sauces put on top afterward if you can
tell them you want it hot you want the
plate hot you want the dish hot if it
comes lukewarm you send it back in a
nice way because you don't want to get
anybody upset in restaurants that's
another thing I learned too okay you
don't want to get anybody upset you
don't know who really is got an axe to
grind or whatever and you don't know
what can happen to your dish if you piss
off someone so um that's just a fact I'm
just telling you right now so the deal
is is that and where did I where did I
even get that information from having so
many clients who worked in the
restaurant business in all kinds of
different ways so many hundreds of
clients over the years over the last
three decades and I've heard
stories I just couldn't even repeat so
the point is is in a nice way you get
your plate brought back hot you don't
want them to redo it you just want it
hot
and so it kills off
everything everything so if you're vegan
vegetarian you do that all right that's
that's one way of doing it if you're if
you're Animal product based you still
want it to come back hot too just in
case but you not only want that you
don't want anything rare you don't want
your meat rare it's one thing you have
to always understand I I don't care if
you've been eating rare meat meat with
no problems you've never had food
poisoning you've been doing great for 20
years in your life 30 years you've been
eating meat rare at your favorite
restaurant there's always that day
there's always that day I've witnessed
it out there in the world you make sure
your burger whatever it is you're doing
grass-fed burger or just just plain old
USDA crap Burger whatever it is you just
make sure it's well done okay at least
medium at least medium you know to well
done or medium the the the least never
wanted rare so you can be protected in
restaurants that's important for both
meat eaters and vegans vegetarians
plant-based whatever you have to use
lemon ask in your restaurants can you
bring me lemons bring me a lemon bring
me a cut lemon or cut it yourself bring
me a lemon and you the good thing is if
they cut a lemon for you the lemon
should kill off a lot of the bacteria
that could have been on a knife but you
squeeze lemon on everything because the
lemon will go on top of your
food but also it'll go inside of you or
a lemon water or something you know
there lemon is a great antiseptic it's
incredible it really helps killing off
so if you for some reason you ordered a
salad and you're at a you know you're at
a meat eating restaurant with family and
you ordered a salad get a lemon squeeze
it all over the salad make sure that
lemon juices on there and maybe even a
pinch of salt if they can bring you some
fresh salt like a sea salt if they have
high quality salt at the restaurant you
put a little sea salt on there it's a
good chance it can help kill off
bacteria so keep in mind that there's a
lot of things you can do to protect
yourself okay sure you might go into a
restaurant thinking much differently now
and and you got me to think in maybe a
bad way cuz now I just ruined your fun
but but but here's the thing don't don't
let it ruin your fun just realize you're
armed it matters you're armed you know
when I was a child when I was a child
you know against spirit's advice I chose
something in a
restaurant um that I wanted I didn't
care what spirit said I wanted it you
know and and I was with family I was 8 n
years old and uh we went out and I
almost died
almost died Spirit told me not to choose
to take the choice but you know when
you're 8 nine years old and you you get
tired of hearing from Spirit you get
tired if anybody's read the first book
you'll know you'll know if you read the
first book you read the first chapter
origins of the medical medium and so you
know I just said hey you I want what I
want that's what I I don't care I don't
want to hear Spirit on this one this I'm
out with family I'm out I'm happy I want
to have what makes me happy and so you
know I ordered something and it nearly
killed me it was agonizing absolutely
agonizing and there was nothing anybody
can do you go to the ER there's nothing
they can do they just look at you look
at you if you're in that much Agony or
in that much pain they just there's
nothing they can do with food poisoning
they just you can stay there or go home
in that kind of Agony and but if you go
home and you get dehydrated that's a
problem too so you stay in the hospital
and you get you hooked up to IV you know
and and that's the most they can do and
that agonizing pain from
eoli or any kind of
bug wrenching into the Linings of the
colon wrenching into the Linings of an
organ is brutal and so it's no joke and
I got away from it I got lucky you know
I was still sick for weeks and it was
until spirit said look you have to get
pairs from your great-grandfather 's
tree and you have to eat just paars
only and only paars and I recovered
rapidly because of it you know I had
Spirit to to thank for that of course to
be there but Spirit gets mad at me many
times and someone said well how can
Spirit get mad spirit's supposed to be
the source no Spirit gets Spirit gets
upset with me
absolutely Spirit knows that hey I made
the choice against spirit Spirit wasn't
pleased at all and Spirit had to get me
out of it and yank me and pull me out of
it and yeah yeah and so with this just
know that we can get sick I've seen
hundreds of cases over the years people
in some dire dire situations so we're
going to go into another part of of of
talking about this so we can figure it
out so let's talk about other safety
measures that matter garlic and food
garlic and food's really important so
say you're just you know say you love
animal products but you also like a
salad too when you're in that restaurant
and you know I don't recommend doing a
salad I recommend all your food being
cooked in that restaurant like I said
earlier and and asking for the plates to
come
hot and so um and and by the way in
restaurants that happens all the time is
the juices from a raw steak are still on
a plate and in restaurants they actually
take the steak off the grill or whatever
it is in the restaurant or out of the
oven or out of the broiler whatever it
is and they put it they put it right on
that that that
plate with the raw juice is still there
underneath the steak so that's really
common practice so that's why you want
it coming back hot um the plate hot too
if you can but another safety measure is
garlic garlic on your salads garlic on
your food garlic in your dishes you
order that quinoa dish garlic involved
in there anywhere with it's cooked raw
very helpful raw Garlic's best but it's
a safety measure to make sure that in
your stone stomach if you have bacteria
in there percolating with everything
else that's in your stomach if you
garlic in there Garlic's so powerful
that it just will spread through the
entire stomach killing off bacteria so
that's a great safety measure for when
you're eating out um another safety
measure before you eat out oregano
capsule take an oregano capsule take one
it's all you need is one and you
literally it could mean saving you from
food poisoning
so hey going to go out to lunch uh with
everybody or whatever it is have an
oregano capsule before you go out to
lunch that oregano capsule will open up
it'll be in your stomach nice and ready
food will go down it'll disperse all
around the food very helpful becomes a
safety barrier so salmonella and eoli
can't run a muck and start going
becoming really
unruly and because it'll run right into
that oregano oil so that's a secret
weapon so I want you guys to focus on
that if you can um so the oregano the
oregano is important um time time on
your food but it's hard restaurants you
know you ask for some time that's a
tough one what can you do you know that
that's a that's a harder one to to uh do
but peppermint Believe It or Not
peppermint tea is always in restaurants
peppermint tea is
antibacterial it's antibacterial it's
not really anti viral too much but it's
antibacterial which just reminded me so
the whole thing the reason why you want
your plates coming back hot your food
coming back hot in case the chef does
have a cut finger that they've been kind
of Nursing and it's been seeping over
time and getting into different food and
everything else just in case the chef
has mononucleosis doesn't know it and is
sweating drip dripping sweat into your
food that's another thing too because if
when this when the chefs are sweating
profusely and it's dropping in all your
food right there over the fire that
though that sweat will probably get
heated up and burned up as they're
preparing your food but it's the sweat
that's still coming off the chef when
the food's been pulled off the griddle
and put into your plate and he's
prepping the plate with that little bit
of little bit of cilantro they put on
top and a cute little sauce they put
remember those sauces look out for them
sauces they put that sauce that ring of
sauce around your
plate and and uh which by the way needs
to be heated up that plate needs to be
hot because the sweat dripping off the
chef dropping into your food and if it's
not hot enough you can be set up for
mononucleosis a new a new variety and
God knows we got enough varieties out
there we talk about that in all the
different shows so so that's something
to be concerned that's why your food has
to come back hot always remember that
but the safety measure of oregano oil is
incredible peppermint tea at the
restaurant great for antibacterial you
could sip a little bit of peppermint tea
before your food comes sip it after your
food comes it's a secret weapon in fact
it's people do that anyway without
realizing it and it stops food poisoning
cases and they didn't even know it they
got off scot-free without realizing it
because they had garlic in their food
because they had some peppermint tea but
I really like the oregano capsules um
that's that's a big deal so here's the
deal you get sick get food poisoning
you're vomiting you got diarrhea there's
not much you can do but you can try to
sip coconut water coconut water a little
bit of coconut water mixed with regular
water it's a secret weapon to try to get
hydrated as quick as possible could even
be in a bottle coconut water canned B
coconut water and you put a little bit
of coconut water in with regular water
and sip it in between bouts of vomiting
bouts of diarrhea no vomiting anymore
and you just have diarrhea and gut pain
sipping the coconut water very important
getting little sips in if you can if
your tummy can feel like it can handle
it hold it down lemon water squeeze the
lemon in water and sipping little bits
of lemon water between it all you might
not have a bad case of it your body
might be cleaning up it might not be a a
bad kind of eoli it might not be a bad
kind of
salmonella might not be a bad you know
um um version of another bacteria but
you you can do the lemon water sipping
in between the coconut water sipping in
between Ginger water ginger tea in in
restaurants um Regular conventional
restaurants that serve uh salads meat
whatever you know plant-based options
and you know regular meat eating options
often carry ginger tea lately so you
know you can call ahead and say what
kind of herbal teas you could bring your
own tea bags never feel uncomfortable to
bring your own secret weapons to
restaurants can really protect yourself
so it's not about being in fear it's
it's about being armed like I said
before this is critical information you
bring it you bring your ginger tea bags
put it in your purse put in your wallet
I don't know if it goes good in the
wallet have it in your pocket when
you're going out to dinner and and you
know and they don't have ginger tea you
have your ginger tea bag Ginger kills
bacteria right in the stomach you can
sip it before you eat have some ginger
tea after you eat it's an amazing
protection weapon um method you know
it's perfect so these are these are some
of the tricks that you have to do like I
said squeeze lemon on all your food too
that's an option too take a lemon to a
restaurant pick a lemon okay because
they might not have a lemon squeeze it
on your salad squeeze it on your food um
now um lemon is always good with any raw
dishes in a vegan restaurant plant-based
restaurant it's always good to have
lemon anyway a lot of times deliveries
of food comes from a food truck to
plant-based neighborhoods you know not
plant-based neighborhoods but
plant-based um you know restaurants so
what happens is the truck will have also
meat frozen meat this that whatnot in
there plus it'll have all the fruits and
vegetables and you know and this happens
in a lot in the cities the cities
usually it happens and you're getting
your drop off and you're getting your
fruits and vegetables but there could
have been
cross-contamination so in vegan
vegetarian restaurants I still would
recommend cooked and not raw in those
restaurants now if you do raw in those
restaurants which could be okay make
sure you ask for lemon squeezed on
things and it matters and sea salt pinch
of sea salt it matters and you can
literally stop any kind of bacteria
right in its
tracks um so these are just different
options but a lot of people they don't
have choices they can't you know they
they end up in whatever restaurant they
end up in because when you're with the
pool of people
and you're just going where everybody's
going to go and no one wants to insult
someone or no one wants to push someone
too hard and you end up at some any kind
of dive whatever it may be you're going
to be prepared now you bring the things
you need you bring your ginger tea you
bring your peppermint tea if they don't
already have it you know what to do with
the lemon you do the oregano oil capsule
before eating out every time it's such a
good safety me measure it's not even
funny it's so good it really can help
you know if you do get sick you know how
to hydrate yourself carefully between it
all if you're that sick you know you
have to get to the hospital for an
IV and if you
know if you know these things you can
arm yourself and protect yourself when
you're preparing like I said all the
different meats and the chickens and
everything in your own kitchens be
careful be careful you know they I mean
I see it look I see it with a cooking
channel once in a while when I'm over a
family member's house and they got the
cooking show on and I'm standing there
watching it I see literally they just
you know some of the chefs they don't
even they don't even wash their hands
they're playing around with raw chicken
and they're running around playing a raw
like like there's nothing wrong or
nothing going on and then playing around
with raw meat like there's nothing going
on never have steak tartar or whatever
that is that whole raw meat thing um
that's a guaranteed way of of possibly
losing your life even if you've done it
over the years and you've gotten away
with it there's times where we may not
get away with it stories of people I've
heard from people losing their lives
getting sick doctors telling me about it
and everything else from food poisoning
is devastating lots of appendix appendix
operations aidomes lots of those because
of it lots of gallbladders removed
because of it um and a lot of ulcerative
ulcerative and and uh issues created
because of it a lot lot of damaged
Linings intestinal tracts and colons um
it's no joke but we can we can clean up
if you had food food poisoning weigh in
the past a long time ago anything you do
applying in any of these shows helps
knock down bacteria helps knock down old
bacteria whether it's old sea diff
sitting in there that's that's been just
you know sitting around not doing much
or you know anything streps strep gets
in food too all these different streps
get in food they're on animal products
and everything when you go into the like
I said when you go into the stores the
stores the packaged animal products are
loaded with almost
virtually a dozen varieties of bacteria
MCA being included and ciff being
included so these are all the things to
keep in mind does it mean stop eating
animal products no if that's what you
like to do um if that's what you feels
right if that's what you subscribe to it
doesn't mean stop stop eating a raw
salad you know at a plant-based
restaurant if you're plant-based or
vegan whatever it is no you can do it
just just take a lot of these measures
be you know be on it be on it and you
can protect yourself and your family and
the whole bid we're going to have to do
a part two on this one someday so uh
hang in there because I feel like I just
scratched the surface I feel like I've
been swimming in scratching the surface
but haven't really pulled the whole
thing together 100% with some of the
information I still need to deliver to
you know that I care know that I love
you guys I do just thank you for your
support and any way possible thank you
for actually taking the messages out
helping others like you do being that
becoming that expert I really really
love you for it and I really thank you
for it it chokes me up because I've seen
so many of you do what you're doing
helping in so many ways I absolutely
adore you love you dearly and uh you got
me man I'm with you you got me I'm
you're in my heart okay lots of love God
bless you take
care