disorders food fear how many people get
an eating disorder when they're sick or
they start getting sick we're going to
cover that also did you catch the
medical medium podcast at Apple podcast
tattoos how to keep your health safe
tattoos ink how to keep your health safe
really important right there I know a
lot of people have ink I respect it I
dig it there's a lot of great artist out
there incredible gifted people that are
doing all kinds of incredible designs
and freehand on people's bodies body art
I'm not against it you know it's not
that kind of thing this is an anti-
tattoo podcast episode but it's really
important because it's an important
podcast episode about tattoos and how to
keep your health safe so it is really
important so I talk about toxic heavy
metals yes toxic heavy metals in your
tattoo ink and how there is no such
thing and I repeat there is no such
thing as tattoo ink that's metal free I
repeat so I just hope that gets out
there and Rings throughout the ether and
then leaves this planet and then heads
through the solar system and then into
the Galaxy and then out out of the
Galaxy and into the universe and there
forth because it's important to know and
maybe people on another planet somewhere
that are doing all this ink and tattoos
and everything else maybe they'll hear
it and that will travel all the way to
that planet and get to them and someone
will be sitting there maybe by a lake
and they're going to hear it and it's
going to be like there's no such thing
as metal free ink there is no such thing
I want people to know this I don't care
if it's crueltyfree animal free the
whole bit listen to this podcast episode
it's not about being afraid of your
tattoo or going to get your tattoo
removed through the latest technology
that they have it's not about that in
fact I say in the podcast that episode
itself don't remove your tattoos don't
remove them unless for some reason you
can't live with the tattoo and you want
to go and you want to get it removed
well that's your body your life of
course you can but I recommend out there
to people I know friends and family do
not remove your
tattoos okay because during the process
all this stuff comes out when you do it
so I wanted to talk about that but I'm
not going to cuz we're talking about
food Fe check it out medical medum
podcast at Apple podcast all right
tattoos how to protect your health okay
very important all right let's go into
it I'm in brain saver you guys good to
see you guys I'm in brainsaver right now
here we are okay and I'm in the Eating
Disorders chapter but there's a section
in this Eating Disorders chapter that's
really cool really profound information
very helpful helpful for so many people
maybe you find that this this speaks to
you maybe it doesn't let's check this
out food fear let's get into it a little
bit often times an eating disorder
develops because of a symptom is that
true yeah oh yeah if you got a symptom
going on something in the intestinal
tract something happening there an
eating disorder can develop just from
that alone okay this is important if you
guys want to know I'm reading out of
brain saver right now if you don't have
this book and you didn't read this SE
here about eating disorders you're
missing out this book is packed it's got
so much information really protective
information too including things to
avoid like certain supplementation and
everything that causes damage to your
health there's so much information in
these books you guys got to check it out
seriously you should get that book if
you don't already have it go to the
library get get it out of the library if
you want okay so for instance if you
have a hot spot in your intestinal tract
so if you got a hot spot if you're
inflamed somewhere in your intestinal
tract if you're inflamed somewhere
anywhere in here and you eat something
and it finds its way going down here and
it's taking its time and it's going
through right and it finally gets down
to that hot spot and it hits it and now
you're nauseous or you got a pain you're
going to think whoa it was that food
food fear develops very easily because
of this this is just one example I'm
going to cut so much into this this
information you're going to love it you
are absolutely going to love this
information so if you had a hot spot
anywhere in your intestinal tra if you
got a hot spot in your dadum see you got
a lot of inflammation in your dadum
because you have hpylori or you have an
old infection that's been festering in
there for 10 years 15 years say you got
all this extra yeast and mold growing in
here you're inflamed because of a virus
or say like a shinkles virus creating
colitis or something else so you got
diagnosed with crohn's whatever it is
that's going on whatever's happening
here you got a hot spot inside your
intestinal tract and maybe it never went
that far and you've never been diagnosed
and you're just kind of like you're
dealing with certain aches and pains or
certain stomach cramps or flatulence or
stomach issues are bloating whatever it
is the food you eat you'll associate it
with those symptoms very quick and
easily regardless of what it is it could
be something really healthy it could be
something really good for you it could
be something like by the way these are
my juices for today if you guys can take
a look I got my celery juice right here
if you're not drinking celery juice
you're missing out and any kind of
nonsense you ever hear about celery
juice it's absolutely BS celery juice
they still can't keep celery in stores
they still can't keep so they can't grow
it fast enough that's how many people
are drinking it getting their lives back
celery juice is incredible I told told
you that so many years and someday we'll
talk about it more grapefruit juice by
the way way fresh grapefruits amazing
ones off beautiful trees boom right in
there and I'm finishing some orange
juice right there so those are my juices
for today if you want to see I have them
here cuz I'm going to be drinking them
I'm thirsty all right here we are Uma
are you on a juice fast no I am not I am
not on a juice fast it may look like I
am but I'm not but I love to drink you
know fresh grapefruit juice fresh orange
juice fresh celery juice love to drink
those incredible all right let's get
into it a little bit if you got that Hot
Spot somewhere in here whatever that may
be or distension or bloating or
something and you eat something and your
bloating gets
worse was it the food that just did that
could it have been or was it just it was
going to happen you already have a
problem problem you're already having
bloting problems was it the food you ate
the day before you may not even know was
it the food you ate 3 days before is it
even the food is it even the food but
you know what
happens this gets messed up right here
and it gets messed up quick that's right
you guys this gets messed up because
this gets messed with it's so easy to go
down a rabbit hole with eating and food
and eating in food when you don't even
know why you're even having a symptom or
a condition or a problem and we easily
associate a food we have instantly to a
problem right so if I had some kind of
inflammation because I had some strep in
my intestinal tract or strep in my colon
and I had some ecoli in my colon and
it's creating all kinds of different
pivots and divots inside my colon and
intestinal tract just say I had that
right and then I eating something or
whatever it is and then I'm not feeling
good because that's starting to ache
down here or however it is I'm going to
be so messed up in my head I'm going to
be like I I don't know if it was that
maybe I should just have some toast some
dry toast or something and scrape off
the burnt stuff off the toast and just
have that plain I'm nauseous I got some
pain it confuses people everything does
no matter what it is that they have you
know going on and there's people who are
suffering from bloating constantly and
they want to get rid of that bloating so
they get told to drink celery juice
because they hear about it working and
saving lives and they go and they have
some and they're bloating still there
and they're like oh it's the celery
juice the celery juice is causing the
problem now it's every day it's a new
thing causing a problem and we get the
food fear so the food fear just goes
crazy in our minds and rightfully so
because it's that confusing and that
difficult to navigate and so people
don't realize the minute you start
getting sick the minute you start
getting symptoms unless you've
experienced this do you know what I'm
talking about it's that intense
wondering wish over there on YouTube my
mind has been messed up with that is for
sure hard to undo it especially when you
just want to be normal again you can go
down this rabbit hole and down it and
down it and down it and down it and it
can get really difficult for a lot of
people you don't know what the heck to
eat you just don't know like what do I
eat what's okay can I eggs oh eggs feel
okay in me for now let's go into that
for a little bit
okay what people don't realize is when
you got inflammation in your intestinal
tract we'll start with intestinal tract
and bloating and digestion and I'm going
to read a little too
so over here Michelle L hey Michelle
over there telling people they have an
eating disorder for cutting out food
groups is
gaslighting you oh God you always make
so much good sense Michelle and that one
right there just hits hits the nail
right on the head so spot on all right
let's go into it a little bit so so
let's start with intestinal tract
anybody who has bloating constipation
maybe they'll have diarrhea maybe they
have other different issues with their
intestinal tract colon and so forth
right and stomach dadum all of it okay
anything that's happening in here and
maybe even a little bit further we go a
little further their pancreas is
slightly inflamed the liver slightly
inflamed clogged up and stagnant
sluggish whatever's happening here and
there's an imbalance because there's so
many things going on they might have
some eoli they might have a little bit
of strp in here too they might have
something happening inside their gut
that's causing problems low HCL they're
not digesting their food something's
going wrong regardless okay we're
inflamed you eat food and you feel it
you feel the food because you're hot you
got hot spots you got places that are on
fire a little bit of eoli here creating
an outer pocket a little bit of strep
here creating an inner pocket you got
some different divots and pivots here
you got a little bit of a swelling here
your Elum is a little bit blocked off
because it's inflamed your appendix is
slightly inflamed down here you're just
in you got all these different places
right all these different hotpots as the
food's moving through you it's hitting
these hot spots playing with your mind
playing with your brain playing with
your
Consciousness and it happens every day
to people you don't know what's right
you don't know what's wrong you don't
know what to eat how to fix it what is
going on even if you've been to doctor
to doctor to doctor and you haven't
found any oh my God I hear that every
day now it's all in the medical medium
books where when people go to doctor to
doctor looking for help and now
everybody's out there saying doctor to
doctor go come here here to my health
coaching after you've been to 20 doctors
come to my health coaching now it's all
you hear now out there and it's like you
know you check out their thing it's like
uh stay away from gluten stay away from
okay all right so let's get into this
these hot spots can create a lot of
problems putting a lot of different
pressure and stress on someone's mind
and Consciousness because you don't know
where to go how to fix it what's wrong
and so many people are struggling on
this level problem is can get into a
situation of
PTSD so every time you put food in your
mouth this can develop into an eating
disorder where you're actually getting a
PTSD eating disorder where every time
food is entering into your mouth you're
scared you're afraid now you're worried
you're worried like is it going to be
okay is it going to hurt I don't feel so
good that food doesn't work for me and
then you'll instantly cast out foods
that actually are are there to help you
heal and recover
you but yet you might accidentally keep
foods that are not helping you and you
keep them in because they feel good in
the moment it seems so that's where the
confusion lies as well we sit there we
don't know what to eat exactly and we'll
eat a food that seems to settle okay
feel okay but little do we know that
food's feeding a problem a condition
it's feeding some kind kind of virus or
pathogen it's adding to a problem it's
putting pressure on your pancreas more
issues to your liver more sluggishness
to your liver and you don't realize it
and now you're just like okay I don't
know what's good what's bad cuz then 3
days later you're eating a food that
seems to be comfortable and seems to be
working 3 days later now you're getting
sicker and you don't know what to do you
don't know what it is and then you're
like well I better eat something
healthier I better try something
healthier let me eat a salad let me eat
some vegetables and then you're eating
some crunchy vegetable you're chomping
on a carrot that's something that a lot
of people go to instantly that aren't
eating that healthy and they don't know
what to eat they're like okay I better
do something good for myself I better
eat something healthy and they end up
chomping on a Raw carrot what happens
when they do that they're they're
they're the cre they're chomping on a
Raw carrot all this roughage is coming
from that hard kind of like crunchy Raw
carrot it they send it down the track
they're inflamed in weird little spots
like in their intestinal tract or the
bottom of their dadum they're inflamed
they got a problem whether it's hpylori
or stpy coli or something else going on
or Ci or something and then when the
food when the when the carrots the
crunchy carrots that fibrous carrot
starts to head down there it hits the
hot spot and now they're nauseous
they're nauseous they're sick they're
like what's wrong with me I can't even
eat a carrot I was told carrots are
healthy and now they're all of a sudden
scared they're in fear now they're
eating butter on toast with an egg or
they're eating cheese and they're like
that's that's the only thing I can eat
is a piece of cheese or an egg or a
piece of toast and they end up in that
situation where they're pretty much on
toast egg and cheese diet I don't know
if you guys have ever seen that it's
like milk toast eggs and cheese that's
what they end up in or rice pudding
that's another one too Teressa oh my God
you are talking directly to my mom right
now she's really struggling this an
important topic I'm so sorry your mom's
struggling right now my heart pours out
to her by the way okay
Teressa um juel says yes my head got
messed up because I was so afraid to eat
and this is a really critical critical
topic because it's happening every day
to people new people every day people
who have already been sick too every
single day Lisa says this is me over
there in IG I'm so sorry you guys
struggled with this along the way I'm
hitting the intestinal track talk first
with this issue but we're going to go
deeper into other places of how it works
with your brain how it works with
emotions how it works with creating the
eating disorder the food fear because
that's what we're talking about here is
food fear and it's food fear developed
from not feeling good and getting a
symptom not knowing what to eat still
struggling with that symptom associating
that food with that that symptom and
then we're now down a rabbit hole that's
what we're talking about today so let's
go into it first I want to take a little
sip here I want to finish some of my
orange you here if that's okay with you
guys tra said this oh wait um TR said
this is exactly my mother explanation
points this is wild you're touching on
exactly everything she's going through
it's like you heard our prayers listen
and I want to talk about to something
very important okay that that you can
heal and you can get better and you can
recover and get past this there's a way
also to understanding how this works
with Foods where you're feeling this way
and you're afraid and you're having that
food fear but there's a way to come out
of it and just having this knowledge
alone is going to help people out there
because once you understand this a
little bit you understand your body then
you understand what's going on and you
could rise above the food fear and the
eating disorders that are created and
the PTSD that's created from it it's all
important Catalina over there in IG this
is exactly how I felt for 3 years whoa
three years whoa where I'm scared to eat
because everything makes me bloated and
then it's scary and here's what happens
on that one since we are in the
intestinal tract talk let's go into
bloating a little bit bloating can come
and go at random times could be
intermittent or always there right
always there but but worse less worse
still there and always there worse less
worse still there and always there worse
worse really bad and then bo back down
to not so bad scale 1 to 10 my bloating
is three scale 1 to 10 my bloating is
five today whoa my bloating is a 10
today well my bloating is an 11 today my
bloating is like a two now I don't know
what did it let me eat something oh it's
back to here well I eat something my
bloating is down a little bit later on
at the end of the day boom your bloating
is up back to 11 back to 12 is your head
spinning my head's spinning that's how
hard it is and that's what people go
through right
there hang on a
sec just I got a celery juice here too
and a grapefruit juice
here and no this is not a juice
fast all
right
I took the celery force and forgive me
but I talk faster I have to try to slow
it
down I talk faster after I take the
celery Force I'm just telling you okay
after I take this I talk faster it can
become annoying please forgive me so
this is the vimergy celery Force you
guys know I endorse these guys and um
they just love this stuff this stuff I
love if you got like anything going on
like that you feel you know you need to
push
through H
yeah all right back to
this let's go into the bloating thing a
little bit the bloating thing is a
tricky one because you can be bloated
from something you ate 2 days ago and
then it still has you bloated and then
you eat something that can get rid of
your bloat so you drink or eat something
that can get rid of your bloat and but
you're now bloated you're bloed from
something else before days ago even a
week ago and now you're trying to eat
something or take something or drink
something that can fix your bloating if
you knew to do it long term if you knew
to do it long enough it could fix it but
you'll never know because
you'll never know you're still bloated
you don't know to do something long-term
enough you won't know what to avoid a
lot of people won't know what to avoid
and we run into a
problem Michelle haters attacking the
way we eat is just sad yep haters are
really sad they are it's a lot of
varieties of haters too like a lot of
varieties of haters there's different
Garden varieties of haters and then
there's just evil evil Sinister haters
and then there's demonically possessed
haters that are evil to and then there's
just I mean it's there's a whole
different ladder of haters by the way
there's jealous haters there's haters
that want to destroy you there's haters
that want to kill you there's haters
that just want to see you whatever dead
and then there's haters that just they
can't help it they're just so jealous
they just want to create problems
there's a lot of haters out there all
right that's the hater scale thank you
celery force can we thank you seler
force we'll do a whole hater scale right
here we'll run through it really quick
all right let's
move so basically the bottom line is
what I see in a lot of people and plus
with the bloating and it wasn't going to
be a bloating talk but it's good to talk
about it a little bit what happens is
that the HCL is so diminished your
gastric lands are so
diminished you have a lot of things
growing in here that shouldn't be
growing in
here your liver stagnant and
sluggish and you're
bloating okay it has to be rectified it
has to heal it you have to recover you
have to get the bloating down like
celery juice is critical for recovering
bloat because it's restoring your htl
it's restoring your gastric glands it's
killing off pathogens yeast mold
overgrowth of unproductive fun
fungus that's important all on its own
it's a medical medium tool you guys know
that tool and there's a lot of other
medical medium tools to get rid of
bloating but the point is is that in
order though to get rid of
bloating one has to understand that they
may be eating foods that aren't creating
their bloating but they're going to help
you get to the finish line but what
happens with bloating is you may eat a
healthy food that's going to help you
get to the finish line but instead you
get bloated because you're so hypers
sensitive that you're going to bloat so
easy you become afraid of that food you
become afraid of 4 ounces of celery
juice you become afraid of
papaya afraid of a steamed
potato you become afraid of a wild
blueberry you become afraid of something
and then you're in this place where
you're afraid now of spinach you're
afraid of a leafy graen and when you get
to that point of fear and you don't know
what to eat we end up going to comfort
Foods foods that we've been eating since
we were a child foods that we've been
eating since we were young and we end up
running to like eggs cheese and toast
again we end up running back to Pasta
macaroni and cheese eggs toast we end up
running back to bread we end up running
back to these kinds of foods or we end
up running back to treats and chocolate
and things like that because we don't
know where to go we get stressed we're
totally frustrated with our healing
process and what's wrong and we just we
go running for things that aren't going
to help us and it happens every day out
there mono eating is a miracle okay a
miracle for people so I'm going to grab
the cleanse the heel book right
here all right so medical medium put
mono eating um on the map all these
years and it's important to understand
how it works right when you do like a
mono eating where it's like bananas and
celery juice or steamed potatoes and
celery juice and if you look you'll see
the different varieties in here what
happens is that you end up building up
your
HCL you end up healing the environment
in your intestinal tract you end up
reducing pathogen loads and you you end
up recovering so so many people go to
the mono eating and cleanse the heel
because it literally saves their life it
saves them from surgeries I can't tell
you how many people that have reached
out out there in the world in medical M
community that were able to avoid a
surgery where their doctor their surgeon
said you don't have to get 20 Ines of
your colon cut out you don't have to get
20 in of your intestinal tract cut
out and they actually literally save
their themselves from radical surgical
procedures because you're doing the mono
cleanse okay in cleanse to heal it's
that powerful and then once you heal a
lot of the hot spots in here too so once
you heal a lot of the hotpots you can
add more healing tools you don't have to
be on the monoc cleanse forever a lot of
people they go on the monoc cleanse for
just a short time and they just correct
themselves they reable themselves it's
incredible a lot of people go on it
longer see casy shman says over there on
YouTube Anthony you suggest it you
suggest it monoc cleans to me and this
greatly turned around my food
sensitivities it greatly projected me on
my healing Journey thank you um casy
shelman thank you for that comment what
happens is that a lot of people with
food
sensitivities the monoc cleanse corrects
them starts to restore the person moves
them P back back out of this and I'm
talking about the monoc cleans cuz so
many people have food fear and if they
have a symptom or condition anything
intestinal tract anything stomach
anything like that that they're
suffering and struggling with it's now a
game of PTSD what do I eat food
fear and we end up with this eating
disorder around all of it and we're
suffering and we're struggling and we
don't know how to get out of it but when
you have direction and you know what to
do and you end up doing something like
the medical medium monoc cleanse and you
choose one that's right for you just
choose the one that you feel will work
because that's the whole thing you can
choose different ones in here you could
try one try another and then what
happens is as you're recovering at least
you have a a schematic at least you have
a catalyst to actually adhere by to take
you to that finish line where you don't
have to be always questioning things
like is this not good is this not good
because you don't have to question some
something that's literally saved that
many lives and healed that many people
the track record the street credit is
already built into this so it's not like
you're going to it like did anybody ever
get better oh yeah Millions have with
the medical medium books but the monoc
cleanses so many have recovered avoided
surgeries it it's really
incredible see muhamed says can I get
this book online anywhere you can go to
amazon.com us if you're overseas you can
look for it too in the bookstores you
can go to Barnes & Noble it's 48% off
right now at amazon.com us that's
cleanse the heel you got the mono
cleanses in here really truly lifesaving
information so all right let's let's
move into some more info we're talking
about intestinal tract gut health all of
that hot spots we're talking about how
someone could be like I can't eat any
vegetables I cannot eat any raw
vegetables aw I can't eat raw lettuce I
can't eat raw greens I can't eat
anything raw it hurts my stomach and it
doesn't digest and what they don't
realize when they can't eat some raw
spinach or they can't eat some raw
Tomatoes or raw cucumbers what they
don't realize is the cucumber is
digesting the tomato is
digesting the lettuce is
digesting they don't think it's
digesting but it is but what they're
feeling is inflamed nerves attached to
the Linings of the intestinal
tract so they're
feeling inflamed areas along the
intestinal
tract they're feeling hot
spots is what they're feeling so as the
lettuce is moving through and the
tomatoes are moving
through and the cucumbers are moving
through it's hitting a hot spot
and they going I'm not digesting this
I'm not digesting this I don't think I'm
digesting I can't eat a cucumber ever
again I can't eat a raw cucumber ever
again I can't eat a tomato I can't eat
lettuce ever
again what they don't
realize is it's okay to eat the lettuce
it's okay to eat the Cucumber it's okay
to eat the tomato but then they're in
fear that it's not okay because they're
feeling something but what they don't
realize is they're feeling a hot
spot they're feeling a Hot Spot
somewhere whether it's a hot spot where
it's just
bloat or it's a hot spot where they're
feeling a cramp or some pressure or a
little bit of pain or discomfort or
something else and they're feeling like
they're not digesting that wrong lettuce
they feel like they're not digesting
there's tomatoes and
cucumbers and that orange they ate or
whatever it is and they're just like I
cannot eat citrus I cannot ever have
citrus I can never have a cucumber I
can't have a tomato rolled out rolled
out they rolled out went out no Citrus
no cucumber no tomato No cilantro no
spinach no lettuce no kale no MH no this
no that they've rolled it all out gone
gone gone they you can't have a raw
piece of broccoli ever you can't have a
raw piece of cauliflower anymore all
those are ruled out and gone so we have
this problem
where they can't eat anything raw
completely rolled out so now they're in
that zone nothing raw so what that means
is they won't even have any raw juice
they won't have raw celery they won't
have raw celery juice which is different
and it works differently you guys know
the whole rules with celery juice
16 ounces on an empty
stomach
strained right strained so it can get in
there do its thing flush clean the liver
rebuild the hydrochloric acid get things
back to back to square
one but the point is all that roughage
they'll never be able to eat a carrot
rolled out carrots
gone raw cabbage in a salad raw cabbage
is gone everything by heirloom tomato
gone so you walk down red bell peppers
gone so it just suddenly it's food fear
I can't eat
anything all of these foods are
gone Apple peaches nectarines Cherries
Berries
gone melons
gone it just disappears it's out of your
diet now so now you're like I can only
do cook food or
toast or eggs and I hear eggs are so
healthy and blah blah blah and
everybody's talking about eggs so let me
go on a whole bunch of eggs four or six
eggs a day because it's the only thing I
can eat because it doesn't seem to hurt
when I eat an egg so what they don't
realize is they end up losing all these
foods that can help them
heal but then because they don't
understand and how know how to read
their hot
spots and they think they're not
digesting it
whatsoever and they have food fear to
towards all these foods and then they
eat an egg and they don't feel anything
no hot spot no problem no discomfort
they eat a nice fluffy scrambled egg
they need a n they eat a nice batch of
fluffy egg
whites and it goes down in here they get
a hardboiled egg and it goes down and it
sits in here and what's happening what
they don't realize is the egg is
liquefying it's turning into a goo and
that goo isn't massaging the intestinal
tract it's not massaging the colon It's
not massaging the stomach and what's
happening is that egg is just turning
into a little like a ball of glue forget
eggs that bread is turning into a ball
of glue forget bread that cheese is
turning into a ball of glue and it
sitting in there and it feels okay it
feels
good hey that bread pasta
basically that wheat
pasta with the cheese sitting in there
like goo and it's not touching anything
so it's not touching any of the hot
spots you're not getting red flags no
red flag here no red flag there no red
flag there but what's happening is the
eggs the dairy products the cheese the
milk the butter all of that that's
sitting in here is
feeding what's keeping you
sick it's feeding what's keeping you
sick and then you end up with the same
symptoms no matter what that come and go
so now it's not like every symptoms gone
cuz you're eating milk eggs cheese and
butter and bread and it's becoming a goo
and it's not touching anything inside
and it's becoming a goo it's not any hot
spots for the moment but you stay sick
you end up getting sicker and then all
of a sudden because everything you're
eating is feeding the bad bugs the
bacteria the unproductive yeast the
unproductive fungus and mold the viruses
because what you're eating is feeding
all of that you all of a sudden get a
spill you get a
spill a spill
over what that means is
it just all blows up the bacteria
proliferated the viruses got a little
too too fat and happy and it spilled
over and it blew up and now you're
sick you're sick you still got a lot of
the cramping the pain you're having like
a spill
over and that's what's happening and
your food options are getting dwindled
down dwindled down dwindled down can't
have any red bell peppers can't have any
yellow bell peppers can't have any
orange bell peppers can't have any
cucumbers can't have arloom tomatoes you
can't have any cherry tomatoes you can't
have any carrots you can't have any
cauliflower broccoli you can't have any
spinach you become more buried in food
fear and more food fair and food fear
you can't have almonds you can't have
this and this and this and this and then
it just breaks it on down where now
you're just like what the
heck yep
and your brain screwed every time you
eat your brain screwed every time you
eat and it's so difficult and so hard on
so many
people but that's just the intestinal
track business we're talking about here
we're not even going to a lot more um
lra over there that's mind-blowing on
YouTube thank you by the way YouTube
they don't they don't do they only give
like 10 people YouTube notifications so
if you guys go on to my YouTube you're
going to have to just check to see if
anything is new there and look and try
to find my YouTube because no one gets
notifications very few people do all
right food fear let's cut into this a
little bit I'm in the eating disorder
chapter there's a reason why food fear
is in the eating disorder section so I'm
just going to show you it's here eating
disorders right here in brain saver
before I was holding up cleanse to heal
okay New York Times bestselling books
right here I was holding up cleanse to
heal cleanse the heal has the mono
cleanse it has all kinds of other stuff
it's incredible book saving lives every
day most popular health book in the
world H hands
down in every single country in the
world it's saved so many lives just in
the last five years four years and and
such it's incredible
this brain saver right here it's
information is priceless and you can get
it for whatever the cost of the book is
or go to the library go to
amazon.com it's on sale right now we're
in the eating disorder chapter in brain
saver it's so comprehensive it's got so
much vast amounts of information let's
go into this a little
bit let's just hit food fear for a
couple of minutes you guys bear with me
often times an eating disorder develops
because of a symptom and I wanted to
bring that back in you get an ache you
get a pain what am I doing wrong what
should I do what can I what can I
whatever this information will change
the world with eating disorders right
here in this book and it already
is a symptom related to not being able
to swallow
correctly choking nausea pain in the
stomach a feeling of tight tightness in
the throat or tightness in the chest any
kind of tightness of the chest you guys
any kind of
anxiety any kind of weird feelings or
tightness in the chest can bring you to
an eating disorder real fast a food fear
real real
fast you're eating and you're getting
tightness of the chest you're instantly
like oh my God is it this food in my
hand it's like food it's cursed it's
cursed this food is evil it's evil it's
cursed
a feeling of tightness in the throat
tightness in the
chest or losing a sense of taste and
smell this is where someone is living
their life and they're eating just as
anybody else would be eating and then
these symptoms start to develop you're
eating what everybody else is eating
you're living your life you're getting a
symptom and now the food becomes
questionable
this is so so
powerful hey Melanie over there on
YouTube thank you for timestamping so
many of those things you do on YouTube
when you do the the comment and you time
stamp it like you do that's actually
really cool by the
way in some cases if it's a chronic
nausea for example then Foods become
pick and choose a game of what's going
to help ease this nausea the nausea hell
the nausea hell have you been through it
before it torments pregnant
women who don't know what to eat they
have a baby
developing the baby developing needs
nutrients the best
nutrients the
nausea is like
this
barrier to getting nutrients to the baby
because when women become pregnant and
they're nauseous all the time they end
up choosing foods that are trying to
work with the nausea versus choosing a
food that's going to be really good for
that early stage of development for the
baby instead they're choosing things
like anything to break the nausea
they're choosing chocolate loaded with
caffeine that's really bad
for the tiny cells that are developing
into a a
fetus and so what's happening so they're
choosing things that are they're trying
to calm the nausey down the morning
sickness so they're just eating gluten
Rich toast with butter they're drinking
coffee yes they're eating chocolate
they're just eating pasta and cheese
they're eating chocolate cake they're
just working with the nausea no judgment
nothing like that I'm giving you an
example of how those early cells of the
baby need celery
juice they need sweet
potatoes they need winter squash kaboa
squash they need beautiful red
potatoes they need
blueberries they need raspberries they
need all of these things these early
cells of the baby that are just
developing need all of these foods but
instead because of the
nausea those foods are on the list for a
lot of women that get that early nausea
with early pregnancy and they're just
looking for just glue they're looking
for just glue to just kind of calm the
nausea
down okay in some cases if someone has
chronic nausea and chronic nausea just
minus the pregnancy like nausea in
general can really rule the roost with
food fear picking choices suffering and
struggling the nausey is a big one Foods
become pick and choose a game of what's
going to help ease the nausea is this
going to help ease the nausea today is
this going to help let me try this let
me try that no that doesn't work for me
oh I better try some celery juice to
ease the nausea oh it's not easing the
nausea oh never drink celery juice again
it's a bad idea it becomes a pick and
choose game of what's going to help ease
this nausea what's not helping this
nausea do any of these Foods I'm eating
contribute to this nausea that's what it
comes it becomes literally
Madness you're not crazy
nobody's crazy who's going through
this but it creates a type of Madness
with the nause this is a prime example
Deborah over there Deborah Lynn designs
that was me nauseous for six months lost
lbs how come when I'm not eating I still
have the nausea there's that person the
person that's still that's not even
eating and they still have the nausea
and then then there's the person
who the nausea goes away when they're
not eating so they're not eating and not
eating and then when they pick a food
and they get the nausea back they
associate a whiplash to that food they
grab an
Apple the Apple they eat apple goes down
to shoot they get the nausea the Apple's
poison there's a mental Association to
the Apple throw the Apple away
LeBlanc says I definitely had food fear
during pregnancy I was so scared to eat
anything with
seasoning
indeed Jennifer gagan says can you
explain the cause of the nausea I threw
up for nine months
straight oh my God it's really difficult
for so many people I'm so sorry you've
gone through
that do do any of the foods I'm eating
are they the reason for my nausea are
they creating the nausea then our mind
and our Consciousness starts to pick up
on patterns and habits because of small
bursts of PTSD developing did you hear
that you guys you guys got to have this
book tell other people about this book
such a great
book you eat something and you're
nauseous so you
identify that food as being the problem
so you learn to avoid that food just as
you get comfortable eating another food
thinking you're safe and good you get
nauseous again you just got comfortable
with that food you're starting to eat an
orange you're comfortable with that food
it didn't give me nauseousness didn't
give me nausea yesterday and now I got
nauseousness today cuz I'm having that
Orange Boom see you later orange Gone
With the Wind
man you just started getting comfortable
with each food and then you're
uncomfortable with that food so Kiss It
Goodbye you think you're safe and you
think you're good and then boom you're
not safe anymore safeness is gone so
then that's another food you're
uncomfortable eating suspecting it's
contributing to the problem is that my
problem is it my problem this can carry
on into other Foods as well nausea
doesn't usually receive a diagnosis
because nausea or maybe nervous could
maybe be nervousness and anxiety
if everything checks out okay in the
abdomen it's passed off as you're just
sensitive so nausea really is the
diagnosis it doesn't really get a
diagnosis especially if everything
checks out okay if you're somebody with
a mystery
nausea and everything looks okay and
checks out
okay you're sensitive that's what is
told to each person what's not told to
the person is they might have a pathogen
stirring the pot they might have a vagus
nerve problem creating a problem they
might have other things too you might
have inflamed nerves vagus nerves going
around your intestinal track and so
forth and it's giving you vagal
nausea this mystery nausea can bring
about serious Eating Disorders even when
reaching out for help even when
searching for a doctor or practitioner
to help ease the nausea to help find out
why you have the nausea every every day
becomes what do I
eat every day becomes what do I
eat that's where we where we end up very
difficult situation for a lot of people
and what time do I
eat what time works for me like what is
the best time to
eat
okay
all
right is it better to eat in the
afternoon is it better to eat in the
evening some cases of mysterious nausea
make it so someone can barely eat
anything at all even if the cause and
the nausea goes away the eating disorder
that arose from it can stick around you
guys how many people had a nausea
problem for a while and it and it carved
out and molded their eating the patterns
from there on out
where it molded and carved out an eating
disorder from there on out what's the
book's name with Stanford it is
brainsaver medical medium
brainsaver don't miss out on having this
information make sure you get it go to
amazon.com
Us by the way just prepare to get your
mind blown if you're a reader if you're
a connoisseur of powerful
information if you love to read and
learn if you want
extensive extensive
information right if you want piles of
information to read That's ahead of time
of research and science than you got it
here um let's go to a little bit more
okay the same goes for mystery
swallowing difficulties or mysterious
tightness of the chest if your condition
is diagnosed as
anxiety Then you will end up with
another diagnosis eventually like an
eating disorder diagnosis and they just
they kind of won't even be able to kind
of put it together like they won't
realize that you got this tightness in
the chest you're vagal nerves your vagus
nerves are having problems you're
inflamed you're developing in PTSD
situation an eating disorder because of
it and then you get a diagnosis like
anxiety and then the doctor gives you a
diagnosis of eating disorder and you're
just like lost lost like what do I do
you don't even know what to eat
cristelle over there on YouTube we make
linear cause and effect
assumptions especially when something's
not right and if it's chronic it can be
a hell of a rabbit hole totally and it's
so hard to trust anyone else anything
else
anymore powerful words by the way thank
you for writing that comment because it
can be be a really difficult Road for a
lot of people rabbit hole and hell for
many okay so over there on
Facebook okay talk says you are speaking
my life habits now I thinking a lot
about eating when what how how much fear
stress oh my God it can be challenging
sometimes and no one understands even
people through experience it who
experien
it
okay even if the audience was agreeable
to start with let's hit that okay this
is
interesting now you have an
audience family
friends practitioners
doctors co-workers you got an
audience even if the audience was
agreeable to start with they were
worried about your symp
sys they're worried about your thyroid
problems worried about your stomach pain
worried about your nausea worried about
your tightness in the chest worried
about your aches and pains worried about
your fibro diagnosis or whatever else
you got they were
worried they were worried about it while
you were searching doctor to doctor to
doctor it can eventually start to feel
like a spotlight is on you I can't eat
this I can't eat that I might be able to
try this I might be able to try that and
then the family member the friend the
coworker whoever it is they're the
audience now they're
like
well really cuz I'm eating this and this
is fine she's eating this and this is
fine he's eating this and this is fine
they're eating that and that's fine
what's wrong with you you went to the
doctor why aren't she fixed yet is the
doctor going to fix
you what are you eating and how much are
you eating the spotlights on you then
the PTSD can start even bigger and
bigger and bigger and eventually feel
like it's swallowing you up and you're
feeling like you never understood check
out brain saer you guys check out
cleanse the heel you should get both
books if you don't have
them really good books take a little bit
more look a little deeper in this
okay regardless of what your symptoms
are regardless of how many doctors
you've seen all eyes are on what you're
eating and swallowing now and how much
you're
eating have you ever been there before
all eyes are on how much you're eating
what you're eating what you're
swallowing what you're chewing if you
have an audience all eyes are on that
regardless of how many doctors you went
to you could have went to the best
specialist the best this person the best
GP the best internist and now you know
you got an audience that's worried about
how you're eating especially if you're
younger if you're younger and you're not
older and you're a young
person then there's really eyeballs on
what you're doing and if you got a lot
of aunts and uncles and cousins and
family members and they all start
thinking you're the one with the
tightness of the chest you're the one
with the anxiety you're the one that
doesn't want to eat this doesn't want to
eat that not sure what to eat here it's
always about a food problem and you're
one of those
people now you're going to be like up sh
you know up shit's creek without a
paddle
right your original symptoms don't even
matter anymore it's like no I started
out with the pain in my chest the
tightness of my chest I started out and
they said it was panic attacks but then
I got tingles and numbness in my arms
and then I got this and then I got this
I got fatigue that doesn't matter
anymore it's all about what you're
eating
now affirmation 65 over there in IG that
was my life
OMG you got an audience now you sought
out doctors to get help but that's long
been forgotten by the
audience especially if you're like 21 or
25 years old or 28 years old
or 18 years old or younger or
however maybe in your 30s but either way
you have an audience now and now you got
like friends friends
friends family family friends family
friends co-workers families friends and
they're all watching you and it isn't
about your symptoms anymore it's just
about you and your food and how you
screwed up it's you and your food and
how you have a must have an eating
disorder now and maybe your symptoms
weren't really real to begin with maybe
you're that just the problems weren't
really real maybe you're not really sick
you were sick you got doctors saying you
were sick I guess but all that's kind of
drifting away cuz it's all about what
you're putting in your mouth in your
foods and your problems and your foods
and that's compiling and compounding the
PTSD causing now even more riffs more
PTSD and now you feel like you're really
down the rabbit hole and no one
understands you and you're
misunderstood mean J over there on
YouTube thank you for being here by the
way you're speaking to me right now you
you said you commented amazing ter appan
can relate to everything you're
describing over there in IG family and
friends could never understand it wasn't
until I had to have emergency surgery
that they believed
me the focus is all gone now it's the
focus on you're not eating enough are
you eating enough you're eating too much
you're getting too skinny you're looking
sickly you need to put some meat on your
bones are you getting enough
protein and you're not eating the right
things then the fear of eating occurs
and
intensifies and that's harder than
anyone can understand and it happens
every day out there there are people
just you know there are people that
Heckle the medical medium community and
and they're just trying to put fear and
doubt in their minds are you getting
enough protein are you getting enough
protein there's so there's it's
everywhere it's everywhere and when
you're sick and struggling and you don't
feel good it's like the vultures come in
is what they do the vultures come in and
they just say the rotten this crap and
they don't understand what you've been
through they don't know what your
struggles are they're not in your shoes
and at your home
they don't get
it even if you
diagnose Even If you're diagnosed with a
named physical condition right off the
bat it's easy to develop an eating
disorder in part because there's still
not a medical understanding of what
causes the
condition so it's not getting healed
somebody with a simple case of heartburn
acid reflux or exam for example can
develop an eating order because it's
always on their mind let's hit that a
little
bit W blueberries over
there the protein brainwashing has drove
me crazy and we will have to deal with
it for the rest of
Life yeah this just that's powerful by
the
way okay so I want to go into this part
this is interesting right here right
even if it's something like a simple
case of of heartburn acid reflux you
guys for example it can develop into an
eating disorder because it's always on
your mind because it's here it's like
heartburn what do I eat oh that bothers
me oh that doesn't bother me that
doesn't bother me that bothers
me a friend I haven't talked to in a
long long time reached out to me and
said you know I got this heartburn acid
reflux thing I did all the testing at
the doctor I did all this everything and
um it's like I'm scared to eat anything
W scared to eat anything anything I eat
I don't know this was working for me
yesterday it's not working for me today
this might work for me tomorrow but it
didn't when tomorrow came yesterday and
your mind goes wof
wof eating a food that seems to be
working gives you a sense of security
then if it isn't working anymore and the
acid reflux or nausea returns it's like
an old friend letting you down old
friend letting you down sometimes it's
not about the symptoms sometimes
experiences when you're eating that food
it's about what they're told about that
food so here's a real brain screw
is even if you discover somewhere along
the way the right food to eat to heal
yourself some [__] is going to like
tell you that it's the wrong food and
it's bad for
you I don't know how anybody can heal
anymore out there I just don't know it's
that bad there's that many sick people
and they're just biohacking themselves
to death and everybody's like squealing
like pigs like do this do that buy my
program do this eat this do
that and darkness is rampant out there
right now I don't know how people are
going to survive in 10 years from now as
it gets worse and worse and
worse yeah they'll poach things for
medical medium information that's healed
people along the way but but they'll mix
it with crap that won't heal them I
don't know how anybody's going to get
better down down the road Natalie says
the sickest and most narcissistic people
prey on those trying to better
themselves we live in a sick world it's
overwhelming sometimes well
spoken I could not have said that better
myself Dr Fawn biohackers are hacking
People's Health away indeed they're
pecking People's Health away
food has an ingrain connection to our
physical being our physical
understanding even if we aren't dealing
with ongoing Health complaints if
someone is home one evening gets some
kind of chest pain for a minute and gets
on the phone with family and friends the
first thing everyone says is what did
you eat
tonight if that person decides to go to
the ER the doctor asks what did you eat
tonight the question always comes up
that's how interconnect ConEd we are
with food in general and that's how we
end up living with food fear like we are
so
interconnected it's one of those details
that Patients First Volunteer every time
they go into the ER to the hospital I
ate this this tonight I ate this tonight
I ate this ter appan says when people
try to frame medical medium yeah frame
that is the word yes as restrictive and
fear-mongering the only reason I can eat
without excruciating pain and fear is
because of medical medium information
I was literally starving to death I
couldn't eat thank you Tara you're the
best I was sitting at home eating my
dinner I had this terrible pain in my
stomach my back my chest my lower
abdomen I thought I don't know what I
thought it come to the ER and that's the
first thing people devou because the
reason why they devou that information
is because it's so intertwined to foods
and eating and our health and foods and
eating you guys I could go on all day
long with this
book that's how much incredible
information is in this book Brain saver
Casey shelman over there on YouTube I
think sometimes it's jealousy and
insecurity about how they eat
sometimes projecting their fears on
what's different but they see the
healing but they project their fears
because they don't want to have to think
about healing and heal
and what to eat and meaning like they
think okay
okay everybody thinks about what to eat
I don't care who they are
everyone and everyone is worried about
their food to some degree no matter what
because you can't just eat 10 loaves of
bread with butter on it you'll end up
with pancreatitis with with a pound of
butter you can't just eat a whole
chocolate cake every single night
because that's not going to help you
can't do a lot of things you got to be
careful with Lis free celery 333 over
there on YouTube I just read an anti-ed
medium post from someone who was on
medical medium for 7 years and gained 30
lbs yet she is posting other supplements
and chocolate and saying to be your own
health expert and stop with the cult
first of all you can't even tell you
can't even trust if that's a real story
meaning like the story they're trying to
frame and paint there's been an attack
on the medical medum community by a
group of people you guys know about the
plotters and so forth there's been a
massive attack on the community um a lot
of people injured in the community we
know because a lot of people have told
us about their harm stories how damaged
they are and injured they are and we're
actually working on that working with
them and doing something about that by
the way and and it's going to be some
people in trouble point is is that a lot
of damage has been done due to Framing
and lies and so forth and the attack and
a lot of fake comments trying to frame
I've been doing medical medium for years
and this is what it did to me oh by the
way check out this supplement from a
hater check out that also is involved
with it all or check out this by my
program because I'm selling a program
now yeah
whatever all right you
guys there's some good information in
here it's really
powerful I could talk about that stuff
all day I just I don't have the time I
want to talk about the good stuff Uma
says over there on YouTube mm has food
fear shifter brain shot I love that
brain shot it's powerful it's right here
in medical medium brains saver protocols
and it's in here too in brain
saver you guys I'll read one little
thing for you here which is really great
too
um luus free with celery 333 on YouTube
true it's a small account I felt it was
fake yeah and we kind of know who it is
by the
way we know who it is they set up
multiple fake accounts constantly and
they have the same old
Spiel yeah so uh-huh and it's kind of
like pathetic and embarrassing if you
knew who it
was net ha says on YouTube Anthony don't
you agree that patience is necessary for
us to have to heal in this journey it is
it is patience is necessary for a lot of
things and a lot of healing truly is you
guys okay there's a piece of information
in here that's so incredible I can't
even get to it right now but it's here
and when you read this you'll be blown
away this is this whole entire eating
disorder
chapter is just packed right I'm just
reading a little bit of it in here it's
just incredible information is Advanced
you guys know it there it is unus order
chapter that's just that could be a book
on its
own it's that powerful and there's that
much information in
there like that's how incredible it is
but you get like six books 10 books in a
medical medium book and they're heavy so
look out so there you go for some reason
you guys if the cover's dirty or
something you can clean the cover off
you know I use like a handy wipe and it
just cleans the cover right off and the
conveyor belt at Amazon and then you
know like it's greasy and stuff so it
gets on the books the books are white
they're brand new books they're are no
used
books you know like if you're ordering a
new book you're ordering a new book not
ordering a used book and you'll see like
the covers get dirty so I like to clean
them anyway but when you get new books
you order them from Amazon you get a new
medical medium book and it comes like
dirty if you if it's too dirty or
something get a new one for free do an
exchange call Amazon get your money back
and order it again but or you can clean
it off or or whatever
but cristelle over there YouTube they
should be careful what goes around
around Winky Winky Winky you are
protected aw and will always be
protected and we will always stand by
you as well thank you thank you and I
want to do the best I can to provide you
guys with
information okay so you can make your
own decisions on what's going
down okay so it just takes time and
energy and they've done a lot of
interfering with me trying to do you
know all the work I do for free for the
community and for people with chronic
illness it is so ridiculous and sad yep
okay you
guys I'm going to be dropping a message
on telegram later on tonight so do are
you actually connected to my telegram
you guys uh following my telegram page
and I'm also going to be leaving a
message okay on mm inside
scoop right which is broadcasting on IG
the broadcast channel on IG the medical
Med Broadcasting
channel mm inside scoop so I'm going to
leave a message on there leave a message
on telegram so make sure you're around
check them out catch up on other
messages have you guys been like
watching Pride and Prejudice at all have
you didn't you know how I talked about
that for a while on Telegram and I
talked all about how healing it is why
it's healing how demons were kept out of
that you know cuz the industry you know
how the movie industry and the TV
industry is can be really dark right
like really dark with a lot of
possession all of that stuff did I talk
about that before like people just bring
their demons into that stuff right and
um and how the film industry can be
really dark really
dark
and the film industry can be really
really dark
and Pride and Prejudice okay the not not
Pride and Prejudice in general just the
filming of the 1994 1995 Pride and
Prejudice I talked about on telegram how
healing it is for the nervous system
there's a reason why it's healing for
the nervous system so if you need
something to watch because you're
sensitive you need something that
actually has a frequency that can help
heal the nervous
system check that out okay check out my
telegrams talk about it I'll do a new
telegram eventually talking about
it Stephen Cincy says love the telegram
messages can you explain why people in
the Bible live so long I can't wait to
explain that from s SOC the information
is mind-blowing your just mind will just
explode will
explode Lis fre accelery again 333
another comment yes love Pride and
Prejudice I have owned the series 1994
51 since it came out on DVD so you know
what I'm talking about there's a
frequency right well no one knew that
that there's this what happened was
because I know because Spirit of
compassion told me
that those demonic forces Darkness
everything was just kept out of that
film because in the film industry it's a
lot of Darkness everything was kept out
of it and it's very powerful and heals
the nerves it's incredible really
incredible including Angelic forces
involved that I talked about on on
telegram I I'll do new stuff on it and
talk about it but yeah you you might
want to check it out
again Alex party says Pride and
Prejudice watch that six or seven times
now whenever I'm struggling I watch that
and it all lifts exactly Alex you know
you know you
know you know love PMP the 1995 version
though that that has it has to be that
one Colin fth it has to be that version
right
there
yeah very healing for the nerves very
healing for sensitive
people there's Angelic forces involved
in the filming of that they didn't know
about and the demons were left at the
door absolutely
incredible
incredible one you can rely
on that can help heal that's that's a
healing tool and and they didn't know
that they don't know that they didn't
know that that was actually a healing
tool when they when they filmed that it
just happened to kick and just right and
Angels protected the filming process of
the 1995 Pride and
Prejudice and sometimes miracles happen
like
this and so the darkness was left at the
door and the angels protected that
filming process and that is a healing
tool a healing tool all right you guys
all right check out my telegram I'm
leave message
tonight love you
guys and
um oh yeah get on my newsletter because
I'm making an
announcement next
week making an
announcement I'm hoping it's next week
okay okay get on my
newsletter you're not want you're not
going to want to miss the
announcement it's important
information just letting you know you
don't want to miss it it's going to have
some details and stuff all
right