making a potato salad right here
I'm making a potato salad I got all
kinds of good stuff right here I feel
like eating that for dinner tonight
talking about food fear as well and
we're day six of the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
and I see that everybody was sketching
their stones that is such an incredible
moment when I remember when I was
sketching my Stones how it felt and what
it does it really connects you to what's
in the stone like all the nooks and
crannies and all the crevices and all
the different lines and designs and the
mineral compositions and everything is
there you really get to know your Stones
when you're sketching them like it's a
whole another level of being intimate
with your Stones which is really a part
of this incredible exercise and healing
Journey seven day healing Journey so
today is day six we're getting close I
wanted to make a potato salad talk a
little bit about food fear and stuff
like that which is fun we'll just see
you
we'll see we'll cover a couple different
things because I know so many people are
so afraid of so many different things
because they've been trained and
conditioned and brainwashed out there
in such a way stay away from nightshades
stay away from oxalates stay away from
uh lectins stay away from this and it
throws you in a big spin a confusion
because it's like what do I eat and
every and then you go to a food
allergist and now you're out of another
food allergist and they're like oh stay
off of this this don't eat kumquats
don't eat right don't eat limes don't
eat cilantro don't eat lemongrass like
the craziest stuff like you got this
list that's this big and and it's like
but you can eat meat and you can eat
this oh you're allergic to avocado
you're allergic to this you're allergic
to that it's crazy how that works so
many people have been totally brain
screwed really bad by that
for so many years because here you are
you're looking for help but nobody knows
why you're sick they don't know why you
actually have your symptoms your Tremors
in your hands and your achy feet and
your body that feels like you have
sandbags it's bogging you down and
holding you down where you have fatigue
where you have brain fog that's making
it so when someone talks to you you
can't even talk you can't even answer
them like you feel like you didn't even
get your words out right and there's all
that and there's plus there's OCD and
depression anxiety there's confusion
there's all kinds of different things
that people go through there's panic
attacks there's different levels of
anxiety there's neurological symptoms
Galore that people have tightness in the
chest tighten it you know funny feelings
in the stomach and aches in their jaw
and pain in their neck and it just goes
on and on and on and then you go and
you're looking for help and you got this
guy and he's like hey uh yeah we just
got your results from all your tests
don't eat Tony come watch don't eat
oranges don't eat Sarsaparilla or
whatever I mean they'll just come up
with anything don't eat this this this
this this stay away from stay away from
this herb stay away from this spice
don't have turmeric and don't have
parsley in this whole list gets insane
and here's what's crazy
the craziest part of this back 10 years
ago 10 years ago you go to the and do
all those different food elimination
tests 10 years ago
and it was different than what they're
saying eliminate now when you go and do
it because
the tests have always been and
the reason why is that they go with the
trends that's how crazy it is it's like
10 years ago they say oh you're allergic
to this this this to almost everybody
like and then as a few years go by and
Trends start changing people are allowed
to eat more fruit because medical meme
broke the fruit fear
and people are eating more fruit and
stuff and now those tests are coming
back for a lot of people and oh that's
allowed that's allowed that's allowed oh
what happens why is the test morphing
shape-shifting into into the trend of
the times I mean you're talking about
like psycho that's psycho it's really
crazy how it works anyway
I'm making a potato salad with the scary
nightshades
the scary night shades so that's what
we're doing and what do I have here I
have a bunch of little things lemon whoa
watch out lemon will kill your teeth
don't have any lemon you won't have a
tooth left you'll be toothless if you
eat any lemon God forbid you squeeze
lemon on something oh don't have your
lemon water every dentist will tell you
that's why your teeth are falling out
really because there's a crap ton of
people on this planet that are in dental
chairs getting their teeth rolled and
they're not doing lemon water that's
amazing how it works that's how crazy it
is
food fear is the topic but we're on day
six of the collecting Stones meditation
Journey we're sketching Stones today
Renata says yeah earlier today I saw a
thread of women talking about doctors
recommending limiting fruit always but
especially in pregnancy and especially
in the final trimester yeah stay away
from fruit because you're pregnant
that's food fear it's also fruit fear I
mean how crazy is that don't eat an
apple because you're pregnant huh
exactly and that's the kind of stuff
that's happening out there so much food
Theory you know what's happening right
now it's like everywhere whether it's
tick tock or anywhere else it's like
everybody's trying to get a rise out of
somebody like know this know that know
this know that it's the trend now know
this no that no this no that no this
right nobody knows why anybody's sick
but that's the trend now too it's like
food fear Galore out there
is what I call it anyway
Melissa says I drew my stones and it
looks like three potatoes that's pretty
funny it's all right I actually Drew my
stones and it looked like three lumps of
coal
that's what it looks like right there
and um
look there's Michelle says some of us
have food fear because we really do
react though yes totally but I wasn't
talking about that and I wasn't talking
about that situation I'm talking about
people they're sick they don't know why
they're sick they're just eating
whatever but you know and then they fall
into the alternative you know
communities and they get told stay away
from an oxalate then they get told they
don't even know it's gonna stay away
from a lectin stay away from celery stay
away from this stay away from that it's
endless endless uh endless that
so anyway
an IG
but the carbs and potatoes makes your
body produce insulin and that's how you
become obese and cause inflammation I
wish that was accurate information but
it's not accurate information
carbs in potatoes don't you know make
you obese that's not how it works
insulin resistance is when you're eating
too much fat so everybody's eating too
much fat they get insulin resistance
that's how it works that's why when you
take somebody who has Type 2 diabetes
and you start removing fried greasy food
out of their diet their numbers start to
level out a little better and better and
improve the reason why is because
they're removing hunks of fat out of
their diet they're taking them out of
fried Foodland which is the highest fat
where it's fried foods it's the highest
level of fat in your diet and when they
start removing the fried greasy fried
foods all of a sudden they're type 2 the
numbers are a little bit better and the
doctor's like whoa things are looking a
little better the more fat you rid out
of your diet the numbers come down and
you get even better if you're type 2
diabetes or you got diabetes your
numbers even get better and better and
better insulin resistance is all the fat
not allowing the glucose which is what
you need to survive to get to where it
needs to go so your pancreas has to
produce all this insulin the insulin
just floats around in your bloodstream
that's the reality like that's real
information what you have is outdated BS
information completely wrong across the
board where you're saying a potato can
actually make you obese no that's not
how it works but guess what though a
potato loaded with oil fat cheese butter
sour cream
and whatever else on top that's not
going to help you because guess what
it's the cheese that makes you fat guess
what it's the cheese it's the butter
it's the sour cream it's all that on top
like that's the stuff right there you
want to eat all that fat yeah that's
gonna push you over the edge push your
liver over the edge and push you in a
bad place so here we go let's talk about
the collecting Stones meditation Journey
a little bit sketching Stones is what we
were doing today we're talking about
food fearing and out of it
but let's start making a salad
so I got a bowl right here
and what I'll do is I think I'll place
it right here for the moment let me chop
up some greens let me get some lettuce
going here's some gorgeous lettuce right
here can I show this to you guys right
here it's a green leaf lettuce
there it is you guys see
I'm gonna chop some of it up I'm not
gonna make it so fine and I'm not going
to make pieces too too big either not
going to do that either so it's going to
be like in between
I think that's actually pretty good
right there pop that in here
so I'm making a quick potato salad
I might have chopped that up a little
too a little too fine there there we go
getting some lettuce together
how many of you guys been down the road
of food beer
scared to death of oxalates scared to
death of a lectin scared to death of a
potato a Nightshade don't know where
you're going the whole Health industry
had demonized sugar to such a point when
we need sugar it's what runs our brain
and muscles you have to have sugar why
do you think the carnivore people where
they were experimenting and they were
just doing eating muscle meat and eggs
and organ meats and then guess what see
you later alligator
so I'm chopping up some lettuce right
here
getting in here
making a salad
guys hold on one second here
one of my stones
one of my Stones right here
but I think I have my other Stones too I
will find them they're temporarily lost
here we go
Tyler lion says just out of the shower
with my Stones just in time for mm live
just in time
your Stones probably feel nice and fresh
freshly washed Dr fun I drew I drew my
Stones they look sketchy
indeed
I believe that I believe that
it's like the carnivore people right
check this out
they start out where I'm just gonna eat
meat only this isn't about anti-meat
this isn't about anti-plant base that's
not it so if you if you don't know
medical medium information and you're
listening you might get confused for a
second be like what's he talking about
Okay so
the organ Meats in eggs and muscle meat
like the carnivore guys started doing
you end up starving your brain
and it gets no glucose and you end up
getting sick they won't really tell
anybody that's what's happening but then
what happens is you end up bringing
honey in so the carnivore people brought
honey in now that's funny so Oregon
meets animal just a muscle animal tissue
organ Meats and eggs and now we're
bringing in honey so it was a whole
couple of years of that BS where the
carnivore guys were bringing in Honey
and then they were you know telling
people what they're doing and how oh
autoimmune it beats autoimmune it does
all this stuff they had to bring in
honey
and now the carnivore guys they're
bringing in fruit now okay so I'm
scratching my head I'm like sounds like
you're just about pretty much reaching a
regular animal protein based healthier
version of a diet so now it's not like
carnivore anymore they moved into
having to bring in Fruit so they're like
yeah my carnivore diet is now with fruit
and honey yup and I use lemons too
they'll do that now it's like okay uh
sure it's very interesting there because
it failed and then you failed people in
the same time that we're following you
that did the same thing so they're
learning on your little experiment while
you're learning on your little
experiment Gina says I lost 35 pounds
eating potatoes three times a day thanks
to Medical medium
and someone believes that the potatoes
will make you obese
and destroy your blood sugar your
insulin resistance will get crazy
these are collard greens if you want to
know
fresh out of the garden right there got
some collard greens I'm just showing you
you guys are okay with that
making a potato salad evil potato salad
a man over there in IG says I've been
eating potatoes for every meal since
January and I have not become obese nor
diabetic
indeed indeed indeed so what I'm doing
is I'm gonna finely chop up these
collard greens in this salad okay
because I don't want them in big hunky
pieces so I want to chop them up a
little bit more finely so if you guys
don't mind I'm just going to do a little
this and I know I'm talking at the same
time so I got to be careful right
just a quick quick Chop on this I wanna
I wanna get them a little bit
there we go
Marissa spiritual said on IG had all my
teeth drilled and never drank lemon
water in my life since having lemon
water every day with medical medium info
my enamel is coming back and healing
because
lemon water helps to kill the bad
bacteria in the mouth around the gums
and teeth
and it doesn't hurt teeth
it doesn't but you know what destroys
teeth
acetic acid
ooh man takes teeth out like nobody's
teeth
like nobody's done this if that makes
any sense
why blueberry dream that's that's
vinegar by the way acetic acid it's
vinegar for anybody that doesn't know
wild blueberry dreams on by Jesus yes my
functional medicine doctor had me off of
all sugars even from fruit for over six
for like over six weeks and I ended up
sicker than ever and in the hospital
with my first Ms episode
oh God
they also pushed me to eat things like
eggs
I tell people if you want to eat eggs
eat eggs but if you're sick if you're
sick you've got chronic illness you got
chronic illness
those eggs will not benefit you they
will not serve you you know that phrase
they never use that phrase
um I know it's used in the spiritual
movement of life it's like do what
serves you right does it serve you does
this serve you right that's what's used
right now in the spiritual realm I'm not
making fun of it totally I'm not but I
just don't for some reason I really
wasn't into that I don't know why it's
not like does this collard green serve
me
you know does it serve me I don't know
there's something about that I felt kind
of like you know A pompous
pompous you know
whatever Posh rich person I don't know
you just sound like does it serve me
this is does it serve my business does
it serve me
as a person but either way
um yeah the eggs will not serve you
they will not if you're sick if you're
struggling if you have any kind of issue
whatsoever
any kind of chronic illness any kind of
autoimmune whatever it is you guys are
making a potato salad you just got on
here evil potato salad talking about
um
talking about
some fun stuff about food fear we're
kind of touching touching a little bit
on night shades maybe oxalates oxalates
maybe some other things too maybe some
lectins whatever touching base on
certain things
oh right here so can I show you guys
this beautiful dinosaur La siento kale
amazing there it is
this is from my garden too I've grown a
few things in my garden right now I got
some basil I'm growing in my garden I
got this Rosemary growing in my garden I
got the kale that's growing in my garden
that onion didn't come from my garden
lettuce didn't come from my garden but I
got a a bunch of things that did
come from my garden and stuff so you can
do this thing work you don't want the
big thick stems inside your salad you
can do this take a look at that right
there
see
that's what you can do
if you want to do that you can do that
look boom
you don't have to have that in your
salad so you're running into that real
chewy chewy
yellow says on IG my PCOS condition gets
better after six months months with
medical medium protocols
I think what happened
to be honest with so many people got
healing from the medical medium
information and protocols all around the
world to such a degree that it pissed
off a lot of Industries it pissed off a
lot of people
um it pissed off people in the health
realm I mean you guys know I mean look
look at the whole thing that's happened
if you're not up on what's happened here
with the uh you know the whole thing uh
against the medical medium Community
right that you guys may be aware of that
happen like it's it's been like this
with it's not my success it's the
success of people healing I would be
nobody or nothing because whatever it is
like meaning like I would no one even
know my name who is that guy and what
happened in the last 35 years is peop
before the books even came out people
knew my name because of the protocols
and the information I worked with a lot
of people helping them heal all through
the industry even before the books came
out it's why I was World known for it
and people around the world traveled to
visit me to get info information they
couldn't get anywhere else right so what
happened is people were healing it was
always people healing information was
healing then the books came out then
millions of people around the world
healing and then it finally pissed
everybody off both in the the health
industry both in the whatever industry
and many in many and even the Product
Industry because when I say you know
that the ionizer water machines make you
sick they do like when I say things it
pisses everybody off then everybody then
say Hey you know let's just whatever and
that's how it works
peace and veggies over there on IG years
ago I had an allergy test done at the
naturopath office said I was allergic to
apples I eat two to three apples a day
and I'm fine just as I was saying before
it's a total head screw
Elvis lives
um I love that I love that handle by the
way uh Elvis is just his work was
amazing aw went to put my stones on the
window so to look out the window I
opened the window shade and there was
another Stone there a fourth Stone it
was quite beautiful okay that's
mind-blowing
foreign
says my stones are enjoying watching
this live with me I am honored I hope
you are enjoying it too your stones are
loving the life
okay Margie says scared of goitre gin
Foods hi I forgot because of my
hypothyroid I forgot
IC Foods I forgot
hard what's wrong with me what is wrong
with me I'm chopping up this hip that's
another brain screw right there and
conditioning and brainwashing all the
mistakes made with the so-called
goitrogenic Foods or introgenic Foods
say three times in a row
of gorgeous gorgeous
yeah so I want to show you what's going
on right here that's another hat screw
by the way we can go into that a little
bit oh
oh
yeah that's right if anybody has
hypothyroid they're going to be scared
with that information not I mean I
understand I'm not
I'm not like judging that I know what
you're saying because that's out there
right the gorgeous any foods but anybody
who says hey you know I got the
hypothyroid exactly I got to be worried
about these they're told that
misinformation out there but do what
your doctor tells you to do I'm just
saying right but I'm saying what I tell
my family and friends is don't be afraid
of the kale don't be afraid of the
collard greens right there don't be
afraid of those those have phytochemical
compounds that enter into the thyroid to
help get rid of the problem now here's
what is interesting you might say well
what's he talking about first of all
medical meme information is the first to
put the truth out about why we have
hypothyroid
and why we have Hashimoto's thyroiditis
from the Epstein-Barr virus entering
into the thyroid
well
these cruciferous cruciferous right here
have properties to help enter into the
thyroid to break down the Epstein-Barr
virus and that's the difference but yet
people are told stay away from the
gorgeous because they don't understand
how it works
anyway I got some kale in here I got
some collard greens
foreign
fear out there is insane insane
okay
we're putting this together we got a
little kale in there we got um some
collard greens in here I think I'm gonna
put a little bit more lettuce I want to
kind of make it a little higher up in
the bowl just a bigger bigger bowl of
that so let me just get that in there
okay
all right
chop up some potatoes let's do that
before we do that I think I'm going to
put some basil now this is a gorgeous
Thai Basil right here
on IG Emily says your info is the only
real info out there thank you for always
remaining consistent giving it to us
straight and never backing down on the
truth even when it's not popular you are
a true gift I'm honored what you'll find
and it's not because of me
I will I will not take the credit it's
SOC what you'll find is consistency
consistency and non-contradictive
that's what you're going to find with mm
info the reason why is because I hear a
voice that's keeping it all straight
because how the hell is it possible to
keep eight large medical textbooks
straight with information and 35 years
of work and not steer off the path
you'll get the best guys out there and
alternative medicine and conventional
medicine they're out there being like
you know they're out there like looking
for fame and they're all over YouTube
and everywhere else they can't keep
anything straight it's one year it's
this one year it's this six months later
it's this they say this but they say
that they do this but they do that
they're so all over the place they can't
keep one thing straight contradiction
contradiction contradiction the reason
why they're not called out for it they
can't keep a crowd long enough they're
cycling new people through their ads 24
7 and new person comes and doesn't know
they just contradicted themselves six
months ago
decided to go to bed a little earlier
last night I don't know if you guys
noticed
throwing some basil in here
decided to go to bed a little bit
earlier last night
Anna had a full day's work
man it's night time again
foreign
says I like that you hear a voice aw
thank you
the years of bullying about it and
everything else that's happened to me is
just off the charts so thank you for
liking the fact that I hear a voice
that's why there's campaigns right now
trying to just wreak havoc
on AW and everything because they just
can't stand it
all right so let's keep on going you
guys are we sketching the stones today
or what we're day six of the of the
collecting Subs meditation Journey
so Kathy
canoe says on YouTube I'm really sad I
have to leave my Stones tomorrow let's
not think about it too much tonight
no
no no
there's nothing about it too much
tonight please no
ah
don't worry about it it's day six we're
not letting our Stones go tonight
all right so okay
all right
let's figure this out I have a salad
building
I am going to put some potatoes in there
if that's okay
potatoes
what I'm doing is I'm cutting it like
this so if you look I sectioned them
into like that
so they're
that's how you cut them so I'm going to
do this do you like your potato pieces
in your potato salads do you like them
bigger or smaller
if you were a guest in the kitchen in
this moment right here with your guest
kitchen right here anyway but if you
were sitting here
I would say do you do like hunky
potatoes do you like them not hunky do
you like them chopped a little smaller
that's what I would ask you guys
all right so um I'm not gonna make them
too big I I like them about that size
I don't like them super hunky
pop those on top just like that
boom let's get another one
nice
instead of throwing fruit in the air
like I like to do I was just um flipping
a potato
okay so I'm gonna do the same thing the
same kind of cutting action are you guys
watching from here
is this another mukbang
all right
okay on IG burning around town on IG
I almost lost my stone baby
I almost lost my stone baby called
guilty I basically already had a funeral
for it until I found it this morning
must be a reason there must be a reason
there's always a reason
always a reason
okay
it's not just happenstance it's not
it happens stance is bigger than anybody
knows but it's not just happenstance
Alexandra Sophia aw can we do another
Stone meditation with different Stones
right after we finish up tomorrow
we'll talk about that we'll talk about
those things tomorrow actually
okay I got my potatoes in here I think I
want this heavier heavier potatoed
let me put one more here
yep
the good old potato
potato you have done people so good you
have not done people wrong
it's the people that put all kinds of
stuff
on potatoes that don't know better
they'll fry the potatoes in oil and
grease still put all kinds of bacon bits
on potatoes can I have a baked potato
please with bacon bits on top sour cream
um
I don't know
okay
it's actually coming out really good
April Clark says I lost one today
seriously wow
okay
let's just finish up what we gotta do
let's make some food we took a little
talk a little bit more about food fear
as we go along I got my basil in there I
got all my Greens in here I'm looking
good I still have some herbs and other
things let's go with some onion you guys
okay with that
onions
wow there's a lot of fear food fear
around onions too there's been a lot of
food here around onions
that's been out there and in the health
movement for a while
I've seen that
okay let's cut this onion
okay all right we're ready
[Music]
if you are new here and you don't know
about the collecting Stones meditation
Journey check out the link in the
medical medium profile and description
on this video so please if you're new
here check out that link and description
learn about the collecting Stones
meditation journey I swear to God
I swear to God
it's an experience like no other
and I can promise you'll never forget it
ever and it will just keep on giving
beautiful things
and keep on giving beautiful things it's
that powerful of experience that
powerful of a journey of a meditation
Michelle over there on IG you still can
register and after tomorrow they will
give you 48 hours to access the whole
meditation that you just missed
incredible
you guys know that
right hey house
hey house uh and I
the medical medium
worked really hard hey house worked
really hard
in um putting this together with me we
teamed up
we teamed up on this one
I needed their help on this one we
teamed up all right so the onions do you
like them hunky do you like them small I
don't like them really small I don't
like them too big either so I like them
in between
and um see over there Tara Tom am loving
the collecting Stones incredible Tara
thank you for being here tonight I'm
putting a half an onion on here it's a
lot of onion but I can't help it
the wild blueberry baby says it's been a
miraculous experience
it truly has I am I'm feeling it I
really am Emily
um over there in IG it has been so
simple and so profound
it really is the true meaning of
profound this collecting Stones
meditation Journey really is it embodies
that true medium the true um that whole
thing
tough as a mother over there in IG I was
in the shower today and I kept on seeing
visions of my past and I'm so glad my
son's right there it was like they were
talking all the taking all the pain away
oh my God
wow
it's like the true meaning is what I was
saying
hummingbird already feels strong healing
with my Stones Melissa over there in IG
I lost a stone once and I kept dreaming
it was outside in my yard with the with
the gravel on the garden and went to
look for it and there it was
um
I'm not kidding though like it gives me
chills it gives me it gives me raises
the hair on the back of my neck
is what it does
let's get some tomatoes in here
oh Tomatoes is a whole other fast
can't tell you how many years of
confusion on tomatoes
how many years of confusion there is
Tomatoes nightshades it's going to give
you arthritis
yeah tomato on that
chicken parmesan
tomato
on that pizza with oil and mozzarella
cheese will give you some arthritic pain
hint hint hint
s
the cheese
the oil the grease the pepperoni on the
pizza not the tomato sauce
good
took years to try to unravel the Tomato
the whole tomato hate thing I fought for
that one
say oh aw's restrictive uh medical means
restrictive
are you kidding
I I spend decades trying to break all
the fear around a darn tomato all the
fear around nightshades and potatoes
all if you're around fruit
the health movement if you got sick 15
years ago or 18 years ago or 20 years
ago if you got sick then I just have to
tell you guys
you would run across the Nightshade fear
where they would bury it into your brain
you would run across the Tomato hate the
potato hate the pepper hate the eggplant
hate then you would run across all the
fruit fear you'd be totally screwed on
the whole fruit for your thing then he
would run across the gorgeous Foods then
he would rot across the cruciferous
exactly because that you would run
across all of this times 10 plus
oxalates and everything else and you
would be literally not eating anything
but I'm the problem when I brought all
that back I'm the problem
Noah's plate over here in IG
I have been doing this Stone meditation
with my four-year-old son and it's been
amazing
I'm gonna throw a couple more tomatoes
in here
say Boogie said on IG are you talking
about literal Stones I'm talking about
literal Stones right here
these are the stones I'm talking about
right here these are my three stones
check out the collecting Stones
meditation Journey if you can please
go to medicalmean.com just check it out
if you want okay on IG have been having
my
have been having many shifts during this
journey too many to call it a
coincidence
so true so true
um let's see on IG my mm healing
lifestyle said I'm feeling so emotional
and feel emotions leaving that is
that is it right there that's it that's
it can I put some Rosemary on this
potato salad are you guys okay
I
personally if you want to know something
about the medical medium
on Disney says on IG Disney says IG one
of my Stones has a happy face on it okay
you're gonna make me laugh because
that's actually incredible
yep Monica says do you make soup I make
soups definitely okay
no one something that people may not
know about me whenever I have potato I
try to always have Rosemary always have
Rosemary
I love Rosemary with my potatoes it is
one of my favorite things in the whole
wide world
if you guys don't mind I'm just gonna
chop up a little bit of rose right here
I just want to chop it a little finer
because I don't want to be chewing on
a whole piece of Rosemary or anything
like that a rosemary leaf I don't want
to be chewing on that so I'm just
actually chopping it up is fine
I can go a little bit more than that but
okay we're almost there Carrie and
Hannah Berry says I love the format of
this journey the videos were great with
the PDF thank you
thank you very much
um Lindsay over there I was on Facebook
Lindsay on YouTube says I have love-hate
relationship with my stones
I have a love-hate relationship with my
Stones too
Michelle Clayton says I keep leaving my
Stone named abandonment
interesting
extremely interesting
I got a fresh lime right here I got a
half a lemon I'm gonna be using that but
first and foremost are you guys okay if
I put chop up a little bit of these
steamed brussels sprouts on top of this
potato salad are you okay with that
because I
would like to do that there we go I got
some steamed brussels sprouts I'm
putting them right on top of salad I
know on that g you guys probably can't
even see this too easy but it's coming
together I got the onions tomatoes there
I got the Brussels sprouts the herbs the
Thai Basil I got a lot of good stuff
going on right there
um I got the kale I got the collard
greens I'm just trying to show you can
you catch that in there
Barbara cologne says over there on
Facebook I picked three stones in
January and I kept them with me since
but there is no comparison with the
attachment that grew with these three
now exactly I did put them aside right
before starting this journey and I was
planning on picking them back up and
doing the same thing we just did in
these seven days because I don't feel
I'm ready to release those yet a lot of
deep connections haven't been made yet I
am blown away Edith
um Agustin over there on YouTube thanks
for being here thank you for everything
Anthony we love you I'm honored you're
here truly and I mean that I mean that
I really do
I do
so I I have a little honey over here
I'm putting a little honey on this
potato salad I'm gonna kind of like I
like drizzling just a little bit
sometimes not all the time but for this
one I want to do that tonight I'm in the
mood for that and I'm gonna put squeeze
some lemon and squeeze a lime that's a
ripe lime right there
Angels 444 blessed I've definitely felt
a shift but I feel Darkness keeps
pulling me down thank God I Rise quickly
yeah I'm gonna rise up
look there's a lot of fork tongue Devils
out there and they're spewing they're
evil and they're spearing their Darkness
there's a lot of activity out there a
lot of Darkness has a lot of that I
notice every time we rise up and we do
even better and we rise up and we do
even better better for the community
better it was like when the light blast
happened all you heard was Fork tongue
devil spewing hatred everywhere on
Instagram and everything so yeah he's
bad he's terrible this is a slight blast
thing and they're just spewing it's
almost like it's kind of like vampires
right when the sunlight goes through the
window and the vampires they don't get
into their coffins in time they just
start going and their fangs come out
right well that's what's happening I'm
noticing the hater clubs against the
medical medium which are plenty of them
they just freak out as the as the light
hits them the light blast caused a lot
of it so what I'm saying is if you're
rising up because that's what I do right
I Rise Up and then you do better and you
do better for people you do you're
working on your healing process you're
you're you're cleaning yourself up
you're helping others you're doing all
this stuff and then Darkness loves to be
like no no you're not allowed to do that
you're not allowed to do that
okay over there in IG
butterfly notice the magical things
happening with my Stones experiences and
events are coming to me
serendipitously for my healing amazing I
feel like it's the stones helping me
this Stone meditation
is unlike anything anything out there I
try to give everybody the forewarning I
possibly could I said you're just you're
going to go for quite a healing ride
truly truly profound healing ride of
Lifetime and you're never going to
forget this experience
today's day six tomorrow's day seven
okay let's top off the salad with
whatever we need we'll go with a little
lemon
this is a half a lemon that I had out
already I'm gonna squeeze that I try not
to get seeds on there if I get the seeds
on there I usually use a little strain
or two so you can squeeze the heck out
of it but I'm just getting some lemon on
here
let's go ripe lime let's see what we
have in here oh yeah it looks good
looks good
it does it does there's a seed in that
lime
there we go
nice
all right
I'm gonna get this big seed that popped
out
you guys don't mind
you get the lemon seeds in there
right and then you're chewing yourself
and you're selling you hit that lemon
seed and it tastes bitter
the bitter taste isn't fun you can eat
the lemon seeds in your salad of course
you can I've done it a million times but
tonight I just want to catch that one
before it goes on down
so yeah
all right I'm gonna drizzle a little
honey on here
not a lot
because I don't I just don't want this
salad extra sweet that's all but I love
honey I'll put a lot of it in tea all of
it okay just putting a little bit on
there we go
for people are crazy
Cyrus over there in IG says on on
medical mean and protocols for two and a
half years been off thyroid beds for a
year healed receding gums also
I am eating with my Stones tonight I
have my salad made my potato salad made
Stones so good to have you here
sebis says on IG dreamed of vampires
this morning very disturbing dream felt
my
discomfort Stone was absorbing that pain
and negative energies from that dream
woke up and waved my arm to clear the
air
powerful
so powerful at IG Journey XOXO healing
and processing a lot in dreams with this
Stone Journey whoa whoa whoa whoa
an IG birding around town I wasn't sure
how big my connection was with my Stones
until I lost one and then felt sad it
was gone so quickly but I found it again
Blown Away
it's incredible
see my medical medium way says has has
been a very interesting Journey a lot
deeper than I expected it is totally
it's totally deeper than so many of us
have expected
Carol blicker said where find the stone
meditation where do you find it go to
medicalmium.com link is in the profile
and in the description as well find that
stone that uh Stone meditation sign up
because guess what you can sign up and
get all the PDFs the videos all for like
for 48 hours after tomorrow but it's all
for free so me too 787 what you doing
tonight
let's see I had a revelation in a dream
while waking yesterday morning about an
injury from a medical treatment that was
given to me 37 years ago very
interesting and confirming me too
understood
I get the code
I do I know what you're talking about
and you know why I'm not talking about
it
you know what Cynthia YouTube wow
Anthony on live
I've been on it medical medium diet for
two years and I feel the best ever I had
an incredible dream after reading the
chapter on sleep and dream in thyroid
healing to my stones are we feeling
that we're healing is over there it's
over there okay I'm gonna mix this up
now you can you can do that you can do
one of two things you can do anything
you want
but
I'm not totally mixing everything up
crazy right I'm kind of just letting
things kind of fall down in there a
little bit let some of that lemon juice
fall down in there
and let the potatoes kind of come down
but I'm not like doing a complete total
crazy mix
there we go
boom
we got a plate
get a plate
let me see how can we do this carefully
let me get some of this
gorgeous potato salad with all these
leafy greens
come on aw don't leave the leafy greens
down there are you trying to avoid leafy
greens
no way never
Julian Castle says day three and four
day four lots of memory surfacing lots
of dreams starting to feel better
day five felt bad like I had the flu
today much better incredible
okay
I am going to
grab out of this dishwasher here I'm
gonna grab a fork
and that's why we're live by the way you
guys were like
hmm
freaking hungry type
an IG
um Emily says acceptable occipital
neuralgia help question mark oh
foreign
do you have the brain books
no
do you have the brain books go to the
library get them for free if you don't
want to get them off Amazon even though
Amazon they're they're discounted right
now
movies
musician says which book talks about
fibroids
um
I mean
you want to know a lot about
Epstein-Barr
that's important no matter what
sorry about this
when you're dealing with fibroids in
general
I talk about how it's it's
um low grade viral infections
so that's the ultimate Epstein-Barr book
right there
but cleanse the heel
cleanse the heel vibrate informations in
here
so maybe it's both these here
janelli says please help with acid
reflux
foreign
do you have the mm books
so much healing can be done with those
books
hmm
guys I can't help it
um
too good
Nora case
I taste the the basil definitely strong
but so good though
a little bit of honey
is kind of like up against that basil
Irina says on IG
I healed my sibo because of medical
medium information thank you Anthony
can you help with mold toxicity
if you listen to the medical medium
podcast
check out medical medium podcast
look into these brain books we're going
to cleanse the heel all that's there go
to the library just get them for free
take your time get into the books
talking about food fear today we're on
day six of the the medical medium
collecting Stones meditation Journey
but as you can see
don't have food fear
myself personally as I'm enjoying this
incredible meal
that has all these powerful leafy greens
but it has tomatoes
potatoes collard greens
right Dinosaur Kale
so much food for you around onions
so much food for around lemons people
being told they're not gonna have teeth
left because of lemons that's so so
wrong so wrong
for something that's so right so right
I mean seriously
so no there's no fear here that's the
whole point medical meme information
brought back these from the dead
from the dead
you guys I don't know if you've been
around enough long enough right
I forgot
forgot the cayenne pepper
I knew I was missing something I knew I
was missing something
I forgot the cayenne pepper on top of my
potato salad
whoa nightshade
scary
that sounds sarcastic
am I being sarcastic
okay I want to put some cayenne pepper
on the salad
all right
but that's the thing
seriously seriously
truly seriously
the amount of brain screw that's
happened in the health movement
is unprecedented it's been totally it's
so
so insane so insane so many people
struggling for so long
santara's healing good to see you over
there on YouTube amazing so you're
saying was so funny 144 days on the
potato mono eating cleanse healed all my
gut issues and so many other symptoms
and a family member tells me quote
careful they put holes in your stomach
misinformation is wild indeed it is
it really is wild
um
cayenne pepper
for some reason that cayenne pepper
way hotter than I thought that would be
it's so hot I'm gonna try to look for
spots that have no pepper
that's good
okay
on IG
Terry Hillman says can you cleanse while
breastfeeding and still keep your milk
supply what keeps milk supply
first of all you want clean milk supply
anything you're cleansing out of your
body is making your milk cleaner
so when you're breastfeeding you're
giving your baby cleaner milk
the more toxins that come out of your
body the less toxic milk there will be
that's one thing another thing that's
really important is
is cleansing isn't
unless you're doing some crazy cleanse
out there that's not MediCal medium if
you're doing like water fasting while
trying to breastfeed that you're going
to lose your milk
you're going to lose your milk
if you're eating a carnivore diet where
it's just all animal protein only you're
going to lose your milk
because the milk is lactose
right it's glucose sorry it's glucose
sugar is in the milk it's critical sugar
and carbohydrates is what the human
body's milk is mostly made out of making
sure that's clear
because that's really what it's about
it's about making sure your milk is high
in sugar high in carbohydrate high in
glucose critical because that's what
builds the baby's brain that's what
builds the baby's muscles that is a big
part of all of it if the breast milk is
lacking sugar the baby starves
essentially or the baby has problems
that's the whole point so if you take
out all your fruit and you take out
potatoes and you take out all of that we
get in trouble right but if we cleanse
and do some crazy cleanse like a juice
fast where it's nothing but these juices
then yeah that's not good
for the breast milk there won't be
enough glucose there won't be enough
carbs inside the breast milk breast milk
is mostly sugar and only a little bit of
protein and only a little bit of fat
that's what breast milk is
human breast milk is a little bit of
protein a little bit of fat and then a
lot of sugar so in the sense essentially
it's sugar water for the baby
and that's what breast milk is made out
of so if you're doing a medical medium
cleanse you're obviously getting food
and ample amounts of glucose
because mircomium cleanses don't starve
a person they don't starve a person
they don't underfeed that's the whole
point these cleanses are geared so you
can cleanse heal still provide enough
for all all that your body needs the
glucose for your brain all of it for
your liver and all that's happening
guys I'm like multi
multitasking everywhere
yep
human breast milk is mostly sugar it's
supposed to be
I'll try to make it as clear as I can
not muddy up the water
so good
such a good salad so anyway
just to kind of finish up on the food
for your thing
um I just want to say that
I do feel sorry for so many people
throughout the decades throughout the
years
that have been thrown off course
with fruit fear
food fear food confusion
and at the same time not knowing why
they're sick and not knowing what's
wrong with them
then catastrophic catastrophic on
humankind
in the health movement world
and what has happened
and what one of the big fear makers
is protein right you're not getting
enough protein you need protein you need
protein puts people in fear and Chaos
your body's gonna fall apart you're sick
because you don't have enough protein
that's crazy because that's all people
have ever eaten
that's all they've ever eaten all these
decades and years and years and decades
is plenty of protein that's the whole
point and they got sick and they were
sick you can be a plant-based person and
you're eating too much soy protein
you're eating up you're eating way too
much nuts you're eating you can still
get yourself you can get tons of protein
and still be sick because what I'm
saying is protein
isn't the answer it never was the answer
I've talked about this for years I've
written about it in the medical medium
book series
the amount of food fear has been
truly at a level
especially in the health room
truly at a level that's confused and
completely thrown people off their game
they're healing for years and decades
and that includes like the cruciferous
right
and it includes also the night shades
and the oxalates
and the lectins and much more and
includes it all and it's thrown just
people into
confusion while they're trying to heal
creative artery says
I have histamine intolerance and Mast
Cell Activation disorder and it's hard
to not fear food my body hates me I also
try to be vegan
our bodies love us unconditionally
they
are fighting for us they're working for
us
and then when we pick up pathogens along
the way because
the industries put the pathogens out
there you know that now more than ever
before just in the last three years
but the industries put pathogens out
there and then people have these
pathogens these pathogens create a lot
of problems we get sick our bodies try
to fight for it but we have to give our
body what it needs to fight for us
healing with Holly 144 says I tried to
warn my stepbrother about the carnivore
diet and he said they are bringing more
fruit and raw honey in now because they
need some glucose and I thought that
came from aw it did come from aw that's
where it exactly came from so the carna
carnivore the carnivore boys
out there right on YouTube and
everywhere else are using medical medium
information
because it's exactly what I predicted
for them I predicted they would all hit
the wall and they did
all the carnivore dudes out there
yelling about how great their diet was
just eat organ Meats just eat eggs only
and they all hit the wall and I said
they would hit the wall years ago
and they did it was exactly as predicted
by SOC and they hit the freaking wall
boom like that and guess what
they're eating honey like no tomorrow
and they're eating fruit like no
tomorrow because they can't even talk
those guys are like they've lost their
minds because they got no glucose and
they knew it they felt the brain fog
come over them and they're like my
carnivore died isn't really helping me I
have to go do my workout now I don't
know what'd you say man I forgot wait
what I hey medical medium talked about
glucose in the brain has to need it okay
let's just put some honey in there
morons
all right
in a good way more hunts in a good way
in a happy way
all right you guys
collecting Stone's meditation Journey
we're on day six
day six
and
it truly is an experience
I think you know what it is is I'm just
getting myself prepared for tomorrow
tomorrow's day seven
all right you guys made my day
okay I'm going to eat
and keep on eating
I love you guys Catherine says do the
robot not today but we will do the robot
soon enough