[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now as
I've always said who is 10 or 20 or 30
even 30 years to wait for answers and
I've seen it before and I see it now
it's going on out there I talked to
people and they're like you know it took
30 years to know that Epstein bar
actually causes heart palpitations no
one knew that it didn't exist out there
the information did not exist out there
and it took 30 years to figure out that
epscene bar causes tingles and numbness
and that didn't exist it took 30 years
for this person person to find out that
Epstein causes anxiety and depression
chronic depression long term and brain
fog nobody knew it never was anywhere
else but here and that's thanks to
Spirit so thank you for actually tuning
in everybody because we're helping out
so many people by getting the
information finally out there because we
don't have time to waste we don't have
time to just hang out we don't have
another 30 years to know that Epstein
bar causes Hashimoto's thyroiditis and
although this isn't an Epstein bar show
today we're talking about foods that
heal chronic illness and of course
Epstein bar causes a lot of chronic
illness so does a lot of other bugs and
pathogens that we talk about like strap
and everything else and you know and
other types of pathogens and of course
we talk about the toxic heavy metals and
other things associated with chronic
illness but the point is today we're
talking about foods that heal chronic
illness illness so we might tap into
some of these other chronic illnesses
and what we deal with every day so
there's no time to waste no time to
spare fasten the seat belts we're
starting today so today's show is about
the Holy four the holy four okay right I
talked to you before about the
unforgiving four right the unforgiving
four which is the pesticides and
herbicides that are in our system for
years like DDT included all the way back
toxic heavy metals Mercury lead arsenic
you know um cadmium um nickel copper we
you know we talked about that and you
aluminum and then we talked about the
radiation how much radiation still
falling out on us how much radiation is
going on there and there's nothing to
worry about in the sense where hey we
got all this stuff going on that's not
about it it's about
knowing what could be hampering your
immune system and what we can do to stop
it fight it clean it up get it out of
your system instead of just playing the
game like hey everything's fine sure 250
million Americans are sick almost 300
million Americans have symptoms
unexplained completely mystery but let's
just pretend everything's okay you know
we're not going to do that all right
we're not going to do that because I
know if you got a symptom and you got
something going on and you got a chronic
illness you want answers um no one wants
to be sick you know one thing I know
I'll tell you guys right now and and you
probably know this better than I do no
one wants to be sick you know and there
isn't such thing as a fear of
healing but what there is is there's a
fear of being sick that's for sure so we
do have that out there that's rampant
there is a fear of being sick so that
does exist okay but nobody has a fear of
healing all right so that right there is
something we have to always understand
you no one wants a tummy ache no one
wants a tummy ache nobody wants a
headache does anybody want a headache
out there does anybody want a tummy ache
does any I'm actually being a little
extra uh annoying today is that what it
is silly a little extra silly nobody
wants to have an ache and pain right I
mean come on and so and I'm serious
about this no one wants
fatigue so we can't just
gloss everything over as if you know hey
all right fine you know we you know here
there's diets out there there's this out
there and you know there's there's
really nothing to be worried about a
concerned um it's your fault you're sick
how about that we hear that all the time
out there oh it's your fault you're sick
um yeah no it's not your fault that you
got these symptoms and we can't gloss
everything over we got to know what the
unforgiving for that we just recently
talked about is we have to know what
that is we have to know it's the toxic
heavy metals we have to know it's the
viral explosion it's the upstein bar the
epidemic we have to know why 250 plus
you know close to 300 million people
have symptoms of all kinds and
conditions in in the us alone we have to
know about the radiation and you know
these things are important they really
are and we have to know about the
pesticides and the old DDT that's been
you know in our systems all these years
and the pesticides and everything else
around it we got to know about this and
so today it's foods that heal chronic
illness using the holy four the holy
four is also in the lifechanging foods
book and the holy four is the groups the
fruits the vegetables the herbs and
spices and the wild Foods so that's the
holy four you got it right there and
it's powerful and it cleans us up and it
gets rid of it lowers viral issues and
it gets us feeling good and so that's
what today is about so don't miss out on
the show whatever you do do not miss out
on it this is a really good show and if
you have to miss out on the show go pick
it up back on the archives or something
because we're going to cover some good
stuff that's what it's all about um got
the event coming up check it out
medicalmedium.com
and um and you know try to get to the
event we're doing the light blast and
that's what we're doing sending light
down from heaven Spirit does this for me
thank goodness since I was a child and I
talk about this before you guys heard me
say this before I was worried about what
else can I do back when I was younger
what can I do to help somebody and
spirit said we're going to do the light
and spirit taught me how to be involved
why Spirit sends the light down on the
crown of everybody's head and we do this
at the event rushes through the body
unblocks energy that's stored up that
people have from just being sick and not
feeling well and they get all stagnant
and and you know and get all acidic and
everybody just you because when you're
sick and unwell it's really difficult we
go through struggles and we don't feel
good we don't feel at our best and we
feel tired and everything just builds up
and then we have all these kinds of
struggles and emotional um struggles
that we do because there's so much
stress and everything else going on in
the world and in our lives and it gets
built up and on top of that we have our
condition itself and the and the cause
of the conditions themselves like for
instance say Epstein bar or something
else and so that light comes down hits
the crown of everybody's head it runs
through the body and it is a rush we do
it we I I don't care what it takes
spirit and I want to make sure everybody
gets this light blast in any shape form
any possibility so you know check out
the events if you can um and also
life-changing Foods book which what
we're talking about you know um we're
talking about that that's because the
book's about these Foods so we have to
talk about these Foods what food that's
in your pantry what food that is in your
refrigerator what food that's in your
refrigerator in your freezer what food
is in the store that you can go and get
and pick up and grab and whatever you
need to do there and and bring it home
and make it and get yourself feeling
better so today is about foods and
that's what we're doing about and I'm
talking about life-changing Foods
because of the book because we're
talking about the Holy four because
that's in there we talked about the
unforgiving four that's in the book and
I can't even scratch the surface of
what's in life-changing Foods book I
can't even scratch the surface I could
do 50 shows and won't scratch the
surface in there um and you know so I'm
going to try to get what I can out in
this show but um it it's really
difficult what I'm saying is when you
get the book and you get it in your hand
you're not going to be disappointed in
fact you're going to be like okay he did
us right he didn't you know this wasn't
just one of those things where a lot of
hype or something and then you open up
the book and there's like one concept
and you're like okay all right no no no
I did you guys right I made sure I
promise I really did when you open this
up you're going to be like okay all
right you know what okay he did good
let's he did good the boy did
good right all right so let's let's talk
about this stuff um let's get into it so
you know hey look the fruits the
vegetables you've heard it before eat
your fruits eat your
vegetables why do we say that is there
an importance to it do you think there's
some kind of importance to it yeah there
really is there really is but it's more
than just you know just maybe a little
bit of broccoli once a week it's more
than an apple once a month I was talking
to somebody the other day cuz I have to
talk to so many different people and I
was talking to someone and they said um
and they said look you know I eat apples
I said how really I go that's great
that's the best thing I ever heard
because apples do this I was I was I was
all a sudden I was like a like a spirit
encyclopedia you guys and I was like I
was like yeah because apples do this
apples do that spirit says apples do
this apples do this apples do this and
and I said oh by the way how many apples
are you eating and he said well I don't
know let me try to think I go well
when's the last time you had an apple
and this person said I think it was I
think it was last month I said what do
you
mean I said what do you mean last month
I said you mean like what you had an
apple last month and he yeah yeah and I
had an apple last month and it was
really well I think it might have been
more than one apple I said that's
amazing you had more than one apple and
this person said yeah because it was in
it was an apple tart this homemade apple
tart I said okay hold on hold on okay
I'm back up here so wait a minute you
didn't have an apple and chop it up and
eat it in slices or put a little almond
butter on it or put a little or put a
little peanut butter on it if that's
what you like or put you know whatever
it is Apple goes good with avocado by
the way if you put avocado on an Apple
slice that tastes really good I'm just
I'm just being straight um anyway so
they go no it was in a tart it was in a
healthy tart it was at I was at this
health food store and they had these
apple tarts and uh I said well what what
else was in it they said well was
glutenfree I said so you sure there was
that much apple in there I go first of
all okay your Apple was cooked which is
not the endend of the world okay fine if
that's what you know it's still got
medicinal qualities applesauce still has
Med medicinal qualities I go so it was
this tart you go okay you had probably
like a half an apple in that tart the
rest was batter you know bread
gluten-free bread and probably regular
sugar probably canola oil you know
because canola oil is bad and um and
regular sugar like table Sugar's bad and
and and so and and this person was like
yeah I guess you're right I I just first
I was really excited it was an apple
tart it I was all Apple I go look look
I'm not trying to pick on you but we got
to get an Apple in you every day and
maybe two apples a day because you got a
liver problem and you got inflammation
caused by you know pathogens and other
things going on in the body you got to
get two apples in a day because that's
when it starts to happen that's when the
magic starts to happen it's the numbers
it's the numbers and that's why someone
said to me another time and said well
you don't like you know animal products
like that's not about it it's not what
it is has nothing to do with that it's
about what food that's going to help the
person the most for what condition they
have so if that means minimizing animal
products because you need room for two
apples three apples a day to clean up
your liver does that mean I hate
something no it just means I'm telling
you what you need to do because I I got
your back on this and I'm telling you
what you need to do and get you to where
you need to be and so and they're like
okay okay that makes sense I didn't
think about it that way so anyway back
to this other person he said look we got
to do better than this apple tart I mean
a jar of applesauce would be better than
that apple tart so the bottom line is
you know we're told to eat are fruits
and vegetables but we're not really
eating our fruits and vegetables and
it's not our fault it's not your fault
it's not my fault if I can't get enough
vegetables in one day cuz I'm running
around like a you know a crazy person
because I got so much on my plate or I'm
traveling or something and I can't get
enough vegetables it's not I mean it's
not our fault we do the best we can but
we but but what we have to do is we just
have to be more mindful about what when
we're eating what we're eating and some
people they just hate that and I totally
get it they're just like I don't want to
know what I'm eating I talk to people
and some people go I don't want to know
what I'm eating I don't care what I'm
eating I just you know it's just I got
busy life I got a busy life I just you
know if I can get a good meal here and
there I'll get a good meal here and
there and and that's all I could tell
you Anthony and that's so some people do
that and I respect that I respect that
because Planet stress did I say Planet
stress sorry about that you guys planet
Earth I do that sometimes and I and I
apologize planet Earth you you know
there's a lot it's a it's a challenge on
here it's a challenge on this ball
that's just rolling around that's
spinning around and you know and I get
it if you got to just grab food to food
to eat and just you got you can't you
you're trying to take care of your
family and you're running around and you
got things going on I respect that I got
respect for anything you got to do in
your life okay and anything you've gone
through okay and that's one thing that I
have and um because you have to have
have that you have to have that I talk
to people and they don't even they they
just don't understand uh what someone
else is going through and and it's sad
because you know when you try to tell
them you got to go look this person's
going through a lot and they go well I
you know what that's not my life that's
their life they caused that I go no
that's not true they didn't cause it and
they're going through a lot and we got
to respect that and it's critical to to
respect that so if you can't get the
fruits and vegetables in every day that
you can't we take one day at a time we
get what we can get in you just
one or two things a day one thing a day
and if you're really sick and you got
and you and listen and you can apply
yourself and do more and more we get you
there faster we get you healing faster
we get you healing your chronic illness
faster because it's about chronic
illness
today and that's what it's about it's
really
important and so yeah I mean this is so
critical it really is all of this
information we're going to cover today
so fasten the seat belts we're going to
get there see one thing I got to tell
you guys one thing one thing about um
belief systems let's talk about belief
systems a little bit it might seem kind
of annoying but it's it's good to it's
good to talk about that I think it's
good to get get that in in there belief
systems are interesting because you know
we can we can get a hobby we could wake
up in the morning get a hobby and I mean
I got hobbies and and boom and just and
all of a sudden we can be an expert at
something we can be an expert at
something okay and and that's totally
cool and there's nothing wrong with that
you know I mean it's it just it can
happen we wake up in the morning we get
a passion for something we say you know
what this is what I want to do and we
become that expert about and it becomes
a hobby and then it goes from a hobby to
you know to all of a sudden now you're
now we're an expert we're at this
expertise level and it's amazing and and
I see that all kind kind of things in
life of all the things we do creative
things and I love it all it's incredible
and I try to do that too I try to you
know have passion for something and I
get interested in something and and you
know next thing you know it I'm like
researching something meaning like you
know what whatever it could be you know
when I was young it would be like model
planes model airplanes and I would know
all the different kinds of airplanes and
stuff and it it would be like you know
it's that kind of thing A friend of mine
is um a sports expert and he's just like
Rambles off and rattles off uh batting
averages and everything else and he said
you he said at first you know he just
got into it it was just kind of a hobby
he caught a couple of games couple of
football games couple of baseball games
couple of soccer games and and then he
says you know it was just like a Pastime
little hobby a past time was a little
bit of a passion and he said he got
really into it and now he's like an
expert he he went from one point of it
to hey you know he can ramble off
everything strategies that you know uh
sports teams use you name it in this
stuff just spins my head cuz I I don't
know anything about that so so you know
but but he be he you know became this
expert at it and then then a belief
system gets built up within it so a
belief system gets built up within it
and it's like it's there you know it
it's just they can't penetrate that
belief system so when I say to them now
you know I'll say look is is is this
team better than this team because they
got this going on and go like no no no
that's not possible I'll be like why
like no no it's not possible because of
this this this and this I said well okay
you got a strong belief system on that
he says well maybe I do maybe you're
right maybe I got to look at the other
team and see what they got going on
better and so what happens is we fall
into these belief systems we come we
become experts we get a passion to start
with and then bam we got a powerful
belief system Spirit told me when I was
young to not hold the belief system when
it comes to one thing okay when when it
comes to one thing okay because I had a
belief system when I was 11 years old I
like these model airplanes and you know
and I I got interested because of a
friend and you know and the friend had
him and I was like whoa this is really
cool you got all these different planes
this is really cool I get it and so it
was getting interested in it and it was
building a belief system to all about it
and spirit said that's fine you can have
a belief system about certain things but
one thing you can't have have one in I
said what is it and spirit said you
can't have a belief system in health you
can't have a belief system in health in
health I said really what does that mean
I was in shock when I was young and
spirit was telling me this and I was
like okay you know you know Spirit
you're going to give me OCD on this what
do you mean you're going to have to
explain this because I believe in health
I believe in healing I believe in
anything health related what do you mean
I shouldn't have a belief system in
health and spirit said you have to keep
open
because all the modalities have
something to
offer all the diets have something to
offer but you can't have a belief system
to just one thing because there's never
just one thing wrong with all of us and
there's never just one thing that fixes
all of us us and there's never just one
belief in health or one modality only or
one thing in health only that can help
us and spirit said you can't have a
belief system in one type of diet one
type of
diet and you can't have and the spirit
was teaching me this I was like whoa
okay okay I I know I I know what you're
saying because spirit said that the
experts behind their one belief
system will tell
you that kale is bad for your
thyroid when they're wrong and kale is
good for your
thyroid okay because and here's here's
how it goes the experts don't know that
Epstein bar causes Hashimoto thyroiditis
in until I released medical medium book
and now they're starting to pick up on
that they're not giving me credit but
that doesn't matter who cares but the
point is is at least the information's
getting out there but kale okay kale
kills off Epstein bar virus in the
thyroid it kills the Epstein bar virus
in the
thyroid so meanwhile the food experts
the belief system experts think that
kale is you know goitrogenic compounds
in there hurts your thyroid you can't
eat it so they tell you don't eat it and
then it becomes a belief system and then
you're stuck you can't eat anything in
that family you can't eat the broccoli
you can't eat the cauliflower right you
guys heard about this right gorog genic
compounds hurting your thyroid you can't
eat kale you can't eat you know collar
greens you can't eat broccoli rob you
can't eat kale sprouts you can't eat bok
choy you can't eat anything okay you
can't eat radishes you can't eat
anything and even some other Foods
they've even added foods to the list now
that they think are that that they think
messing around with the thyroid and so
they got other Foods in the list now and
it becomes a belief system and guess
what it becomes poisonous meaning the
belief system is poisonous and guess who
it hurts it hurts us our children their
children their children and their
children keeps on going we can go 100
years from this with this bad belief
system so we can go 100 years and this
is just one bad belief system okay see
how it works and spirit taught me when I
was young and said look you know you got
to understand this belief system thing
you know you got to you got to you got
to know this and and I said okay you
know what all right fine and spirit said
okay you want to have a belief system
for something else you want to have a
belief system for anything else that's
going
on fine but not in this field not in
this field not in alternative medicine
not in health not in the well-being of
others okay I said so I said to Spirit
can I have just one belief system in
health and spirit said what would that
be I said cuz I have one in Mind and
Spirit said what would that be Anthony
and I said I believe that everybody can
heal and I can
believe that that not only that they can
heal but they can rise above rise out of
it move forward with their
life and and get better and reclaim
their life back and get their life back
spirit said I like that belief system so
I kind of was trying to one up Spirit
there spirit said that's great okay but
the bottom line is you guys you got your
bottom line is when it comes down to
meaning like a protocol or a not a
protocol but like a exactly like a a
regime the problem is when it comes down
to chronic illness and we're talking
about the Holy four fruits and
vegetables herbs and
spices okay wild Foods we're talking
about those the holy four that helps get
rid of the unforgiving four that I talk
about in life- changing Foods when it
comes down to those there's going to be
Foods in this Foods in this holy for
like
kale that actually cleans up your
thyroid and helps you recover from
hypothyroidism and
Hashimoto and other thyroid conditions
and thyroid disease
and the belief system that experts are
actually creating right now which is you
don't eat kale for your thyroid is
detrimental you'll even see it now
unlike shows on TV you'll see it
anywhere now it's it's really getting
out of control and that's a poisonous
belief system so we have to be cautious
about that it's really important now
here's where it goes wrong experts in
health don't know what causes a th thid
problem until of course you know we we
published medical medium but they they
didn't know was wrong with the thyroid
problem so to offer to offer information
and say that kale will hurt your thyroid
when they don't even know what causes a
thyroid problem is where it all goes
wrong and so that's why we're here today
that's why we're here today to do this
and make sure the information is right
make sure that you have everything you
can to heal everything in your hands all
that you need and that that's what it's
about this is just one example of what
I'm trying to talk about now I talk
about the 880,000 meals I I know broken
record broken record just say it um I
probably sound like a broken record
right there I could take it I could take
it you can tell me okay but the 80,000
meals that I talk about all the time in
a lifetime if we didn't eat enough meals
because in a whole lifetime we might
have close to 80,000 meals 990,000 meals
70,000 meals depending on what's going
on depending on what's Happening and So
within those average meals of an average
lifetime let's just say we have to make
sure that some of these meals start
getting better so if we did half our
life and 40,000 meals were up subpar
they just weren't that great they were
you know um many of them were bad many
of them were processed foods many of
them were poisonous many of them were
over fatty foods fried foods you know
all the stuff that you know that isn't
great right
and so if half of that
lifetime was that then we got some
making up to do and that's what I like
about the Holy four because we got to
start making up our meals and that's the
plan too and you can go far with that
you can do some serious makeup serious
makeup and really move forward with that
so one thing to understand too which is
really great is all the different body
systems we have a lot of different body
systems you got the endocrine system
lymphatic system okay neurological
system reproductive system it goes on
and on and on there's more than that so
within all the different body systems
that we have okay they do different
things and they need different things so
we need some varieties so we need some
varieties in our Foods so when I was
talking about you talking to that person
about the apples the apple and the apple
tart and everything I go were you eating
enough fruits and
vegetables and the person said are you
going to try to take away my animal
proteins I said it you know what it's
not about that are you eating enough
fruits and vegetables is there enough
room for fruits and
vegetables that that's what I just want
to know well yeah you know I had a bagel
this morning and I had some jelly on the
bagel that that was pretty good and then
you know after that um you know I had
coffee and the coffee yeah had half and
half in it and
then let's see I had the apple tart and
that was you know kind of like a lunch
kind of thing I go well that was all you
had for lunch I said no no I had a
turkey sandwich before the apple tart I
said okay and then it it keeps on going
on and I'm like you know what there's
just no room there's no room to put
anything in there that you need the
things that you need the fruits and
vegetables you need and the holy
four and that's what we're talking about
today think about in your your food
regime and this doesn't mean you have to
feel bad let me tell you something life
gets crazy it gets busy we get habits
habits are developed because we we just
they just happen it happen because we
got so much on our plate and we're just
doing what we got to do but think about
you know where's the fruits and
vegetables where's the herbs and spices
you know where is the wild food that
might be in your plate if you're doing
the wild blueberries the Frozen wild
blueberries one a day that's your wild
food and by the way that's a fruit too
of course and a wild food so you got
something going on there you got
something going on there right there
it's the it's the Frozen wild
blueberries recently too I was talking
to a couple of people and they were like
you know I don't get the wild blueberry
part I just like the you know the
blueberries they're aren't they all the
same it's blueberries they're not the
same the cultivated blueberry and the
Half Pint clamshell at the supermarket
in the produce section is a very weak
food even though it's a good food for
you don't get me wrong if that's all you
got you better eat those regular
cultivated blueberries but it's a weak
food compared to the Frozen wild
blueberry right down the aisle and
that's make that makes up that makes up
for all the processed food meals you
might have eaten it starts to make it up
when you have that Frozen wild
blueberry every day and that stuff is
pulling out those blueberries have
antioxidants phytochemicals that are
pulling out toxic heavy metals out of
your brain so you don't get Alzheimer's
disease so you don't get Parkinson's
disease so you don't get dementia so you
don't get memory
loss okay so you don't get brain tumors
so you don't get you know um so you
don't get cancers in the brain so you
don't get tumors in the brain so you
don't get you know you know adenomas in
the brain you know pituitary cysts and
when you're doing those wild blueberries
Frozen wild blueberries you're making up
for years and years of processed food
and or just poor quality quity food or
food that just didn't have any real high
nutrient value say it's not processed
say it's home-cooked meals say it's very
good wholesome whole homecooked meals
but it's the same thing it's chicken
every night for 30 years I'm not saying
you know chicken's the worst thing in
the world I'm saying that it doesn't
have a lot of nutrients to make up for
the loss of all the nutrients so we need
to make room for more of that you know
and I got this feeling that's that's
pretty much what happened with the Paleo
movement the Paleo movement was just
just just butter tons of butter tons of
pork tons of bacon and there's still
some of that out there and you know tons
of chicken tons of turkey and tons of
meat and the Paleo movement's now moving
to lots of fruits and vegetables with
lower amounts of meat and I was talking
to a Paleo expert recently and I said
well why are you doing that and I said
because we're seeing people get better
more and I said so what did you see in
the past and this paleo expert said to
said to me well I saw in the past 5
years ago when I got into the Paleo
movement when I got into it 5 years ago
I was all excited because it took away
processed foods this is a really a
really unknown paleo expert actually and
he he was being honest with me and he
was saying look when I got into it
Anthony it was like I got into I got
into it because it took away gluten and
it took away processed foods and then it
took away the grain thing where all the
grains and all that
and I started seeing people improve so I
would make sure they were having an egg
you know butter and you know butter in
the coffee in the morning eggs you know
eggs that whole thing and you know
whatever milk you know whole milk and
and then they said well then we took out
Dairy a year later and saw more
improvements so we just put them on pork
you know once a day meat for dinner you
know um pork in the morning chicken for
lunch meat for dinner had a few
vegetables in between and because we
took them off of all their their heavy
grains and we took them off of all their
sugar and processed foods we were seeing
some improvements but then we got kind
of stagnant with it all I said what do
you mean by stagnant tell me what are
you talking about and and this paleo
expert said well you know people just
weren't getting people with chronic
illness the kind of people Anthony that
you see every day and you saw all these
years they just weren't getting as good
as we wanted them to get so we added
more vegetables and we noticed they were
starting to improve and then a year
later we noticed they're improving more
3 years later we started bringing green
juices in so now the Paleo movement's
all with all these green juices so
everybody's Downing these green juices
which is amazing a miracle and then he
said we brought and then we noticed we
can get people better even more with
certain green juice with just regular
green juices and more vegetables and
more vegetables so now we got you know
the pale movements divided right now see
guys it's actually divided it's crazy
it's like how many divides can we have
it's actually unbelievable so now I was
talking to this you know this this this
paleo expert and he was telling me now
he said well you now it's like now yeah
it's divided it's now it's this pale
movement where it's just you know some
nuts and seeds and some avocado and some
some vegetables and then a handful of
berries and and then a piece of meat and
then the other side of the py movement's
all pissed off at them now you know the
people who just haven't caught up to
that and they're like and that's what he
was telling me he was telling me they're
they're pissed off cuz they haven't
caught up to it I was like well tell me
about it and he saidwell they're still
on the whole pork for breakfast thing'
you know pork for breakfast thing so you
know you don't do the fruit in the
morning you do you don't do the berries
in the morning you do you know the pork
for breakfast thing and they're they're
totally into that and then you do do you
know one salad a day and and then you do
the chicken and he said so it's dividing
it's dividing and he and I said why do
you think it that way he says because
they're not as experienc they just don't
know that it takes more fruits and
vegetables more vegetables um to
actually heal someone so I was like you
know what everything you're telling me
is is is is is amazing because that's
say oh that's that's how it's happening
he said yeah so now what we're doing is
he said Anthony now we're doing to get
the best results out of people we're
doing more fruits of vegetables we
minimizing animal proteins kind of like
what you recommend a lot and I said
that's incredible that's incredible and
the reason why it moved to that degree
you guys folks it moved to that degree
because fruits and vegetables are the
holy four they're the holy four that's
what it is why do I say holy well well
first of all the the wild blueberry is
like the Jesus Christ food it's a
resurrection food can literally help you
rise out of the ashes literally
emotionally physically mentally can help
you rise out of the ashes so that's why
it's a holy food and you know and and so
many of the other foods have these
qualities let's talk about some of these
Foods this is just so fun
today so let's talk about let's talk
about some of these Foods let's talk
about raw honey raw honey don't be
afraid of raw honey you know know
there's this big debate out there it's
all sugar it's too it's sugar no it's
sugar it's glucose it's sugar it's
fructose and glucose it's with
200,000 phytochemical
compounds gathered and I talked about
this one time before gathered by bees
from species plant species all over the
place wild
species wild flowers
a wildf flower that we can't even eat
meaning an herbal specimen we can't even
eat because it's got too many alkaloids
or it might it might be too toxic
because there's all these different
herbs out there that you can't eat you
know when when you know when I do this
wild foraging with spirit and spirit and
I go out into the you know out into the
bush and we go looking for things and I
say to Spirit what's this I say to
Spirit what's this herb what's this bush
I say to Spirit what's this tree and
spirit tells me what everything thing is
is this edible is this not edible is
this mushroom edible is it not edible
you know the whole bit if I go through
go go into the woods or go into the bush
or going to you know or going to a field
I asked spirit and that the spirit's
been training me my whole life and um
spirit will say that's a beautiful Wild
Flower yes and you can't eat it you
can't use that herb that herb is
actually toxic but a bee can land on
that flower and take miracle miracle
medicine out of that flower you guys
this is what Spirit would tell me can
take a miracle me medicine thousands of
compounds that can't even be studied by
research and science can't even be
studied it would take 500 years for them
to know how many chemical compounds are
in the in that flower that nectar of
that flower right there that that be he
just took back to the nest to make
honey okay and then add that to other
wild
flowers that are edible and non-edible
or usable and non-usable by medicine add
that to other ones and the amount of and
what happens is is that phytochemical
and that flower in that one species of
herb that we can't use the
phytochemicals in there we can use them
the B takes those
phytochemicals homeopathically right
from that flower something we can't do
in science the bee does the lab work for
us takes it back to the nest and
transfers it into something usable for
us that's a miracle cancer fighting
disease fighting chronic illness
fighting over 200,000 chemicals
phytochemicals that's just the Baseline
there are more I'm just talking about
the Baseline the reason why I put
200,000 chemicals in the life-changing
Foods book is because that's the
powerful Foundation of how many
chemicals are in there exactly that's
the that's the powerful one it's a
little over 200,000 but there's more
that won't even be on science's radar
for a thousand years and seriously here
and that's raw honey so are we going to
ignore the raw honey I mean it's it it
can it can stop cancer from growing it
can help us in all kinds of levels it it
has enzymes that are not listed anywhere
or just C discovered anywhere enzymes
that help us heal and grow so that's raw
honey all on its own it's it's not only
just loaded with all the minerals
calcium potassium zinc selenium
phosphorus chromium miminum manganese it
can go on and on on it's not even just
loaded with those it's loaded with co-
minerals like Co
microminerals that help us to stay alive
that's just honey alone so let's move on
to nettle Leaf nettle Leaf the herb
let's move on to that one you know I
talk about the unforgiving four there's
radiation that's in the air falling out
of the sky from just Fukushima there's
radiation falling out of the sky from
going back from World War II there's
radiation just in general that we're
exposed to at the dental office we get
an x-ray cuz we bump our butt or we bump
our leg or knee we get an x-r whatever
it is there's radiation it's everywhere
we flying planes where all the radiation
is it's up there so let's get it out of
our bodies let's get it out of our
bodies and the net Leaf does that it
helps us it pulls out it's an
anti-radiation wild food you can get
natal leaf tea okay okay so check this
out you guys say you don't have time for
fruits and vegetables say you don't have
time for fruits and vegetables you just
got to eat whatever it is to survive I
respect that I'm on your side I stand
behind you 100% right there okay I'm not
the food police I support you because I
know what life's like and I know what
it's like to be sick in the world cuz
I've seen it I've seen it my whole life
since I was a kid watching it it I know
and I could feel it I could feel it and
with all that I know it you know you
might have a lot going on in your plate
so if you can't get a lot of fruits and
vegetables in you I stand behind you
100% if all you can get in you is one
piece of bacon well let's me forget the
bacon if all you get you is just you
know a few beans and a piece of chicken
or a piece of turkey and a piece of
salmon and that's all you can get in you
then fine I stand behind you but let's
do this let's get nettle Leaf Tea in you
let's get nettle Leaf Tea in you nettle
leaf tea just nice big cup of nettle
leaf tea it builds up the bones it
builds up the bones it's bone protecting
it's bone building osteoporosis
osteopenia it's bone fixing it's so high
in silica Nal leaf and over 40 trace
minerals that are bioactive bioavailable
they go into the bones you won't hear
this in other places you're only going
to hear it on the show and in this book
life-changing foods but the point is is
that that's what it Harbors it Harbors
that silica those bioavailable
simulatable states of
minerals and it has even pain reliever
phytochemicals for pain relief in Nettle
anti-inflammatory medicine in Nettle so
that's what I'm talking about
there let's try to get through this
sweet potatoes you guys like sweet
potatoes everybody anybody raise their
hand who likes sweet potatoes raise
raise your hand okay you like sweet
potatoes awesome awesome I'm glad sweet
potatoes are powerful a really powerful
food okay this is what I like about this
it
promotes productive bacteria in the
stomach when you eat sweet potato what
that does is it has phytochemicals that
purposely promote productive bacteria
and the natural sugars in a sweet potato
which are saturated with you know
anti-cancerous properties those natural
sugars they only are designed to
stimulate productive bacteria good
bacteria in the gut bad bacteria
dies when it tries to feed on sweet
potato so sibo people with sibo with all
that strep of cacus I talk about in
their gut strep is what's behind sibo by
the way and no one talks about that
you're only going to hear that here so
anybody who just turned you know like if
this is the first time you turned on the
show I have to say that so you don't
think that that information is just
everywhere because it's not but strepa
cacus anti antibiotic resistant strepa
cacus is responsible for
sibo and that when it tries to feed off
of sweet potato it
dies it dies or it retards or it falls
back okay and and that's what happens
it's the power of sweet potato that's
why sweet potatoes help with meacon too
they help you know knocking down
SEI they help knock down H pylori sweet
potatoes help kill H
pylori and the thing is H pylori feeds
off of eggs and it feeds off of dairy
products milk cheese and butter if you
take out milk cheese and butter and you
take out egg and so you someone will say
to me they'll be like I have eggs once a
month I go well you're feeding your
hpylori once a month and it might be all
the H pylori needs just alive but if you
take out the eggs you take out the dairy
and then you and then you bring the
sweet potato in you're killing off your
H pylori how about them apples how about
those apples so seriously helps with
crohn's help with colitis the power of
sweet potatoes
amazing let's shoot to
radishes radishes they're kind of tough
to eat right cuz you know they're
they're they got to they got to
sulfur Rich taste and they're kind of
tough to eat in that way but they're
medicine radishes are medicine don't
ignore them go to the supermarket if
there's one thing to try so say you're
on a budget and you can only get so many
foods for your family you only got so
much money and financially in the budget
and you can't get you can only get so
many things and so there's maybe
something you can't break into yet
you're like well I can't really start
getting that food it's too much money in
the budget I got to just worry about
this other stuff try to just grab one
thing grab
radishes just grab radishes cuz radishes
protect us from heart disease protect us
from heart attack protect us from heart
problems viral conditions that cause
heart disease that are not on the radar
of of modern medicine or research and
science that Spirit knows about you name
it cardiovascular
issues um cholesterol problems bad
cholesterol you want to help start
lowering bad cholesterol you bring
radishes in and if you bring radishes in
every day that's when the magic starts
to happen you bring them in every day
and you start knocking down bad
cholesterol radishes bring back the
liver liver problems cause high
cholesterol and elevated blood pressure
radishes help clean that up here's the
best part of radishes I like you know
how there's all this Prebiotic talk you
know what foods are prebiotics and so
forth radishes are the most powerful
Prebiotic there is most powerful
Prebiotic in the gut there is is radish
it's one of the most powerful it's right
on the top of the list actually it's
actually the radishes are the second
most powerful Prebiotic there is next to
Wild blueberry which is the first most
powerful Prebiotic in existence the
Frozen wild blueberry is the most
powerful Prebiotic in existence and then
the radishes are
second and so and then radish greens
they got phyto chemicals cancer fighting
alkaloids that fight cancers so that's
what that's what these greens have get
the ones with the fresh greens cuz you
want to wash those greens give them a
little rinse and you want to actually
have those in your salad they have
antiviral properties they knock down
viruses and that's a big deal that's a
really big deal so that's
radishes we got little time left we got
to get through this leafy greens bring
them in very important leafy greens if
you think you have a hard time digesting
digesting leafy greens you really don't
you're you're digesting them fine you
just feel them that means you have
sensitivities you have you have
sensitive nerves in the gut or the
intestinal tract and you're feeling the
roughage of the leafy green move on down
but you are digesting it I promise you
that so if you don't like the way that
feels if you have if you're sensitive
like that then eat a little bit of leafy
green some people can eat tons of them
they have less you know less you know
nerves are less sensitive cuz they're
not chronically feeling you know too
many nerve problems I know people that
have anxiety or sensitive nerves in
their tummy and they're inflamed they
tend to try to eat mush and only kind of
like cooked mush and like just oatmeal
and stuff because it or eggs and oatmeal
and cheese and all that so they don't
feel it rub their intestinal lining you
know what you what so what happens is
when you eat a green a lettuce it's
rubbing the Linings of the intestinal
tract to clean out eoli and clean out
strep and seff and all and staff and all
bad you know and other things that we
worry about worms and you know and
different parasites people are concerned
about out there you know it pulls all
that out um very important to understand
celery
juice celery juice celery has a
bioactive sodium okay it contains
co-actor microtrace mineral
salts all right yet discovered by
science and research these are different
varieties of sodiums in celery they just
haven't been able to literally in the
lab figure out the different
compositions that that that are actually
in celery the different sodium salts
this is why it fixes digestive problems
it raises hydrochloric acid fixes the
liver heals the liver changes people's
guts around completely Crohn's colitis
IBS all kinds of irritable bowel issues
you name it celery juice is a miracle
food and it's one of the Holy four it's
one of the foods in the Holy four group
and we can get that in there people are
changing their lives with the celery
juice you know what I heard which is
really funny Whole Foods Whole Foods has
changed their system to offer just
celery juice so when you walk in they
don't think you have 10 heads when you
ask for straight celery that happened
because of you guys because you took the
information from the medical beeting
book from Spirit and you're out there
and you're asking your juice places to
juice celery and it's changing the
environment out there and God bless you
I swear to God that is just mindblowing
to me because it means that you're
getting spirit's information out there
for me and I am indebted to you I am
indebted to you and just know that
please know that all my heart and and
all my soul cuz I'm just I'm just blown
away by that let's hit asparagus before
we got to go asparagus right everybody's
looking for the Fountain of Youth
they're looking to get young again
everybody wants to that Fountain of
Youth and get young again will asparagus
keep us young there's an energy in
asparagus when it's sprouting out of the
earth it has power in it power to make
it into a tree because asparagus turns
into like a shrub a small shrub tree
like thing when it gets to grow and it
grows all tall and big and what happens
is when it's cut short like that that
it's harboring a power in it to bring
back our youth bringing back our kidneys
bringing back our liver reversing
disease reversing aging all from
asparagus it can fix neurological
disorders help promote the healing of
neurological disorders Spirits are that
spir spus are that powerful hey hey
Angelic Spirits are that powerful too we
got to call upon the
Angels okay we're going to hit
dates we're going to dates don't be
afraid of the sugar and dates dates
eliminate literally almost every bug
that exists in the intestinal tract they
don't feed bugs they get rid of it if
there's an overgrowth a Candida
someone's concerned about dates lower
the overgrowth so that you have the
candida you're supposed to have which
keeps Us Alive by the way you don't want
to get rid of all your candida cuz we
will die if we get rid of all our
candida you have to keep some of it
there so dates actually and you heard
you heard me talk about that somewhere
else in one of the other shows so if you
ever want to you know just look at the
candida chapter in the in the mm book
too the medical medium book the dates
literally help get rid of all these
poisons too they grab onto poisons
dragging them out of the body high in
potassium for neurotransmitters as well
dates help restore neurotransmitters so
when people are depressed because of
Epstein bar or people are depressed
because of toxic heavy metals and their
neurotransmitters are d down and out
dates bring them back because of the
trace the 70 trace minerals and
potassium help bring that back maybe we
can hit one more the good old Apple
let's hit the
Apple okay never underestimate the power
of the Apple it is one of the most
powerful
anti-inflammatory we're talking about in
sephtis which is brain inflammation
we're talking about irritable bowel
intestinal problems you know we're
talking about viral infection that cause
all the inflammation we talk about
apples are medicine do not we cannot
deny the power of the Apple it's the
ultimate colon cleanser pectin removes
and collects en rid your bodies of
microbes and bacteria viruses yeast mold
it gathers and expels and putrified
material from old protein stuck on the
sides of the impacted on the sides of
the intestinal tract apples get rid of
it and apples get rid of sibo knocking
down strep
and they're loaded with manganese and
mbum you can't avoid apples my friends
they
can't couple of other ones we don't have
time to explain so much but
cilantro don't be afraid of cilantro you
know that taste when people feel like
they they they have a genetic resistance
against cilantro they don't have a
genetic problem that's not what it is
that's not why they don't like the taste
so understand that that's not why it's
just that when you eat cilantro and
you're really toxic it can really taste
bad if you eat cilantro and and you're
really toxic like if you're really
intoxicated and you got tons of heavy
metals and other kinds of pesticides in
your in your liver and in your gut and
you get all these different you know
from alahh and everything else and you
eat cilantro it's going to start pulling
it out and you're going to start tasting
something weird the minute you even
touch the cilantro listen you
guys I believe in you I stand behind you
I love you dearly you know and all the
work you're doing even if it's one thing
in your life right now I love you for
that and I'm honored I didn't get this
gift for me it wasn't given for me
Spirit made that clear when I was young
and said this gift isn't for you it's
for everybody else so they can get the
ability to heal and that's what we have
to do here and that's why I'm here I
believe in you I love you I stand behind
you 100% please know that you're a
blessing patch yourself on the back have
some compassion for yourself you deserve
it I love you dearly