hello day seven of the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
and we're making some potato waffles
voila here we go
so let me just start getting the potato
waffles at least going a little bit
before we run into the topic of food
fear
we're going to talk about some cool
things with that
but I have to tell you guys I let my
Stones go
it was hard but I did it
how many of you have let your Stones go
today or is it going to be this I got
this feeling many of you are going to
wait
a long time today
till the end of the day before you let
go of your stones
so are you guys like or did you let go
of your Stones yet did it happen
so I'm just wearing not yet High not yet
uh oh you guys are holding on to your
Stones today's day seven
oh crispy perspective says I'm going to
wait oh no
um we have to let the stones go today we
have to
we really do Kim says I'm still crying
with them you don't want to let them go
I let mine go and nobody let theirs go
so I you know
telling my Stones don't worry
everybody's gonna let their Stones go
today not to worry you're not going to
be the only ones that are gonna go oh
don't worry we're gonna have to let them
know
here we go everybody's gonna let them go
and nobody let them go no right all
right
it's an emotional day I thought I would
make potato waffles
talking about food fear as well
so what I have right here are steamed
potatoes these are steamed potatoes I'm
just taking the skins off not because
you can't eat potato skins that's not it
we do not fear
potato skins nor do we fear
potatoes
okay
Park
I hear something
I hear a potato waffle machine going
beep beep which means we're pretty much
ready
all right let me just
get some of these skins off of here
have you guys ever had potato waffles
this is going to be fun so can I put
this in here
and I'll grab another potato they all
look good they're all steamed potatoes
please do not fear a potato
because of all the misinformation that's
out there
lots of misinformation everywhere
we're going to talk about food fear a
little bit
everybody coming on there did you
release your Stones today or is
everybody holding on to your stones
Gina said hey W I let my Stones go in
the river about an hour ago
whoa
wow
show me Tuesday 144 says on YouTube I
released my stone so you did release
them
[Music]
Glenda says I'm waiting until tonight
how does it feel
Barbara says yep my plan is to release
them at sunset
yeah I figured I released mine early I
did
I did
I felt like if if I didn't I may never
let them go I felt like if I didn't do
it I mean never
let them go
but I did it
and I gotta tell you it's not easy I'm
trying to kind of like I'm trying to
keep like
whew
but it was it was really an incredible
experience
day seven it is I just saw that listen
I'm making potato waffles we're talking
about food fear
how many of you
have
been told to avoid something
when you go to a nutritionist dietitian
when you go to somebody a health coach
nutritionist dietitian trainer
naturopath doctor any kind of medical
doctor chiropractor whatever you go to
have did you just walk in
and they're like eat whatever you want
sure there might be some old MDS of the
past but even they were like try not to
eat too much red meat 30 years ago but
still how many were like oh yeah no you
shouldn't go and eat whatever you want
you shouldn't be eating at fast food
restaurants every single day you should
be careful or you should avoid this this
and this and this right avoid processed
foods avoid fried greasy Foods avoid
this food avoid there's rules everywhere
rules everywhere does it matter who you
go to who you see what nutritionist what
dietitian what PhD what doctor what
naturopath what acupuncturist with
chiropractor what whatever doesn't
matter who where what how there's going
to be rules there's gonna be don't do
this don't do that don't do this you go
to a functional medicine doctor and
they're just going to be like a nurse
practitioner at the functional medicine
doctor's office is you're gonna be okay
let's sit down Mrs Jones
let's take a look at everything here we
got a whole list of foods to avoid a
whole list of things you should do with
your foods and eating and a whole plan
here and here's 50 000 bad supplements
with with gelatin in it and all kinds of
garbage and fish oil and all this crap
here Miss Jones here's your big list of
foods to actually avoid and here's your
piles of fish oil supplements and every
other crap under the sun
you guys does it sound familiar at all
on any level just kind of curious
all right let's get some uh waffles
going let me do one more
I mean I even see you know medical
medium haters out there and stuff
they'll be like oh yeah he's just you
know
he's got you know too much restrictions
or too much this really because mm info
brought the carb thing back
where you can have carbs what about all
that torture no one allowed carbs
anywhere no carbs anywhere
fruit is back because of medical medium
information
but here's what's funny oh don't do
medical media
need check out medical medium check out
this nutritionist guy on social check
out this PhD guy he's got all the right
things to do and whatever and then you
check out that guy and that guy's like
make sure your your beef is never USDA
make sure your beef is grass-fed make
sure your chicken is pasture raised make
sure that you have raw milk not regular
milk it's like what I thought there were
no rolls I left medical medium to come
to this guy here and I thought I was
going to come to this guy and there'd be
no rules we just eat what we want no
everybody's got the rule book out
but what you'll hear is don't eat too
many fruits don't eat the dirty dozen
don't have vegetables because of the
dirty dozen so many rolls it's
everywhere am I right look out for the
dirty dozen don't eat any fruits look
out for sugar look out for this you can
go to anybody you want I see that out
there I see people out there like oh
yeah the haters out there the naysayers
the medical medium they'll be like don't
listen to Medical medium he's dangerous
he's bad but hey go to this guy he's a
PhD nutritionist guy on social check him
out you check him out and he's like got
a 50 000 rule book
talk about food fear it's like food fear
times a hundred it's like food fear it's
like make sure your meat is this make
sure your chicken is dish make sure you
do this make sure you do well watered
chicken that was raised on well water
make sure your eggs are this kind of
eggs make sure you look out for the
dirty dozen and by the way I'm going to
a fast food restaurant with my family
tomorrow because why not you can have
all the cheat days you want
yeah I'm gonna listen to that guy when
it comes down to chronic illness when it
comes down to chronic illness you can't
mess around you have to know what's up
and then they'll say oh moderation and
balance that's the way to go and I'm
such a smart PhD nutritionist guy and
I'm such a smart yeah
um oh you're gonna have grass-fed you're
going to have beef make sure it's
grass-fed because I'm such a smart
nutritionist PhD guy and by the way I'm
gonna go pull into this restaurant here
and order a healthier option at this
restaurant with my family let me go do
that oh it's about balance in moderation
meanwhile the guy just wants a treat
he's going into the restaurant to get a
treat not even thinking about the
chronically ill about how they've tried
everything under the sun the seasoned
people who were chronically sick who
tried all the things and cut out all the
stuff and they needed an answer the
medical medium info has got more people
out of the woods than anywhere else
hands down and still there's people out
there like oh no this guy knows better
here
rides with Milton says I just released
my stones in a river whoa I see a crying
face
that's that's that's powerful though
powerful lumises I met someone from
medical meme Community this morning and
we showed our stones to each other oh
wow T Henderson says over on YouTube
toss the stones in a river felt like the
stones were ready to go
this is just blowing my mind man blowing
my mind for real
Mary C I'm sitting by the river this
place is beautiful my stones will love
their new home and we're going to talk
about that too I want you guys to know I
did prepare a little bit of something
you know about this about releasing the
stones and what this means and what's
happening so this isn't just talking
about food fear I want to go into that a
little bit Jeanette said I'm excited to
let them go
Lori no Noel says on YouTube going to
beach later to say goodbye wow going to
the beach later to say goodbye
that's a big deal it's a really big deal
senso Studio says can I let them go and
visit them once in a while and ask how
they are doing you can indeed at that
time the stones
may have been neutralized so wait till I
tell you this this is going to be
mind-blowing a little bit we'll get into
that neutralized
gen1223 over there in IG what are you
guys talking about stones and River
kidney stones are we talking about
kidney stones you guys we're talking
about the medical medium collecting
Stones meditation Journey where over a
hundred thousand people signed up to the
journey and they chose their three
stones in nature and now it's seven days
later and we're releasing the stones
back into nature and a tremendous amount
of healing has happened with this
meditation it's really powerful that's
what we're talking about
so glad you asked you can still sign up
and see the replay video for 48 hours
indeed
link is in profile link is in the
description don't miss out make sure you
check it out while you can
it's an experience truly an experience
okay let's start getting these waffles
going
let me just get a couple of these things
out there we go
we're going to kind of mash these up a
little bit carefully
good to see you guys we're talking about
food fear
what a brain screw the food fear
you go anywhere you go on Tick Tock
doesn't matter where you are
and everybody's like know this know that
know this know that know this and
everybody's like what no this know that
know this no this no this no this no
Dairy no bud no but no whatever no it's
crazy right
but no they don't get yelled at
manula says alert everyone I was
contacted by an mm imposter last night
he wanted to do a reading and wanted a
donation
oh my God please report that in posture
to report in posture at
medicalmedium.com if you can so it's
report
imposters with an S at
medicalmedium.com please report them
there
all right
we need to report those imposters those
evil imposters
that want to take people's money take
advantage of them say they're me
and they're sick too there's some of
these imposters are absolutely sick
first of all they're all
obviously sick right
like
you know and then on top of it some of
them are really Disturbed really
Disturbed individuals
and then what happens is a couple of
people be like I had a reading with
medical meme this has been happening for
years by the way I had a reading with
medical medium
no
he did not
so what I'm doing is mashing up these
potatoes getting it ready for
potato waffle machine
says aw I hope you did not hit the
turtle
I dare say
foreign
I did not hit the turtle I promise I did
not hit the turtle
I helped Turtles and I saved Turtles
but I definitely didn't hit the turtle
what we're talking about marja what
marja is talking about we're talking
about the video I just released
of me releasing the stones early
this morning
so we're just mashing these up a little
bit more real quick
I think what happens is that
that there's some serious jealous
jealous
jealous people
they're jealous because they see medical
medium out there they're jealous because
they see the books out there when you go
into like Barnes and Nobles
you go into Barnes and Nobles
you see all the medical medium books in
there
and Barnes keeps them in there because
people love the medical medium books
and they people they heal from the
medical medium books and then they tell
somebody else about it and they say go
to Barnes and Noble and people go in to
the store and they get the books out of
Barnes and Noble right but for haters
and naysayers it's really annoying to
have to walk into Barnes and Nobles
like you know like naysayers do and they
do that they go in there and they go
into the health book Department because
they're all interested in health and
they walk down the aisle and it's shoved
right in their face
and they hate it and then they think
they got all this power and their right
their social media channel so they just
use it to be like medical medium is
terrible medical mediums this medical
mediums uh it just eats them up alive
that the books are sitting there in
Barnes and no for years right
okay let's make a waffle
and they're so sick of hearing it
everywhere edible medium celery juice
whatever
so Jeffrey says over there in YouTube I
released my Stones today it was a relief
frankly to let go of those three
emotions they were released into a
fast-moving Mountain Creek
that is incredible
you release them in a fast-moving
Mountain Creek
I wish I was there I wish I was standing
by that Creek with you and I wish I
watched the stones go in to that Creek
that was rolling along I would love to
see that just love to see that Miriam
over there on YouTube where can I
release them if no rivers around no Pond
no Lake no River
um no Waterway no beach if you don't
have any of those options you can
release them in nature a path a trail
toss them into the woods it couldn't be
literally on the side of a road Into the
Woods back into nature where you just
you send them out and they go and
they're in nature getting grounded and
regrounded and neutralized we'll talk
about that in a little bit Tara Edmonton
says nutritionists told me to avoid all
fruit
nutritionists had all these rules
rolls rolls rolls Ellie Anderson said
they told me my son should avoid all
sorts of fruits and veggies such as
lemons celery and mango thank God I
found you very shortly after that
because it was so stressful and scary
and didn't make sense
thank you Allie over there on YouTube
this is the experiences people have out
there and that's says a lot it says a
lot
so what you'll find out there okay that
there's a movement a small movement of
mm haters that's just let's just let's
just call it like it is let's just be
you know straight out about it right and
they're trying to use different tactics
one of the taxes tactics is
um restrictions with medical medium
first of all medical meme information
can be literally just drinking celery
juice and that's all you do and you eat
whatever you're eating that you want to
eat it can also be more than that it can
be the morning cleanse then it can be
the next thing that it can be the next
thing you can do any you can take your
feeling as far as you want to go but the
information is there about how to do it
but what happens is like the haters
they'll be like you know they'll try to
spook people out there and they'll say
he makes you avoid this medical mediums
to you know he too restrictive into this
really
because all you have to be is like a
pregnant woman and walk into your
functional medicine doctor's office and
you will get an ass kicking when you
walk in there no fish no this no that no
this the list like this you walk out of
there with a list this big
you can be somebody that just okay let
me check out this nutritionist dude that
they're talking about or let me check
out this dude over here there's this
dietitian let me go check them out and
you go in there and dietitian is like
make sure you're this make sure it's
pasture raised make sure your eggs are
organic make sure you're this and just
like what what there's a ton of rules oh
stay away from carbs stay away from this
say oh yeah you can have chocolate once
in a while and you can have this once in
a while but stay away from this this and
here's the crazy thing
they don't know why you're sick to begin
with well you got all your neurological
symptoms why you've been sick for 10
years that's what's really funny right
and then glycosate right like the whole
thing with like
um
the whole thing too with pesticides
right
that whole thing too
I've been talking about pesticides for
years years years and they'll say avoid
pesticides right
avoid pesticides because pesticides have
terrible things in them and look it's
out there the whole bit
and they'll do that too and it's like
yeah because here we need to avoid
pesticides you want to go and drink
pesticides do you want to go and drink a
whole bunch of pesticides yeah you got
to avoid it of course you of course you
do unless you just want to live in a
world
where
there's there's words on here you've got
to be careful what you said by the way
on social I'm letting you guys know
there's some words
that are key words
just you don't want to say in Social
there's a reason whether it's it's wired
in and there's a reason and I got enough
I got enough
censorship and everything else through
the roof
so you know what I mean by the pesticide
thing and that word that I stopped
myself from saying God
right you know that word okay that word
by the way is uh that's a trigger word
on social in the engines anyway the
whole point is
is that
um they
of course I mean you can be somebody
that doesn't avoid anything at all
just eat what you want where are you
where are you gonna hear that though
where are you gonna hear that from any
reasonable person eat and do everything
you want
while you're sick
while you're sick and nowadays even when
you're not sick people
professionals aren't saying do what you
want
that's that those days are gone those
days are gone they're in the dust
they're in the past those days
rules rules rules rules everywhere
everywhere everywhere everywhere problem
is though can have all the rules but not
know what's wrong with the person and
why they're really sick and struggling
with their autoimmune and every other
condition they have
and the thing is with mm info it's
healing people around the world and
already has a track record of it because
you find out why you're sick and what's
wrong and then you find out why there is
options choices you can make for this
and choices you can make for this and
what direction you want to go
it's really quite incredible all right
let's get a waffle going here
but I mean seriously it's a real real
head screw
overall the amount of things people are
told to avoid
I think the worst thing I hear is avoid
sugar
and sweets when really it's not the
sugar and the sweet I'm not saying it's
good to eat a whole bunch of table sugar
like you you shouldn't just go and scoff
down a bag of table sugar
you know like that's something you
shouldn't do
all right let's let's get a waffle in
here let's see what size we have
let's hope that pretty much does it
yeah I think we did it
kind of put a little weight on there
but I think the carbs and the sugar
avoid carbs and sugar without really
understanding why and what kind of carbs
you're talking about the reason I talk
about it is because once you start
healing you get attacked by people
they will go out of their way to DM you
and comment and convince you not to do
medical medium and they use these
tactics once you are seasoned enough to
understand what I'm talking about you'll
know what they're doing so the goal is
to DM people that's what the haters are
doing right now they have a full
campaign on all the time
the goal is to DM you or reach out to
you or put posts out there to confuse
people then reach out to them once they
comment and be like yeah
and it's tactics that that are being
used to throw people off of their
healing to throw them off of their game
as they're trying to recover
seasoned people can pick this off and
understand this but unseasoned people
will have to lose another two three
years of their healing process maybe
five years of the healing process
because they've been thrown in a
different direction
people's families or friends also do it
peer pressure happens all the time
because it's no fun to avoid fun Foods
all right so we got some waffles going
that was a big waffle so here we go
scoop that up
great smell
hmm
so good
excited
I got some cayenne pepper here I can't
get enough of my cayenne's out of the
garden so I try to find every single
excuse to use them I think what I'll do
is I'll put a couple on top I've got
some nectarines here actually my slice
some nectarines
put those on top of a waffle got maple
syrup this is a real simple recipe you
can go to town you can do what you want
you can go to town
[Music]
that's right David
it's always somebody watching
so you guys if you just got here this is
day seven of the medical meme collecting
Stones meditation Journey
I promised you you'll never forget this
journey I promise you that you'll never
ever forget it
and
this is a very moving day and a very
emotional day I've released my Stones
today I hope that you got a chance to
release your Stones I know that many
people are waiting probably towards the
end of the day to release their stones
and there may be even a few people that
probably won't release them they should
though it's good to release them today
that would be fantastic
Rhonda Johansson says some people just
can't handle the truth about
Troublemaker Foods that's true too
I think we just lost TT
I smell a waffle a delicious waffle
cooking right now
so let's talk about Road walks it's
something that happens all the time
say you're somebody and you're just
eating complete just standard European
or standard American
that's what you do
you're raised on standard American
you're raised on standard European
because they're both bad
Europeans will tell you they're both bad
and you're raised on that standard
and then you start getting sick
and then you seek help and you go to
just a regular doctor and the doctor
doesn't care about what you're eating
you might find a doctor that just
doesn't care they just want to do work
up check things out they won't even ask
you about your diet or anything like
that
and they send you on your way maybe they
give you a drug or two prescription and
they send you on your way
and then
you're just not getting better
so you go to another doctor
Jenny Jenn says the days of speaking
freely and openly are gone bye bye
I agree
this waffle is cooking I have the
temperature
jacked up
and then you go to another doctor and
another doctor says you know what what
are you doing for Foods because the
doctor's more interested in that and
you're like hearing it now all of a
sudden you're like stay away from this
stay away from sugar stay away from
sweets you're starting to hear that it's
a slow slow climb upward to your healing
process
and even then even if you find a guru
somewhere that's telling you what to
avoid
chances are you won't know the answers
to why you were sick to begin with and
why you're even avoiding everything
you'll just hear the blanket statement
avoid these things because it causes
inflammation
avoid these things because it's not good
with autoimmune
but you're still in the woods and you're
still deep in the hole
because that's not enough
and then you run into a whole bunch of
different things in people along the way
this person says tripod map this another
person says right try gaps another
person says boom triggers another person
says oh try but let's type another
person says oh try this try that
and you hear it over and over and over
again
and then it oscillates
and then it's lectins and then it's one
thing after another carbs sugar too much
sugar and then you hear it and now
you're just in the abyss of hell
let's see on IG you are doing the same
thing you are saying they are doing
laugh out loud over and over
that's my point thank you for saying
that on IG that's my whole point
because they're telling me
out there the haters have a campaign
saying that I have restrictions that mm
is restrictive and you should be allowed
to eat anything you wanted
by the way in the same breath they say
that they say check out this
nutritionist guy here on social check
out this PhD over here on social check
out this guy and when you check them out
they're giving you a hundred rules
that's my whole point
[Music]
but here's the best part of the point
they don't know why you're sick
and the medical medium books tell you
why you're sick and that's why this the
street cred and the record is that huge
of people healing around the world but
that makes me a dangerous person because
too many people are healing and too many
people are finding answers
and then you get jealousy and hate in
the competitor world of the natural food
movement which is all about marketing
and sales and they don't like medical
medium in the way especially when
medical medium blows the horn and the
whistle on a whole bunch of things that
are really bad for you out there
and then I just become this thing that's
in the way
and that's how it works
now let's take a look at this waffle but
I'm not quite sure it's done
a couple more minutes
can't wait to make another one
medical medium directory has a lot of
things that I use check it out
in case you're interested in something
or whatever
I don't own the companies
[Music]
getting a plate out
people are asking questions
that's why I said that
lamb tail said on YouTube My Dentist
told me to stop drinking lemon water and
I said no laugh out loud he was not
happy but I couldn't lie
patient
Dental patient
do not use lemon water
because you're going to destroy all your
teeth you know what's going to destroy
everybody's teeth vinegar
vinegar
do you see vinegar anywhere
get rid of it
can you still heal and do a little
vinegar depends on what's wrong with you
because there's a scale
like I said you can drink celery just do
celery juice your acid reflux is gone
you move on with your life fine
something else going on you you need to
increase you need to bring in other
things you got to learn how to become
your expert your own expert and you need
to know the tools and you can do that
with MN mm info but keep in mind right
if you're worried about teeth drop the
vinegar because they will annihilate
your teeth over time apple cider vinegar
will by the way I pissed off the apple
cider vinegar industry really bad in the
last so-called years so many years
Duff says on IG everything I've read and
listened from you makes absolute sense
and works I'm feeling great trying to
spread the word to those that are
willing to listen thank you you are a
warrior
you are a warrior because the medical
medium Community takes a lot of crap
when they say I'm healing with medical
medium then a whole bunch of trolls come
in
or haters
we all have a choice of what we consume
over there NRG
so I'm cooking this a little bit longer
I let it hit that temperature Where It
beeped Boop
Boop letting it cook a little bit longer
I want my Waffle crispy
yeah if we know the truth about things
Erie says Anthony can you consider the
idea of visiting Sweden I would love to
visit Sweden
someday
we only have a choice if we know
we have a choice
we can't make a choice if we don't know
the answers
why we're sick
we can make a choice but it could be a
wrong choice
when we learn why we're sick truly why
we're sick then we can make choices and
if we know tools to really help us we
can make choices
I'm going to make a couple different
waffles
thank you for being in my kitchen you
guys
foreign
I think I'm going to use this platter
right here if you guys don't mind
put it right here
I'm going to make a couple of waffles
letting it cook for another minute
okay there we go
I think
[Music]
even says that happened to me 11 years
ago at the doctor's office and I had to
figure out Health on my own and when
vegan but have needed to clean up my
diet even more as I got older and your
info has saved me and I want to talk
about that right now about vegans
this is an important piece of
information there's vegan and there's
medical medium vegan
there's animal based then there's
medical medium animal base
there's plant-based
but there's medical medium plant-based
very important to know entirely
different two different things so many
people went vegan and stayed sick or got
sicker so many people went plant-based
and stayed sick and got sicker they
still had to learn why they were sick
and then all the different tools and
options they can apply while being
plant-based or vegan
The Details Matter Hannah says on
YouTube Hannah I always read your
comments on YouTube too
so that's an important distinction right
there and a critical one at that
when someone says well I'm vegan I don't
need to do medical medium it's like okay
as if all the answers are encompassed
and just being vegan
you can be vegan and still eat all the
wrong things while you're sick because
you can still be vegan and not know why
you're sick you can still be plant-based
eat all the wrong things while you're
sick
and not know why you're sick as your
plant-based you can be animal based and
not know why you're sick and eat all the
wrong things you can be this really
healthy healthy meaning healthy kind of
eating animal-based person
still be sick get sicker not in a while
you're sick
you can that's how it works medical meme
information isn't about
you know
I mean it's that's the bottom line
Jackie B says before I found NM I was
naive vegan so you weren't medical
median vegan right
and that's something that people don't
understand they Encompass the whole
vegan thing and that's it
all right so let's get this out
on IG Cosmic Affinity they were trying
to get 12 vials of blood out of me
yesterday and I wouldn't let them do
that so I left thanks for the blood draw
episode epic episode I think you said
yesterday and wouldn't let me do less
that's what it is so I left they
wouldn't let you do less
well
I don't want to put you know put my
blood in the waffle right here where my
vials of blood right here
um
we'll talk about that for a little bit
that's another important distinction
right there the blood draw information
is critical and it sets medical medium
information apart from all the other
vegan people out there in the world and
plant-based authorities or whatever you
call them I'm not against getting your
blood drawn I'm about doing small
amounts and I'll talk about that for a
second I think it's well deserved
deserving
I just hope I cook this waffle good
enough because
um
yeah I did
do I drive you guys crazy when I cook in
the sense where you're like I could do a
better job than medical medium get me in
that kitchen medical me
he's always up to he's always up to no
good when he's cooking
okay
get another waffle going
I'm gonna put it right in the middle
look at this
let's get that rolling
prime example of the difference between
medical medium plant-based and regular
plant-based
because if your medical medium
plant-based you'll learn
that it's critical to be cautious on how
much blood is drawn
and you maybe would have heard the
podcast or read the Brain book and
learned all about it about
getting half files getting asking your
doctor for Less blood at one time
because you lose your immune system
you lose your immune system and you can
be plant-based sick
go to your functional medicine doctors
that even are fine in baggy bean
plant-based draw too much blood
periodically because you're sick and get
sick or plant-based and that's the
difference between plant-based
non-medical medium plant-based medical
medium
that's just one example keep that in
mind
by the way you guys were day seven of
the medical medium collecting Stones
meditation Journey
and here's what's crazy
like insane
the sicker you get the more blood they
take
take you think I'm done
and the sicker you get again the more
blood they take but the more blood they
take and get ready for this
you can be death bed sick and they will
take even more blood essentially they'll
kill you
but ask your doctor what's right for you
I'm just saying that's what I recommend
friends and family
be cautious about the the amount of
blood being taken at once find a new
Doctor Who will listen you can advocate
for yourself
pressing this waffle down a little bit
because I want to just spread that out
yeah
and that's one of the examples right
there which is really important just
like you could be plant-based but
literally fat yourself to death and
throw yourself into pancreatitis you can
be plant-based and be dropping oil
eating too much Nut Butter I'm not
against Nut Butter I'm not against
avocado that's not it but if you're
really sick and struggling and you don't
know what's going on and you go
plant-based and now you're just chowing
the cacao and you're chowing all that
cacao butter I'm serious you guys this
is an important topic
and you're you're gobbling down that
cacao powder and that those cacao nibs
and all those chocolate bars in your
plant-based
yeah you can still get yourself sick if
you're sick
light heart over on IG says that's what
they did to my grandma with cirrhosis
bled her to death
reason why I have these vials and this
vial this
big tube of blood because when I was in
I was in the doctor's office and they're
pulling too much out I just grabbed it I
said no you're not that that's it you're
not taking any more I'm going and I went
out the door I put it in my fridge you
know I'm kidding around I didn't do that
this is ketchup
[Music]
it's ketchup
so all these things matter so we'll go
into a little bit first I wanna I did
promise you guys I was going to talk
about
The Seventh-Day collecting Stones
meditation journey and releasing the
stones I just want to give you this
really important piece that's critical
okay so what these Stones were doing all
week as you were getting that connection
with your Stones was absorbing
Old Wounds old hardships all kinds of
different scars on our soul
on our spirit all of this that we
contend with that's buried in stuff deep
down inside of us and we're getting that
and it's what's happening we're getting
that out of us and it's drawing into the
stones
and as it draws into the stones Stones
fill up because what those minerals do
in the stones is they receive
information and frequency and there's
frequency within your voice there's
frequency coming out of you there's
frequency coming out of your body out of
your soul all of it and the stones are
absorbing that
and then we throw the stones away into
the water on the seventh day I did that
this morning we throw them throw the
stones back into nature and nature then
eats up those emotions in a way that
distance makes a distance between us
different than if we went out to nature
for a meditation or we went out to
Nature to take a walk and clear our head
and to actually
change our own frequency when we got to
Nature and we take a walk a hike we do a
little run we go out there and meditate
we listen to the birds we look at the
water
and we're doing that to help us heal
right well what this does is the stones
absorb a lot of that old hurt and then
we let the stones go we pull the hurt
further away from us when the hurt
leaves the Stones The Hurt doesn't run
back to us and recreate patterns we have
this more of an empty space inside of us
now for room for new experiences new
references new positive experiences to
fill back in on the void that was being
taken over by all those stuff down
emotions this whole time now we're
sitting festering down deep inside
mysticals Ms says I was unexpectedly in
hospital last fall they took my blood at
least twice per day as hemoglobin was
low I said to a nurse maybe it would be
better if they didn't take so much blood
from me mystical Ms completely
understand
I've watched the industry bleed people
to death but nobody accounts for it
nobody talks about it nobody knows how
much blood is taken from people when
they're sick and then you go to a
specialist and they take another 12
vials then you go to another specialist
they take another 12 vials wait a minute
I'm not done
then you go to a Lyme disease specialist
and they take 40 vials
do you know what happened to all of the
early Lyme disease cases back in the 80s
and back in the 90s they were bled
sickness and then when they got sicker
and sicker from their lime and from
getting their blood draws they were bled
more and bled more
to Insanity to the death of many people
to the death of many people
very important to know
it's terrifying Jackie B is terrifying
exactly I concur
smoking cigarettes was safe
until it wasn't
asbestos was safe until it wasn't
thousands of pharmaceuticals were safe
until they weren't and pulled off the
market
over the decades
pesticides are safe till they weren't
taking a ton of blood was safe until
it's not
cellular healing on IG says they took
two vials wait a minute I almost said
I said
cellular healing says they took 21 vials
before I went into labor
21 vials
before Labor
so her healing says in a form of evil so
you have to speak up for yourself it's a
form of evil so you have to speak up for
yourself you have to speak up for
yourself and that's empowerment so what
the haters don't realize about medical
meeting medical meme information is its
true empowerment for you to protect you
I can't believe when I see it all the
time but then I can believe it the
haters I can believe the haters they're
jealous right but you see the haters out
there trying to rip down medical medium
in any way possible you see it out there
and you saw the attack on me
not too long ago
you see that
right
and medical medium information is
telling people to protect themselves and
Empower themselves so they don't get
bled to death
but they don't care
Joe Catherine says they took blood from
my very sick baby son until all of his
veins had collapsed
huge problem happening out there
huge problem
armett says I work in a children's
hospital and off the Record advised my
patients families to request half vials
critical
truly critical
Infinite Wellness good to see you my
lime doctor bled me dry
tens of thousands of women were bled to
death in the 80s
from Lyme disease
they didn't die
from Lyme disease they were sick
from live right and you know medical
medium books talk about what causes lime
they were sick
they were never going to die
meaning in that moment in their life in
that condition in their life and that
age in their life but they were bled
to an endless sickness and to death for
many of them that's the wake
of the lime world
there are authors and podcasts doctors
that I won't name that were part of the
LIE movement of bleeding women to death
and nobody even knows this and knows
their history
the amount of information I know and
what happened throughout alternative
medicine is just would blow your
freaking mind if you guys
sat on a couch with me and had dinner at
my house with my family and I told you
what I knew in so many ways your heads
would just explode
he'd be like what that person that's out
there well who oh my God your heads
would just explode
the thing is they don't have to take so
much blood
they don't have to take so much blood
very important to know
they only need to take a little drop
I'll show you
and I've showed this to you guys if you
guys have known me for a long time
the truth is is that little dot right
there would give you a thyroid panel
metabolism panel they call it
a liver panel
that in babies gives them a forgives
baby's full thyroid panels
diabetics don't even need a drop of
blood down to check their sugar levels
but only needed a drop tinier than this
they can take a blood tinier than this a
blood drop tinier than this off of a
pair of jeans from a shallow grave from
1980 from somebody being murdered
murdered and buried in the woods and
they can go and scrape off a speck of
old dried out blood
and they can do a whole nutritional
panel on it
and don't ever get fooled by that whole
BS thing that they need to do a serum
that they need to do with serum that's
not how it works
Denise says I was told that the body
replaces it in about four to five hours
and that's probably the biggest line of
in the medical world I've ever
heard
is this waffle done let me get the blood
off the cutting board if you guys don't
mind you get it back in the fridge
waffle number two
meanwhile most people with symptoms have
a low immune system or immune system
problems
their immune system doesn't come back in
four to five hours could take weeks and
could it take even months every time
they draw the blood it could take months
to get their immune system back on track
their bones are struggling to produce it
their bones are struggling they have to
go into overload to produce all that
immune cell
look at that two waffles
hog heaven without the hog
the amount of stress on the body the
electrolytes that are removed the
um let's go check you for nutritional
deficiencies
and at the same time let's take 14 vials
of blood or five vials of blood still
too much let's take five vials of blood
and remove all of your nutritional
critical electrolytes trace minerals
minerals immune cells let's just remove
everything
let me tell you something that's really
important that'll blow your mind
if you had a blood test right after a
blood test
okay check this out
doctors won't do this no one will do
this because it will literally show how
sick the system really is and I'm not
saying good doctors good doctors could
be great doctors and just not know this
that's not the problem check this out
you can get a blood test for nutritional
deficiencies and they take out five
vials of blood
and then if after they took those five
vials of blood and they sent those five
vials of blood out
if that same day they took another five
vials of blood you would see that the
second round of blood would be truly
deficient because the first round took
so much critical parts of your supply
your nutritional Supply that's how
demented the whole thing really is
all right what I'm going to do is I'm
going to put my waffles here
you guys okay with that
whoa whoa don't roll away
how's that
Cara milch over there on YouTube what do
you do if you lost three liters of blood
still here
but how do you repair yourself after
losing that much blood so in so there's
protocols in brain saver by the way
even protocol protocols meaning
protocols before blood tests protocols
after blood work all of that so I'm
going to do you guys is I'm going to
slice
this nectarine
you don't have to do this
I'm doing it but you don't have you know
like this is just
I have these really great nectarines
right now
[Music]
oh crap
I forgot
we need to be deathly afraid of fruit
like deathly afraid of nectarines that's
right I'm that's right medical medium is
so restrictive so like what am I doing
I'm I'm poisoning you guys with fruit
like what am I doing
anyway I'm gonna slice up this nectarine
heal infertility says now I know why I
feel sick after a blood draw oh yeah
and here's the problem if you're
actually sick with a chronic illness and
you don't recover fast enough from a
blood draw check this out
and you call the doctor and say look I'm
feeling sick don't want you in for
another line of blood for another blood
draw and then ready for this you get
sick or two weeks later because of that
second round of blood and guess what
you're now at a specialist office
getting 24 vials of blood and now you're
going downhill downhill fast they just
need to take a lower amount of blood I
talk about that all in the brain saver
books
so I'm going to do is I'm going to slice
I'm gonna slice
this here if you guys don't mind I'm
gonna put that like that
an IG Dale hodgin says like Anthony says
they don't need loads of blood when at
crime scenes for DNA profile
one drop of blood at a crime scene
would take care of a liver
liver enzymes
Billy Rubin all of it like thyroid panel
um like you name it it would just take
care of all that one stinking drop
I'm gonna try to do it this way now I'm
going to slice it different ways
[Music]
marja what an information
wow
I haven't talked about blood draw in a
while it wasn't going to be a blood draw
talk
it just wasn't it's it's the seventh day
the medical medium collecting Stones
meditation Journey
everybody's throwing their stones
into nature letting go their stones
can I have this
um
I'm Gonna Save this
because I want to eat that part and then
eat that part and then eat all the way
around the pit
good
it's an insane nectarine nectarine
season insane
Alicia on YouTube the lab keeps saying
if they take small amounts of blood that
the patient needs to come back for more
blood drawn because the lab can't run
the test not true
there are so many people who are so
dehydrated and can they can't even get
blood out of people and they take the
smallest vial of blood
it's just that that's how the scam works
don't let it mess babies they take small
vials and they run everything because
they know better they know they can't
take 12 large vials out of a baby
because they'll kill the baby think
about that so what they do is they take
tiny baby vials in only a couple and
they run all the same tests how do they
do it you have to make a serum I don't
understand it's a small amount of blood
how does it work
thank you
I can ask myself questions all day long
and I'll get the answers for it and it
will be because the system is scamming
people
I'm just gonna throw one more waffle in
here
yoga love meditation on IG
they took three vials to test for low
iron and I fainted
three full vials can do that for a lot
of people
they really need to do take quarter
tubes
two quarter tubes if the doctor says
well we can only run these amount of
tests with those two quarter tubes and
you come back a couple weeks and you
take two more quarter tubes right that's
what I would do too
if that's the case
I have another waffle coming up I'm
gonna try to make waffles that are a
waffle that's
your blood is your life force
it demands respect
your blood is a life force that demands
respect
and who's messing around all that blood
tell me
where's it all gone sit through getting
thrown out is it excuse for experiments
is it used for D you know for genetic
you know experimentation on us what is
it where they do what are they doing
with all the blood
Violet hummingbird says when I got my
blood drawn the workers were dressed as
vampires for Halloween
I don't know why I'm laughing
Alicia g i healed my carpal tunnel
neuropathy back pain hip pain insomnia
and I lost weight without lifting a
finger with the medical medium
information thank you aw and SOC
whole life SOC takes all the credit
my whole life
whole life
not me SOC takes all the credit I can't
write these medical textbooks it's soc's
information my whole life
I get no respect no respect
Max Vaughn says big drama here half hour
before release time
I dropped my smallest stone called anger
and it rolled in a crack and I can't get
it out all I could fish out was an old
penny so that's that
what
oh my God Lisa oh says on Facebook
Anthony
thank you for the stone collecting
Journey so profound and healing thanks
for cooking and inspiring us even more
your stone fell into a tiny crack the
anger Stone
and you try to fish it out and the only
thing you can fish out is an old penny
there's got to be tremendous meaning in
that
tremendous meaning in that
I know I'm speechless over that one I am
because I'm asking SOC questions that's
why
I'm asking questions
I got another waffle cooking if you guys
don't mind we're live right now we're on
day seven
of the collecting Stones meditation
journey I promise you this to be an
experience that you'll never forget
Elvis lives
I love Elvis
just released my jailhouse rocks
let's rock explanation points everybody
let's rock so you're an Elvis fan
call it in a trap
you're an Elvis fan
I can't walk out
all right
educating myself good to see you my
anger Stone spontaneously exploded laugh
out loud
I'm laughing a little bit but I'm not
going into that whole like laugh attack
thing thank God or you know I hit the
floor
remember that happened on the Amazon
live a long time ago when I hit the I I
hit the floor I was laughing so hard I
couldn't I was rolling around on the
floor
Elaine says on YouTube they took three
vials of blood from my daughter when she
was about 10 years old and she hardly
weighed anything she almost immediately
vomited afterwards from the drastic
changes it created
hemorrhagic shock
that's what I said I said hemorrhage
um
even the thing is is I talk about this
in the brain saver books what determines
hemorrhagic shock
what determines it because science
doesn't really know they're like well
when most of the blood is drained out of
your body that's pretty much when you go
into hemorrhagic shock well really
because there's people that go and
donate blood and they're in hemorrhagic
shock and they can't even get out of the
chair they're in shock for weeks and
weeks
they barely can get them home in some
apple juice in a cookie it doesn't cut
it
Michelle says love Elvis too
respect respect
marja says Dr Nesbitt came and helped
you out of from a laugh attack it was
the only time he was useful
indeed
but Dr nesbeth does like Elvis
Dr Nesbitt saw Elvis in Concert many
many years ago
Dr Nesbitt is a very old chicken doctor
yep
all right I'm just cooking one last
um waffle I'm gonna probably throw it in
a plate over here
you guys saw mine
okay and then I'm gonna get some maple
syrup on them but I didn't want to put
the maple syrup on them yet I wanted to
give it a little time before I do that
you guys are at my kitchen
I am at your service
a mattress service marja says I release
my stones into a creek
whoa let me see that I release my stones
into a creek that I didn't know existed
close to my place Maria sorry Maria
I gotta get name straight here juggling
a lot I release my storage into a creek
that I didn't know existed close to my
place they guided me there I got back
into my car and the song Freedom from
George Michael was playing on the radio
that's incredible
loan over here on Facebook says I had a
difference in my thoughts immediately
after letting them go I don't think like
I used to
I had a extremely personal experience
when I
put my stones out there and yes one of
the stones almost hit a turtle
but it didn't hit the turtle
it did not hit the turtle
it almost hit the turtle and I was like
whoa
oh
didn't hit the turtle
Kimmy said my four day old newborn had
so much blood taken to test
oh my God for galactosemia it was the
worst 18 hours of my life watching it
unfold
kills me
it does
the blood draw information is just one
example of mm information you could be
plant-based but not MediCal medium
plant-based you could be animal based
and not MediCal medium animal based
you can say you're doing medical medium
and not even really do medical medium I
know that some people do that out there
they do one little thing at one point
and then they say I tried medical media
but they really didn't even read the
books there's so many different
situations
Ardent over there in Facebook says I
collapsed after donating blood and never
again exclamation point was tired for
weeks afterwards
people sick should not donate blood
meaning like it's not it's too hard on
the body and they only the the 98 of
blood roughly around that that number
depending on what year the majority of
people donating blood are sick women
because you're told to donate blood by
their doctors
and organizations they send women who
are struggling and suffering with
sickness and chronic illness to donate
blood that's who's donating blood it's
not all the people that are walking
around fine and they're not suffering
from chronic illness yet they're not
told to donate blood it's literally all
the women who are sick being told to
donate blood
does that make any sense to you
oh
Dr Fawn says yet if you create a company
that can do many tests from a drop of
blood you'll end up in jail and
character assassinated correct you also
help to heal millions of people around
the world right with medical medium
books and information you also get
character assassinated
mwah
okay you guys let me get some maple
syrup
going
we got another waffle
oh
this one needs a couple more minutes
leave that one on there let it
get going
Christina over there on IG I'm vegan and
my boyfriend is animal based mm unites
us
I'm gonna I'm can I screenshot that and
save that because that is actually an
amazing comment
come on
would you mind if I save that comment
are you okay with that
put a little maple syrup on here
you know um I'm a fan of maple syrup I I
hope that's okay and no one's mad at me
right now but I I really like maple
syrup
[Music]
I hope nobody's like
angry at me for that
the Samara says on IG it gives me
anxiety to read some people on Instagram
questioning and bashing mm do they ever
just really mean
mean for people trying to heal it is and
that's why they do it because they're
mean-hearted mean-spirited they don't
give up about anyone
they don't like me
because
I exist
and hear a voice and so they pick on
people in the community they bully their
bullies they are the bullies
they are the bullies let's just be
honest they are the bullies
indeed they are and they're bullying
right now they're putting out posts left
and right they're just bullying
everywhere out there right now it's like
there's a whole campaign right now
against medical medium it's just bully
everything
will everybody bully me Michelle says
was told I had eating disorder on
medical medium and need to go to
a psych place
yeah bullies
bullies bullies
exactly
meanwhile
go to this
PIR nutritionist on social media a guy
that's only been doing it for a few
years go to him
and you'll get this
make sure your beef is this make sure
your eggs are that make sure you stay
away from all sugar make sure you do
this make sure you do that oh and by the
way I'm gonna go to a fast food
restaurant with my family twice a week
because it's all about balance and
moderation I'm not saying you can't do
that I'm just saying
let's be straight up
be straight up
you're not perfect
and you probably don't know Jack I just
be honest
Ran France says over there on YouTube
they took 12 vials 12 full vials while I
was pregnant
some duplicate tests from two separate
lab orders they said they can't share
results with each doctor so they had to
take doubles was downhill from there for
me
God it makes me so upset it just makes
me so obsessed
it just does
it makes me so upset
makes me want to get my pirate
outfit on
is what it does makes you want to get my
pirate outfit
all right
I'm going to have some waffles should I
get
should I do a more educated say what
it's called etiquette
should you more sophisticated
Posh way of eating
a fancy restaurant here
darling
did you bring me my waffles yes yes
uh where's the maids
okay did you bring my favorite maple
syrup
did you oh you're gonna be punished I'm
gonna fire you that maid can never work
for us again dear make sure that person
is homeless afterwards
my maple syrup came wrong too much maple
syrup on here
let me have a little
are we gonna be in the Riviera
next month
make sure we donate some money to
Charities that we'll never see the money
it should tax write-off
did anybody point the fork at you I know
I said
um
did anybody ever point before got you
anyway
it was so good and they do this with the
fourth they're at the table with you and
they're like pointing the forks at you
that's like wait a minute why are you
pointing the force at me
did you ever have anybody do that I had
so many point of work at me
um
I told you not
oh my God this sliced nectarine on here
you guys are sick that's freaking sick
hold on I forgot something darn it
no no
I forgot my cayenne pepper
I get it you guys probably don't like
this
I I understand
but you know
I just want to put a little Cayenne on
my Waffle is that okay
a little bit of cayenne on there and for
some reason
I did not put enough maple syrup
on my Waffle
fantastic
oh yeah
damn
so good
I mean dang
dang so good
we're live I don't know what to say
um
I can make these all day long I just
want to say
show everybody who hasn't released their
Stones today is the day we're releasing
our Stones I've released mine I hope he
released yours already what an
experience
and what a journey
and um
truly
my heart pours out to all you guys
grateful I know you guys
grateful that
We're All in This Together
there's something that happens when we
release these stones
all jokes aside
all kidding aside
okay
we carry baggage
we do suitcases
of baggage
some smaller suitcases some bigger
suitcases but we
in order to survive here on Earth we
stuff stuff down we say sometimes oh I'm
just gonna let it roll off my back but
it doesn't mean it rolled off your back
and there's that phrase where people say
I can forgive but I'm never going to
forget
you're never going to forget because
that wound is actually in the soul it's
actually a part of you now it travels
with us when we leave here
when we leave here
this is an opportunity
to start drawing some of that out of us
so when we name those three stones and
we make that connection with those three
stones and those three stones have
chosen us or we chose them or they chose
us or we chose them
those stones are absorbing that wound
that information no scars and absorbing
that and then we get to day seven and in
that day seven it's time and we release
those stones back out to Nature we
release them back out there
and those stones
that were your friends all along that
did not judge you did not make fun of
you weren't mean to you
they were there they were conduits they
were
sponges to absorb any pain suffering
along the way Old Wounds to clear a
space inside of us because when that
space is filled up with all that hurts
it's hard to press forward without being
triggered and we get stuck in patterns
so what I'm trying to say is those
stones are the pattern Breakers
come on we throw those stones away the
stones take
that hurt and that hurt doesn't come
rushing back into you because it's
thrown in the air it's attached to the
Stones it's in the Stones it's absorbed
into those minerals and when those
stones
go flying
and hit that water or hit those woods or
hit that nature
boom it's already neutralizing
already being diffused
and unable to rush back to us if you're
bedridden and you cannot release these
stones of yours have someone else do it
for you and if you can't do it on the
day seven that's okay if you're someone
who's bedridden if somebody who's you
get so many you've been compromised in
so many ways you've been injured or
you've been suffering or struggling
you're just too sick right now in the
moment to get up and go somewhere or you
don't have a way to travel and get
somewhere have somebody else release
your stones for you it's okay and if it
can't happen today that's all right
we're doing another day
singing sweetly says can I start again
tomorrow I have lots of baggage
give it a couple days give it a couple
days give it a week give it a little
time to just let what happened happen
because things are going to surface
feelings are going to happen Sears gonna
sense healing you're going to sense
healing emotionally give it a chance to
sense it to feel it give it a chance for
it to happen
and then yeah you can do it
Maria says on YouTube can you walk down
the street and drop the stones
indeed you can
you can't
and the birds
in the sky
and the breeze
that's flowing across the Earth
that's going down the street
and the rain that's coming from above
all of that
will eventually
hit the stones and help neutralize them
a lot of people aren't going to want to
release stones
but it's a good day to release them if
you can and have the option
top secret hustle over there on YouTube
says can I keep Stones longer I would
release them this was a seven day
healing Journey exercise
are
you might say you'll keep them a little
longer and let them go but you may never
let them go and you want to complete the
healing we have all done it together
let's actually make it
a thing we all do together
RS says to think I used to donate blood
monthly to survive they pay a bit of
money and gave me a meal when I was poor
I really needed that but now it makes me
feel so sad how much blood I gave away
but it's okay it's okay lightheart but
you know better now and you know and I
know that you did it to survive you
never never beat yourself up for that
you did it to survive
if I was on the street and I had no
place to live I had no way to pay
anything or buy food or anything like
that you know what it can push you into
something like that when you're sitting
in a chair getting blood drawn because
of that
it can happen
lightheart
and I'm sorry you've had a difficult
time
that's your life
I know G The Voice Within says do you
have to go to the same place you got
your stones to release them no you do
not
nope you do not have to go to the same
place
you don't have to
you can go
to a different place to release your
stones
insane
I'm gonna eat both these waffles but I
have an extra one right there
K gear collection says in IG how can I
participate in the healing Stones
Journey if I miss this one there's 48
hour window that you can actually
download and see
what it was about
and make sure you participate for the
next one
dear dear
is the gardener out there
did The Gardener get paid this week
withhold their pay
I did not like
how the gardener was planting our
flowers
hmm
make sure you are on the medical medium
newsletter
if you can
here
tell the chef this Chef is fired
for my Waffle it's not in my liking
make sure you are on the medical
newsletter
updates there and where the announcement
of the events are there too make sure
I have appointments all morning
I have massage appointments
I have a facial scheduled I have a
pedicure
Trina says mine named self-sabotage
turned darker whoa
well
I have appointments all day and I have a
luncheon
what's this now
on YouTube
if ift says if the best year says
I tried
so many emotional releasing modalities
over the past 20 years plus years
nothing compares to releasing emotions
with the stones no processing required
I'm gonna frame that and put that on my
wall in my office okay when I put that
on the wall in my office I'm gonna frame
that
because it is that powerful it is that
life-changing I know I know
I love you guys
I'll see you next time