talking about eating disorders food fear
how many people get an eating disorder
when they're sick or they start getting
sick we're going to cover that also did
you catch the medical medium podcast at
Apple podcast
tattoos how to keep your health safe
tattoos ink how to keep your health safe
really important right there I know a
lot of people have ink I respect it I
dig it there's a lot of great artists
out there incredible gifted people that
are doing all kinds of incredible
designs and freehand on people's bodies
body art I'm not against it you know
it's not that kind of thing this isn't
an anti- tattoo podcast episode but it's
really important because it's an
important podcast episode about tattoos
and how to keep your health safe so it
is really important so I talk about
toxic heavy metals yes toxic heavy
metals in your tattoo ink and how there
is no such thing and I repeat there is
no such thing as tattoo ink that's metal
free I repeat so I just hope that gets
out there and Rings throughout the ether
and then leaves this planet and then
heads through the solar system and then
into the Galaxy and then out out of the
Galaxy and into the universe and there
forth because it's important to know and
maybe people on another planet somewhere
that are doing all this ink and tattoos
and everything else maybe they'll hear
it and that will travel all the way to
that planet and get to them and someone
will be sitting there maybe by a lake
and they're going to hear it and it's
going to be like there's no such thing
as metal free ink there is no such thing
I want people to know this I don't care
if it's cruelty-free animal free the
whole bit listen to this podcast episode
it's not about being afraid of your
tattoo or going to get your tattoo
removed through the latest technology
that they have not about that in fact I
say in the podcast episode itself don't
remove your tattoos don't remove them
unless for some reason you can't live
with the tattoo and you want to go and
you want to get it removed well that's
your body your life of course you can
but I recommend out there to people I
know friends and family do not remove
your
tattoos okay because during the process
all this stuff comes out when you do it
so I wanted to talk about that but I'm
not going to cuz we're talking about
food fear check it out medical medum
podcast at Apple podcast all right
tattoos how to protect your health okay
very important all right let's go into
it I'm in brain saver you guys good to
see you guys I'm in brainsaver right now
here we are okay and I'm in the Eating
Disorders chapter but there's a section
in this Eating Disorders chapter that's
really cool really profound information
very helpful helpful for so many people
maybe you find that this speaks to you
maybe it doesn't let's check this out
food fear let's get into it a little bit
often times an eating disorder develops
because of a symptom is that true yeah
oh yeah if you got a symptom going on
something in the intestinal tract
something happening there an eating
disorder can develop just from that
alone okay this is important if you guys
want to know I'm reading out of brain
saver right now if you don't have this
book and you didn't read this section
here about eating disorders you're
missing out this book is packed it's got
so much information really protective
information too including things to
avoid like certain supplementation and
everything that causes damage to your
health there's so much information in
these books you guys got to check it out
seriously you should get that book if
you don't already have it go to the
library get get it out of the library if
you want okay so for instance if you
have a hot spot in your intestinal
track so if you got a hot spot if you're
inflamed somewhere in your intestinal
track if you're inflamed somewhere
anywhere in here and you eat something
and it finds its way going down here and
it's taking its time and it's going
through right and it finally gets down
to that hot spot and it hits it and now
you're nauseous or you got a pain you're
going to think whoa it was that food
food fear develops very easily because
this this is just one example I'm going
to cut so much into this information
you're going to love it you are
absolutely going to love this
information so if you got a hot spot
anywhere in your intestinal tract if you
got a hot spot in your dadum see you got
a lot of inflammation in your dadum
because you have H pylori or you have an
old infection that's been fering in
there for 10 years 15 years say you got
all this extra yeast and mold growing in
here you're inflamed because of a virus
or say like a shinkles virus creating
colitis or something else see you got
diagnosed with crohn's whatever it is
that's going on whatever's happening
here you got a hot spot inside your
intestinal tract and maybe it never went
that far and you've never been diagnosed
and you're just kind of like you're
dealing with certain aches and pains or
certain stomach cramps or flatulence or
stomach issues or bloating whatever it
is the food you eat you'll associated
with those symptoms very quick and
easily regardless of what it is it can
be something something really healthy it
could be something really good for you
it could be something like by the way
these are my juices for today if you
guys can take a look I got my celery
juice right here if you're not drinking
celery juice you're missing out and any
kind of nonsense you ever hear about
celery juice it's Absolut BS celery
juice they still can't keep celery in
stores they still can't keep they can't
grow it fast enough that's how many
people are drinking it getting their
lives back celery juice is incredible I
told told you that so many years and
someday we'll talk about it more
grapefruit juice by the way fresh
grapefruits amazing ones off beautiful
trees boom right in there and I'm
finishing some orange juice right there
so those are my juices for today if you
want to see I have them here cuz I'm
going to be drinking them I'm thirsty
all right here we are Uma are you on a
juice fast no I am not I am not on a
juice fast it may look like I am
but I'm not but I love to drink you know
fresh grapefruit juice fresh orange
juice fresh celery juice love to drink
those incredible all right let's get
into it a little bit if you got that Hot
Spot somewhere in here whatever that may
be or distension or bloating or
something and you eat something and your
bloating gets
worse was it the food that just did that
could it have been or was it just it was
going to happen you already have a
problem you're already having bloting
problems was it the food you ate the day
before you may not even know was it the
food you ate 3 days before is it even
the food is it even the food but you
know what
happens this gets messed up right here
and it gets messed up quick that's right
you guys this gets messed up because
this gets messed with it's so easy to go
down a rabbit hole with eating and food
and eating and food when you don't even
know why you're even having a symptom or
a condition or a problem and we easily
associate a food we have instantly to a
problem right so if I had some kind of
inflammation because I had some strep in
my intestinal tract or strep in my colon
and I had some ecoli in my colon and
it's creating all kinds of different
pivots and divots inside my colon and
intestinal track just say I had that
right and then I'm eating something or
whatever it is and then I'm not feeling
good because that's starting to ache
down here or however it is I'm going to
be so messed up in my head I'm going to
be like I I don't know if it was that
maybe I should just have some toast some
dry toast or something and scrape off
the burnt stuff off the toast and just
have that plain I'm nauseous I got some
pain it confuses people everything does
no matter what it is that they have you
know going on and there's people who are
suffering from bloating constantly and
they want to get rid of that bloating so
they get told to drink celery juice
because they hear about it working and
saving lives and they go and they have
some and they're bloating still there
and they're like oh it's the celery
juice the celery juice is causing the
problem now it's every day it's a new
thing causing a problem and we get the
food fear so the food fear just goes
crazy in our minds and rightfully so
because it's that confusing and that
difficult to navigate and so people
don't realize the minute you start
getting sick the minute you start
getting symptoms unless you've
experienced this do you know what I'm
talking about it's that intense
wondering wish over there on YouTube my
mind has been messed up with that is for
sure hard to undo it especially when you
just want to be normal again you can go
down this rabbit hole and down and down
it and down it and down and it can get
really difficult for a lot of people you
don't know what the heck to eat
you just don't know like what do I eat
what's okay can I have eggs oh eggs feel
okay at me for now let's go into that
for a little bit
okay what people don't realize is when
you got inflammation in your intestinal
tract we'll start with intestinal tract
and bloating and digestion and I'm going
to read a little too
so over here Michelle L hey Michelle L
over there telling people they have an
eating disorder for cutting out food
groups is
gaslighting you oh God you always make
so much Good Sense Michelle and that one
right there just hits hits the nail
right on the head so spot on all right
let's go into it a little bit so so
let's start with the intestinal tract
anybody who has bloating constipation
maybe they'll have diarrhea maybe they
have other different issues with their
intestinal tract colon and so forth
right and stomach dadum all of it okay
anything that's happening in here and
maybe even a little bit further we go a
little further their pancreas is
slightly inflamed the liver slightly
inflamed clogged up and stagnant and
sluggish whatever is happening here and
there's an imbalance because there's so
many things going on they might have
some ecoli they might have a little bit
of strep in here too they might have
something happening inside their gut
that's causing problems low HCL they're
not digesting their food something's
going wrong regardless okay we're
inflamed you eat food and you feel it
you feel the food because you're hot you
got hot spots you got places that are on
fire a little bit of eoli here creating
an outer pocket little bit of strep here
creating an inner pocket you got some
different divots and pivots here you've
got a little bit of a swelling here your
ilum is a little bit blocked off because
it's inflamed your appendix is slightly
inflamed down here you're just in you
got all these different places right all
these different hot spots as the food's
moving through you it's hitting these
hot spots playing with your mind playing
with your brain playing with your
Consciousness and it happens every day
to people you don't know what's right
you don't know what's wrong you don't
know what to eat how to fix it what is
going on even if you've been to doctor
to doctor to doctor and you haven't
found anything oh my God I hear that
every day now it's all in the medical
medium books where when people go to
doctor the doctor look looking for help
and now everybody's out there saying
doctor to doctor go come here to my
health coaching after you've been to 20
doctors come to my health coaching now
it's all you hear now out there and it's
like you know you check out their thing
it's like uh stay away from gluten stay
away from okay all right so let's get
into this these hot spots can create a
lot of problems putting a lot of
different pressure and stress on
someone's mind and Consciousness because
you don't know where to go how to fix it
what's wrong and so many people are
struggling on this level problem is it
can get into a situation of
PTSD so every time you put food in your
mouth this can develop into an eating
disorder where you're actually getting a
PTSD eating disorder where every time
food is entering into your mouth you're
scared you're afraid now you're worried
you're worried like is it going to be
okay is it going to hurt I don't feel so
good that food doesn't work for me and
then you'll instantly cast out foods
that actually are there to help you heal
and recover
you but yet you might accidentally keep
foods that are not helping you and you
keep them in because they feel good in
the moment it seems so that's where the
confusion lies as well we sit there we
don't know what to eat exactly and we'll
eat a food that seems to settle okay
feel okay but little do we know that
food's feeding a problem a condition
it's feeding some kind of virus or
pathogen it's adding to a problem it's
putting pressure on your pancreas more
issues to your liver more sluggishness
to your liver and you don't realize it
and now you're just like okay I don't
know what's good what's bad cuz then 3
days later you're eating a food that
seems to be comfortable and seems to be
working 3 days later now you're getting
sicker and you don't know what to do you
don't know what it is and then you're
like well I better eat something
healthier I better try something
healthier let me eat a salad let me eat
some vegetables and then you're eating
some crunchy vegetable you're chomping
on a carrot that's something that a lot
of people go to instantly that aren't
eating that healthy and they don't know
what to eat they're like okay I better
do something good for myself I better
eat something healthy and they end up
chomping on a Raw carrot what happens
when they do that they're they're
they're cre they're jumping on a Raw
carrot all this roughage is coming from
that hard kind of like crunchy Raw
carrot they send it down the track
they're inflamed in weird little spots
like in their intestinal tract or the
bottom of their dadum they're inflamed
they got a problem whether it's H pylori
or stpy coli or something else going on
or Ci or something and then when the
food when the when the carrots the
crunchy carrots that fibrous carrot
starts to head down there it hits the
hot spot and now they're nauseous
they're nauseous they're sick they're
like what's wrong with me I can't even
eat a carrot I was told carrots are
healthy and now they're all of a sudden
scared they're in fear now they're
eating butter on toast with an egg or
they're eating cheese and they're like
that's that's the only thing I can eat
is a piece of cheese or an egg or a
piece of toast and they end up in that
situation where they're pretty much on
toast egg and cheese diet I don't know
if you guys have ever seen that it's
like milk toast eggs and cheese that's
what they end up in or rice pudding
that's another one too Tressa oh my God
you are talking directly to my mom right
now she's really struggling this an
important topic I'm so sorry your mom's
struggling right now my heart pours out
to her by the way okay
Teressa um juwel says yes my head got
messed up because I was so afraid to eat
and this is a really critical critical
topic because it's happening every day
to people new people every day people
who have already been sick too every
single day Lisa says this is me over
there on IG I'm so sorry you guys
struggled with this along the way I'm
hitting the intestinal track talk first
with this issue but we're going to go
deeper into other places of how it works
with your brain how it works with
emotions how it works with creating the
eating disorder the food fear because
that's what we're talking about here is
food fear and it's food fear developed
from not feeling good and getting a
symptom not knowing what to eat still
struggling with that symptom associating
that food with that symptom and then
we're now down a rabbit hole that's what
we're talking about today so let's go
into it first I want to take a little
sip here I want to finish some of my
aren't you here if that's okay with you
guys tra said this oh wait um TR said
this is exactly my mother explanation
points this is wild you're touching on
exactly everything she's going through
it's like you heard our prayers when
listen and I want to talk about to you
something very important okay that that
you can heal and you can get better and
you can recover and get past this
there's a way also to understanding how
this works with Foods where you're
feeling this way and you're afraid and
you're having that food fear but there's
a way to come out of it and just having
this knowledge alone is going to help
people out there because once you
understand this a little bit you
understand your body then you understand
what's going on you could rise above the
food fear and the eating disorders that
are created and the PTSD that's created
from it it's all important Catalina over
there in IG this is exactly how I felt
for three years whoa three years whoa
where I'm scared to eat because
everything makes me bloated and then
it's scary and here's what happens on
that one since we are in the intestinal
tract talk let's go into bloating a
little bit bloating can come and go at
random times could be intermittent or
always always there right always there
but worse less worse still there and
always there worse less worse still
there and always there worse worse
really bad and then B back down to not
so bad scale 1 to 10 my bloating is
three scale 1 to 10 my bloating is five
today whoa my bloating is a 10 today
well my bloating is an 11 today my
bloating is like a two now I don't know
what did it let me eat something oh it's
back to here well I eat something my
bloating is down a little bit later on
at the end of the day boom your bloating
up back to 11 back to 12 is your head
spinning my head's spinning that's how
hard it is and that's what people go
through right
there hang on a
sec just I got a celery juice here too
and a grapefruit juice
here and no this is not a juice
fast
all
right I took the celery force and
forgive me but I talk faster I have to
try to slow it
down I talk faster after I take the
celery Force I'm just telling you okay
after I take this I talk faster it can
become annoying please forgive me so
this is the vimergy celery Force you
guys know I endorse these guys
and um this just love this stuff this
stuff I love if you got like anything
going on like that you feel you know you
need to push
through H
yeah all right back to
this let's go into the bloating thing a
little bit the bloating thing is a
tricky one because you can be bloated
from something you ate 2 days ago and
then it still has you bloated and then
you eat something that can get rid of
your bloat so you drink or eat something
that can get rid of your bloat and but
you're now bloated you're bloated from
something else before days ago even a
week ago and now you're trying to eat
something or take something or drink
something that can fix your bloating if
you knew to do it long term if you knew
to do it long enough
it could fix it but you'll never know
because you'll never know you're still
bloated you don't know to do something
longterm enough you won't know what to
avoid a lot of people won't know what to
avoid and then we run into a
problem Michelle haters attacking the
way we eat is just sad yep haters are
really sad they are it's a lot of
varieties of haters too like a lot of
varieties of haters there's different
Garden varieties of haters and then
there's just evil evil Sinister haters
and then there's demonically possessed
haters that are evil to and then there's
just I mean it's there's a whole
different ladder of haters by the way
there's jealous haters there's haters
that want to destroy you there's haters
that want to kill you there's haters
that just want to see you whatever dead
and then there's haters that just they
can't help it they're just so jealous
they just want to create problems
there's a lot of haters out there all
right that's the hater scale thank you
celer force can we thank you celer force
we'll do a whole hater scale right here
we'll run through it really quick all
right let's
move so basically the bottom line is
what I see in a lot of people and plus
with the bloating and it wasn't going to
be a bloating talk but it's good to talk
about it a little bit what
happens is
that the HCL is so diminished your
gastric glands are so diminished
you have a lot of things growing in here
that shouldn't be growing in
here your liver stagnant and
sluggish and you're
bloating okay it has to be rectified it
has to heal it you have to recover you
have to get the bloating down like
celery juice is critical for recovering
bloat because it's restoring your HCL
it's restoring your gastric glands it's
killing off pathogens
yeast mold overgrowth of unproductive
fungus that's important all on its own
it's a medical medium tool you guys know
that tool and there's a lot of other
medical medium tools to get rid of
bloating but the point is is that in
order though to get rid of
bloating one has to understand that they
may be eating foods that aren't creating
their bloating but they're going to help
you get to the finish line but what
happens with bloating is you may eat a
healthy food that's going to help you
get to the finish line but instead you
get bloated because you're so hypers
sensitive that you're going to bloat so
easy you become afraid of that food you
become afraid of 4 oz of celery juice
you become afraid of
papaya afraid of a steamed
potato you become afraid of a wild
blueberry you become afraid of something
and then you're in this place where
you're afraid now of spinach you're
afraid of a leafy graen and when you get
to that point of fear and you don't know
what to eat we end up going to comfort
Foods foods that we've been eating since
we were a child foods that we've been
eating since we were young and we end up
running to like eggs cheese and toast
again we end up running back to Pasta
macaroni and cheese eggs toast we end up
running back to bread we end up running
running back to these kinds of foods or
we end up running back to treats and
chocolate and things like that because
we don't know where to go we get
stressed we're totally frustrated with
our healing process and what's wrong and
we just we go running for things that
aren't going to help us and it happens
every day out there mono eating is a
miracle okay a miracle for people so I'm
going to grab the cleanse the heel book
right here all right so Medical medium
put mono eating um on the map all these
years and it's important to understand
how it works right when you do like
aano eating where it's like bananas and
celery juice or steam potatoes and
celery juice and if you look you'll see
the different varieties in here what
happens is that you end up building up
your
HCL you end up healing the environment
in your intestinal tract you end up
reducing pathogen loads and you end up
recovering so so many people go to the
mono eating and cleanse the heel because
it literally saves their life it saves
them from surgeries I can't tell you how
many people that have reached out out
there in the world in medical Med
community that were able to avoid a
surgery where their doctor their surgeon
said you don't have to get 20 in of your
colon cut out you don't have to get 20
in of your intestinal tract cut out
and they actually literally save their
themselves from radical surgical
procedures because you're doing the mono
cleanse okay in cleanse to heal it's
that powerful and then once you heal a
lot of the hot spots in here too so once
you heal a lot of the hot spots you can
add more healing tools you don't have to
be on the monoc cleanse forever a lot of
people they go on the monoc cleanse for
just a short time and they just correct
themselves they reable themselves it's
incredible a lot of people go on it
longer see KY shelman says over there on
YouTube Anthony you suggest it you
suggested monoc cleanse to me and this
greatly turned around my food
sensitivities it greatly projected me on
my healing Journey thank you um Casey
shelman thank you for that comment what
happens is that a lot of people with
food
sensitivities the monoc cleanse corrects
them starts to restore the person moves
them P back out of this and I'm talking
about the monoc cleans cuz so many
people have food fear and if they have a
symptom or condition anything intestinal
tract anything stomach anything like
that that they're suffering and
struggling with it's now a game of PTSD
what do I eat food
fear and we end up with this eating
disorder around all of it and we're
suffering and we're struggling and we
don't know how to get out of it but when
you have direction and you know what to
do and you end up doing something like
the medical medium monoc cleanse and you
choose one that's right for you just
choose the one that you feel will work
because that's the whole thing you can
choose different ones in here you could
try one try another and then what
happens is as you're recovering at least
you have a a schematic at least you have
a catalyst to actually adhere by to take
you to that finish line where you don't
have to be always questioning things
like is this not good is this not good
because you don't have to question
something that's literally saved that
many lives and healed that many people
the track record the street credit is
already built into this so it's not like
you're going to it like did anybody ever
get better oh yeah Millions have with
the medical medium books but the monoc
cleanses so many have recovered avoided
surgeries it it's really
incredible see muhamad says can I get
this book online anywhere you can go to
Amazon .c us if you're overseas you can
look for it too in the bookstores you
can go to Barnes & Noble it's 48% off
right now at amazon.com us that's
cleanse to heal you got the mono
cleanses in here really truly lifesaving
information so all right let's let's
move into some more info we're talking
about intestinal tract gut health all of
that hot spots we're talking about how
someone could be like I can't eat any
vegetables I cannot eat any Raw veget
vegetables aw I can't eat raw lettuce I
can't eat raw greens I can't eat
anything raw it hurts my stomach and it
doesn't digest and what they don't
realize when they can't eat some raw
spinach or they can't eat some raw
Tomatoes or raw cucumbers what they
don't realize is the cucumber is
digesting the tomato is
digesting the lettuce is
digesting they don't think it's diges
gesting but it is but what they're
feeling is inflamed nerves attached to
the Linings of the intestinal
track so they're
feeling inflamed areas along the
intestinal
track they're feeling hot
spots is what they're feeling so as the
lettuce is moving through and the
tomatoes are moving
through and the cucumbers are moving
through it's hitting a hot spot and
they're going I'm not digesting this I'm
not digesting this I don't think I'm
digesting I can't eat a cucumber ever
again I can't eat a raw cucumber ever
again I can't eat a tomato I can't eat
lettuce ever
again what they don't
realize is it's okay to eat the lettuce
it's it's okay to eat the Cucumber it's
okay to eat the tomato but then they're
in fear that it's not okay because
they're feeling something but what they
don't realize is they're feeling a hot
spot they're feeling a Hot Spot
somewhere whether it's a hot spot where
it's just
bloat or it's a hot spot where they're
feeling a cramp or some pressure or a
little bit of pain or discomfort or
something else and they're feeling like
they're not digesting that raw lettuce
they feel like they're not digesting
those tomatoes and
cucumbers and that orange they eat or
whatever it is and they're just like I
cannot eat citrus I cannot ever have
citrus I can never have a cucumber I
can't have a tomato rolled out rolled
out they rolled out one out no Citrus no
cucumber no tomato No cilantro no
spinach no lettuce no kale no mosh no
this no that they've rolled it all out
gone gone gone they can't have a raw
piece of broccoli ever you can't have a
raw piece of cauliflower anymore all
those are ruled out and gone so we have
this problem
where they can't eat anything raw
completely ruled out so now they're in
that zone nothing raw so what that means
is they won't even have any raw juice
they won't have raw celery they won't
have raw celery juice which is different
different and it works differently you
guys know the whole rules with celery
juice 16 o on an empty
stomach
strained right strained so it can get in
there do its thing flush clean the liver
rebuild the H hydrochloric acid get
things back to back to square
one but the point is all that roughage
they they'll never be able to eat a
carrot rolled out carrots
gone raw cabbage in a salad raw cabbage
is gone
everything by heirloom tomatoes
gone so you walk down red bell peppers
gone so just suddenly it's food fear I
can't eat
anything all of these foods are
gone Apple peaches nectarines Cherries
Berries
gone melons
gone it just disappears it's out of your
diet now so now you're like I can only
do cook food or
toast or eggs and I hear eggs are so
healthy and blah blah blah and
everybody's talking about eggs so let me
go on a whole bunch of eggs four or six
eggs a day because it's the only thing I
can eat because it doesn't seem to hurt
when I eat an egg so what they don't
realize is they end up losing all these
foods that can help them
heal but then because they don't
understand and how know how to read
their hot
spots and they think they're not
digesting it
whatsoever and they have food fear to
towards all these foods and then they
eat an egg and they don't feel anything
no hot spot no problem no discomfort
they eat a nice fluffy scrambled egg
they need a n they eat a nice batch of
fluffy egg
whites and it goes down in here they get
a hard-boiled egg and it goes down and
it sits in here and what's happening
what they don't realize is the egg is
liquefying it's turning into a goo and
that goo isn't massaging the intestinal
tract it's not massaging the colon It's
not massaging the stomach and what's
happening is that egg is just turning
into a little like a ball of glue forget
eggs that bread is turning into a ball
of glue forget bread that cheese is
turning into a ball of glue and it's
sitting in there and it feels okay it
feels
good hey that bread pasta
basically that wheat
pasta with the cheese sitting in there
like goo and it's not touching anything
so it's not touching any of the hot
spots you're not getting red flags no
red flag here no red flag there no red
flag there but what's happening is the
eggs the dairy products the cheese the
milk the butter all of that that's
sitting in here is
feeding what's keeping you
sick it's feeding what's keeping you
sick and then you end up with the same
symptoms no matter what that come and go
so now it's not like every symptoms gone
cuz you're eating milk eggs cheese and
butter and bread and it's becoming a goo
and it's not touching anything inside
and it's becoming a goo it's not hitting
any hot spots for the moment but you
stay sick you end up getting sicker and
then all of a sudden because everything
you're eating is feeding the bad bugs
the bacteria the unproductive yeast the
unproductive fungus and mold the viruses
because what you're eating is feeding
all of that you all of a sudden get a
spill you get a
spill a spill
over what that means is it just all
blows up the bacteria proliferated the
virus has got a little too too fat and
happy and it spilled over and it blew up
and now you're
sick you're sick you still got a lot of
the cramping the pain you're having like
a spill
over and that's what's happening and
your food options are getting dwindled
down dwindled down dwindle down can't
have any red bell peppers can't have any
yellow bell peppers can't have any
orange bell peppers can't have any
cucumbers can't have arloom tomatoes you
can't have any cherry tomatoes you can't
have any carrots you can't have any
cauliflower broccoli you can't have any
spinach you become more buried in food
fear and more food fear and food fear
you can't have almonds you can't have
this and this and this and this and then
it just breaks it on down where now
you're just like what the heck
yep and your brain screwed every time
you
eat your brain screwed every time you
eat and it's so difficult and so hard on
so many
people but that's just the intestinal
track business we're talking about here
we're not even going to a lot more um L
over there that's mind-blowing on
YouTube thank you by the way YouTube
they don't they don't do they only give
like 10 people YouTube notifications so
you guys go on to my YouTube you're
going to have to just check to see if
anything is new there and look and try
to find my YouTube because no one gets
notifications very few people do all
right food fear let's cut into this a
little bit I'm in the eating disorder
chapter there's a reason why food fear
is in the eating disorder section so I'm
just going to show you it's here eating
disorders right here in brain saver
before I was holding up cleanse to heal
okay New York Times best selling books
right here I was holding up cleanse to
heal cleanse to heal has the mono
cleanse it has all kinds of other stuff
it's incredible book saving lives every
day most popular health book in the
world H hands
down in every single country in the
world it saved so many lives just in the
last 5 years 4 years and and such it's
incredible this brain saver right here
it's information is priceless and you
can get it for whatever the cost of the
book is or go to the library go to
amazon.com it's on sale right now we're
in the eating disorder chapter in brain
saver it's so comprehensive it's got so
much vast amounts of information let's
go into this a little
bit let's just hit food fear for a
couple of minutes guys bear with me
often times an eating disorder develops
because of a symptom and I wanted to
bring that back in you get an ache you
get a pain what am I doing wrong what
should I do what can I what can I
whatever this information will change
the world with eating disorders right
here in this book and it already
is a symptom related to not being able
to swallow
correctly choking nausea pain in the
stomach a feeling of tightness in the
throat or tightness in the chest any
kind of tightness of the chest you guys
any kind of
anxiety any kind of weird feelings or
tightness in the chest can bring you to
an eating disorder real fast a food fear
real real
fast you're eating and you're getting
tightness of the chest you're instantly
like oh my God is it this food in my
hand it's like food it's cursed it's
cursed cured this food is evil it's evil
it's
cursed a feeling of tightness in the
throat tightness in the
chest or losing a sense of taste and
smell this is where someone is living
their life and they're eating just as
anybody else would be eating and then
these symptoms start to develop you're
eating when everybody else is eating
you're living your life you're getting a
simp sympt and now the food becomes
questionable this is so so powerful Andy
melany over there on
YouTube thank you for timestamping so
many of those things you do on YouTube
when you do the the comment and you
timestamp it like you do that's actually
really cool by the
way in some cases if it's a chronic
nausea for example then Foods become
pick and choose a game of what's going
to help ease this nausea then nausea
hell the nausea hell have you been
through it before it torments pregnant
women who don't know what to eat they
have a baby
developing the baby developing needs
nutrients the best
nutrients the
nausea is like
this
barrier to getting nutrient to the baby
because when women become pregnant and
they're nauseous all the time they end
up choosing foods that are trying to
work with the nausea versus choosing a
food that's going to be really good for
that early stage of development for the
baby instead they're choosing things
like anything to break the nausea
they're choosing chocolate loaded with
caffeine that's really bad
for the tiny cells that are developing
into a a
fetus and so what's happening so they're
choosing things that are they're trying
to calm the nausea down the morning
sickness so they're just eating gluten
Rich toast with butter they're drinking
coffee yes they're eating chocolate
they're just eating pasta and cheese
they're eating chocolate cake they're
just working with the nausea no judgment
nothing like that I'm giving you an
example of how those early cells of the
baby need celery
juice they need sweet
potatoes they need winter squash caboa
squash they need beautiful red
potatoes they need
blueberries they need raspberries they
need all of these things these early
cells of the baby that are just
developing need all of these foods but
instead because of the nausea those
Foods aren't on the list for a lot of
women that get that early nausea with
their early pregnancy and they're just
looking for just glue they're looking
for just glue they just kind of calm the
nausea
down okay in some cases if someone has
chronic nausea and chronic nausea just
minus the pregnancy like nausea in
general can really rule the roost with
food fear picking choices suffering and
struggling the nausea is a big one Foods
become pick and choose a game of what's
going to help ease the nausea is this
going to help ease the nausea today is
this going to help let me try this let
me try that no that doesn't work for me
oh I better try some celery juice to
ease the nausea oh it's not easy in the
nausea oh never drink celery juice again
it's a bad idea it becomes a pick and
choose game of what's going to help ease
this nausea what's not helping this
nausea do any of these Foods I'm eating
contribute to this nausea that's what it
comes it becomes literally
Madness you're not crazy nobody's crazy
who's going through
this but it creates a type of Madness
with the nausey this is a prime example
Deborah over there Deborah Lynn designs
that was me nauseous for 6 months lost
lbs how come when I'm not eating I still
have the nausea there's that person the
person that's still that's not even
eating and they still have the nausea
and then then there's the person who the
nausea goes away when they're not eating
so they're not eating and not eating and
then when they pick a food and they get
the nausea back they associate a
whiplash to that food they grab an
Apple the Apple they eat apple goes down
to shoot they get the nausea the apples
poison there's a mental Association to
the Apple throw the Apple
away leblanca says I definitely had food
fear during pregnancy I was so scared to
eat anything with
seasoning
indeed Jennifer gagnan says can you
explain the cause of the nausea I threw
up for nine months
straight oh my God it's really difficult
for so many people I'm so sorry you've
gone for
that do any of the foods I'm eating are
they the reason for my nausea are they
creating the nausea then our mind and
our Consciousness starts to pick up on
patterns and habits because of small
bursts of PTSD developing did you hear
that you guys you guys got to have this
book tell other people about this book
such a great
book you eat something and you're
nauseous so you identify
that food as being the problem so you
learn to avoid that food just as you get
comfortable eating another food thinking
you're safe and good you get nauseous
again you just got comfortable with that
food you're starting to eat an orange
you're comfortable with that food it
didn't give me nauseousness didn't give
me nausea yesterday and now I got
nauseousness today cuz I'm having that
Orange Boom see you later orange Gone
With the Wind
man
you just started getting comfortable
with each food and then you're
uncomfortable with that food so Kiss It
Goodbye you think you're safe and you
think you're good and then boom you're
not safe anymore safeness is gone so
then that's another food you're
uncomfortable eating suspecting it's
contributing to the problem is that my
problem is it my problem this can carry
on into other Foods as well nausea
doesn't usually receive a diagnosis
because nausea or maybe be nervous could
maybe be nervousness and
anxiety if everything checks out okay in
the abdomen it's passed off as your just
sensitive so nausea really is the
diagnosis it doesn't really get a
diagnosis especially if everything
checks out okay if you're somebody with
a mystery
nausea and everything looks okay and
checks out
okay you're sensitive that's what is
told to each person what's not told to
the person is they might have a pathogen
stirring the pot they might have a vagus
nerve problem creating a problem they
might have other things too you might
have inflamed nerves vagus nerves going
around your intestinal tract and so
forth and it's giving you vagal
nausea this mystery nausea can bring
about serious Eating Disorders even when
reaching out for help even when
searching for a doctor or practitioner
to help ease the nausea
to help find out why you have the nausea
every day becomes what do I
eat every day becomes what do I
eat that's where we where we end up very
difficult situation for a lot of people
and what time do I eat what time works
for me like what is the best time to
eat okay
all
right is it better to eat in the
afternoon is it better to eat in the
evening some cases of mysterious nausea
make it so someone can barely eat
anything at all even if the cause and
the nausea goes away the eating disorder
that arose from it can stick around you
guys how many people had a nausea
problem for a while and it and it carved
out and mold it they're eating the
patterns from there on
out where it molded and carved out an
eating disorder from there on out what's
the book's name Miss Stanford it is
brains saver medical medium brain saver
don't miss out on having this
information make sure you get it go to
amazon.com
Us by the way just prepared to get your
mind blown if you're a reader if you're
a connoisseur of powerful information
if you love to read and learn if you
want
extensive extensive
information right if you want piles of
information to read That's ahead of time
of research and science then you got it
here um let's go into it a little bit
more okay the same goes for mystery
swallowing difficulties or mysterious
tightness of the chest if your condition
is diagnosed as
anxiety Then you will end up with
another diagnosis eventually like an
eating disorder diagnosis and they just
they kind of won't even be able to kind
of put it together like they won't
realize that you got this tightness in
the chest your vagal nerves your vagus
nerves are having problems you're
inflamed you're developing in PTSD
situation eating disorder because of it
and then you get a diagnosis like
anxiety and then the doctor gives you a
diagnosis of eating disorder and you're
just like lost lost like what do I do
you don't even know what to eat
cristelle over there on YouTube we make
linear cause and effect
assumptions especially when something's
not right and if it's chronic it can be
a hell of a rabbit hole totally and it's
so hard to trust anyone else anything
else
anymore powerful words by the way thank
you for writing that
comment because it can be be a really
difficult Road for a lot of people a
rabbit hole and hell for many okay so
over there on
Facebook okay talk says you are speaking
my life habits now I thinking a lot
about eating when what how how much fear
stress oh my God it can be challenging
sometimes and no one understands even
people through experiences
who experienced
it okay even if the audience was
agreeable to start with let's hit that
okay this is
interesting now you have an
audience family
friends practitioners
doctors co-workers you got an
audience even if the audience was
agreeable to start with they were
worried about your
symptoms they're worried about your
thyroid problems worried about your
stomach pain worried about your nausea
worried about your tightness in the
chest worried about your aches and pains
worried about your fibro diagnosis or
whatever else youve got they were
worried they were worried about it while
you were searching doctor to doctor to
doctor it can eventually start to feel
like a spotlight is on you I can't eat
this I can't eat that I might be able to
try this I might be able to try that and
then the family member the friend the
coworker whoever it is they're the
audience now they're
like well really cuz I'm eating this and
this is fine she's eating this and this
is fine he's eating this and this is
fine they're eating that and that's fine
what's wrong with you you went to the
doctor why aren't you fixing yet is the
doctor going to fix
you what are you eating and how much are
you eating the spotlights on you then
the PTSD can start even bigger and
bigger and bigger and eventually feel
like it's swallowing you up and you're
feeling like you never understood check
out brain saver you guys check out
cleanse the heel you should get both
books if you don't have
them really good books take a little bit
more look little in this
okay regardless of what your symptoms
are regardless of how many doctors
you've seen all eyes are on what you're
eating and swallowing now and how much
you're
eating have you ever been there before
all eyes are on how much you're eating
what you're eating what you're
swallowing what you're chewing if you
have an audience all eyes are on that
regardless of how many doctors you have
went to you could have went to the best
specialist the best this person the best
GP the best internist and now you know
you got an audience that's worried about
how you're eating especially if you're
younger if you're younger and you're not
older and you're a young
person then there's really eyeballs on
what you're doing and if you got a lot
of aunts and uncles and cousins and
family members and they all start
thinking you're the one with the
tightness of of the chest you're the one
with the anxiety you're the one that
doesn't want to eat this doesn't want to
eat that not sure what to eat here it's
always about a food problem and you're
one of those
people now you're going to be like up
you know up shit's creek without a
paddle
right your original symptoms don't even
matter anymore it's like no I started
out with a pain in my chest the
tightness of my chest I started out and
they said it was panic attack but then I
got tingles and numbness in my arms and
then I got this and then I got this now
I got fatigue that doesn't matter
anymore it's all about what you're
eating
now affirmation 65 over there in IG that
was my life
OMG you got an audience now you sought
out doctors to get help but that's long
been forgotten by the
audience especially if you're like 21 or
25 years old or 28 years old or
18 years old or younger or however maybe
in your 30s but either way you have an
audience now and now you got like
friends friends
friends family family friends family
friends co-workers families friends and
they're all watching you and it isn't
about your symptoms anymore it's just
about you and your food and how you
screwed up it's you and your food and
how you have must have an eating
disorder now and maybe your simp
symptoms weren't really real to begin
with maybe your digestive problems
weren't really real maybe you're not
really sick you were sick you got
doctors saying you were sick I guess but
all that's kind of drifting away because
it's all about what you're putting in
your mouth in your foods and your
problems in your foods and that's
compiling and compounding the PTSD
causing now even more riffs more PTSD
and now you feel like you're really down
the rabbit hole and no one understands
you and you're
misunderstood Shan J over there on
YouTube thank you for being here by the
way you're speaking to me right now you
said you commented amazing Cherry appan
can relate to everything you're
describing over there in IG family and
friends could never understand it wasn't
until I had to have emergency surgery
that they believed
me the focus is all gone now it's the
focus on you're not eating enough are
you eating enough you're eating too much
you're getting too skinny you're looking
sickly you need to put some meat on your
bones are you getting enough
protein and you're not eating the right
things then the fear of eating occurs
and
intensifies and that's harder than
anyone can understand and it happens
every day out there there are people
just you know
there are people that Heckle the medical
medum community and they're just trying
to put fear and doubt in their minds are
you getting enough protein are you
getting enough protein there's so
there's it's everywhere it's everywhere
and when you're sick and struggling and
you don't feel good it's like the
vultures come in is what they do the
vultures come in and they just say the
rot in this crap and they don't
understand what you've been through they
don't know what your struggles are
they're not in your shoes and at your
home they don't get
it even if you
diagnos even if you're diagnosed with a
named physical condition right off the
bat it's easy to develop an eating
disorder in part because there's still
not a medical understanding of what
causes the
condition so it's not getting healed
somebody with a simple case of heartburn
acid reflux or exam for example can
develop an eating disorder because it's
always on their mind let's hit that a
little
bit W blueberry's over
there the protein brainwashing has drove
me crazy and we will have to deal with
it for the rest of
Life yeah this just that's powerful by
the
way okay so I want to go into this part
this is interesting right here right
even if it's something like a simple
case of heartburn acid reflux you guys
for example it can develop into an
eating disorder because it's always on
your mind because it's here it's like
heartburn what do I eat oh that bothers
me oh that doesn't bother me that
doesn't bother me that bothers
me a friend I haven't talked to in a
long long time reached out to me and
said you know I got this heartburn acid
reflux thing I did all the testing at
the doctor I did all this everything
and um it's like I'm scared to eat
anything ew scared to eat anything
anything I eat I don't know this was
working for me yesterday it's not
working for me today this might work for
me tomorrow but it didn't when tomorrow
came yesterday and your mind goes wof
W eating a food that seems to be working
gives you a sense of security then if it
isn't working anymore and the acid
reflux or nausea returns it's like old
friend letting you down old friend
letting you down sometimes it's not
about the symptoms sometimes experiences
when you're eating that food it's about
what they're told about that food so
here's a real brain screw
is even if you discover somewhere along
the way the right food to eat to heal
yourself some [__] is going to like
tell you that it's the wrong food and
it's bad for
you I don't know how anybody can heal
anymore out there I just don't know it's
that bad there's that many sick people
and they're just biohacking themselves
to death and everybody's like squealing
like pics like do this do that buy my
program do this eat this do
that and darkness is rampant out there
right now I don't know how people are
going to survive in 10 years from now as
it gets worse and worse and
worse yeah they'll poach things for
medical medium information that's healed
people along the way but they'll mix it
with crap that won't heal them I don't
know how anybody's going to get better
down down the road Natalie says the
sickest and most narcissistic people
prey on those trying to better
themselves we live in a sick world it's
overwhelming sometimes well
spoken I could not have said that better
myself Dr Fawn biohackers are hacking
People's Health away indeed they're
pecking People's Health
away food has an ingrain connection to
our physical being our physical
understanding even if we aren't dealing
with ongoing Health complaints if
someone is home one evening gets some
kind of chest pain for a minute and gets
on the phone with family and friends the
first thing everyone says is what did
you eat
tonight if that person decides to go to
the ER the doctor asks what did you eat
tonight night the question always comes
up that's how interconnected we are with
food in general and that's how we end up
living with food fear like we are so
interconnected it's one of those details
that Patients First Volunteer every time
they go into the ER to the hospital I
ate this and this tonight I ate this
tonight I ate this ter appan says when
people try to frame medical medium yeah
frame that is the word yes as
restrictive and fear-mongering the only
reason I can eat without excruciating
pain and fear is because of medical
medium information I was literally
starving to death I couldn't eat thank
you Tara you're the
best I was sitting at home eating my
dinner I had this terrible pain in my
stomach my back my chest my lower
abdomen I thought I don't know what I
thought it come to the ER and that's the
first thing people devou because the
reason why they devou that information
is because it's so intertwined to foods
and eating and our health and foods and
eating you guys I could go on all day
long with this
book that's how much incredible
information is in this book Brain saver
Casey shelman over there on YouTube I
think sometimes it's jealousy and
insecurity about how they eat
sometimes projecting their fears on
what's different but they see the
healing but they project their fears cuz
they don't want to have to think about
healing and health and what to eat and
meaning like they think of okay
okay everybody thinks about what to eat
I don't care who they are
everyone and everyone is worried about
their food to some degree no matter what
because you can't just eat 10 loaves of
bread with butter on it you'll end up
with pancreatitis with with a pound of
butter you can't just eat a whole
chocolate cake every single night
because that's not going to help
you can't do a lot of things you got to
be careful with lupus free celery 333
over there on YouTube I just read an
anti-ed medium post from someone who was
on medical medium for 7 years and gained
30 lbs yet she is posting other
supplements and chocolate and saying to
be your own health expert and stop with
the cult first of all you can't even
tell you can't even trust if that's a
real story meaning like the story
they're trying to frame and paint
there's been an attack on the medical
medum community by a group of people you
guys know about the plotters and so
forth there's been a massive attack on
the community um a lot of people injured
in the community we know because a lot
of people have told us about their harm
stories how damaged they are and injured
they are and we're actually working on
that working with them and doing
something about that by the way and and
it's going to be some people in trouble
point is is that a lot of damage has
been done due to framing and lies and so
forth and the attack and a lot of fake
comments trying to frame I've been doing
medical medium for years and this is
what it did to me oh by the way check
out this supplement from a hater check
out that also is involved with it all or
check out this bu my program because I'm
selling a program now yeah
whatever all right you
guys there's good information in here
it's really
powerful I could talk about that stuff
all day I just I don't have the time I
want to talk about the good stuff Uma
says over there on YouTube mm has food
fear shifter brain shot I love that
brain shot it's powerful it's right here
in medical medium brainsaver protocols
and it's in here too in brain
saver you guys I'll read one little
thing for you here which is really great
too um
lubus free with celery 333 on YouTube
true it's a small account I felt it was
fake yeah and we kind of know who it is
by the
way we know who it is they set up
multiple fake accounts constantly and
they have the same old
Spiel yeah so uh-huh and it's kind of
like pathetic and embarrassing if you
knew who it
was net H said says on YouTube Anthony
don't you agree that patience is
necessary for us to have to heal in this
journey it is it is patience is
necessary for a lot of things and a lot
of healing truly is you
guys okay there's a piece of information
in here that's so incredible I can't
even get to it right now but it's here
and when you read this you'll be blown
over way this is this whole entire
eating disorder
chapter is just packed right I'm just
reading a little bit of it in here it's
just incredible information is Advanced
you guys know it there it is unus order
chapter that's just that could be a book
on its
own it's that powerful and there's that
much information in
there like that's how incredible it is
but you get like six books
10 books in a medical medium book and
they're heavy so look out so there you
go for some reason you guys if the
cover's dirty or something you can clean
the cover off you know I use like a
handy wipe and it just cleans the cover
right off and the conveyor belt at
Amazon and then you know like it's
greasy and stuff so it gets on the books
the books are white they're brand new
books there are no used books
you know like if you're ordering a new
book you're ordering a new book not
ordering a used book and you'll see like
the covers get dirty so I like to clean
them anyway but when you get new books
you order them from Amazon you get a new
medical medium book and it comes like
dirty if you if it's too dirty or
something get a new one for free do an
exchange call Amazon get your money back
and order it again but or you can clean
it off or or whatever
but so over there YouTube they should be
careful what goes around comes around
Winky Winky Winky you are protected aw
and will always be protected and we will
always stand by you as well thank you
thank you and I want to do the best I
can to provide you guys with
information okay so you can make your
own decisions on what's going
down okay so it's just takes time and
energy and they've done a lot of
interfering with me trying to do you
know all the work I do for free for the
community and for people with chronic
illness it is so ridiculous and sad yep
okay you
guys I'm going to be dropping a message
on telegram later on tonight so do are
you actually connected to my telegram
you guys uh following my telegram page
and I'm also going to be leaving a
message okay on MM inside
scoop right which is broadcasting on IG
the broadcast channel on IG the medical
Med Broadcasting
channel mm inside scoop so I'm going to
leave a message on there leave a message
on telegram so make sure you're around
check them out catch up on other
messages have you guys been like
watching Pride and Prejudice at all have
you done you know how I talked about
that for a while on Telegram and I
talked all about how healing it is why
it's healing how demons were kept out of
that you know cuz the industry you know
how the movie industry and the TV
industry is can be really dark right
like really dark with a lot of
possession all of that stuff did I
talked about that before like people
just bring their demons into that stuff
right and um and how the film industry
can be really dark really dark and
the film industry can be really really
dark and Pride and Prejudice okay the
not not Pride and Prejudice in general
just the
filming of the 1994 1995 Pride and
Prejudice I talked about on telegram how
healing it is for the nervous system
there's a reason why it's healing for
the nervous system so if you need
something to watch because you're
sensitive you need something that
actually has a frequency that can help
heal the nervous
system check that out okay check out my
telegrams talk about it I'll do a new
telegram eventually talking about
it Stephen Cincy says love the telegram
messages can you explain why people in
the Bible live so long I can't wait to
explain that from s so the information
is mind-blowing your just mind will just
explode will
explode Lis fre accelery again 333
another comment yes love Pride and
Prejudice I have owned the series
19951 since it came out on DVD so you
know what I'm talking about there's a
frequency right well no one knew that
that there's this what happened was
because I know because Spirit of
compassion told me
that those demonic forces Darkness
everything was just kept out of that
film because in the film industry it's a
lot of Darkness everything was kept out
of it and
it's very powerful and heals the nerves
it's incredible really incredible
including Angelic forces involved that I
talked about on on telegram I I'll do
new stuff on it and talk about it but
yeah you you might want to check it out
again Alex party says Pride and
Prejudice watch that six or seven times
now whenever I'm struggling I watch that
and it all lifs exactly Alex you know
you know you
know you know love P&P the 1995 version
though that has it has to be that one
Colin fth it has to be that version
right
there
yeah very healing for the nerves very
healing for sensitive
people there's Angelic forces involved
in the filming of that they didn't know
about and the demons were left at the
door absolutely
incredible
incredible one you can rely on
that can help heal that's that's a
healing tool and and they didn't know
that they don't know that they didn't
know that that was actually a healing
tool when they when they filmed that it
just happened to kick and just right and
Angels protected the filming process of
the 1995 Pride and
Prejudice and sometimes miracles happen
like
this and so the darkness was left at the
door and the angels protected that
filming process and that is a healing
tool a healing tool all right you guys
all right check out my Telegram and
leave message
tonight love you
guys and
um oh yeah get on my newsletter because
I'm making an
announcement next
week making an
announcement
I'm hoping it's next
week okay get on my
newsletter you're not want you're not
going to want to miss the
announcement it's important
information just letting you know don't
want to miss it it's going to have some
details and stuff all
right see you guys