hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now if you're
brand new to this show just so you know
cuz this is really important this is the
only Health show anywhere where the
information here isn't agenda driven
that's really important to know that
means the information doesn't come from
interest groups originally medical
funding with strings attached botched
research with the thumb on the scale to
make things go a certain way because
tons of money went into something and
believe it or not you should believe it
cuz this is true in alternative medicine
included there is thumb on the scale
deep within it it wasn't it wasn't like
that a long long time ago this is the
only show that doesn't have any medical
lobbyists information that might have
been you know driven from that in the
past internal Kickbacks persuaded belief
systems all those persuaded belief
systems those things are potent you
can't change somebody's mind if they've
been if they you know if they believe so
strongly in something and doesn't matter
if you hand them the truth on a silver
platter in front of them you can't
change their mind there's people out
there you can't there's nothing you can
do to break that belief system I don't
know if you've ever run into that before
run to anybody like that before well
there's persuaded belief systems
involved with private panels of
influencers behind conventional and
alternative medicine let's not forget
about health field payoffs and trendy
traps which are actually really annoying
I talk about trendy traps this is the
only show where the information I share
from that I share with you comes from a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
Source a higher source a gift that was
given to me which I've called called The
Curse over the years because I always
hear it non-stop since the age four when
I diagnosed my grandmother of lung
cancer that's when it all started for me
and this Source has been helping out
tens of thousands of people throughout
my entire lifetime and I've dedicated my
I've had to dedicate my whole life to
this and nothing but this this isn't
something that started three years ago
or 2 years ago or 7 years ago or 12
years ago and goes on and go goes on and
goes on it's a voice I've heard that's
guided people in the right direction and
but like I said before you know you can
have the truth in your hands doesn't
mean someone's going to accept it out
there in the world it's a sad thing and
and you know hey that's just how it
works for so many reasons and when it
comes down to vital healing information
it's critical to Healing people to
Healing people critical information that
hasn't been touched by anything else for
those agenda issues that are out there
where it's just about you know money
invested into research that research
better come through with something
because you're going to get a lot of
investors mad this is clean pure stuff
I'm saying that because right now in the
industry people could be like oh what
what did he hear this information
somewhere and now he's talking about it
oh wow what uh may you could probably
find that on the internet no you can't
anyway check out my book thyroid healing
check that out as soon as you can you're
not going to be disappointed you're not
it's like like when life-changing Foods
came out last year and I said on the
radio show I said look I don't think I
let you down I don't think I let you
down I I I gave you everything I had I
put information about food no one knows
about that I got from Spirit and then
what what did we hear when the book came
out I've heard a numerous people out
there saying you didn't let us down you
didn't you didn't let us down you didn't
you didn't and that's like well I I I
think I did it again meaning got you
something from Spirit information that's
mindblowing that can help you heal about
thyroid information you've never heard
before and known about and I don't think
I let you down and there's more than
just that in this book so just get it
when you can and you know I I really
really want it in your hands like with
everything I got not because that's
that's the whole point that's the whole
point you know I I get it look you know
we people out there in the world we
write books we try to get information
out to help people and and everything
else but you know when spirit's telling
you this has this is critical and it has
to go into writing and I've been hearing
this my whole life I just never wanted
to commit to the books I was doing all
the I was I was in the trenches like so
many amazing doctors and healers and
practitioners and and people that are
helping people when I was in the
trenches and I was doing that for
decades and and and many decades
completely unpaid unpaid just for free
until literally I was basically in in a
in a dog house on the side of a riverbed
on on Hay straw catching pneumonia and
and then I realized okay well I have to
of course survive like everybody else
but the point is is that with all of
that spirit is said you have to get this
information in these books this is it
has to be in there for people people so
I hope you grab it I hope you grab it
and take a look and read and I think
you're going to be quite surprised um
we're talking about pregnancy pregnancy
today we did a pregnancy show before but
this is a this is kind of an offshoot
because I wanted to dedicate time and
effort in into supplements and foods for
pregnancy because it's such a big deal I
mean a huge deal and it's not just the
concerns and the questions and what do I
take what do I it's more than that this
is this is a child we're talking about
this is life we're talking about and
this is life we're bringing into the
world this is life we've where we're
dedicating our entire body and being and
Life to and you know in order that you
know we we get to the point that that
success of of having a beautiful being
in our hands and you know so this is
important this is important and um so I
really want to cover into that I got a
couple of funny things to say I want to
say something here okay before we go
into that and this kind of relates to it
cuz this isn't good for pregnancies but
the world has been taken over it has
been taken over yes literally taken over
it's it's it's unbelievable what has
happened what are you thinking in your
mind what are you thinking in your in
your Consciousness what are you thinking
about in your in your thoughts right now
the world has been taken over and it is
evil it is evil that has done it and I'm
going to tell you right now okay it is
it is and I don't think it can be
stopped I just don't think it can be
stopped not this anyway I know I'm
always positive about stuff and I'm like
no no no no you know there's yes you we
can move forward there's no question
about it no matter what but in this
little thing I got to tell you and I've
talked about it before a little bit the
world has been taken over what has it
been taken over with in a disastrous way
fragrant fragrance that chemically
created in an oil base that you plug
into your wall and you destroy your home
and you and you invade everybody's lungs
and invade the sinuses it's that bad
fresheners air fresheners the worst
invention on the planet possibly
possibly destroying rental homes by the
thousands and hundreds of
thousands destroying vacation spots
not that I go on vacation I don't know
the last one I've had but the point is
it's destroying vacation spots
destroying I hear about this all the
time destroying homes destroying
offices you can't even go to a dentist
office you can't without it being
plugged in everywhere wreaking havoc and
it's even getting into schools
elementary schools high schools middle
schools and and students in college are
even plugging them into their dorms to
mask to mask the smell of beer or the
smell of partying or just the smell of
just mold or whatever but these things
are disastrous they're so antagonistic
to the brain to the sinuses to the body
it's not even funny I'm serious about
this and it was getting bad years ago
it's at a point now that's that's
unbelievable is it good for pregnancy no
I talked about that a little bit in the
last pregnancy show it's not good for
pregnancy so pull them out of the wall
and throw them out pull them out of the
wall and throw them out I don't care
what brand it is what kind see what you
have to understand something you have to
understand I don't mean to so be so
bossy by saying that but with this you
just do okay this isn't like essential
oil this isn't like a natural essential
oil that you have in a little mister or
or essential oil that you put on your
wrist or essential oil that you put in
the bathtub or anything like that that's
not what this is this is unknown
chemicals because the recipes will never
be taught or told to you these are
chemical factories with Vats of lethal
highly toxic chemicals and they're just
they're they're concentrated and
concentrated and they're just completely
synthesized in in the worst way possible
this isn't this isn't like oh Touch of
Rose a touch of this A Touch of that no
it's not and it's horrendous on the
sinus cavity the brain I won't even talk
about what it can do to you because it's
just it it's annoying as heck it can
make people who suffer from problems
make them worse make people who have
fibromyalgia worse make people and look
you can't be in fear about it you just
got to plug them out you just got to
unplug them I mean and you just got to
throw them away that's what you got to
do that's what you have to do I'm just
telling you right now for the benefit of
your childrena for yourself that's one
thing I wanted to say so
let's let's talk about supplements for
for for children meaning meaning when
they're still inside of us and and
before they're inside of us let's do
that and Foods so I want to give you a
little history little history going
back the supplement companies of the old
day still exist now those are the bad
ones the bad ones I say that because
during the
1930s when alternative medicine was
rising Rising up to help us all the the
incredible herbalists the original
nature doctors the original
chiropractors the original anybody who
was involved in the old days I mean they
were being slaughtered left and right I
talked about that all the time there
because what happened was modern
medicine was in a was was upset
conventional medicine was so angry at at
natural
practitioners that they basically did an
acis inquisition basically against them
I'm I'm not kidding ostracized them in
so many different ways they were jailed
they were they were tortured I'm serious
about that you don't know it I'm serious
this was a bad time because it was
Rising the alternative medicine was
rising and that was really bad for
business for conventional medicine but
so what happened was conventional
medicine pharmaceutical companies
partnered with supplement makers bulk
crappy supplements factorymade junk in
massive amounts of bulk powders bulk
everything and then it went into some of
the old vitamins the just junky ones and
they're in there today in the vitamins
today in the conventional Market in the
conventional in in the market I'm not
going to mention names not going to
mention
names but we can do say use your
imagination let me mention one
um a vitamin called one a
night or one a week maybe you could use
your imagination classic a vitamin
called
um um let's see
tum tum you could use your imagination
you probably figured it out all right
right this is just examples vitamins
that back in the '90s early 90s cuz you
couldn't get a vitamin back in the early
90s you go into the the pharmacy and
they had two vitamins there and they
were junk vitamins and they had dyes in
them and they had red dye purple dye
blue dye cancer-causing dyes God knows
what all that you know that was in there
they had all that in there but that
those supplements aren't gone today
they're there so when you look for a
pre-
needle you got to go back to the
original to the original before the
Vitamin World kind of lifted off the
wrong way
back in the 30s and turned into the 40s
and 50s when you take a vitamin was that
one kind of horse pill that was filled
with lowgrade bulk junk from Factory
Pharmacy Vitamin World okay that's what
it was well you don't want to because
well here's the deal prenatal are made
out of that still made out not all of
them but they're still made out made out
of that they got fancier names now they
get different brands now can get them
doctor
prescribed but they're
junk do am I saying throwing them away
no I'm saying you just have to be
cautious to know that there's better
ways I mean they may not hurt you they
they may not hurt you they won't but
there's better vitamins better pren
needles out there so important to
know you
know gourmet coffee right you want a cup
of gourmet coffee do you want to go to a
really good gourmet coffee place or do
you want to go to a fast food restaurant
that now has Gourmet Coffee which one
would you which one would you rather go
to the fast food restaurants which I
won't name either which I won't name
either the fast food
restaurants okay they had coffee for
decades right it was garbage everybody
knew that come on everybody did it was a
cup a small cup of crap is what it was
and it tasted like you know roadkill and
you know oil engine oil all right that
was a cup of coffee you got that at the
fast food restaurants if you wanted a
real cup of coffee you had to go to a
special place maybe a fancy place maybe
some kind of eery maybe maybe to um you
know not to the early diners the diners
of today though have cormet coffees now
but you go you know you get whatever it
is you would go and and you would go
looking forward it a nice Gourmet Coffee
a better coffee a better get the whole
bit you wouldn't want it at you know
whatever place you wouldn't want it at
that fast food place and but here's the
deal here's the deal all right so I'm
saying this gourmet coffee thing because
there's a reason it's like that W
supplements because now here's the deal
those fast food places that had the
worst cup of coffee and knew nothing
about coffee possible possibly are toing
that they got this SE and they got
better coffees all these different fast
food restaurants but why would I want to
go there to get get the cup of coffee
wouldn't I want to go to a to a place
that knew about Gourmet Coffee long
before someone tried to imitate it
possibly yeah would you want supplements
for
pregnancy that are actually like whole
food and really real to protect your
baby and you instead of going with new
you know I mean meaning like going with
places that never knew about supplements
to begin with what I'm trying to say is
if you look at baby formulas and you see
vitamins and minerals in baby formulas
there's so many bad ones it's
unbelievable especially the old days the
canned baby formulas you got genetically
altered soy oil you got corn tons of
corn syrup corn syrup corn syrup you got
all these bogus pharmaceutical bulk
vitamins thrown in there and you see the
list in there they'll have the whole
list in there and and it it it really
and this is from the makers that don't
know anything about
Gourmet Gourmet you know milk for babies
Gourmet formulas that come from a mom
what I'm trying to say is alternative
medicine knew how to do it right from
the beginning conventional medicine knew
nothing about vitamins knew nothing
about vitamins from the beginning and
knew nothing really about baby Health as
far as vitamins minerals and
food now they know better better they're
knowing better but that's like the fast
food restaurant that just realized
gourmet coffee is the way to go they
didn't know about it for decades for
decades they sold the worst coffee ever
the conventional formulas meaning the
then you got the conventional medicine
selling the worst baby formulas ever on
the planet you may as well sell them on
mars or so they're so bad mean just ship
them off to another planet actually
don't even do that because I care about
life on any plant the whole point
is the whole point is is that you want
to get down to the roots of the Whole
Foods to the Natural formula to things
meaning to the natural vitamins and
minerals that are inside your own
natural formula to breast milk and if
you can't breastfeed then you want
options you want options without a doubt
but you don't want the worst baby
formula that basically carries the
pattern of the old day from the 1940s in
the 1950s and the
1960s and even even just recently even
recently and don't get me wrong you know
conventional medicine is great for so
many things I'm ripping into them a
little bit today but that's because they
didn't know anything about
vitamins or what mommy should be taking
or doing but now they seem to be experts
recently and then you get a mix you get
these doctors that were all conventional
and then yeah they want to learn more
more alternatively and that's thank God
God for that that's that's the
difference today that makes a difference
that makes it so much better and that
part I totally
treasure but you know we the whole point
is you want to get either way you don't
want you don't want the stuff that came
from the fast food restaurant a long
time ago and then get the good stuff
from that fast food restaurant because
there's always some loophole that isn't
good in the end what I'm saying is you
don't want that classic prenatal that's
filled the junky bulk vitamins that have
been in stock at factories overproduced
for 20 30 years and then literally
thrown into supplements today did you
know the conventional
vitamins they have a stock going but
back
decades sitting in warehouses that end
up going fresh as if they were fresh
into supplements that go on the market
as of 6 months ago then the expir then
the expiration date goes on that vitamin
then it goes on it doesn't go on is it's
sitting in factories in piles and piles
and
piles sitting in factories and and
seriously in mounds of this stuff
because they have a backlog why do they
have a backlog because it was
financially smart at the time it was
good for tax reasons good for all kinds
of corporate reasons pile the stuff up
till the cows came home and then use it
later and that's what's in prenatals
today you have to be careful you have to
get the right prenatal the ones that
don't have that the ones that have Whole
Foods the ones that could protect you
you don't want your prenatal from that
fast food restaurant that just kind of
learned about it now either and all of a
sudden they learned about it now great
you want your prenatal from the people
that originated originally knowing what
really was right all long as far as the
concept of whole whole food whole
vitamins Whole Food real food that was
the concept at the beginning and then it
totally totally got ripped apart and ex
and and thrown in 20 different
directions along the way so yeah you
want Gourmet Coffee you go to a gourmet
place because you're going to trust that
they really are experts in it you go to
a fast food restaurant ohoo they're
serving gourmet coffee now but what did
they serve people for 40 years in their
in their chain
garbage
garbage look the bottom line is I just
want to make sure that you know you're
on the right
supplements so let's talk about prenal I
can't help it because it's such a good
one to talk about first of all prenatal
vitamins aren't really ideal you can
take them fine that's good but they're
they're put together with the thought of
what Mommy
needs the thought of what Mommy needs
for their baby okay number one and that
was on Old standards old standards of
blood work from from years ago from
years ago What alternative medicine has
done unfortunately this is one thing
they've done that's not good is they've
taken they've gone by the standard of
what conventional medicine already
created for what mommy and baby needs
they've gone on that standard so that
means it's what how many different
vitamins and minerals that are in there
which ones they choose the whole bit are
chosen off of the
standard that was created a long time
ago so you're telling me the standard in
conventional medicine that was created a
long time ago that holds true has it
held true in any part of conventional
medicine not really not really it hasn't
because we figured that oh no this drug
is bad oh no that drug is bad oh no 20
years later oh this drug is bad got to
create a new one oh um this this this
surgery is bad no we got to do it a
different way a new way oh this is bad
um this technique is bad got to do it a
different way um is salt good for you
when you're when you're you know out in
Sun is it bad for you um too much water
when you're dehydrated good for you bad
for you it's constantly going back and
forth conventional medicine doesn't know
where they're going with all that there
there up and down left and right but
their old standard of of what mommy
needed in 1950 in the first prenatals or
whatever it was around that time I mean
why did alternative medicine just adopt
that they adopted that why from what I
said at the very beginning of the show
there was interest groups all the way at
the very back of the beginning of the
first bits of information alternate
medicine just you know pulled in that
old information and just started using
it but it's contaminated information
once
again and so what does this mean this
means that you can make your own
prenatal with using the right stuff that
outbeat prenatals
spirina alone has more for you and your
baby than any pill horse pill with a
little bit of this and a little bit of
that and a little bit of this and a
little bit of that in the pharmacy the
prenatals or a prescription prenatal it
can't touch what a teaspoon of sparina
can do with helping your baby that blue
green
color in there it's a
miracle what that can do for your baby
and development for brain and everything
I mean literally a little a big horse
pill with nothing with fillers in it big
horse pillar with fillers in it you know
prescrib the prenatal with some because
some guy some some guy back in 1948 said
women need this these are the minerals
and vitamins they need for when they're
pregnant and then that carried
on I'm
serious
and um and so here's the deal you can
make your own prenal natal too or you
can add to it like I said a little
spirulina that's a great one because
what that has as far as from vitamins
and
minerals is is is much more advanced as
far as in the form they're in they're
the bioactive and bioavailable form I
don't like Corella Corella because
Corella here's what Corella doeses
Corella what it does is it it takes
heavy metal and it drops it it takes
heavy metal and it drops it and
protecting the baby and protecting mom
one way of protecting baby protecting
mom is making sure toxic heavy metals
are not in the program whatever you do
that are not in the program and if there
is toxic heavy metals that are in the
body in mom's mom's body because she's
going to have them that's just the way
it works now she's going to have them
and and that means the baby could have
some and you don't want to use Corella
cuz Corella if it even extracts heavy
metal from Mommy from mommy's
brain or from mommy's liver it's going
to drop it right away it's irresponsible
meaning this Corella itself is like that
football player on the field that you
just can't trust or that hockey player
you can't just trust and pack the puck
to you can't you can't trust that one
because it's always always goes
wrong it's the same thing with Kow
because the toxic Heavy Metal the
Mercury's going to get dropped along the
way and anybody who totes cor like the
god you I still see it today I can't
even believe it after I talked about it
medical medium book one and I talk about
it all the time and I I I put
information out there I still see people
like oh carella he not spirina carella
carella is the one no it's not it's not
it just doesn't work I'm sorry it's got
nutrition in it but it doesn't work for
for heavy metals so what I'm saying is
sparina can take metal out of the body
and not let it
go and not let it go hence not let it go
and get to your baby somehow not let it
go and get to your baby somehow but
instead fortify your baby with
unbelievable
micronutrients what do you think makes
that color that color sure Corella has a
good color too without a doubt but but
like I said it's not the same thing and
it's not as nutritious anyway as
spirulina what makes that color you know
what makes that color a force that's
beyond all of us a force that's up in
the up in heaven a
force okay way up there a spiritual
power so whatever your belief system is
and I I I treasure everybody's belief
system whether you believe a light is up
there a Creator you you don't believe in
God you don't believe you believe in
something else you believe that we just
we just derived out of a lake and as the
as the centuries as as the thousands of
years pass and millions of years past we
grew into something else whatever you
believe in I respect it and I honor it
no matter what it
is and so whatever you believe in fine
but believe that that's what's
responsible for spirina that color in
spirina that's what's responsible for
that color and that color is using the
word magical completely insults that
color it's it's it's it's bigger than
that so it's a great food teaspoon of
Spirulina can do more than
99.9% of all of of all prenatals out
there for a mommy and
baby and maybe even
100% but that's one thing that's really
good you another thing that's really
good is barleygrass juice powder
barleygrass juice powder it's another
one that's a great one that's a great
one it has power to it similar to
spirina but Power because because it's
not just the nutrient profile the the
the microminerals subclasses that aren't
even studied subclasses of minerals and
and vitamins and amino acids that aren't
even disc you know people think all the
amino acids are discovered they think
they're all discovered as if as if
science dedicated it all science puts
trillions of dollars into genes that's
all they care about it's not it's not
what's in barley grass juice powder and
what amino acids are not discovered in
them trust me who's going to waste their
time and money and interest groups are
going to waste all their time money into
that endeavor no one exactly but
undiscovered amino acids are critical
for baby Health baby growth for mommy's
health during pregnancy teaspoon of
barley grass juice powder does more than
any any any prenatal does more than that
and then you do you know teaspoon of
Spirulina teaspoon of barley grass juice
powder you can do a half a teaspoon if
you're nervous about do a quarter
teaspoon because it's that incredible
for you it's that incredible for you
could do A4 teaspoon some other
supplements I like I like
methylfolate moms have a hard time have
a hard time methylating liver the liver
goes under a lot of pressure a lot of a
lot of of strain and stress so
methylfolate is critical cuz it's it's
about getting that methylation even
better than it can be the
conversion of nutrients into other
nutrients that can't be studied by
research in science it can't be and what
happens when it enters the stomach and
goes everywhere through the body it'll
never get discovered by research and
science I mean we're talking 500 years
from now if the world doesn't blow
itself up 500 years from
now and anything is is is that's that's
what the whole point is is about that
that conversion it's about converting
inside the body converting everything
converting when pregnant and
pre-pregnant it's all about conversion
conversion meaning your liver does these
magical things converts this into that
converts this into that takes every
micronutrient moves it into something
else tags it with hormones that are
undiscovered by research and science
that bind on to it and drive it through
the body so methylfolate helps to
improve
methylation and I like that one there's
the 1 mgram capsule could take it once
in a while you could take it um talk to
your professional about it talk to your
doctor about it bring all this to your
to your to your doc and you're pregnant
bring it all to your doc you know let
your doc nay or yay whatever I totally
totally respect that without a doubt
100% but methylfolate is really helpful
helps the liver it does and that's a
great thing it's not there to detox the
liver cuz you don't want to detox the
liver of years and years of garbage
sitting inside of it while pregnant you
don't want to do that you don't want to
do a heavy detox don't do anything crazy
don't do one of those you know cleanses
clean cleanse not like a food cleanse
but some kind of liquid cleanse where
it's just liquid only for long term
while you're pregnant don't ever do
anything like that I think you I think
you know that um but the bottom line is
these are some of the things to use
iodine a little bit of nent
iodine now you can talk to your
practitioner about that too a little bit
of nent iodine
um one tiny drop every now and then if
you want right on the tongue you can do
that that's something also that is is
helpful why is that helpful because
iodine deficiencies cause immune
function
problems within not only Mommy's body
but baby's body so now if you don't want
to do a little bit of n iodine and you
don't have to you can talk to your you
can do something else maybe take a strip
of dolls eat a strip of dolls
that's that Atlantic Sea vegetable just
eat one strip once in a while you get
nice little iodine kick from that that's
really good so that's something you can
do and you know food doesn't have iodine
in it even food organically grown is
still lacking iodine those fields see
the organic fields are over
overproduced thank God they are they
give us great food but overproduced
overproduced and I'm saying that because
the fields go
Barren why am I saying Barren because
when you're pregnant you're not Barren
you know what I mean it what women worry
about when they can't get pregnant
they're worrying about that whole bar
being Barren or something and there's
ways to get pregnant there's ways of
having a baby and there's ways of
fighting and fighting through that and
surviving through that and and having b
a baby and giving birth to a baby but
what that means is it's like it's like
we want to put something back into that
soil and that's that's what some organic
farms do they put back into their soil
back into there and they try to get
things back and you know what one thing
they put back into I'm talking about
this CU it's so important I know this
one Farm you know what they put in their
fields this organic they're not putting
manure and a lot of organic Fields put
manure they're not putting or you know
manure anything what are they putting
they're putting seaweed tons and tons of
seaweed like tons of it what I mean tons
truckloads of seaweed they dump into
their fields till it in they till it in
they let it sit for a year without using
the field so that the snow comes and the
rain comes and it brings all these other
micronutrients and it mixes with the
seaweed makes these living chemical
compounds making living living soil and
they do that and the iodine goes up in
the soil
and that's really amazing but we can't
always rely on what farm is that what
farm is that nobody knows right nobody
can just eat at one Farm oh let me
that's that farm across five states away
let me go see if I can get some fresh
spinach from them here's the deal so you
want maybe a little strip of of dolls
would be okay that's all you don't need
a lot of it Atlantic Sea Coast that kind
I really like that's something that's
powerful supplement
wise now vitamin D
vitamin D is a big one on the list
meaning like um doctors are offering
that I'm not a big vitamin D fan because
vitamin D uh does a couple things first
of all it thins out the blood and when
you're pregnant you know I don't like a
lot of vitamin D I it's because you
don't want to thin out the
blood too bad when you're pregnant you
don't want to do that mean you don't
want to go you got to be very careful so
what happens is you got to I've seen
some women they're on lots of vitamin D
before pregnancy or maybe over the last
couple years meaning over the couple
years before becoming pregnant and you
know vitamin D3 is the way to go by the
way if you're going to do vitamin D
vitamin D3 I was talking about that a
long time ago when everybody wasn't
using that one so vitamin D3 and what
happens is that people go on the Habit
they go on the kick they brainwashed
vitamin D you need Vitamin D the
brainwashed vitamin D vitamin D vitamin
D is just one thing that you we can even
get from the sun the sun gives us so
many more important things that isn't
even on the list because science
research hasn't discovered it just got
to understand that um but vitamin D the
problem is with that we get so
brainwashed into Vitamin D thinking this
is this is like the greatest thing on
the planet that we
need and we get into a habit of taking
it and then we get pregnant and we take
a lot of it not good at all not good at
all just going to say it right now too
much vitamin D thins out the blood you
don't want to thin out the blood while
pregnant or even pre-pregnant meaning
pre- pregancy trying to you you're
working to try to get pregnant you got
to be careful with that that's what
that's what I mean but if it's there's a
little bit in something a little bit in
a good prenatal uh
fine but I wouldn't go out of your way
and taking a lot of it get the smallest
dose maybe get the drops the liquid
drops or get a really small amount of
IUS if you want to take it I'm just
giving you advice on you know taking
vitamin D very important so that's
something I wanted to kind of um talk
about you got to see the world doesn't
agree upon one thing you you know that
right like the whole world doesn't agree
about one thing right right no no
complete diversity in the world
everybody agrees on different things
that's the way it should be that's the
way it should be you know everybody's
got their own own beliefs and everything
else and you name it it goes list goes
on like No One Believes In thinking this
this one car is the best car and
everybody should be driving it right do
you think everybody should be driving
the same car so just think globally
think about everybody in the us alone
should they all be driving down the same
the same car can you imagine everybody's
driving the same car so every single
couple and family and every single
boyfriend and girlfriend and every
single single person and every single
friend believes this one car is the car
to drive so everybody's driving it you
wouldn't see that right just like you
wouldn't see everybody agrees on this
one cup of coffee and don't drink coffee
while you're pregnant whatever you do
and you know what I mean like not
everybody agrees in the same brand right
on the
planet but what you will and not not
everybody believes you should be
drinking coffee on the planet but what
you'll see about vitamin D is the whole
planet right now believes you should be
taking it that you should be on it that
no matter what that's the most important
supplement that that's what you should
be on the whole planet the whole planet
it there's something wrong with that I'm
just being straightforward there's
something terribly terribly wrong with
that I'm just saying the vitamin D3 is
not the uh worst thing in the world it's
not the best thing in the world do you
need it all the time not
necessarily not necessarily does it
offer a lot not a lot not a lot I'm not
anti-d I'm just saying when the whole
world believes in one thing and one
thing
only there was a reason for that going
all the way back at the beginning of
wherever that started just look out look
out so just be careful don't be taking
tons and tons of it don't be taking
50,000 I use you know be careful if you
if you're if your practitioner want you
on it then then yeah but just be careful
on how much you take and take breaks
take breaks so that's something I want
to come across so here's the deal Foods
I want to cover some foods foods are
important now
it it when it comes down to pregnancy
you want to you want to be careful now
the word protein is rampant out there
protein protein protein protein it's all
about protein all about protein protein
doesn't make babies protein doesn't make
babies if that was the key if that was
if that was the the truth then breast
milk would be all protein it would be
all protein breast milk has minute
amount of protein and every woman is
different every woman is different
some women have 1.5% protein in their
breast milk some women have literally
.9% and their healthy women and they're
eating plenty of protein some women have
um
2.5 some people have
3% but that's pretty much Max and that's
in breast milk that's in breast milk
okay why if it was the most important
thing in the world for pregnancies and
for babies after birth it was the most
important thing in the world why
wouldn't there be more protein in
mother's milk which
is holy
milk
well okay are we going to doubt or judge
nature are we going to doubt and judge
nature no not in this situation are we
going to doubt mom's
body are we going to do that are we
going to doubt our you know the mother's
body are we going to do that but yeah we
do we do doubt that so so what happen we
shouldn't so what happens women are
eating protein protein protein and what
is what does too much protein do it
starves the baby because what does the
baby feed on for
development baby feeds on sugar yeah
shocker shocker I talked a little bit
about this in the last show too shocker
that's a big I know right surprise
that's why breast milk is sugar water I
Ted about the L I know I just can't help
it but I got to talk about it more in
depth it's sugar water you have to
understand that with lowfat it's lowfat
sugar water that's what it is
interesting very interesting CU glucose
is what develops a baby underweight
babies occur and mommies underweight
babies occur from high fat high protein
diets and not enough
carbohydrate that's what occurs I'm
seeing it in the latest I'm seeing it in
women lately because they've adopted the
high fat high protein Trend with no
carbohydrates and they they stuck to it
versus craving versus falling for their
Cravings meaning saying oh no I better
not have that half a potato oh no I
better not have I better not have um you
know that little bit of hummus oh wait a
minute I better not have um too much
avocado because avocado's got a little
fat in it but it's got more sugar in it
okay I better not oh it's a fruit okay
so I better not have that fruit I better
not have that banana I better not have
any of that I better not have you know
that winter squash it's too many
calories too
starchy and and they and and they get
scared because they're trained through
the trend the trendy trap of high
protein high fat sure if you're not
pregnant and if you're a guy listening
to this you're not going to get pregnant
you want your high fat High trendy diet
I'm not go ahead if you if it's you feel
like it's doing you good I I'm fine
because it's not about that it's about
mommy and baby and what they need that's
what it's about it's not about what
Anthony William likes or Anthony William
loves or Anthony William believes and
it's about what mom mommy and baby need
and so what happens is some moms and
I've seen this and I've had calls from
it I've had to talk to people about it
have contacted me that they've gone you
know so they were so strict in their
high protein just vegetable meaning you
know salads and high protein diet which
is high fat because it's you know it's
high protein high fat with other fats in
there lot lots and lots of coconut oil
and lots and lots of fat and lots and
lots of this you know healthier versions
of course all healthier stuff that could
be fine for some guy who's not pregnant
or fine for a woman who's who's just you
know maybe maybe trying to try a
different diet but because they were
pregnant they got underweight babies and
they got under uh they got uh less
breast milk on top of it less breast
milk they had a goat formulas they had a
goat formulas and they and and their
babies were underweight born
underweight be because they followed the
trend to such dots and teas they crossed
their tees and dotted their eyes so much
so far on that Trend where it's like
high protein high protein and they
really stuck to it to such a degree that
they didn't give in on a treat that had
glucose meaning fructose or sugar they
stayed away from bananas they stayed
away from critical things that give
babies micronutrients vitamins minerals
and glucose to develop they got underway
away babies they stayed away from
potatoes red potatoes purple potatoes
they stayed away from those things
beautiful gold potatoes because they
were such in fear of it from trendy
traps and moms are suffering from it
something to think about what that means
is don't be concerned about protein be
concerned about your calories be
concerned about your calories coming
from more of some kind of sugar Source
that's not table sugar God forbid and
not not corn syrup or anything like that
but sources like potatoes okay really
important like winter squash really
important okay like you know artichoke
hearts which is a starchy kind of you
know a few brussel sprouts which is
really starchy these are some things to
get some important nutrients too and and
lots of fruit different kinds of fruits
not just a pint of small berries because
it's allowed in your diet you know more
than that different kinds of fruit
fruits and more of them like a melon
have a melon in the morning have lots of
slices of of of beautiful melon your
baby will love you when it's when your
baby's in the womb and and developing
inside your uterus your baby will love
it because your baby will be getting
what it's supposed to be getting from
breast milk after your baby has arrived
and then and then you know your baby
want he or she wants that breast milk
filled with glucose and you want to keep
your breast milk good so you want to
make sure you lots of fruit you want to
E look you can go back to your high
protein High extremely high fat diet
Trend after you need your breastfed
maybe maybe a you know you can still
have some protein and you still want
different vegetables and leafy greens
which is really good protein you still
want you still do some animal protein
I'm not saying you can't do animal
protein while
pregnant that's not what I'm saying this
is an important thing to understand you
can still have some it's just it can't
dominate the entire diet and you can't
be afraid of fruit you can't be afraid
of a potato while pregnant because of
what I'm seeing and I knew about that
many years ago too many many many years
ago so supplement wise while you're
pregnant just know be careful on what
kind of herbs unless you're really
Guided by your practitioner a doctor a
really good practitioner that knows
about pregnancies and everything else be
careful about herbs and stuff because
here's the thing you don't know what
your baby likes you don't know how your
baby's going to react if you don't react
to something that's you that's Mommy
that's not baby we don't know how
babies's reacting to something we don't
know that so don't do any exotic crazy
herbs don't do anything like that you
know you're doing something really
gentle you're doing a little bit of you
know a little bit of a sip of lemon balm
tea and you're doing a little bit of
that or you're doing something gentle a
little touch of peppermint tea or you're
doing you know some nettle leaf tea
something you know gentle filled with
lots of nutrients and you want a cup of
that it's fine unless you got a
practitioner that really knows their
herbs really knows their herbs and
they're even
cautious and that's perfectly fine too
and you know but but what I'm basically
saying is we don't know what babies's
doing reacting really to something that
you know something that we're taking
it's same thing like that with way out
supplements here's to deal with
supplements if you take something like
evening primrose oil which is is
actually you know is actually what it's
something you can use if your baby's
missing the deadline and of birth and
your baby's like yeah your baby's like
not on time and you know the doctor's
talking about inducing labor you know
evening primrose can really help induce
that labor can really help push Things
Push things through but get the baby to
move through but your baby shouldn't
react to Primrose Oil evening primrose
your baby shouldn't react but wait if
there's a capsule that has 50 different
things in it 50 different herbs and 50
different things and vitamins and
minerals or 50 different you know amino
acids of different kinds and you know
mean meaning like kinds that aren't
really good versus kinds that are
naturally in a
food what I'm saying is you got if say
you got a complex supplement you got be
cautious on those like keeping it's
somewhat basic somewhat basic is what
I'm trying to say so it's important to
know it's like mono mono and I don't
mean mononucleosis like I talk about a
lot I mean mono food sometimes is really
good for pregnancies not having a
billion Foods on your plate a billion
Foods you know not having a dozen Foods
on your plate at
once not having being just a little bit
more sensitive to to
concoctions concoctions for the pallet
if you go out to dinner at a fancy
restaurant and you know and there's just
throwing at you all kinds of different
things and it's just you know and it's a
lot of different sauces made of all
different kinds of concoctions and all
things be careful with that is what I
mean keeping more mono mono eating you
know I dig mono eating for healing too I
do I do I can't tell you how many people
got their lives back from eating ban B
and romae lettuce banana and
celery by
itself and got their lives back I can't
I can't even tell you how many decades
I've been able to pull people out of the
trenches of Hell literally meaning with
their illness and what they've G what
they were going through from banana and
and celery for a little while point is
is mono is not a bad thing and when
you're pregnant you want to you don't
want it complex to such a degree you
don't want to be fancy restaurants
eating complex kind of combinations or
even Abominations of food be careful be
careful and that's something to consider
keep it more mono you know you're having
a few potatoes and you know you're
having some you know steamed you know
baked winter squash little bit if you
want to sprinkle a little touch of olive
oil on there you can if you want meaning
something for you know flavor or a
couple of other different things some
different herbs and spices that are
really really mild I mean you can do you
can do things like if you want to keep
it as mon as possible you don't know
what you're going to get in restaurants
when it comes down to your baby saying
hey I don't like that I mean you might
like it like the taste but your baby's
like wait a minute I don't like this so
that's something to consider um like
every show it goes by too fast and I
feel like I can't even touch the topic
the way I want to uh we're going to do
another pregnancy show we're going to do
a third and I think we're going to do a
fourth I I'm not even done with with the
supplement part I think I think there's
still stuff to do and I haven't even
touched the foods so I'm so
sorry maybe I rambled a little too much
but the points were important very
important I know it covered stuff
similar to the last one but I wanted to
cover it more in depth please forgive me
please forgive me and we're going to do
another show and we're going to cover
more that's what we're going to do just
know I care take one day at a time just
know I'm proud of you and just know
you're an amazing person bless your
heart I love you dearly take one hour at
a time let's all move forward together
and uh I really do love you
bye-bye