live anthony william the medical medium
we just released the free is a bird
meditation
wait to you try it it's a surprise like
no other
here we are live i'm going to tell you
guys about the free is a bird meditation
the power it has to heal emotional
wounds
is unmatched like any other when you try
this meditation prepare to be mind
blown so it's the third meditation
released it was the big surprise for
today
have you tried it excellent meditation
marge you said
incredible and this meditation
helps to relieve emotional pain within
minutes in people it's that kind of a
powerhouse
and i'm giving you a forewarning okay it
takes you for a ride
it it flies you above the emotional pain
and hardship
and it frees this cage that wraps around
the soul
so prepare yourself for this one so the
free is a bird meditation
release today the power this has to heal
the soul
unmatched it's an experience you have to
you just have to try
but i'm going to give you that
disclaimer that forewarning on this one
okay
because these meditations actually work
it's a big difference when meditations
actually work work where they
release emotional pain and they
heal betrayal and broken trust and they
heal wounds from broken relationships
and losses
so i'm preparing you right now that's
what's going to happen in this free is a
bird meditation
it's that medical medium podcast at
apple podcast if you listen to this
meditation at another platform that's
not apple podcast it's going to be
censored in some way
you're not going to get the full version
it's not going to or either upload right
so it's
medical media podcast at apple podcast
that's the platform
in order to hear the freezer bird
meditation it's free
this this is a free resource and a
mind-blowing one
and it reconnected you with with as a
child flying in your dreams
pia said incredible this this is uh
rhonda says it was amazing you have no
words it you know
i want to tell you guys something about
this meditation right here okay
and this meditation
is a journey
to not just free the soul but
to leave the pain that we deal with
in our emotion in our emotional state
down below
us as we fly above it as we fly above it
and this meditation that spirit of
compassion has created for me
over the years and it's another one i
haven't released
until now okay this meditation i've used
you know with family i've used with
friends and i know i've released other
meditations over the years i've have
always released meditations over the
years for many years now
but this one right here is a whole other
experience
i'm preparing you for this one so you
have to
just be prepared when you do this
meditation
okay because it really is going to be an
experience you haven't felt before
it's a medical medium podcast at apple
podcast i'm giving
you that right there that forewarning
and
um actually says the meditations have
been so uplifting
this one right here actually unlocks and
frees the wire
cage that's around the sole and that
wire cage is made
up of broken relationships friendships
confrontations misunderstandings being
judged
losses in your life all these things
that we kind of put we push aside we
push aside
and it builds up and it builds up and it
stays in us and it stays with us
and it gets in our way then we can't
trust
and then we make decisions out of the
fact that we can't trust
so we make decisions that may not be the
best because of this you want
this pain this emotional pain that so
many carry out
and if you got anxiety or
depersonalization
or you got any kind of mild depression
or anything going on
this meditation is to help you get above
it all to give you that
chance and i hope you guys hope you guys
have
listened to this one it's the free of a
free is a word meditation
it's a medical medium podcast at apple
podcast and that's the official platform
that's uncensored so you can hear the
uncensored version which is so powerful
um mergiana said i did the brain
meditation
incredible um gene says just joining
where do i find the meditation gene
you find it at medical medium podcast at
apple podcast
that's where you find subscribe the link
is in
the description so that's where you can
see it the link is in the description
and make sure you subscribe
it's a medical medium podcast at apple
podcast it's a free resource that's the
uncensored version it's where you go
and that meditation you can also try the
moon meditation also after you do the
freezer bird meditation you can try the
brain meditation
these are the most power three most
powerful meditations
out there right now circulating in the
world
the most powerful ones because they come
from above
that's the difference these are not
man-made meditations
so that's what you have to know it's so
important to know that
because they come from above they're not
man-made they
actually work and they're easy to do
i guide you through it and i hold your
hand and i walk you through it
so the link is in the description you
have to check that one out
phrase the bird meditation and it's free
a free resource
no commercials no advertisements no
infomercials they're not at the medical
meeting podcast
that's not gonna happen as of right now
no way so you can listen to
medical media podcasts and listen to it
not only free
but free from commercials and all of
that
and you guys i was so excited to release
this meditation i can't even tell you
like
it's been days and days and days i've
been focused on it i've been so excited
i know the power it has i know what it's
going to do for you guys
and where it's going to take you guys on
your healing journey i'm going to answer
some questions too
because i want to answer questions how
are the meditations working for you
um and i can answer any questions you
guys might have
so it's really important there too while
the green they've all been so powerful
hard to describe how healing it's beyond
words
this one i love this one you know a lot
of times we go through a life
we're misunderstood has that ever
happened to you guys have you guys ever
you know lost something important to you
in your life have you ever been betrayed
have you had somebody break your trust
or broken promises throughout your life
maybe a broken relationship did someone
cheat on you
did you have a divorce in your life
which is so difficult
what kind of challenges have you been
going through are you going through
financial challenges
this meditation is critical for that
critical for also alleviating fear
and anxiety and pain emotional pain
it's got the power to give emotional
relief
within minutes that's what the free
free is a birth meditation will do and
margie says it's truly freeing
incredible and um tammy says i love the
meditations
but i keep falling asleep during them
laugh out loud that's fantastic because
because if that's what it's doing then
you're healing
you're healing on a deep level because
when you fall asleep during one of these
meditations
i'm still there guiding you through it
and the healing process is happening
through the subconscious mind
so it's really really powerful your
neurons in the emotional center of the
brain are still connecting to the
meditation
you can't go wrong with that um you love
them all it's i saw that comment coming
up that's incredible too
um and so we all get lost and we all get
disconnected down here it's the way it
works on planet earth freezer bird
meditation can really help
you guys should check out did you check
out the coffee matcha
chocolate episode check that out if you
can
please and and share that one that
episode
it's an epic episode packed with
information
it's the uh seventh episode i think it's
the seventh episode
so um lorraine l i'm loving all these
meditations lorraine what do you think
about the freeze of bird meditation
i was thinking about you lorraine about
this one because i know you know a lot
about meditations i know you're really
seasoned and experienced and i was
wondering what you were going to think
about this one
and i was kind of excited to know what
your feedback would be
trisha said i fell asleep to the moon
meditation and woke up to the free as a
bird meditation tricia
that's incredible you're welcome you're
welcome that's that's incredible
so proud of you really am because you're
doing this hi again alexandra um
ichoda says they really are easier to do
than any other meditations i've tried
that's what meditations are supposed to
be they're supposed to be
giving not taking so i just want to tell
you that a meditation
because i learned this from spirit of
compassion a meditation is supposed to
be only giving to you
not taking anything from you meaning not
taking
energy not taking your thoughts your
time it's not supposed to do that
this is a med these are meditations that
only fulfill
and give and then get rid of poison
that's in our soul get rid of hardship
and hurt
but man-made meditations are still great
i still recommend them someone likes
them hey
that works you do it whatever if you
love doing that but
they're more difficult to do because
they actually spin your wheels and they
they make you
work for it but at the same time don't
give you enough
back i hear this all the time i hear it
from gurus that i know
spiritual healers that i know out there
in the world and they'll tell they'll
tell me that there's a lot of
meditations that work and don't work
and these are geared to do the work
for you i'm guiding you through it
they're actually releasing the pain
suffering the emotional loss and the
fear and
because these meditations are from above
something really important to know try
it try it if you're if you if you guys
want to
for sure um amber says i'm dealing with
heartbreak wow
and and you love someone deeply and um
you don't know if we're good for each
other will this help you yes i would
what i would recommend okay if you're
going through that
i would recommend the moon meditation or
the free is a bird meditation so i would
probably go back and forth on both of
those
if you got a lot of fear though
somewhere inside of you
the brain meditation that's a really
good one too or you had really serious
losses
that one would be really good the brain
meditation but you guys
share these if you can we're a grass
roots movement
is what we are this whole movement
has been built on people actually
healing
versus money dumped into things and pr
and marketing and all that we didn't
have any of that spirit and i
okay spirit of compassion and i didn't
have that it's always been about
someone healed and told somebody else
another person healed told somebody else
so if you can share these episodes so
other people can heal so
because when i wake up in the morning
i'm like okay who needs to heal
who needs this information who needs
the powerful experience that they can
have
so they can move past what's holding
them back who needs to heal in some way
both physically with the books and both
emotionally with the meditations
michelle l says my favorite is still the
moon that that's awesome because the
moon is that powerful michelle i'm
hoping i could top that one
in in your heart and deliver a
meditation that you'll be like whoa this
one's actually now my favorite
but free as a bird is that powerful and
i'm glad the moon is too that's
incredible and i'm gonna make sure i
keep on delivering to you guys because
there's more to come this is the third
meditation
don't miss out on this one the healing
that can happen
is just incredible um alyssa said hey
alyssa brain meditation blew my mind
discovered powerful truths about my own
courage and connection to soul
moon meditation was to uh was so
cathartic
can't wait to try free as a bird i can't
wait can you share it too with other
people too that you think that could
really benefit
anyone um so important that's really
awesome that you guys are experiencing
this
and you're really doing these
meditations i'm so proud of you
it's really so great um aysling
said oh my god me too i am knocked out
of sleep too
i go into deep sleep and i wake up at
the end that's
that is healing because what's happening
i'm doing the work for it for you so
that you can even
sleep during the meditation think about
that
you can actually sleep during the
meditation while i do the work with
spirit of compassion's information right
and healing technique so i do the work
as the messenger
so your subconscious mind is getting the
information while you're sleeping
and you're healing and that is really
powerful
it's really incredible um tobias say
tobias
it's amazing that you can listen to this
for free absolutely tobias
medical medium information has always
been for free and there's always been
this old saying out there
that if you have to charge for somebody
to think it's valuable
uh i don't buy into that okay i don't
all right
because i know that's the whole gig out
there and you know with all the stuff
it's like
charge then they actually think it's
worth it or valuable
so pay for it and then they'll actually
see it's worth no
that's not that shouldn't work like that
okay you give it out for free
if it's powerful it's powerful if it
works
it works okay medical medium books have
already saved millions of lives around
the planet
medical medium information has already
saved lives and celery juice is one of
the tools
um but the bottom line is these
meditations guess they're free
of course the link is in description
share it with someone else
for free share it with someone else so
they can heal
if you don't have an apple device go to
medicalmedium.com
and go to the menu see podcasts in the
menu and just listen to them for free
there
but apple is the place that i officially
lost it
well lost it officially launched it and
so that people can find their way and
not be lost
during their healing because that's the
whole point because it's uncensored
there and i was worried
that if i launched it on another
platform official
launch at another platform that you guys
would actually
not get the pieces you need you know
there's just lost clips in it
it gets it gets uncensored that's not
going to happen
these podcasts these episodes are
uncensored
on apple right here um so margaret
says coffee matcha chocolate episode was
super cool
shocked at the information thrilled to
know
share it with somebody if you can that
is a shocking episode without a doubt
violet says i'm so excited i just
purchased the omega celery juicer
and i'm reading your cleanse to heal
book that's the cleanse of heal book
right there
it's a medical textbook to heal people
i'm glad you got the celery juice or the
omega celery juicer it's the mm-900
hds it's on sale today i'm pretty sure
20 off that's 60 off it's a juicer that
i personally use
um i licensed my name to that company to
them for that
because you know they said they said
look we love what you do
um we want to have a juicer that is
above all the rest that actually
squeezes every last
bit of juice out of it you see it i'm
like yeah that's the only way to go it
saves people money
it's a juicer that pays for itself
that means when you get that omega
juicer the the mm-900 hds
when you get that juicer it pays for
itself
that means you buy less celery you're
getting more juice and at the
end of the year you just got a free
juicer and another free juicer and
another free juicer
so check that out okay and it's my my
favorite juicer is what it is it's my
favorite it's the mm-900 hds
still on sale since somebody mentioned
it still on sale
that's the juicer i love um okay so
it's it's a mega the omega juicer that's
the one
anyway um ashley says i feel i feel
lighter after going
through all the meditations yeah
actually they're that
powerful and you know that's so great
uh emilia do you do you do the
meditations yourself
yes of course i do and i feel bad about
it because
the brain meditation and the freeze of
birth meditation
i coveted those all through the years
because i don't think i actually
launched anything with those and now
it's like no you guys need these
i've done them my whole life cheryl i
just jumped on here where do i go and
find them
cheryl you ready medical medium podcast
at apple podcast the link is in the
description
okay if you don't have an apple device
go to medicalmedium.com
that's all and go to the menu you'll see
podcasts in the menu so you can actually
listen
right there for free but it's all free
so just
just go to medical medium podcast at
apple podcast listen to the free is a
bird meditation share it with someone
else your life will change
their life will change it helps to draw
out the emotional pain you fly above it
you get emotional relief in minutes from
the freezer burn meditation
try the moon meditation the brain
meditation
definitely try those okay if you want
that's the emotional healing side of
things
if you want the physical healing because
you got ailments or things like that
do the cleanse the heel book the medical
textbook right there
it's important to know lotus jan says i
love your coffee matcha episode and it
was great i grew up not
not reading coffee so so happy that
someone
like you is talking about caffeine lotus
incredible
that episode the coffee matcha tea
chocolate episode
mind-blowing the chemtrail episode
mind-blowing the fruit fear episode
mind-blowing the egg
eaters lose all episode mind-blowing air
fresheners
episode mind blowing you guys heard
these
um i'm dropping information no one's
ever heard out there
dropping information no one has ever
heard
out there on any of this stuff and i'm
releasing it
dropping it out there and yeah truth
bombs everywhere but you guys can handle
it i know you guys can handle it
corey if anyone ever had a question
about
you i say just head to his ig he has
healed millions the proof is in the
pudding
corey the street cred is there thank you
for recognizing that the street cred is
there
if you look there's a little label on
the front of that cleanse the heel book
right there
it says millions sold around the world
because millions of copies sold because
millions have actually healed from
medical medium information doctors use
them in their offices
i talk to doctors every day giving them
information every single day
they contact me and they reach out the
proof is there there's thousands of
healing stories
there's actually hundreds of thousands
of healing stories
and millions actually healing overall um
and kathy having weird dreams since
meditations that's the amount of healing
you're doing and pressing prince says
your meditations oh i missed that
comment up there i think it went up
presley prince said your meditations are
amazing find they truly work and are
very
powerful really looking forward to doing
free as a bird once again thank you for
sharing
pressing prints thank you for sharing
because i know you're sharing these
share the meditation out there share the
links
share it tell them to go to apple
podcast medical medium at apple
podcast please you know help others
through this way um
teresa lee says i love them this
meditations i wake up light-hearted and
full of joy incredible
it really is um please share and leave a
review
so if you guys look i hate asking you
guys anything
i really do i know i'm always about just
what can i do
for you guys what can i do to get you
information to heal like in all the
books
what can i do to get you information in
any way i can so you can get your lives
better and better and better and better
and i don't want to
be i don't want to like you know be a
burden on you guys and ask you anything
but if you can
if you got a chance go to apple podcast
leave a review
at the medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast if you can't leave a review
if you're digging the meditations if
you're digging these episodes these
truth bombs
so you know it would really be helpful
if you can so other people can find
their way
find the information and find their way
and that's a big deal that's really a
big deal so
um the link is in the description right
there
share the episodes uh carolina says yes
so easy and light
that's amazing right there um so
um robin says thank you so much you're
incredible
you're incredible because they know the
work you're doing on your healing
process
katie says newbie where can i find the
meditations katie
uh medical medium podcast medical medium
podcast
at apple podcast and look for the brain
meditation the moon meditation and the
free as a bird meditation your mind
will be blown it will be blown that's
the official
launch pad is apple podcast for the
medical medium
meditations and medical medium podcast
because that's the uncensored place
for these because these episodes
are mind-blowing with information that
would be sense or truth
information so i'm just letting you know
so on other avenues and stuff um
alexandra says anthony how do we decide
which meditation to focus on
i like doing the brain in the morning
and before bed i do the moon
and i added bird last night when you
post it well here's what i do
i like the brain meditation myself i
like it in the morning
that's what i do like i like the moon
meditation at night that's the one i
like free is a bird
i like in the afternoon i mean you could
do any of them at any time
that's what i've done a lot so it's
really cool
anyway um lynn says i'm so happy
that these can be done while sleeping
and i don't have to use eyesight i am
blind
thank you anthony you are awesome you
don't have to use eyesight
but you have eyesight on the inner on
the inner and you can
you can work with that and what you're
hearing from me
as i'm guiding you through and they are
that powerful you don't have to have
eyesight
you don't have to have the physical
eyesight so i'm so
happy about that i'm so happy um
ashley says yeah you need to be
uncensored yeah so anyway um
incredible you guys jennifer says i will
never purchase another
product i know what you are up against
oh my god and you know thanks you guys
are incredible look
the bottom line is i'm going to continue
to produce
so you guys have episodes to use for
your own healing
and to share i want you to be able to
heal
i want you to be able to rid emotional
hardship and pain at least the effects
of what has happened to us when we get
hurt in any way
emotionally i want you guys clear i want
you guys able to heal and move things
past you
it's why the books are here too help you
on that physical level
but i want to help you guys on the
emotional level like i've done in the
books but also i want to do it this way
too through the podcast
i also want you guys to be able to
protect yourselves and your family and
have the most powerful information
a podcast can ever offer hands down the
medical meeting podcast
offers more more truth and healing
information
that protects you than any other podcast
hands down without a doubt i was told
that the other day by a couple of
doctors
that are in there they're in a league of
their own in their in their field
two mds and they said they've listened
to all the episodes
in their practice they have an internal
medicine practice they listened to all
the episodes and they said hands down
out of any podcast they listened to in
health it's the most informative the
most powerful
the the most truth that comes out all of
it
and i want to make sure i continue that
with you guys and like i said check out
the juicer too
um someone mentioned it it's 60 off the
omega juicer
it's 60 off it's 20 it's 20 20
off in price and it's the mm-900 hds if
you're looking for a celery juicer that
squeezes
the juice out so that you save money it
pays for itself
pays for itself i'm excited about it
lately because i noticed that
my salary bill is going down because i'm
buying less celery because it squeezes
every last juice so i just
when you add that up by the end of the
year what that saves you
pays for the juicer over and over and
over and over again
lorraine l i've been unbelievably stuck
for over six years today something
shifted with the freeze of bird
meditation lorraine
that's blowing my mind blowing my
mind my god it's incredible it's
incredible
um you know i'm so proud of you guys i
really am
listen to the egg episode if you can
share that one
that one is it's jarring it's a truth
bomb
and i'm not telling you you need to stop
your eggs but you want to hear that
episode check out the caffeine
matcha tea chocolate episode wow check
out the air freshener episode so you can
protect yourself
air fresheners sent to candles clones
perfumes and how what that does inside
of
us check out that one fruit fear look at
the fruit for your episode too because
it's a whole nother level
and if you want you can try the
chemtrail episode which
this still shocks me when i listen to it
and um
anyway proud of you guys blown away
um snow i care i believe in you guys i
know you're working hard with your
healing process every day i'm just going
to make sure i focus on
what can i do for you how much can i get
to you guys
like how much information can i get for
you guys to you guys like
how much meditations how many of those
how many episodes
how much truth how much you know mind
blowing information
healing information just know that i
care and i believe in you guys
and pat yourself on the back okay keep a
light heart have compassion for yourself
you're a good person all of you guys you
didn't do anything wrong
nothing's your fault of why you're sick
or you had any struggles
keep a light heart know that i stand
with you