medium right here so you guys we're live
got a lot of talk about episode 15
launched today it's out
the fruit picking meditation that one
right there you gotta try even have some
fruits with me here i got some apples
because
that's in the meditation right there so
you're gonna have to check it out
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
just so you know
got some raspberries too i don't know if
you ever picked raspberries
if you ever gone someplace and picked
them or pick them off the side of a road
or anything have you gone to a pick your
own apple orchard
and picked your own apples really
healing i've got some blueberries right
here look at this
and i also have celery juice here too
but i
to tell you guys um this meditation
is an anti-anxiety meditation
just anti-anxiety meditation instead of
anti-anxiety medication
you know you know i want to kind of move
you guys over to anti-anxiety
meditations is what i want to do because
that's the way to go and you know i mean
a friend of mine said you know what i
got off of my anti-anxiety meds
and he said i got off of my anti-anxiety
medications with your anti-anxiety
meditations
all right so anyway and of course you
don't have to do that you can keep your
meds be happy it's all good i'm just
saying
that that's these meditations are so
powerful
so incredible hey michelle miller hello
everybody's coming on
um but i want to tell you guys this
fruit picking meditation is is a special
one
in my heart because you know it
it has the power to reverse ptsd for one
has the power to eliminate
depersonalization
has the power to eliminate anxiety drop
it down
minimize it get rid of it over time it
just has
just such an amazing healing powers and
i don't know if you guys got to the
meditation it's that medical media
podcast at apple podcast in case you
don't know
i don't know if you got to it yet but
when you get to it you'll
you'll remember they're right in there
when you get there there's a worm
in the apple in the meditation so
kind of look for that when you get a
chance okay uh jennifer says such
beautiful meditation
it's so gentle but powerful exactly and
it connects us to the fruit trees that
connects us to the fruit orchards
and you walk down this country road
lorraine l hey good to see you glad
you're here this one made me
unexpectedly emotional whoa
it's really interesting you know
lorraine i know you've gone through so
much in your life
you're really seasoned you like know
health big time you know all about
health you've tried everything you've
done all kinds of stuff
and um if it got you emotional whoa then
that's that's really
incredible because just you know so much
healing is happening and you know all
about healing
crystal says the moon meditation last
night was whoa powerful healing you guys
are doing the moon meditation
have you done it so i want to tell you
about that we had that blue moon
yesterday right
last night and um i did the moon
meditation again so if you want to know
where that is it's medical mean podcast
link is in the description so you know
but i did the moon meditation too i'm
gonna do it again tonight
because we're still in that epic
that epic moon we're still in that epic
moon
if you guys have done the moon
meditation last night do it again
tonight
do it through this epic moon for sure i
mean
you can't lose the amount of healing
that can happen
it's just incredible link is in the
description
anyway so i'm going to talk about some
some different fruits and stuff like
that in a little bit too
got some wild blueberries in the moment
here and in the meditation
you can actually pick the wild
blueberries now when you're in the
meditation just know
you don't have to have ever experienced
um picking fruit before in your life in
order to heal from this meditation
you don't have to you could actually
experience it
all on its own in this meditation the
power that happens there but if you had
a chance in your life to do it
and pick fruit of any kind pick
raspberries you know along a country
lane in your life or
in a in an apple and a raspberry
grove somewhere a bramble grove
somewhere i mean if you've ever had a
chance you could reconnect with the
power of this
for healing ptsd um the link is in the
description
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
don't miss out this is
episode 15. and then you got the brain
meditation got the moon meditate the
moon meditation you guys got to do again
tonight you got it if you haven't done
it
you're missing out we got this big epic
massive healing moon and i know some of
you guys are like the moon is evil
the moon is dark the moon is the moon is
like
the devil's in the moon and look out for
the moon it's
the moon is witchy it's it's it's
witchcraft the moon is
it's it's you know it's whatever it is i
know that
some of you guys are really get upset
about the moon i've noticed that i've
seen it in a comment here and there
we're like
no stay away from the moon you're not
supposed to do anything with the moon
i get it but listen try it try it
do some healing and try it okay do some
healing and try it it's an
epic moon the moon meditation draws
out that pus and i call it pus you know
poison and pus it draws it out
and i'd rather have you do the moon
meditation
and keep that old wound deep down inside
of you
that's all and yellow and
and you know and all of that and just
harboring that inside of us like
betrayal well you know you got hurt one
time you emotionally somebody
emotionally hurt you betrayal broken
trust you got let down
um ptsd depersonalization depression
okay i want to go back to the fruit
picking one though
episode 15 the fruit picking meditation
what's incredible about this meditation
okay is it's amazing for depression
for depression amazing
it's an anti-depressant
meditation is what it is that's what's
incredible about the fruit picking one
you do it over and over again and you
get in touch
uh alexandra i listened to the apple
picking and moon meditation last night
it's beautiful really enjoyed the fruit
picking
i love the warm part right remember the
warm part that worm
that's the bad stuff inside of us and
you gotta hear the meditation to know
what happened to that worm
you know what's really important um
anyway dana dana says thank you so much
you saved our lives
we'll just thank you for just doing what
you're doing working hard on your
healing process
are you doing your celery juice right
there look at that one
look at that one i have that's a big one
right there
it's 32 ounces so um that's that's the
way to go
um irma says we have a grateful
fruit grapefruit an orange farm what
what a grapefruit an orange farm and
allow
customers to pick and they love it right
i'm oh my god why didn't i bring a
grapefruit right now
and an orange i'm supposed to have an
orange with me you know that would be
really great
especially with kids picking the fruit
we are in bay view
texas incredible you got you got citrus
i love citrus you know that
you know that um picked an avocado from
my tree last night
incredible medical mean way that's
really cool you picked one of those you
got an avocado tree incredible
um you know guys the fruit picking
meditation it really does
rewire it rewires
there's the power of nature and picking
fruit in a meditation is unmatched as
far as rewiring
certain fuses that we have in our brain
in the emotional center of the brain and
because that's what you're healing you
know the anxiety show um you guys listen
to the anxiety episode because that's a
mind-blowing episode right i just
released that
um before this fruit picking meditation
the anxiety show i talk about the
emotional center of the brain how it
gets
injured you got to hear that episode too
you really they go hand in hand there's
so much anxiety right now out there
so much depression right now we're in a
really crazy time right now
and anyway medical media podcast at
apple podcast
medical media podcast apple podcast
leave a review
if you enjoyed the moon meditation or
any of it please
leave a review there um because it's
really helpful
it really is i try not to ask for
anything from you guys i try to
make sure everything's free free free
free what can i do know this no charges
know this just everything free
but if you can leave a review at apple
podcast the medical media podcast
that would be so amazing and share um
i mean honestly how much that would help
you wouldn't believe
so hello medical medium i am hooked on
you and your amazing messages
you get you're fascinating um karen
awesome thanks for thanks for working on
everything you do in the books dude
cleanse the heel right here it's a heavy
medical tech basically it's a very heavy
book it's a big book
it's a medical textbook over its recipe
book too in here
wrapped up in with everything else 75
recipes
over 200 symptoms and conditions anyway
look you guys when it comes down to
depression
we start to lose a part of our like
neurotransmitter function
when we're depressed and we're depressed
and we're depressed and going through so
much
and what happens is that
neurotransmitters they get really wonky
if we're in a state of severe depression
if we're in a state of high anxiety
and the fruit picking meditation is so
powerful
for healing this and
it's really an antidepressant which is
so powerful darcy said loved the moon
meditation and did moon meditation again
last night cool
i'm doing again tonight um
because every night especially with this
epic moon you don't want to miss it
hey nicole just said i just listened to
the whole anxiety episode
incredible i hope you loved it did you
hear that part when i was like hello
pesticide company
pesticide insecticide company um can you
come here with your deadly chemicals and
spray my lawn and spray the inside of my
house
doesn't matter if my little kids breathe
it in uh it's safe right
oh it's not safe wait it is safe oh wait
you're not supposed to tell me that
oh wait okay why don't you come here i'm
going to go see my doctor because i have
to go see my doctor about my anxiety
you come here and spray my whole lawn so
my kid's playing it and make sure you're
spraying the inside of the house too
i don't know if you heard that part in
the anxiety episode but
i try to tell people you shouldn't be
spraying that stuff you want to keep
your family safe
um anyway so julia said last night i did
the moon meditation and oh my god
it was like electricity throughout my
body incredible you know julia
i'm gonna do it again say hey dr fun
whoa
dr fonz here incredible so an amazing
medical doctor
um healing people helping helping with
people's health in so many ways
incredible that so many people are here
ashley applesauce good to see you the
moon is amazing and powerful you could
feel it incredible i'm glad you're not
afraid of the moon
there's people that are afraid of it and
i understand i get it i'm not i'm not
like upset about that i understand
jade says where's the moon meditation
link is in the description
apple podcast medical medium at apple
podcast that's the uncensored platform
that's the one you want to hear it on if
you hear it on another platform
it's going to be censored little pieces
missing i'm a very
censored guy it's crazy i mean that's
what happens when you
get people better and millions heal
around the world from
you know celery juice you think you
think the industries want this
to actually be around and be out there
and people getting better from it no
they don't no they don't
so that's it right there so that's the
apple podcast i mean the macamian
podcast at apple podcast and that's the
moon meditation that's a fruit picking
meditation i just saw that
so yeah um you love the moon meditation
maria awesome are you gonna do it again
tonight
and you're gonna do it did the moon
meditation i loved it but when you said
you can open your eyes
oh the comment went up there i don't
know why they go so fast sometimes it's
unbelievable
listen all i know you guys is that these
are anti-depressant
and anti-anxiety meditations and
you know the power they have for helping
you heal
and lorraine elle says can you believe
i've never been fruit picking
it made me want to be a child again and
go fruit picking incredible
incredible um you know
look you guys i think uh trisha marie
hey
trisha maurice here um so i want you
guys to have every chance you can to
heal
and these meditations are part of it so
there's still an epic moon going on i'm
going to do it tonight but
i'm going to do the fruit picking
meditation too today
susan lynn says i wish there was a cure
for tinnitus
the cause of my depression
i'm looking in medical medium cleanse
the healing you could always bring this
book to your doctor if you want to
and a lot of doctors have them anyway
but in here if you look
very interesting you'll see over 200
symptoms and conditions and you'll see
the causes
of things and you'll see tinnitus in
here and
tinnitus is in here along with so many
other things i mean you guys this is
the book and this book's already healing
people around the world
and has healed people by the thousands
and thousands and thousands right now
it's being reported that this book is
saving lives like the other medical
medium books so
so you're dealing with tinnitus and
tinnitus is really brutal
if you look right on here as i mess up
my book here
you'll see tinnitus in there
and you'll see the cause and what to do
for it and you look and there's all
kinds of cleanses and stuff you guys
this thing's on sale right now at
amazon.com us
i mean it's it's more than half off it's
unbelievable really
so affordable and at this time of year
that's the perfect thing
um so mina
listening fruit picking today which was
impressive experience
after that in the afternoon i got
healing energy whoa that's incredible
so proud of you that's amazing so i got
the wild blueberries and the fruit
picking
meditation i talk about the wild
blueberries down the side of the country
road
you're walking down that country road
your feet are touching the pebbles
on the dirt road and when you look to
the left
there's wild blueberry bushes on the
side of the road and you go in there a
little bit
and you end up picking some i mean how
incredible
all through my life i've always known
this because the spirit of compassion of
how
healing this really is it just is so
healing
elizabeth i did the fruit picking
meditation this morning and it took me
back to the time of picking figs off my
family's tree in mexico
whoa a very wonderful experience
elizabeth that's amazing
and it's very healing you could do that
fruit piggy and you know when the depend
on time of the year it's gonna be it's
so helpful to do it
trisha maurices i just finished the
anxiety episode
um before the fruit picking meditation
whoa
incredible um we're live right now if
you guys want to know this is not a
recorded video we're actually live i'm
on here right now with you guys sarah
says
the anxiety episode explained every
single type of anxiety that my family
and i experienced so mind blowing
you know the thing is
is with the anxiety um with the anxiety
episode it's so packed
line for line that i told a friend the
other day listen to it again
so um she listened to it again she's
like i missed a lot of it
and i was like yeah listen to it again
let's do it again
and she was like i missed even more
there's so much in here
jennifer said my son did the moon
meditation last night
hard to get 15 year old olds to do
anything but he made it through and then
fell asleep
whoa so much healing done right there
it's so incredible
it's a big moon it's an epic moon i
would do it again
and the fruit like this and like i said
before
episode 15 the fruit picking meditation
it's incredible mindy says i'm asking
for healing for my birthday tomorrow
oh happy birthday like a pretty happy
birthday to you okay
and um yeah you guys i want you guys to
be able to get all the healing you can
get in
pressing prince said cleanse the heel is
a must for everyone
it really is the best book i have ever
owned that's an honor coming from you
because i know you know a lot about
health books and everything else um
that's really an honor
that's that's a massive compliment right
there pressing prince
because i know i know you know the whole
jam out there
and what's going on and what's happening
i know you actually know all that
um you guys incredible so so much
healing to be done
so much to do so medical medium podcast
at apple podcast
you don't want to miss these
opportunities the
moon is epic still and that heart says
i did the moon meditation then listen to
the egg podcast you know something
that egg podcast that right there is
is mind-blowing the egg podcast episode
and thank you for listening to the
episode because
i gave that episode everything i had
and it is just a powerhouse hey lunell
is here
hey loon you made it i think what are
you i think you're you're overseas right
so it's hard to catch these time frames
so it's good you caught it in the middle
of the afternoon right now
so you said hi don't know how you do it
but thank you for being able to
understand how it feels to live with
certain conditions
even though you do not have them it's
incredible you know
loon and i just want you to know
something okay
even though i don't have them and i'm
blessed to not have them
and blessed to have soc in my life and
everything
i still have to understand what
suffering is when someone's suffering
with it and living with it
and since i was a child at age four it
was told to me
then and that from spirit of compassion
that i had to actually not only
understand it
but feel it to a point to a point that
was
definitely almost dangerous when i was
young but i
had to still feel it i had to still
uh resonate with it i had to experience
it in some way
and um so i i just that's why i'm able
to describe the symptoms and describe
all the struggles and understand it
i have to it's the only way to really
understand it or understand what
someone's going because i always say
unless you've been in their shoes
you don't know nothing unless you've
been in their shoes and
so spirit of compassion told me when i
was younger growing up look i want you
to
feel like it is to be in their shoes
just just as much as we can
and keep you strong at the same time
it's never it's never been easy
michelle says censorship sucks yo yeah
does it ever man
forget it my ig page you can get on
there you're kicked off in one second
it's unbelievable
um by the way you know i mean it's just
it's it's amazing
so looky guys i want you to know that
apple podcast is the uncensored platform
that's the platform to listen to these
episodes on because
that's the platform that's uncensored
all the other platforms
they're censored in some way for me
there's even if you don't think so
michelle sanderson i listen to the egg
podcast
i'll never eat an egg again i wonder if
there's egg
in chocolate because my acne flares up
so bad
and and fast when i eat a piece
chocolate wall that's
that the chocolate that that's the
caffeine so did you listen to the
caffeine episode
listen to the caffeine episode because i
talked about chocolate
matcha coffee the adrenaline factor
i talked about the caffeine you know
making the adrenals just
flood over and everything patty mary
my 12 year old son drinks 36 ounces of
what that's 32 ounces
36 ounces oh my god it's amazing
that's amazing 12 year old son drinks 36
ounces of cj every morning for three
years now
i need to have him do the meditations
now he is healing from adhd
oh my god that is
please tell him i am
mind blown and proud of him can't even
say it enough
um i mean seriously
the amazing kid amazing kid um
yasina says thanks aw you've been so
helpful with all your amazing work
healing isn't always easy
with your encouragement and your healing
tools it's possible the healing tools i
talk about
and i talk about i wish i had a bunch of
other foods with me right now but we got
the apples because of the you know
picking fruit meditation
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
you guys that's the place to listen to
it
it's a free resource it's like i don't
want any confusion here okay
i'm not trying to sell something like
that podcast like oh get to my podcast
because you better get to it because i'm
going to make all this big money when
you go to my podcast no
it's a free resource and i'm actually
like working really hard on
so that you guys have it it's a
docu-series it's not a podcast really
it's just
we call it a podcast but it's a
docu-series on
podcast you guys it's not coffee talk in
the morning work get the next guest
done get the next guest done who cares
today well next guest oh whatever
they said does it work not done whatever
no it's a docu-series on podcast to make
sure
you have the tools you understand your
illness and symptoms
that you know what foods to avoid like
the eggs and i'm not saying
you don't have to avoid the eggs if you
don't want to but i talk about why if
you do want to
um and so it's really important there
carmen says how do you choose which
supplement to take first out of the list
read the supplement chapter
i put all that information in here so if
you've got cleanse to heal
and you see all the supplements and
dosages and everything read the
supplement chapter the whole thing
it's in there you just gotta look for it
good question really good question i'm
glad you asked because it's important
it's important
uh rebunken says i tried the fruit
picking meditation this morning
really enjoyed it incredible and
elizabeth
says i could really taste those wild
blueberries do they have the wild
blueberries in mexico
i wonder if they do you know i never
knew if they did or not
um but yeah that's incredible um but you
could taste the wild blueberries right
because you you buy the wild blueberries
and stuff
because exactly you can get them you can
buy them now the frozen wild blueberries
have them right here
but it's hard to find a spot to pick
them live and stuff l
it's hard for people to understand
anxiety it so is
did you hear the opening of that episode
the anxiety episode where i go
come on knock it off what do you mean
you still have it
just exercise and get rid of your
anxiety what do you mean you're bald up
on the couch shivering and shaking
did you hear the beginning that one it's
hard for people to understand
anxiety i agree my mom advised me to
breathe deeper because it's a cure for
it
um the problem is with anxiety you get
the tightness of the chest
and focusing on your breath sometimes is
not the answer
it's really difficult really difficult
but i'm not saying mom's wrong or right
mom's mom's the best
anyway um but you know the the bottom
line though is
i want you guys to heal with all these
tools jennifer
bobbik says i keep your book in my desk
it's an invaluable
amount of information creating new
recipes along with you
love my fruit trees in the moon
incredible incredible
um really is you guys are amazing so
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
it's a huge moon still
still a huge epic moon scott
scott schroeder you said ad-free
podcasts
yes ad-free podcast
what is that why am i doing that uh
everybody doesn't do that like why would
i
exactly you guys i'm a number one you're
a ton's best-selling author
and i'm not supposed to have ad-free
podcasts just so you know
but i do and i want to make sure you
guys
aren't up against infomercials and
commercials and
all that stuff in the podcast it's a
docu-series
apps these are docu series episodes and
i don't want i don't want ads in their
old
ads i mean if you know i'm not doing
them now that's for sure
josh said i just did the fruit picking
meditation whoa
i fell right asleep in the middle it's
so relaxing i couldn't stay awake
here's how it works okay whether it's a
moon meditation
the brain meditation okay the free is a
bird meditation
the fruit picking meditation if you fall
asleep
in the middle of it or fall asleep in it
your healing
and your healing your subconscious mind
is actually hearing the meditation
and your neurotransmitters and neurons
and
the emotional center of your brain is
receiving all that information
your whole body is so you can fall
asleep during these meditations
these anti-anxiety meditations and
anti-depressant meditations
martina i am happy to see you live i'm
live by the way i'm live you guys if
anybody doesn't know
it is nearly eight o'clock in the
evening right now you know i try to get
on early
because you're you're overseas you know
or somewhere else on the planet and who
knows what time it is right
so yeah i just want to make sure you
know exactly exactly
i can't believe how so g says i can't
believe how valuable cleanse the heel
has been tiny changes has given my life
back
cleanse the heel is is a powerful book
it's
it's unmatched out there i hear it all
the time by doctors who know all the
health books out there
and there's so many so many pieces of
information for your digestive tract for
all kinds of different conditions and
symptoms and diseases it's
it's endless in there the information
anyway
so in the fruit picking meditation
you'll be able to
you know experience the fruit picking
and heal at the same time
and it's a big deal cornelius says thank
you
it is it is amazing in our logical
podcast oh
neurological podcast i forgot about that
you explained all my symptoms better
than i ever could
you know what
you know there's people out there they
go oh i know this and that there's
there's health gurus out there and
they're like
chanting their lymphatic system stuff
and they're chanting they're
they're chanting their spiel
on something about you know iridology or
something or they're chanting something
whatever it is and
that's great and all but do you really
know why people are sick
probably not number two
do you really know what people suffer
with and how they suffer
because if you don't know that then
i don't know you have to know
their symptoms better than they do
because if you don't you don't know what
it's like to be in their shoes so you
better understand it
you gotta you gotta because you gotta be
in the game
to get them better and you gotta know it
all link is in the description
and i still got more to learn from soc
for spirit of compassion i still got
more to learn
i just have to learn learn and learn
darlene says your podcasts are
mind-blowing
incredible oh share them you guys share
them
share them with anybody share them with
anybody please you know share them share
them
we're uh grassroots moving you know how
um
you said earlier one of the comments
right would you get you know how you
said i think with scott is that what
well you know how you said that that
there's no ads
it's ad free right because there's no
money being
tons of money being dumped in with big
pr marketing firms
there's none of that here it's
grassroots movement so share it if you
can
uh cornelius says coffee episode is
stunning
that's one of my favorites did not touch
coffee after listening for two
weeks now so difficult to give up oh
yeah it's difficult to give up
but i managed thank you incredible
incredible that's
a hard one to give up is that coffee
is is that coffee so it really is you
know but you guys
you know link is in the description
share it with other people
let them hear the moon meditation like
hey did you hear the moon meditation
i just want people better and you guys
know that by now
i don't have to say it jennifer fry hey
jennifer i'm glad you're here today
because you're here a lot
uh the moon meditation sure is purging
some massive stuff
during this blue moon whoa i thought it
was powerful on a normal full moon and
it is powerful on a normal full moon
but with this yeah that's what i was
saying
and the thing is we still got an epic
moon we're not done
it's an epic moon gotta take advantage
of it
do the moon meditation go to medical
medium podcast at apple podcast
we gotta do it um michelle l michelle oh
yo
she's an expert she's not an apple kick
incredible you're on apple cake
um you guys i'm so proud of all of you
you know that i got 32 ounces i'm still
mind blowing
my mind blown uh about 36 ounces
um my god a 12 year old doing 36 ounces
for three years best thing ever
best thing ever so you guys i want you
guys to know
that i care about you because i know
that you guys struggle
and you struggle with a lot of different
symptoms and conditions and i want you
to
heal and get past them more and more
share the information if you get a
chance leave
leave a review if you can at medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast if you
leave a review
that will help others because that's i'm
always like how can i help others
how can we do it sonia says the fruit
picking meditation was a great way to
remember
my past fruit picking experiences now
being in lockdown far from nature
that's why i wanted this one
out there it's a big piece big piece
terry hey the brain fog was spot on
right right the brain fog episode
spot on yeah i'm glad you guys don't get
upset about my
my sense of humor in there and stuff and
my jokes and stuff like that
you know i liked the b12 episode when i
was mimicking
impersonating a chicken and in the b12
episode i was impersonating a chicken
and the chicken was saying i'm getting
my body ready so you have b12
you gotta i'm not saying that that's
exactly how it works but you gotta
listen to the episode
because that's not how it works but
anyway all right you guys
love you much okay some more blueberries
and apple right here
that's uh raspberries and wild
blueberries
okay guys look i've got two apples right
here i'm going to eat these later
i'm not going to let these raspberries
go to waste definitely gotta eat these
fruit picking meditation do the moon
meditation too
kimberly miller kimberly is the moon
meditation still effective
if you do it in your room with with no
access of the moon yes
absolutely the moon can be behind a
building
it could be it doesn't matter the
meditation takes you and connects you to
the moon that's the whole point
uh the whole point so anyway you guys um
and valerie says yes had my strongest
effect from last night's moon meditation
thank you so cnnw
and it's always going to be healing even
on half moons wait
i want to tell you guys you got to do my
half moons too
because there's something that actually
incredi there's something incredible
that happens
on the half moon i forgot to mention it
in the meditation itself
um anyway love you guys and
hope you guys take care of yourself like
you do and
i'll see you next time all right bless
your heart
and remember um be easy on yourself
pat yourself on the back have compassion
for yourself take care