now we're talking about gallbladders
talking about adrenals kidneys
talk about kidney stones we're talking
about
lots of things we can talk about the
bladder too
but what we're going to talk about is
why
everyone thinks it's perfectly fine and
normal to have kidney stones and
gallbladder stones dysfunctional livers
dysfunctional kidneys adrenals that are
all burnt out we walk around and we
we just accept it or we don't know about
it and then when we learn a little bit
about it
we just accept it again or when we find
out we have a kidney stone or we have a
gallbladder stone
we think hey we better just eat a
certain way and it turns out that
certain way is actually disastrous for a
kidney stone gallbladder
a gallbladder stone it's interesting how
things work you guys i'm excited
this is the last day tomorrow's the last
day last
two days of the mm-900 hds sale
and it's important to know because 65
off it's
20 off save 65
on the mm 900 hds so today the sales
going on
tomorrow the sale is going on and i'll
show you how it works the whole bit
there's no metal gears in here and metal
on metal which gives you those metal
shavings nobody sees because they're
microscopic shavings and then you get it
in your juices
none of that's in here which is really
cool this is one bad
ass machine so anyway you want to be
on a device like a juicer
any juicer is fine right instead of a
medical device i told you about that too
you guys you don't want to be on other
medical devices because
you could have been doing other medical
devices like this
preventing you to be on other medical
devices right so
glad you guys are coming on i'm excited
hope you guys are catching this
and let's talk a little bit about it
about everything so here's what we do
we're raised on eggs who is raised on
eggs i just want to know
who's raised on cheese who was raised on
eggs
right you raised on cheese raised on
raised on that who was raised on butter
who's raised on butter nice stick of
butter right here
right red cheese
who's raised on cheese good to see you
guys we're live right now
were you guys how much cheese and butter
and eggs have you guys eaten
just just wondering how much cheese
butter and eggs
right a lot of cheese buttered eggs
raised on cheese butter and eggs
how many pizzas have you guys had
how many pizzas there's a pizza right
here in the medical medium kitchen
how many pizzas have you guys eaten
right
i'm not shaming anybody i'm not judging
anybody nothing like that
nothing like that at all i'm just
thinking what are we doing
to reverse all those meals we
ate all those meals what are we doing to
reverse
all that build up all that sediment in
the gallbladder right
that's your liver right there that's
your gallbladder right here the
gallbladder
gets filled up with sludge and sediment
and sludge and more sediment more sludge
and it gets heavy so our gallbladders
get heavy and then we get stones
building up in there too
and a big part of that is
all the eggs we've done all those years
all the butter we do all those years
right anybody that says butter's healthy
i just i just have to laugh
i have to laugh i can't you know dr
nesbitt rescue us
i have to laugh because
butter is really a tough one on the body
real tough
okay burns out the liver feeds all the
viruses and bacteria
feeds everything proliferates everything
that's bad for us
but what it also does is it causes you
to lose calcium out of your bones
so we're all in the business of just
blowing our calcium reserves out left
and right that's what we do
we blow all of our calcium reserves out
left and right
that's how it works we acidify our
bodies
with all that butter and all that cheese
got some cheese sticks right here
now if you guys how many of you guys
have done the cheese sticks
right cheese sticks done the eggs what
about
buffalo chicken wings you guys have done
all the buffalo chicken wings right
buffalo chicken wings what about the
chicken nuggets
how many guys done the chicken nuggets
you guys done the chicken nuggets again
you guys done that i know give me a 10
piece chicken nugget
give me a i'll take that 40 piece
chicken nugget i'll take that six piece
chicken nugget
hey how many chicken nuggets have you
guys done right and
right and then how much bread have you
done too really acidic
all that bread is really really acidic
how much bread have you done
something right there you know bread
cheese
eggs right
chicken nuggets fried battered stuff
how much of that have you guys done too
many too many
i just wanted to say too many i am
feeling so called out right now
right well it's okay it's okay
i'm not trying to be tough on you guys
it's okay if you did all that that's all
right
if you guys just came on here i'm
talking about kidney stones gallbladder
gallbladder stones
all kinds of different problems that we
get okay sediment in the gallbladder
all right important to know all that's
important
this is the mm-900 hds the sales lasting
today and tomorrow you can save 65
i'm gonna juice in a little while
because celery juice is critical for
cleaning up the sediment in the
gallbladder it's critical for cleaning
up the liver critical for cleaning up
the kidneys
dissolving stones that's the medical
device right there that's the medical
tool it's 20
off of megajuicers.com just so you guys
know so megajuicers.com
right now 20 off save 65
for the best juicer i've ever seen and
it saves money like no
other and that's what's incredible about
it if a head of salaries like two
dollars and fifty cents two dollars and
forty nine cents sometimes it's two
dollars sometimes you can get it for a
dollar
sometimes you can get ahead of celery
depending on what time of year
you know a bunch of celery you can get
you know cost a little bit more
sometimes it costs a little less
what i love about the juicer is that for
me i've had to buy
half the celery less half less celery
than i normally
buy so if i needed a case a week it's a
half a case
if you're somebody that needs a half a
bunch of celery
right a day then you're going to
basically
it's going to cut it down to a little
more than a quarter of celery you'll
need right a little more than a quarter
that's that's what i've been noticing
all this time so the juicer pays for
itself and pays for itself
if you're somebody that needs two
bunches a day then you're saving already
probably three quarters of a bunch
easy because it squeeze out so much
juice and then it adds up and it adds up
and then over the course of the year you
just bought yourself two new juicers
three
new juicers for free it paid for itself
cheryl said did all that
now i no longer have a gallbladder
which is why celery juice is important
all on its own you know for many years
people have come knocking on my door at
the office like i don't have a
gallbladder because i know
or i'd see they don't have a gallbladder
be like you know you're missing
your gallbladder right yeah i'm missing
my gallbladder
okay they take gallbladder pluck
gallbladders out of people left and
right
because they gotta they gotta pluck
gallbladders a lot of times they do it
without
having to some people have mystery pain
nobody knows what it is
it's a mystery pain and they pluck those
gallbladders out
just for the sake just for just for the
sake of it
they just pluck them out pluck them like
apples off a tree pluck put put
pluck pull pluck gall bladders goblins
gallbladders right
kidney stones are really common
everybody's got kidney stones it depends
on what's happening
so we'll cover that a little bit so
right inside your kidney you guys
inside your kidneys all that butter all
that butter ends up in the kidney
all that all those eggs end up in the
kidney all that cheese ends up in the
kidneys
sits in there on the shelf sits right
there on the shelf
you get the protein stones and the
calcium stones sometimes you get a
combination of both protein and calcium
stones
everybody's got it you may not know
olympic athletes have it they have
kidney stones
i mean i can't tell you how many olympic
athletes that come to me for help for
different stuff with their health as as
they're getting a little older
and next to you know they've got kidney
stones how's that possible
it's possible because if you're not
you've still if you're not eating good
you're eating really acidic you could be
really really really acidic and still
have lots of muscle and still be able to
perform but be really really acidic
but stuff all breaks down later on and
breaks down all
later on and breaks down inside those
kidneys right on the shelf right there
and these little
these little nooks and crannies in here
you get all these little tiny crystals
calcium crystals protein crystals
and i'll go into like why we get the
protein versus calcium so let's do that
protein versus calcium you guys just
came on here this the mm-900
just letting you guys know sale is over
tomorrow
65 off 20
off it's the mm-900 hds it's a mega
juicers.com it's your celery model
it's the only one that's on sale right
now at megajuicers.com
take advantage of that sale take
advantage if you can hello from france
amazing
um you know because everybody's asking
me for a juicer juicer juice which used
to use with juicer
what's the best juicer on the whole butt
the whole bit you don't do dairy
so many people so many people wait until
something comes like you just wait
you wait you're living your life and
living your life and then all of a
sudden
boom it hits you know a lot of people
got chronic illness they got autoimmune
and you don't need other things adding
to it you don't need all of a sudden
those kidney stones when you're already
dealing with autoimmune you don't need
all of a sudden that gallbladder problem
when you're doing
when you're already dealing with
autoimmune good to see you guys trying
to read comments as we're going along
i'm trying to juggle
literally juggle a whole bunch of stuff
right here spirit of compassion is
talking to me
i'm reading comments we're talking about
the juicer let's do this
so
we leach calcium is what we do we leach
it from
our bones that's how we do it okay we
lose our calcium as time goes on
right and
we all end up there we all end up there
and all our calcium ends up in our
kidneys and we
pee it out all the time we pee our
calcium out
every single day we pee it out that's
what we do
we peel a little bit more of our calcium
out every day even if you don't have a
big calcium stone in your kidney
you've got all these little calcium
crystals in your kidney your kidneys
build up all these tiny little calcium
crystals and we
we pee out those crystals every single
day we pee out those crystals
that's what we do so our frame
starts to slowly disintegrate as
every year and decade goes by a frame
slowly disintegrates our skull
starts to dissolve inside out inside
out that's where it starts to dissolve
okay that's where it dissolves
from the inside out it gets thin
and then you're 60 years old 55 years
old
sometimes 45 sometimes whatever
and you and you're walking along and you
slip and you bend your head
and you fractured your skull because
things are getting thinner
julie says you said in cleanse to heal
there's toxic calcium
is this what you are referring to leach
bone calcium the toxic calcium is from
dairy products
so that's the toxic calcium that's one
of them
the other toxic calcium comes out of
chemtrails floating out of the sky
man we are and you know comes floating
out the sky
it comes okay toxic calcium is also on
water supplies right
but toxic calcium is also in the dairy
products that's the calcium that's the
toxic calcium too and toxic calcium
causes
the leaching of our our you know good
calcium
that causes it as well because you know
and so
problem is we walk around so acidic and
then we're doing the caffeine you guys
and we're doing the vinegars we're doing
the caffeine we're doing the vinegars
and we're
leaching calcium left and right
and that calcium crystals build up in
the kidneys
and the reason why we leach it is we
have to buffer the acids we have to
buffer the acids
that's how our body works to protect
your organ brain your brain
and your heart to buffer the acid guys
just came on
sale is on for two more days on the mm
900 hds just so you know
two more days 65 you save
megajuicers.com the mm-900 hds
so really important to know
how protein works okay
protein doesn't break down in
everybody's guts anymore we don't break
our protein down we think we break our
protein down but we don't
because our hcl doesn't allow it we
don't have strong hcl anymore
everybody's losing their hcl
they're losing our hydrochloric acid
it's important to know
right here
okay our stomach
our stomach tends to wear out people's
stomachs wear out all we do is take our
stomach for granted
just take it for granted i'm gonna take
my stomach for granted
that's right i'm gonna take my i'm gonna
have
i'm gonna have a few slices of pizza i'm
gonna take my
stomach for granted who cares about my
stomach i don't care about my stomach
i'm hungry i'm hungry i don't care about
my stomach
let me take my stomach for granted right
wait i'm eating healthy here wait i'm
eating healthy
i mean healthy i got a nice protein
patty nice burger right here i'm eating
healthy
i'm eating my protein patty nope taking
your stomach for granted
taking it for granted right do you like
being taken for granted
i'm having my chicken breast right here
just
disclaimer 4-1-1 to the animal protein
people
okay i support animal protein diets and
i support plant-based diets
i'll rip apart the plant-based diet in
10 seconds flat
10 seconds flat i'm not biased and i'm
not sure this isn't an
anti-animal protein campaign but you
want to keep on doing too much chicken
too much chicken you're gonna burn out
those stomach glands
burn them out lila says
sylvia phil spinach is among those green
veggies
that contain the highest amount of
oxalic acid wrong
eating too much spinach may result in
the formation of calcium oxalate
oxalate wrong which can cause kidney
stones not true that's called
misinformation and that's what's sad
because you're going to carry that mr
information around
and that's really really sad no one has
ever eaten
enough spinach to prove that point okay
you know somebody that's gobbling down
barrels and barrels like spinach you
know somebody's eating a big giant
container or two of spinach
every single day did they get kidney
stones who do you know that ate that
much spinach are you talking about a
spinach leaf on somebody's salad
somewhere are you talking about in a
restaurant a fancy restaurant somebody
put a spinach leaf who orders spinach in
a restaurant do you go into a
restaurant did you order spinach at a
pizza place so it's it's spinach that's
causing the
the stones so um is that what it is
okay is that what it is because i'm kind
of curious gonna call this pizza place
because they sent me a pizza and i
ordered a giant spinach salad from this
pizza place
yep that's what i did hello
oh hello uh
yeah the yeah hi i ordered a pizza
yeah you didn't give me that gigantic
spinach salad i
ordered you sent me a pizza instead i
know you're a pizza place
yeah i know i eat pizza like once a week
for 20 years
what yeah i ordered a gigantic spinach
plate
because that's what's giving me my
kidney stones is that all that spinach i
order everywhere i go
uh-huh yeah so why did you send me a
pizza why didn't you give me that big
spinach
pie i asked for
no one's going around gobbling down
spinach
no one's no one's on enough spinach to
say ever in a million years that that
causes an oxalate that
that's an oxalate problem causing a
kidney stone who would know
everybody that's ever walked through the
door in my office for 35 years
who had kidney stones and surgeries left
and right didn't eat any spinach
hold on i i got a diner dropping off
something for me now
yeah uh-huh they're dropping off
i ordered from his diner a big spinach
salad from a diner and now i'm gonna
have to call them
i don't know why this diner sent me this
yeah i've eaten this so many times but i
wanted a big spinach salad
bobby's diner yeah you there yeah i
ordered a gigantic spinach salad that's
what i get at a diner
all these years how many diners have you
guys ever gone to huh did you order that
big spinach salad at a diner
well you gave me this what do you mean
yeah i know i eat this when i'm at
diners once in a while
but where's the big spinach salad i
ordered
because i didn't water it you're right
the thing is you guys
you guys the thing is is this okay i
understand there's misinformation out
there and and to the credit of the
person
you know to the credit of the person
that says you know that spinach causes
uh you know an oxalic acid stone or
you know actually causes you know a
stone a stone in the kidney
it's misinformation and i don't blame
you for having misinformation it's just
that information hurts people
it'll make someone who doesn't even eat
spinach anyway
it'll make them never eat a spinach leaf
if they even had a spinach leaf
two years ago in some weird mixed green
salad over a friend's house
the point is no one's eating spinach
spinach has never given anybody a kidney
stone
ever spinach is an incredible food you
should juice it if you get the mm-900
juice it
juice it with a whole bunch of different
stuff it's an incredible food
what i love like the mm-900 i'll run
spinach through here
i don't just do celery in here but
spinach helps to bring people back
it helps to bring you back from hell
it helps to bring you back from chronic
illness and autoimmune disease
medical medium spinach soup has brought
back a lot of people and
and it's misinformation it's so sad so
sad who eats
who's ever eaten enough spinach what
doctor's eating enough spinach to get
himself his own kidney stone from
spinach none
they get kidney stones because they're
eating eggs
that's eating eggs how many eggs have
you had compared to how much spinach
have you had in 30 years
meanwhile you will get a kidney stone
and it won't because of a piece of
spinach and because your caffeine your
vinegar
your kidney stones are caused by
caffeine they're caused by vinegar
acidic acidic foods and now kombucha tea
all the all the people yoga mamas with
their kombucha tea
yoga dudes with their kombucha tea will
end up with kit with kidney stones
they'll end up with kidney stones down
the road once they get past that age
30 and they're all getting paid age 38
and they've been used to drinking
kombucha tea for 10 years
they'll get their kidney stones because
they'll be on their vinegars and
kombucha tea and they're caffeine
and they'll be on their eggs still and
they'll get their kidney stones
that's how it works that's how it works
we've got a lot to cover we're going to
talk about stones we're going to talk
about
that we're going to talk about all kinds
of stuff i'm going to run a little
celery through here
here we go you guys i love this machine
every time i run a stick through it and
i never had that ever
with any other machine i tried all the
machines all of them this is a cold
press juicer
on sale right now by the way i've never
had this with any other machine where
this happens
ready saving money saving money
saving money saving money
[Music]
head of celery cost me 249.
head of celery cost me 249. i know on
tick-tock you can't see this
right cut in half
for me anyway almost cut in half
okay so juicer pays for itself for me
over and over again never had that with
any other juicer ever instead
the other juicers cost me more money
more money more money and that's what
they did
so i never had that where every time a
stick runs through i'm like
i'm saving money saving money
[Music]
she's just paying for itself celery
juice is critical for
kidney disease kidney problems kidney
stones
gallbladder problems bladder problems
i'll add that one in
bladder absolutely because bladder
problems
with all that strep in everybody's
bladder and all that
all the stuff with their bladders
there's also sediment in people's
bladders too they need to be cleaned out
half the cost question mark what do you
mean
i'll tell you what i mean okay
every any other juicer i've ever had all
the best ones the so-called best ones
expensive ones
i've i've purchased some of the most
expensive juicers there are
where it was insane it was stupid to do
and i did right
and i would run celery through it i have
to go to the store
and you know and get my case of celery
right
case of celery if you depending on how
much it costs for
a bunch of celery whether it's two
dollars or 229 or 2.49 or
1.99 for you know a whole bunch of
celery right
i'd have to go and get a case of celery
when i got the mm-900 hds
it was a little just a little more than
a half a case of salary
so it was a half a case of celery and it
was
life-changing for me i was like oh my
god what can i do with all the extra
money this is insane the juicer paid for
itself
over and over and over again because it
squeezes every last drop
out the pulp is dry it's fluffy
it's light it's dry there's no juice in
here
and the pulp's not moist you have this
juicer and you love it
an idiot amazing so what happens is
saving money saving money saving money
that's what i'm doing it's incredible
it's on sale right now tweet for
tomorrow today but that's it
sales over but at 65 dollars you can
save
[Applause]
and it's 20 off it's a mega juicers.com
it's the mm 900 hds but it's not just
any omega
it's the mm-900 hds you can use it for
any
any juice any kind of juice you want to
make it's fine you can use it
you don't have to have this juicer to
juice celery you can juice celery with
any juicer
totally so as long as you're juicing
celery that makes me happy
[Applause]
as long as you're juicing celery that
makes me happy
you love tammy says tammy winters says
you love
your juicer incredible you love this one
don't add anything to it you guys you
add something to it you're not
you're not going to be cleaning up those
kidney stones gallbladder sludge
you're not going to be killing off any
pathogens this is herbal medicine
herbal medicine you're creating an
herbal tonic
[Applause]
[Music]
this is not a vegetable
[Applause]
[Music]
celery juice eats away
at your stones in your kidneys eats away
at the sediment
and sludge in your gallbladder celery
juice
eats away the garbage that's stored up
in your liver
eats away right
your liver your gallbladder
and liver celery juice eats away it
enters into the liver through the
paddock portal highway
right portal vein gets sucked up into
there
and it eats away eats away at
all that sludge all that garbage in
there what's in there
which you guys have been eating for 20
years 15 years 30 years
how many burgers how many how many hot
dogs
how many anything what about nuts and
seeds just so you don't no one's off the
hook being a vegan
if you're doing it wrong you're eating
all those nuts and all those seeds
you're doing all those nut butters that
guess what that's really acidic
and you're gonna get those kidney stones
too many nuts and seeds
and all the fats and oils will give you
kidney stones and it'll still gunk up
your gallbladder you're not off the hook
as a plant person and i'm pro if you're
if you're on a plant-based diet stay on
a plant-based diet if you're on a
plant-based diet
stay on a plant-based diet if you're on
an animal protein diet that's what you
want to do stay on it
don't switch sides you don't have to
switch sides you have to run back and
forth
but but you need to know how to clean
things up either way because you can be
plant-based and dirty everything up and
and not heal in fact get sick
here's how the plant-based diet works
you eat lots of fat plant fat
until you get sick and then you get you
get run and scared
back to your eggs you get run and scared
back to your eggs
right because you're you're told that
you needed eggs like why aren't you why
aren't you doing eggs
saving money saving money
[Applause]
love it never had that with a juicer
before in my life
try them all
this is a cold cold pressed juicer
right and um
no metal gears grinding against
each other no metal gears
don't know a juicer better it's quiet
you can juice without tons of noise
you don't hear
[Music]
you don't hear all these crazy noises
you don't hear that when you're juicing
with this
the only problem with juicing with this
juicer is it's too quiet
for me because then i have to hear
spirit of compassion
when i really don't want to hear spirit
of compassion all the time
as you probably know if you read origins
of a medical medium in my
new edition
[Music]
anthony are you plant-based it's
it's a secret it's a secret
i might be it might be it might be
plant-based you never know
i love the plant-based diet love it love
the plant
what's the juicer's name see omega
juicers.com
but that's not the juicer it's the
mm-900 hds
okay so what you'll find in the mm
900 hds is you'll find dry pulp right
dry pulp that's where the money's at
the money's in the dried pulp right
that's where the money's at it's the
dried pulp
it's not the wet slimy pulp that you
lose
all of your juice it's the dried pulp
and that's where it's at
and it's important to know how that
works it's dusty dry you can dump the
pulp out
and this is very very very fibrous
celery right here
extremely fibrous right but what you
won't find
is that wet juice just dry
all the little pieces they didn't stick
they're dry right
that's that's the difference that's
where the money's at right there
that's where it's at
gotta strain your juice straining the
celery juice is important
keep that in mind so straining it's
really important
a little fell out there because i'm
being all
quick right here because i'm trying to
do this for you guys really quick so i
dropped a little touch of it
but can you imagine real wet pulp where
you lose all the juice anyway and then
you spill a little drop and now you're
like oh my god
now i really lost it all well that's
incredible really is incredible
so that's your juice right there let's
talk about what it does
so the key the whole key
about celery for for one it's herbal
medicine
it does something it's doing something
fast in people sometimes so quick their
gerd goes away boom one shot one week
acid reflux goes away fast nothing else
does that
april taft good to see you dr desmond
and that's what's amazing that's what's
amazing i saw your comment about dr niz
but
that's amazing on how it works quick
like that
so it's it but we have things stored up
inside our kidneys inside our liver
inside our gallbladder
we have stuff stored up in our stomach
you guys let me show you something
let me let me show you something you
might find it interesting
okay inside your stomach
all right inside your stomach
there's pockets we have pockets that
build up inside our stomach
we got pockets that build up in the
basin
the basin where your stomach where your
food
leaves your stomach and starts heading
down your duodenum
a pocket builds up with sludge right
there
a pocket of sludge and then it gets
heavy
and then your stomach stretches around
the duodenum entrance
and in a divot forms and you get sludge
that's been
in there for 20 years sitting in your
stomach that's never left your stomach
you need something to do some cleaning
and to get in there and clean that out
so you can clean that out of the stomach
and clean it out of there and then the
other thing is everybody's stomach lands
are toasted
they're toasted erna says
my acid reflux was gone within two to
three weeks it was mind-blowing
can you imagine can you imagine how
incredible is that
right how incredible
adele yes my asset reflex has gone since
following you
incredible you know what's funny about
that you guys that should be breaking
news
that should be breaking news because you
guys aren't paid for
bots you guys aren't being paid to say
that
like with all the paid campaigns on the
trends out there they're all
99 were being paid unless or they're in
the mlm marketing so
right what happens or they did celery
juice it healed them and then they're
saying some other product did it
that they're selling or mlm or something
what's incredible is that should be
breaking news out there in the world but
you know what the world doesn't want
you know the powers that be in this
world they don't want everybody healing
you guys know that i think you guys got
wise to that keep you guys sick
keep you guys sick keep big farmer rich
keep the system moving keep the system
going
make it so the hospitals can charge tens
of thousands of dollars just for staying
in there and getting a couple of tests
just you know make sure the system's
rolling on along right
exactly so your stomach lands inside
your stomach get toasted over the years
any kind of caffeine you've had
chocolate matcha tea green tea black tea
coffee right all the caffeinated stuff
caffeinated beverages energy drinks
right
any kind of caffeine pharmaceuticals all
have caffeine in them even if it's not
listed did you know that all
pharmaceuticals have caffeine in them
caffeine industry and pharmaceutical
industry they're one in the state
they're actually in bed together
mike how much celery does one drink
in a day's time try to get to 16 ounces
on an empty stomach every day if you can
that's incredible
and if you're using the omega juicer the
mm-900
you're saving money so you have so you
can buy less celery to achieve your 16
ounce goal how incredible is that
is this mm-900 hds you can get it at
megajuicers.com it's your celery model
please i need uh looking here please
i need complete detox parasite or
backed up food mold everywhere
so what people have to understand about
parasites and you can bring this
information to your doctor if you want
but people have bacteria not parasites
that's what's eating them up in their
guts
they got the bacteria they got the strep
neo e coli they got the staff they got
the c diff that's what's eating people
up in their guts
that's one thing right there anyway 16
ounces on an empty stomach
is the base the baseline move up to 32
ounces
of celery juice on an empty stomach 32
ounces on an empty stomach
person that's worried about parasites
whatever go to your doctor ask your
doctor
if your doctor would like medical medium
information
bring the doctor medical medium cleanse
the heal
ask your doctor if one of these cleanses
is right for you
to help you with whatever situation you
got just ask your doctor bring the book
to your doctor
ask your doctor but for me i would i
would look in the book for me if it was
me
model n how much does it cost and how
can people
order it so you can order it at a
megajuicers.com so omegajuicers.com
right and it's the mm-900 hds or you're
going to have the wrong juicer if it's
not that model
right that's the and it's on sale you
save 65
it's 20 percent off check it out
32 ounces is a great place to get to if
you can get to 32 ounces every day
the things you can deal with that is
incredible now let's talk about this
this is important okay
i'm not going to be able to stop you on
any level
eating your cheese i can't smack it out
of your hand
i can't just show up at your doorstep
and you're about to have your cheese and
just smack the cheese out of your hand
i can't do that i can't stop you from
having your eggs
lord knows many of you guys are eating
eggs every day right i don't blame you i
don't shame you i don't judge you
i don't but i can't stop you from eating
your eggs
you're gonna do it right i can't stop
you from eating fried food i can't stop
you from eating your buffalo chicken
wings
i can't stop you from having your pizza
i can't stop you from having too much
beef
cheese and bread
like the cheddar cheese i can't stop you
from having caffeine
i can't stop you guys from doing nothing
but hopefully i can inspire you guys
just inspire you guys to have something
in your court that
battles what you're doing wrong
have like a medical device in your
corner that's battling what you're doing
wrong
maybe i could inspire you somehow
in any way i can any way i can
inspire you so that you have something
in your court
right something in your court that's
that's helping
battle what i can't what i can't stop
you doing
i can't stop you guys from having your
chocolate i can't stop you guys from
having your donuts
how many donuts have you guys had i love
when someone says to me this
i love when so how many donuts have you
guys have i love when someone says
i have vegan donuts aw i'm clear i'm in
the clear
i'm like yeah all that canola oil in
your
in your donut your vegan donut
right all that fat in your vegan donut
all this other stuff in there you're not
in the clear you know even plant-based
people are in the corner
i can't stop you from eating vegan
donuts and i can't stop you from eating
regular donuts
sue is it common to have lots of
diarrhea after having celery juice
well it's like this so
i want you to be your own detective
never had diarrhea before
you don't have diarrhea at all you don't
have the runs at all so
it's something that never happened and
it only happens when you have celery
juice
then you're having to die off so what i
tell people
is reduce the amount
that means you're sensitive reduce it
the other thing is is celery juice is
going to flush and clean
it's going to flush and clean and it
goes away over time the runs with celery
juice if you're one if you're one of
those
that just means you've got a lot going
on so sue it means you've got a lot
a lot of bacteria in there got the
bacteria
everybody has all the strep and they
have all the the the
they have all the e coli they have all
the staff they have all the c
diff and it's loaded in there the other
thing is strain your celery juice that's
another thing too to be your own
detective
and it's really helpful it eases that
another thing
too is you know if i was having diarrhea
and it was
with celery juice and i didn't change
anything didn't do anything different
didn't catch a stomach bug either that's
something to be
to consider too did you catch a stomach
bug did you eat in a restaurant
around the time you started your celery
juice because it's easy to just blame
the new thing you started right
it's easy i've seen people blame
everything for anything i've seen people
blame
oil pulling for diet for oil pulling
for diarrhea they started oil pulling
the week they got food poisoning and
they're like oh my god it's
oil pulling i've seen people just blame
anything and everything
so what i'm saying is if if it was me
regardless i would be
lowering the amount that's what i would
do but you do what your doctor tells you
so how many donuts has everybody had how
many bagels
ashley rose using celery juice and
taking out troublemaker foods is how i
lost 80 pounds in a year
oh my god incredible i was never able to
lose weight in my life but when i
learned my liver was completely maxed
from ebv you're so smart antibiotics and
other toxins and metals
i knew this was a lifestyle change i can
use to heal
incredible that's exactly how it works
the liver gets maxed
the gallbladder gets maxed everything
like your liver gets filled with all
kinds of toxins and poisons all kinds of
acids and protein and garbage and
calcium calcium deposits it shouldn't be
in there everything
gets in there pesticides herbicides
fungicides petrochemicals air fresheners
scented candles all gets in there
perfumes colognes
gasoline at the gas station you breathe
in every day you guys
you know what it used to be there used
to be a gas attendant
at the gas stations and the gas
attendant would pump gas for like 30
years and then die
did you guys know that just die it's
just petrochemical disease
they just died now gas attendants
aren't breathing in gas all day long
right sometimes it only lasts 10 years
as a gas attendant before they die
15 years 20 years they were like you
know
that's what to do you you would be a gas
attendant you go
uh uh what would you like unleaded
whacked back to the back then it was let
it right and even now whatever
you know even after that shortly after
that was unleaded right
so it's like what do you want unleaded
okay let me just stick that pipe in
there and breathe it in and
okay there you go ma'am right and so
what who took the hit was the gas
attendants took the hit
they're the ones that died after they 20
years
they died of cancer 20 years of
breathing in everybody's
gasoline fumes because they were pumping
gas for 20 years right
okay but now our 16 year old daughters
and sons are pumping their own gas
right but no one's saying well huh wait
a minute here uh
my daughter is breathing in gas once a
week
twice a week depending on how much
driving is happening just sitting there
with the pump in there spilling gasoline
drops
on you know her leg or his leg breathing
in
all the fumes is that bad for my kids
is that bad because now my kids are
going to pump gas for the rest of their
life
who's getting the petrochemical out of
their kids
they're not doing that instead just you
know foods that
keep that petrochemical in and then you
get sick when you're older you don't
know why
by the way you guys just a 4-1-1 next
week is the heavy metal detox cleanse
challenge the heavy metal detox cleanse
challenge
next week pumped about it so pumped
about it
so i can't wait i hope you guys are
going to be there
and it's important to have cleanse the
heal it's important to have a juicer
this is the mm-900 hds i talked about
how it saves you money i talked about
why
all that it's doesn't have the metal
gears grinding against each other
i know some people they try to like
they're always trying to like get one up
on me everybody's like let's try to get
one up on aw
again uh let's tell them about this
great juicer that's a cold pressed
juicer i'm like well yeah the one with
the metal gears
nice try buddy nice try
metal gear so i can have metal tiny
metal shavings you can't see in my juice
real smart
anyway there's the cleanse of heel book
heavy metal detox cleanses next week i
hope you guys are there make sure i have
a juicer so let's keep on talking about
some
cool stuff here
celery juice goes in and it's fixing
things
things that you don't even know got
messed up year after year after year
after year
you got different bugs and pathogens and
viruses cytomegalovirus
ebv simplex 1 simplex 2 and a lot of
people right
hhb6 shingles viruses streptococcus
bacteria
all keeping people sick with trigeminal
neuralgia aches and pains migraines
tingles numbness ringing in the ears
vertigo and dizziness
fatigue everybody's got that going on
then everybody's got their livers filled
with all the junk i just talked about
scented candles air fresheners all the
perfumes and colognes
toxic heavy metals pesticides herbicides
fungicides petrochemicals plastics it's
just
pharmaceuticals all in people's liver
and body right
so and then people are fattening
themselves to death fat fat themselves
with that fat themselves with that
that's what everybody's doing we're just
fasting ourselves to death let's just do
that let's
let's do that let's make sure there's
plenty of sausage on this pizza i'll
have a slice of sausage pizza please
just fat ourselves to death oh wait
you're plant-based avocado yourself to
death
avocado nuts and seeds and oils walnuts
walnuts walnuts almonds almonds almond
butter
canola oil in these dressings i'm vegan
though and you buy a
dressing it's loaded with canola oil
safflower oil and sunflower oil
and you're like tanking it so what we do
is we compact all the poison inside of
us and everything starts to get amiss
it's like that engine man
that's not running good not one
yeah and then you wonder why your
kidneys start going you wonder why you
get the kidney stones you wonder why
your gallbladders start going you wonder
why everything starts to go amiss
everything just starts to fall apart as
you get older your teeth start caving in
from the inside out
your teeth start caving in from the
inside out that's not a joke
that's some legit stuff i'm saying
your teeth crumble from the inside out
from all that acid
but who's drinking celery juice every
single day to try to stop it
to try to level the playing field at
least
i can't stop you guys from doing your
chocolate
i i can't you can make a
billion of me and have me knocking on
your door and you'll lock me out of your
house
to get that chocolate down probably some
of you
know who's been honey who's banging at
the door
it's a aw he's banging at the door keep
him locked out of the house
i gotta get this chocolate bar down
because this other doctor on youtube
this doctor on youtube said that
chocolate is good for us
i can't i can't stop you from sabotaging
yourselves we're on
robot central of sabotaging ourselves
that's what we do that's what we do we
do
sabotage seventh house give me the
grenade grenade
give me the pin pull the pin out of the
grenade pull it out of the grenade
pull it out of the grenade correct
self-destruct self-destruct well robots
robots sabotage sabotage sabotage
youtube doctor says it's good for me
sabotage sabotage sabotage whoa a
podcast doctor says it's good for me
chocolates good for me sabotage snapchat
pull the pin out pull up and out
that's what we do
i've stopped losing my hair after
quitting chocolate
susan it the chocolate
is the big thing for women's hair loss
women aren't supposed to lose their hair
they're not supposed to lose their hair
women aren't supposed to guys they're
supposed to lose their hair
this is that's actually true like
there's guys out there
they're supposed to lose their hair
women are not supposed to lose their
hair
and the adrenals get eaten up by that
chocolate that coffee
that matcha tea but what are we doing to
like
counter it what do we do in a counter
anything
chris's sage says my friend told me
their dentist says your teeth naturally
get
sensitive as you get older meanwhile
this person loves vinegar and foods
vinegar
eat your teeth up like nothing you're
taught
it's normal so you don't question it
yeah you don't question it
you're taught it's normal yeah
that's what we're taught you don't
question
anything so our teeth
start to crumble from the inside out
they get sensitive we're taught it's
normal you're just getting older
you're just getting older
you fall on the sidewalk and break your
face much
easier than it should break you're just
getting older no
you're losing all your calcium mike knew
some i've always heard a little bit of
dark chocolate every now and then
was good for you i got a phone call
coming in
yeah paid for by the caffeine company
i got a phone call coming in the head of
the caffeine corporations are calling
now
um i have an appointment with the heads
the heads
of the caffeine corporations now
yeah i do i do
i think they're calling now
hello you're the head of the caffeine
industry
yeah um so i just heard that a little
bit of chocolate
is okay i can do a little bit i can
okay um oh
pregnant women too okay that's good
well you know it's a psychoactive drug
right
uh-huh there's a little baby inside
mommy
is it good to put that psychoactive drug
in there it is
really okay that's good it's good for
the baby to have a psychoactive drug
in the womb okay okay what else
um chocolate is good in moderation
okay what's moderation a chocolate bar
every couple of days
okay that's good awesome
why are you guys why are you guys doing
this
anyway because the caffeine industry is
like the biggest industry in the world
next to big pharma
wow what happens if every can i just ask
you a question
since you're the head of the caffeine
industry what if everybody got wise and
stopped
consuming caffeine
all the share what the shareholders
really
the the empires they built
yachts uh gigantic mansions
bentleys that would all disappear
i see i see all right well maybe i'll
try to help you out and i'll just tell
everybody a little can be okay
i don't want you guys to lose your
bentleys and your yachts and your
mansions
that would really stink if all you
shareholders lost that
all right i better i better i'll side up
with you hey can you send me some free
chocolate
if you send me you want to pay me off
i got the the caffeine industry guy
wants to pay me off right here
you do you want me you want to pay me
off and then i'll tell everybody that
chocolate's actually a good idea
i'll think about it okay bye
all of the bad stuff coming into your
body every single day starts catching up
to you in the scale tips
tips tips tips
and when your ass falls down from it you
think the caffeine industry
industry is going to save you hey i got
the caffeine industry behind me
oh good yeah okay caffeine industries
behind me you guys
whoa whoa yeah that all the the
chocolate industry is gonna save me
save me up right when i get sick you're
gonna save me so i
yeah i'm i could go backwards okay
you're okay until you're not i'm okay
i'm okay i'm okay i'm okay
i'm okay i'm okay i'm okay i'm okay
i'm not body fights for you fights for
you fights for you fights for you fights
for you
until one day it can't
i wish i had a medical tool like this
years ago
i wish i was at least countering all
that poison
and mind control
mind control you guys ever hear about
mind control
right like the mind control slaves the
mind control system
right that's what they do
they mind control you they make sure you
don't
break the status quo of the industries
make sure you're doing all your
pharmaceuticals
make sure you're doing all your caffeine
you get mind controlled
and then you're like hey i just got a
celery juicer and i'm going to drink my
first celery juice
but wait i'm looking at an article
celery juice is bad for you
oxalates uh it's bad for you celery
juice is bad for you says who
some chiropractor here writing an
article that was paid to rip down celery
juice
no one heals from celery juice i better
stop
mind control it's like
and that's what it is it's to stop you
from getting better
you guys have to fight through all that
mind control and brainwashing to get
better
you guys have to fight to get better
addictions that make
people money
that's what happens
so the mind control and the addictions
and that's how it works
it'll make the money makers more money
while you're addicted
what about all the medical bills when
you're sick
oh don't worry insurance will cover that
i don't know i hear all the time my
co-payments are killing me
that medications not covered in my plan
i lost my dental plan um
i had to still pay eighty dollars on
that bottle of prescription that cost
four thousand dollars but i still my
insurance covered it
thirty eight hundred dollars but i had
to pay a hundred dollar co-payment
i don't have health insurance
i hear that all the time too ashley rose
juice to get the medicine from the herb
eating is not the same eating's not the
same you're not gonna get enough of the
herbal medicine from eating it you can't
some nutritionists will say chop it up
in little tiny pieces and put it in your
tuna salad
because tuna's got protein protein's so
good for you
who hasn't eaten a lot of protein who's
not who's not on protein
everybody's sick they're acting like
proteins while you're sick
you're not mean pro not having enough
protein is why you're sick
i'm scratching my head on that one
because everybody's protein the heck
out like protein out something fierce
man
like proteined out everybody's eating
protein from when they're born to
whatever and they're fatted out
tank in the fat oh fat's good for you i
forgot another new campaign developed
by alternative medicine and conventional
medicine real smart until you're sick
sage says all the treatments i've used
made me worse
anything that helps is never covered by
insurance
so grateful for all thank you aw
that's how it's done right
out there so who who hasn't had enough
protein are you kidding me
yeah just tons of protein anyway guys
mm-900
hds this is it the sales only from today
and tomorrow
65 you save but you do more than that
when you're juicing celery
you save you're saving money as every
stick
goes through there's no other juicer
that i have found yet
that saves you money as the stick is
going through and you're getting your
juice
and that money adds up for me it's
thousands of dollars it's paid for
itself over and over and over and over
and over
so megajuicers.com
sales for the next couple days i'm gonna
head off to ig
uh instagram i'm gonna turn tiptuck back
on
we're gonna talk about all kinds of
stuff so i'm excited you guys
i love you guys i'll see you on ig in
probably 15 minutes i just want to clean
up a little bit and
we're going to have some fun love you
guys