[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 or 20 years or 30
years to wait for answers and I've run
into a lot of people over the years that
are like you know what I've had this for
20 years I've had this problem for 20
years and it just didn't have any
answers to know really what to do or
what's going on and uh and who wants to
wait that long I mean people when they
get something going on I mean you know
and even if it's for a week even if it's
for two weeks even if it's a symptom for
a month I mean whoo and and I've seen
people where all of a sudden they got
something going on and it's it's just
like it's like hey I I can't live my
life or or if they're living their life
they just can't stand a symptom or some
kind of condition absolutely I mean
without a doubt it's it's really hard
it's really hard um you know and and it
makes things difficult today we're
talking about the gallbladder the
gallbladder wo gallbladder spasms things
like that all kinds of gall stuff gall
stone
hey you know and maybe you don't have a
gallbladder maybe your gallbladder was
taken out maybe it was
removed maybe it was removed you know
gallbladders are funny and uh and we we
need to talk about them that's the whole
thing that that's what we want to do I
think I think you know I should have
done a gallbladder show a long time ago
without a doubt I should have done one
you know I talk about research and
science a lot and in in the sense that
you know in chronic illness I feel like
it's it's fallen behind it actually was
never caught up to begin with all the
way from the start and and um you know
and I say that a lot I say that a lot
when it comes down to chronic illness
but when it comes down to a good surgeon
removing a gallbladder that's got
infected that became
infected you know or or
spasming so bad and the person is just
suffering and you know or or you know a
gallbladder that that's basically going
to
rupture and hey and and we you you you
find a good surgeon and that's where
research and science is paid off that's
where it's paid off right there and um
so you know I appreciate that I
appreciate that and I respect that
highly respect that highly appreciate
that um but when it comes down to
chronic illness in general all kinds of
different ways I mean you know science
and research hasn't gotten there
including the production of a gallstone
the basic understanding is there but
what's behind all that like how do we
avoid that how do we stop
that what's that about well that's that
doesn't exist in science and research it
just doesn't may you know and and you
know and so we really need to cover it
and so when you know this is Advanced
information we're talking about here in
the show without a doubt this
information this is the only show where
the information here doesn't come from a
place an agenda driven place you know
like the interest groups and all the
strings attached to medical stuff and
medical funding and research that's been
all messed up and botched up and the
thumb on the scale medical lobbyists
that sit there and they just want
certain drugs to go through they don't
you know and that's all it's about both
you know and all these things can
literally be an alternative and
conventional medicine it really can
believe it or not internal Kickbacks
persuaded belief systems and private
panels everywhere whereare that
influence
decisions decisions and then of course
trends that start off of a lot of this
information so we have contamination
contamination in alternative medicine
information and of course conventional
medicine information it's the only show
that we keep all that out 100% that
means that we just don't go on the
internet we don't go on the internet we
don't need to we don't go on the
Internet and try to hack it all out and
S search all kinds of studies and things
that are all skewed and all messed up
and all agendas behind it and all kinds
of different panels behind it in all
kinds of different ways it was
manipulated and
contaminated we don't go by those old
laws um just the only show that comes
that's Pure Clean comes from a source
that was given to me since Age 4 and
have helped tens of thousands of people
find their way and get the information
they need throughout my whole lifetime
all these decades and that's where you
are now so that's where we are in this
show right here and gallbladder we're
going to go into this this is a good one
I really do feel this that uh we're
going to have a good
time we're going to have a good time I
remember my first experience um with a
gallbladder not my gallbladder but a
first experience with uh somebody who
came to me with a
gallbladder and and I remember it well
it was a long long time ago um I don't
want to date myself or anything or make
myself sound too old I like to think I'm
still
young but um and I remember I remember
when I first had my office years and
years and years ago and you know opened
it up to the public so it wasn't just
helping people out randomly everywhere
else I mean I I I helped people out all
all along the way I remember at age 134
I was a stock boy in a uh in a store in
a grocery store and I would help people
out all the time um I had clients that
developed because of that because Spirit
would give me information and I would
see what's going on with People's Health
right there right there in the grocery
store aisle right there in the grocery
store aisle so I I had a love for all
that I had a love for food and and
everything around because what Spirit
was teaching me constantly and and what
I needed to do for people and and um so
I liked being in that atmosphere it was
great because you know people are
shopping for food and and it makes them
think it makes them think and um and and
it's such so great and you give somebody
advice and you're like you know what you
need you need cucumber juice for those
gall
stones and then you know after that when
I finally had an office um I remember my
first my first case coming in with with
uh gallbladder problems and you know
right when the person walked through the
door Spirit was like gallbladder
gallbladder you know we got a pile of
sand in there we got a few stones in
there we got two varieties of stones in
there and there's even more varieties
than what's what's you know recorded as
far as what medical science and you know
research understands and so it was
really interesting and and and I have a
love for that I have a love for the
liver and gallbladder and everything
around it um so so I remember that first
case really clearly in the person was
suffering
suffering uh it was
heartbreaking and they didn't want to
get it taken out and since surgeries
have gotten better for gallbladders I
mean back then they weren't as
great and um it was more of a difficult
surgery it was a complicated surgery
back then believe it or not now you know
there's there's there's there's better
techniques there's better techniques for
you know snipping a gallbladder out
underneath the liver under there and um
it was a tricky place for surgeons to
have to go and find back in the old days
they had to swim around and take a
really good look you had needed a really
good guy or a gal with a really good eye
um back then and um and knew you know
knew that gallbladders don't sit
perfectly in the same place for
everybody and that's something I want to
talk about too is that um gallbladders
just aren't in the same spot for every
single person how's that possible I
thought we were all created equal in
some way or identical in some way with
our bodies right no no no no no no um
the strangest things with our body one
is with gallbladders they're not always
in the same spot well you know you might
be thinking well where are they how
where could a gallbladder be besides
tucked underneath the liver under there
under the right side up there you know
where where would it be well an inch
over how about that how about an inch
over which makes a huge difference when
you're when you're a
surgeon an inch over um how about like
cocked up a wrong way not or or a
different way how about that how about
that how about a gallbladder that's not
just sitting the way it's supposed to be
but since childhood since meaning since
birth and everything it it it took a
different position how how about that
how about a gallbladder that's a
different shape entirely different shape
it's not that that little pear shape
that little pocket but it's it's got an
apple shape how about those apples right
so it's sitting differently not every
gallbladder looks the same not every
gallbladder looks the same I talked to a
surgeon actually uh pretty recently and
and and I was I was telling the surgeon
about that kind of very thing and he
says it's amazing that you even know
that he said and I know and the surgeon
you know he a friend of mine and he goes
and he goes and I know you know all
these things because that's what you
done that's what you do we you know we
know that but it's still it's still
mindblowing that you know this that's
what the surgeon said to me so my friend
said to me it's still mind-blowing that
you know this he knows why I know this
because of spirit but it's still it was
weird it was weird to him to hear
it because because all not all
gallbladders look the same if you cut
enough of them out if you've cut enough
of those babies
out over the years you you'll know
between women's gallbladders men men's
gallbladders the whole bit you would
know and um you know it it just it takes
experience and being that I've never
snipped out a gallbladder before ever
he's just like it's just I don't just
don't I I I know you hear Spirit but I
still don't get it how you know these
little nuances how you know these little
things and um and because of that though
the different shapes and sizes and
everything it shows that we're all
unique in all different ways without a
doubt but back in the old days back in
the older days finding that finding that
little gallbladder in there you know
wasn't always so easy took some time
took a little searching took a little
TLC and but now now I mean surgeons are
you know we found different ways of of
of using you know different technology
for for getting in there and we got
better scanning machines and so forth
and all that and you know and thank God
thank God that's right I mean I stand
behind science and research I stand
behind medical advancement 100% I'm
always peed off about about chronic
illness the area there I think that was
just just totally just you know I just
think we've all been left left out to
dry on that and I can't help it you know
medical denial with chronic illness is
unbelievable and I can't help it I can't
help it I just you know I'm still yeah
yeah I'm still burnt up about that after
all these years I've seen too many
people suffer no answers for people and
the answers they do get now is is
becoming
ridiculous and look I'm not against the
whole lime disease thing but I'm going
to tell you right now um everybody's
going to be diagnosed with Lyme disease
everybody in chronic illness everybody
everybody because the system is messed
up terribly terribly anybody with
anything lupus diagnosis those are going
to be a thing of the past it's all going
to be pushed off the lime everything's
going to be lime Ms anything Ms is going
to be pushed off the lime anything is
going to be pushed off the
lime and that's that's by Design that's
by Design By the way that's by Design if
that's getting anybody upset right now
because limes tends to tends to you know
the whole lime thing tends to get people
just red up and they get angry and
pissed off and just read my chapter in
book one whatever you do and read it
with an open mind don't read it with
anger in your heart read it with an open
mind it's
important um so yeah yeah in and but
with the gallbladder thing you know it's
it's great we have great people you they
can help somebody with a gallbladder
problem we have great great
surgeons but it's as far as information
about how to prevent the gallbladder
problem as far as
information to uh dissolve
Stones you know the one thing I don't
like is gallbladder
flushes y I don't like them no no
no I don't like them at all doing this a
long time and Spirits always said you
know no gallbladder flesh is why I've
seen people pop a good Stone in that
duct get it
stuck when we didn't need to do a
gallbladder flush we didn't need to try
to do gallbladder flush we could have
just dissolved the stone what was in the
gallbladder while it was sitting in
there all nice and pretty in a good spot
and we could have slowly dissolved it we
could have gotten a liver in a better
condition so it wouldn't keep on
producing a gall stone or growing it we
could do a lot of things we don't have
to try to do this flush and accidentally
pop a giant Stone up into the duct and
get it stuck and then it's emergency Sur
emergency surgery time or get it in get
it popped in there and get it stuck and
get it
infected over time little strep a cacus
that's already in your digestive tra and
in your in your your IND wadum and
everything else that backtracks and
finds its way up there a little bit of
strip caucus that you know it's always
sitting in people's livers that just you
know jumps up
into jumps up to the gallbladder it's
waiting for something stupid to happen
that's what it's doing it's waiting for
something stupid to happen like a stone
getting jammed because of a flush and
then getting a little bit swollen in
there because the tissue starts to get
irritable and then boom the strep jumps
in there and Dives right in and then
infects the heck out of it and then now
you're rushing to the hospital and it's
partly turning green I I can't tell you
how many times I've seen that happen
from gallbladder fleshes till this day I
bang my head against a wall when I hear
about another one and I'm just like why
why is this misinformation out there why
is this stupid misinformation out there
what is going on I bet you the liver
people are pissed at me right now
there's a lot of liver gallbladder
flushing people out there they're
probably just going to get all angry and
I'm sure there's plenty listening I'm
sorry just forgive me if you can I'm not
you know
I like the fact that you care I like the
fact that you're healing people I like
the fact that you're working on healing
people in different ways you probably
know all kinds of incredible
information and and and everything else
and it's not your fault if you're
telling people to constantly do a
gallbladder fleshes it's not your fault
at all it's not and you know just what
it is is it's just it's it's information
that you gathered somewhere else from
some original Source somewhere that just
was wrong to begin
with and uh and that's how it's done
that's how it's done that's how all the
misinformation goes around out there I
bet you some people are uh hanging up
from the show right now and they're like
I'm not listening to him anymore I'm not
listening to that jerk
anymore I've helped people with
gallbladder fleshes I'm not listening to
that jerk anymore he's basically telling
me I've been doing things wrong I don't
want to hear that on a
show but um but look I'm saying that
because seriously seriously listen
listen keep a lie heart keep a lie heart
you know the one thing I've had to do
with with with all these years and and
and this show included and and in the
books is I've had to hurt people's
feelings once in a while and I don't
mean to do it on purpose you know
meaning the sense I don't want to hurt
anybody's feelings I don't I
don't I I just you
know there's a there's a fine line you
know there's a fine line about
everything you know you want you want to
support everybody for everything they're
doing but you also want to watch
everybody's backs you know I've seen a
lot of surgeries that were unnecessary
over the years I've been doing this for
a long long time and it's funny someone
said to me when did you start 5 years
ago when did you start being a medium 5
years ago I mean what talk to my parents
talk to my parents and you you you
listen to them and going all the way
back you know vouching for me with
stories all the way since Charlie you
you talked to them You' tell you you ask
them when I started being a medium you
know and it's not just that I mean I've
been I've been working on people forever
working with people forever and going
all the way back and it hasn't been just
5 years hasn't been just 7 years hasn't
been 9 years hasn't been 12 years hasn't
been 15 years been a lot longer and so
I've been able to witness a lot just
like a good surgeon Witnesses so much
just like a good surgeon you know I mean
who's got a track record
a long-term track
record and you know and and basically
the bottom line is I'm not trying to
hurt anybody's feelings I'm just saying
hey look instead of doing the flushes
anymore let's redesign it let's change
it up let's let's figure out something
different let's figure out another way
which spirit and I already
know but let's figure out another way to
dissolve Stones wouldn't that be nice
would wouldn't that be great we can
dissolve them how about that or stop
producing them how about that or both
wouldn't that be nice absolutely
absolutely without a
doubt so Stones what's the deal with
those or what are they made out of right
well made out of
cholesterol okay made out of you know
pigment too made out of pigment Billy
Rubin Billy Rubin I like that name is
that the right way to say it Billy Ruben
you know and um I say that because I
like I like it when it's called Billy
Rubin I don't know it's just cool cool
name cool
name and
um and somebody might say that's not the
correct way of saying it it's called
biley Robin biley
Robin there something I me that happen
where I call something by by you know by
a name that I I think it's
called and someone's correcting me like
no that's not the exact way it's
supposed to be said and so anyway Billy
Rubin it's Pigman right and uh what's
Billy Rubin it's it's red blood cells
it's just discarded red blood cells
that's that's actually all
right that's all correct you know that's
just the way it works that's great
that's great cholesterol why is
cholesterol building
up in
somebody's liver and spitting out into
the
gallbladder why
is excuse me why is
why is why is why is cholesterol doing
that why
is Billy
ruin building up and becoming a stone
though why is it becoming a stone why
are these becoming a stone I mean you
that's the question that's the question
what's the what's the purpose what's
going on there why is that
happening and why is the
liver being part of this why is it being
a big part of it is being responsible
for it what's going on in somebody's
life what's going on in somebody's diet
what's going on in somebody's liver
that's creating those
stones what's going on
there and that's what we're going to
talk about that's what we're going to
talk about right there and what about
the pile of sand that builds up you know
if you don't change your oil in your
car are you thinking the same thing I am
are you thinking the same thing I right
right if you don't change your oil in
your
car what happens just the oil filter
starts getting really
clogged it just gets really
clogged that's what's going on well
that's what's
happening with the
gallbladder that's like your oil filter
kind of like your oil filter in a way so
getting really gunky in there really
clogged and gunky in there if you don't
change your oil if you don't change your
oil in your
liver if you don't change the oil in
your engine in the
[Laughter]
car right I mean it just gets gunier and
dark it turns jet black and it just it's
it's got all kinds of metal fragments in
there because the engine doesn't have
viscosity anymore so the you know the
crankshaft is just spinning in the
valves and everything else is just it's
just um it's just everything's getting
Mucky
everything's getting
Mucky and then the oil's getting dirtier
and dirtier and the the air filter is
not being changed and all this garbage
is going
in right I mean some of you probably
know that some of you probably don't
some of you are probably like I don't
know I just turned the key on the car
and that's
it and that oil turns into a sludge a
sludge turns into a sludge
like scrape off the bottom of the oil
pan a
sludge that's how it
works so they don't change your oil it
gets dirty and Mucky and ugly it turns
into a sludge a
pudding thick black pudding the bottom
of your
pan and it's set it's settlement
sediment right sediment is that what it
is and um the oil filter gets clogged
and everything
else or maybe it's just sediment at the
bottom of the pan maybe that's what that
gallbladder is it's like the bottom of
the
pan and all that Gunk and settlement is
in there and that's
different believe it or not that's the
third thing science research isn't
really identifying they talk about that
they talk about lots of different Stones
you get an ultrasound you get a CAT scan
an ultrasound an MRI and the nurse
practitioner the nurse comes in or the
doctor comes in and says oh my God
you're your your gallbladder is hundreds
and hundreds of stones it's filled with
sand
and that
sand isn't
always gall stones meaning it meaning it
isn't always cholesterol Stones is
information that's not known out
there news flash that saying and isn't
always Billy Ruben those red blood
cells it's a third
component that's science of research
hasn't tapped into that gunk in that
gallbladder is all kinds of stuff it's
dead viral carcasses dead viral
byproduct dead pathogen byproduct dead
um uh bacterial byproduct
Plastics spit up from the liver from
antibiotics petrol oil petrol
oil and I'm not doing the analogy the
metaphor I'm not doing that part I'm not
just talking about the oil on the bottom
of a pan is real engine oil in the
bottom of a pan of a car you
guys I I'm talking about real petrol oil
put in
antibiotics they don't need to put that
in there by the way I mean I scratched
my head I'm scratching my head right
now they don't need to put that in there
just one of those additives that don't
have to be in
antibiotics they just don't have to be
there isn't that funny isn't that funny
I mean you know we talk about foods and
everything preservatives and foods and
you know you want your chicken
antibiotic free right you want all that
you want your chicken be free range you
you know you don't want preservatives
you don't want aluminum nitrate you
don't want aluminum pumped into to your
chickens you know they they you know
inject aluminum and turkeys and chickens
plump them up I mean you don't want that
in there right you don't want all this
whatever in there but when we take an
antibiotic they put all the stuff in
there I mean they don't have to that's
the sad part they don't have they don't
have to have petrol oil in there but
where does that petrol oil go it's small
amounts real small amounts doesn't
matter liver the liver you know the
liver gets pissed off
anyway and it storage it stores these
these
petrochemicals and you can get other
exposure to petrochemicals
too and from other drugs and other
sources other avenues and liver you know
eventually just if the liver is not
getting cleaned up if we're not eating
right if we're not taking care of the
liver if we're not doing what we need to
do for the
liver if our diet's not good if we're
pounding in tons of protein and fat in
our diet
thinking that's the way even if we're no
carb and we're exercising and we're
starting to look better and we're
starting to get a little bit more fit
our liver is still taking a hit like oh
my God nobody knows that by the
way and so what does the liver do it
pushes pushes that stuff right up into
the gallbladder and it's not Billy Rubin
it's not our friend Billy
Ruben it's you know it's not our friend
CEST
raw making names out of these two things
all right I'm being silly today there's
nothing to be silly about with gall
stones and
gallbladders see a lot of people go
through a lot of trouble I think I'm
just giggly
today it's
unbelievable um yeah you got to keep a
light heart we got to keep a light heart
okay so there's something else that gets
going there's something else going on in
that sludge it's a whole bunch of waste
that's not analyzed by research and
science they don't analyze that you know
why it's got a guilty Trail in it it's
got a guilty
Trail it's
got a trail it's got It's
evidence it's evidence of all kinds of
crap I mean everything there's heavy
metals in there literally and you know
what's so bizarre what's so bizarre is
that that's what's in engine oil that's
that's that when engine oil is not
replaced and it and it sits at the
bottom of the pan you guys it gets
filled with these little micro micr
chips of metal that are coming out of
the engine because there's no
viscosity well there's heavy metals
saturating the liver from all kinds of
reasons all kinds of reasons medical
reasons you know medical
stuff uh Medical Products uh all kinds
of different things just you know stuff
falling out of the sky uh food pots and
pans people scraping pots and pans
restaurants restaurants are the worst
the worst unless it's a good one unless
it's a good one that's really taking
care of everybody in the food properly
so if you're a restaurant owner I'm sure
that's what you're doing if you're
listening to this show then that's
definitely what you're do you're doing
without a doubt but the bottom line is
that metal heavy metals toxic heavy
metals sit in that sludge but that
sludge never gets
analyzed never gets analyzed they never
do and and and and if and if they have
which they probably
have um I'm sure they kept out the bad
stuff bad stuff in any study because
like I said at the beginning of the
show blah blah blah this information
doesn't come from this this this this
this this contaminated this this sources
this this this this trendy traps the
payoffs all that crap it's like I said
at the beginning
because what's in that sludge is a whole
bunch of
evidence all kinds of metals Plastics
petroleum oils can you believe it yeah
yeah yeah yeah and nobody knows it and
that's the third aspect of what's inside
a gallbladder mind blown mine is Spirit
blows my mind all the time mind blown
seriously if yours isn't then I
understand but mine is
boom I mean and that's the third part so
let's go through them a little bit all
right the cholesterol Stone why is
cholesterol like amping up and becoming
a rolling stone in there what the
heck what is going
on that's because a liver is becoming
dysfunctional a liver is becoming
dysfunctional because big part of its
diet and other part of it the liver is
getting sluggish and dysfunctional
stagnant even fatty even if it's pre-
fatty liver and not diagnosed
what about old Billy Billy
Ruben right why is that happening
because red blood cells mean a liver is
under stress and it's contaminated with
a lot of toxins and pathogens and stuff
like that so it's it's dealing with he
hemoglobin a lot differently and red
blood cells start to they start to do
something they start to glue each other
together the pigment starts to glue
itself together and creating a stone
when the liver is too
overburdened
and then you know like Grandma's apple
pie you just need the right recipe you
just need the right recipe I said that
probably one of the earliest shows ever
that we did one of the early
shows and I've also said it many many
years ago grandma's Apple Pie tastes
just the way it does because it's just
right because she puts just a little bit
of nutmeg in but not too much and not
too too little little bit of salt not a
lot of salt balancing it with the
sweet I'm being silly today I know sorry
you guys seriously seriously let's take
this as serious as
possible but seriously though with
Grandma's apple pie it's just right for
a reason it made a recipe for a reason
with Billy ruin and and and in
cholesterol stones to do what they're
doing it takes also a recipe of what's
in that other sludge P pile what's in
the other sludge pile the sludge pile is
the evidence of what's going on inside
the liver which creates the recipe of
creating the stones for God's
sake yeah mind blown information
overload because it's never been
released anywhere that information of
course just like 85 90% of everything
else on the shows I
do I'm saying that in case you know if
you're on the internet a lot of people
they're like okay okay what do to see
okay let's get on the internet okay
let's let's look into this and now
they're like going you they're going
crazy they're looking they're
looking so it's really about the liver
in this situation it's about the liver
producing an amount of of toxic waste
from not being cared for but it's the
right kind of toxic waste that can glue
red blood cells together creating that
pigment stone that Billy Ruben stone
that stone I hate that
stone I hate that stone cuz that one's a
weird one Billy Ruben that stone I I
don't like that stone a little harder to
dissolve I've had to get a lot of people
to dissolve
them absolutely I had to change your
diet around the right way to get them to
dissolve I had to do different things
but I I I hate that
stone cholesterol Stones eh I don't hate
we can break those down no
problem we can we can we can break them
down easier faster we can break down the
Billy Rubin too I mean that's okay too
we can do that stone too and we can get
rid of some of the sludge but we don't
want to do it with a gallbladder
flush a silly gallbladder
flush I'll tell you right now you don't
want that cholesterol Stone to pop up
into that duct and lock itself in and
maybe you're lucky maybe you're lucky
and it won't as a lot of people do they
get by they get lucky on that it's a
good it's but I don't like r roulette do
you I don't like it I don't like taking
a gun with one bullet spinning the
chamber putting up to my head for fun I
just don't like that I'm not a Russian
Roulette kind of guy maybe when I was a
kid maybe when I was a kid I'd be like
all right I I'll take the chance you I
was you know maybe when I was 10 11 12
years
old I would you know take
chances not like anything stupid like
that but I would be like all right all
right I I I bet we can do this I bet we
can take this bicycle and we can jump it
over this Ravine with this little wooden
ramp I got Spirit watching my back
Spirit won't let me get hurt I'll F I'll
Fly Like a Bird on this
bicycle I'll jump this River with this
bicycle I'll take a chance there's
chances are what's my odd Spirit 90%
chance you're not going to make it 10%
chance that you're going to make it and
when you do make it to the other side
you're probably going to have broken
bones all right I'll take my chance well
what's the guarantee about that 10% with
broken bones well 1% you won't have any
broken bones just really bad bruises and
injury okay I'll take the chance
1% and you know so yeah but but I don't
like doing that I don't like doing any
of that now that was when I was young
but the point
is the point is is that we don't want to
do that you don't want to do the flushes
you don't want to pop a stone stone in
there in the
duck and in the
duct okay so let's move on let's move on
we're trying to cut through this um
telling you guys too many stories spasms
and infections gallbladder infections I
hate gallbladder
infections you can get food poisoning in
a restaurant and it can take out your
gallbladder
boy man that food born toxin that food
born bacteria that salmonella anything
like that can Rush up to that
gallbladder I mean if yeah if you're
lucky and you're just vomiting for a day
or for a couple of hours or quickly or
you just got a bad stomach ache and
you're burping and burping and burping
because of a food born toxin in a
restaurant and I you guys should listen
to my to my uh I think the show's called
like food poisoning show or something
like that I forgot now I forgot doing so
many shows now I just I
forgot I think it was food food
poisoning you should listen to it listen
to it carefully okay cuz last thing you
want is to get food poisoning I've had
friends get food poisoning of the worst
kind I I oh my
god I've had friends I've had people
clients uh I've had you know doctors
friends getting the worst food poisoning
ever in their
life um you know but you name it and and
what happens is with food poisoning is
is sometimes it can get us really good
and it could and that bacteria could
Rush right up to the gallbladder and
infect it get it to spasm like hell for
a long time until the body can
overcompensate and clean it up and
sometimes it can't and then surgeons
have to remove the gallbladder if food
poisoning I'm drinking cucumber juice
right
now by the way just kind of sipping it
in between a little
bit cucumber juice why would I be
drinking cucumber juice on a day we're
doing gallbladder because cucumber juice
helps to
dissolve gallbladder stones but it does
more than that it helps to alleviate
sludge out of the liver in a different
way that it doesn't have to back up
Purge back up into the gallbladder sit
there and settle into a pile of Gunk
pile of engine oil in that
gallbladder that's almost like the
gallbladder is the bottom of the pan of
an a car oil
pan and um you know what happens what
happens here what happens here is that
food poisoning is one thing that's one
thing but also eoli that sits inside our
intestinal tract long term or strep or
ecoli especially ecoli too you know they
sit in our intestinal tract for long
term and if they break out and you get
gastritis and they kind of bubbles up
and breaks out in your intestinal tract
and you got a bout of gastritis you
could always get in trouble with your
gallbladder and appendix
too so we want to just take care of
things the liver tries to trap as much
bacteria and pathogens as it can
possibly
trap the liver's immune system tries to
destroy as much bacteria as possible
you know I'm not a what is it uh
confrontational kind of guy at all you
know I'm not one of those guys um you
know with going going uh going all these
years with hearing spirit's
voice and helping people you know I mean
there's been times over the years where
people are just in
disbelief that they're even healing from
the information you know I remember when
I was younger years and years ago
getting people that were healing and
still they can't believe I'm hearing the
voice and giving them the advice that's
actually getting them better they just
think it's some kind of fluke I've
remembered cases like that once in a
while every now and
then and I even remember confrontation
when I was younger too every now and
then I remember this one one case going
all the way back I think I was 18 years
old and um this woman came to me no
doctor would listen she was so fatigued
she couldn't just get out of bed it took
everything everything she had to get to
the office everything she had to get to
the
office and
um and she she had New Hope Spirit found
a virus that she was suffering with she
had severe chronic fatigue from a
neurological
virus and it was inflaming everything in
her body she was she was literally at 40
or 50 doctors best clinics across the
country this is a you know long time ago
before the world has changed and before
the internet uh turned into the internet
and everything else before there was an
internet I'm sorry before before there
was an internet when I remember she was
recovering first time first time in
years recovering she can get out of bed
and start recovering and her husband was
mad angry because I wasn't a medical
doctor cuz I was a medical medium the
medical medium so I remember he came to
the office by
himself and and she was recovering and
he came to the office all disgruntled
all
angry and he said that uh he didn't he
didn't want her coming anymore to uh for
appointments even though she was getting
better and he admitted she's getting
better but but there was something
inside of him that just couldn't stand
the fact that it was it was the medium
thing couldn't stand it so he hindered
her healing hindered her healing I
didn't know she overcame it and took the
advice and
recovered and um but she had such more
more more more you know struggles
because of the delay of the
hindrance and so confrontation is
something I don't like and what happens
is that when the liver is under
confrontation cuz that's what happening
all the time the liver it's under
confrontation non-stop it's under
confrontation with with a diet that
we're under it's under stress it's under
it's constantly being attacked it's
constantly being braided it's constantly
being antagon you know antagonized it's
constantly being irritated you know
livers up against a tremendous amount of
that all the time so it it it it breaks
its ability down to do what it's got to
do it's got an immune system that wants
to seek and
destroy the liver has its own immune
system that wants to Seek and
Destroy pathogens but when constantly
you know the confrontation involved it
it could Sidetrack it confrontation
meaning eating the wrong Foods
tremendous amount of adrenaline in your
life tons of
stress and then it it it can't send the
soldiers out the liver takes has no
mercy it takes no mercy it is an immune
system designed to
destroy
kill yeah yeah that's right that's right
it's not weak in that
nature you know it doesn't like
conversation on any L level it doesn't
like problems but it's not it won't back
down it won't back down unless it's
forced to and it's getting sidetracked
to that
degree and um so I always think about
that you know I I I I just want
everybody happy since I was a kid I want
everybody happy I want everybody healing
and I want everybody happy uh and even
even as a kid I used to say the spirit
why is this person disgruntled when
their most beloved person in their
family is so it's getting so much better
he's been so sick and spirit would say
well you know it's it's like ego stuff
and it's it's jealousy stuff it's just
weird stuff it's a whole pile of just
emotional
damage emotional damage and I said well
you know it's amazing because you know
and that reminded me of people's
livers people's
livers you know what's getting in the
way of people doing the right thing for
their liver a lot of bad information and
misinformation out there that has those
things attached to it like ego and and
all kinds of different things and
agendas and everything else that are
going on and it gets in the way of
people healing gets in the PE it gets in
the way of people ever protecting their
liver protecting their liver healing the
liver looking after their liver and a
liver needs help and it needs that
attention it needs that attention and
this this woman
actually I mean this was this was
horrific what she was going through
horrific and healing for the first time
she just needed she just need needed
some of that information the liver just
needs some
attention needs some attention so it
could do what you you need to do her
immune system needed a little bit of
caring a little bit of compassion a
little bit of the right information for
the first time in her her life so that
her immune system could go and seek out
and Destroy and do what it needs to do
and not get sidetracked the liver needs
a same thing it's got an immune system
that wants to Seek and Destroy and kill
things but it gets sidetracked so
confrontation is not good no matter what
in in you know when it comes down to
healing and so many people have to deal
with
it so what do we do we want to dissolve
Stones we want to clean up the liver we
want to do the right things low protein
diet low protein diet you think you got
a liver thing developing low protein
diet why cuz it's lowfat lowfat diet
lowfat if you're a vegan cut back on the
nuts cut back on the nuts and seeds too
many nuts too many seeds nut pies
nutcakes whatever I even if you're all
whatever and I respect that I love it I
love raw vegan stuff I love raw
plant-based I'm totally behind that 100%
oh my God I've seen people I've seen
people get rid of the worst diseases
ever in history with those the 28-day
cleanse the 28 day cleanse in my book
one is literally 28 days of low to no
fat plant-based mostly
raw why to to get the liver
to where it needs to be to get the liver
to do more than to dissolve stones to
dissolve stones for God's sake to get
the liver in a better place doesn't mean
I'm anti-animal protein or anything if
somebody wants to eat animal
protein but when somebody's doing these
gallbladder flushes and then going after
the gallbladder flesh they're eating all
this animal protein a week later and
they're pounding that liver down that
liver the amount of bile it has to
produce is unbelievable to break down
fat and animal fat and animal protein
and and forget the animal stuff that
liver has to do so much to break down
plant fat like nuts tons and tons of
nuts and oils so if a vegan also a
plant-based person is eating of
vegetarians eating still all this fat
constantly eating tons of it the liver
still has to produce tremendous amounts
of bile salt the pressure and the stress
it goes
under is ridiculous he can't dissolve
stuff Stones Under that you can't clean
up the sludge at the bottom of the
gallbladder the bottom of the oil pan
you can't you can't do
that and if you're eating animal protein
and you dropped your carbs fine okay you
dropped chocolate cake that's the best
thing you can do that's great but yet
you're just doing vegetables and lots of
animal fat without realizing it is your
calorie to survive because of some
trendy diet out there from somebody that
knows absolutely nothing about the liver
because that's what I've seen that's
what I've seen even the best experts out
there
with the fanciest diets know nothing
about the liver I'm sorry they just
don't I know I sound like Brash or
boasting I don't even know what it
sounds like but it's it's legit it's
what it is that's what it is I know I
sound uh pointy about it I get it I get
it I can't help it I can't help it
sometimes because I just want people
doing the right thing I mean I wake up
in the morning and I say
Spirit you know I just want people doing
the right
thing well at night I go to bed and I
say God just you know just help people
please send all the Angels you can and
help as many people as you can just
please don't send me one okay I don't
deserve it there's so many people that
are better people than me way better
people than me you know and and and and
and they deserve every Angel there is in
the world every Angel there is in the
world you know in the universe every
Angel there is in heaven you know the
thing is is that that you want to
dissolve these Stones you want to clean
up the liver you want to take care of it
lower your fats lower your protein if
you're big on animal protein drop it
down to one serving a day if you're big
on nuts and seeds cuz you're you know
plant-based drop those nuts and seeds
down fruit is the greatest preventative
ever for keeping gallstones from
producing is fruit can you believe that
I should have rewound that the what's
the greatest preventative ever for
keeping gallstones from producing and
even making them dissolve is fruit why
didn't I switch that around I said fruit
first
God the less fruit you eat in a lifetime
the less fruit you eat in a lifetime the
greater chance of gall storms to gall
stones to well Gall storms yeah gall
stone creating a crap storm inside the
in your gallbladder creating all the
pain and
suffering but the less chance you will
grow a gall stone the greater chance
you'll dissolve one lemon water lime
water lime water lemon water lime water
dissolves
Stones dissolve Stones don't eat animal
protein for breakfast whatever you do
you'll never get a gall stone or you'll
never get a cholesterol someb Billy
Ruben stone or or or sludge out of the
liver never if you're an animal protein
lover it has to be at a different time
of day it can't be in the in the morning
if you're a vegan you can't be doing nut
stuff in the morning if you're worried
about gall stones go if if you're
worried you got a gallbladder problem
you can't be doing piles and nuts in the
morning it's got to be things there got
to be some fruit got to be some fruit
smoothies got to be you know the wild
blueberries got to be different fruits
and dissolve cranberry cranberries
handful of
cranberries celery sticks handful of
cranberries anything anything any kind
of fruit celery juice great dissolver of
of of of gunk in the liver to stop it
from purging back up into the gall
gallbladder incredible weapon amazing
weapon vitamin C the the basic
supplement vitamin C is incredible for
taking care of the liver and
gallstones vitamin C that alone is
unbelievable what a weapon that is aloe
vera what a weapon that is but cucumber
juice SEL juice these are weapons for
getting the liver cleaned up and and and
healed hold back the fat in the morning
do fat-free mornings and if you think
you got a really big gallbladder problem
do the 28 declin from book one but just
hold back the fats live a life where the
morning doesn't have fat in it if you're
worried if you're worried about gall
stones gallbladders liver problems hold
back the fats hold back the protein in
the morning that you do your green juice
you can do lots of fruit you don't have
to starve you don't have to starve maybe
mid morning you can bring a little fat
in but just hold it back from morning
morning don't even have milk which is
fat in your coffee in the morning
because you just put fat in there which
what it does it puts stress on the liver
the liver can't do what it needs to do
it just had a night from hell every
single night the liver has a night from
hell trying to process and and take care
of the the the the the garbage that's in
your diet in your life the poisons that
are inside the liver that inherited from
your parents all the way down and that
liver is so filled up with poisons it's
unbelievable and it strains all night
and it has to work all night while
you're sleeping and in the morning what
do we do we put something in there like
an
egg and we're going to end up with a
cholesterol Stone I'm sorry maybe not
now maybe you're exercising and you're
losing weight and you're on this new
diet fancy diet and you think eggs are
great and you're not going to get a
cholesterol Stone that's not how it
works you'll get that cholesterol Stone
down the
road that's
right but you got to be fat free in the
morning you think you think you got real
problems with your gallbladder go fat
free long term go long term if you can
do the 28 days I know people have done
longer they've dissolved their
Stones you could but but the lemon water
is critical for dissolving Stones
cranberries dissolve Stones cranberry
juice cranberry water cranberry water
blend some cranberries with some water
cranberry water
actually actually
dissolves
Stones while the blueberry dissolve
Stones you know the Frozen wild
blueberries those are Stone dissolvers
and they clean up the liver they clean
up the background of what's creating all
these problems that we talked about in
the
show the liver cleans up all these
backgrounds all the background garbage
the background noise that's coming up
that that no one wants to analyze the
gunk inside a gallbladder and nobody
wants to look into cuz it's like dirt
looking in a dirty closet it's like the
medical industry looking in a dirty
closet and analyzing what's in there and
be like how did that get in there oh it
got in there because uhoh yeah and the
industries in the chemical Industries
and chemical companies and all the
different industries that produce so
much stuff that ends up in our liver how
did that end up in there how did
pesticides from that company that one
specific company we know of how did that
end up in somebody's
gallbladder
how did that end up no one wants to look
into that I mean I mean Jesus I mean no
one wants to look into any of that of
course not because it doesn't fit the
agenda it doesn't fit where the interest
groups are it doesn't fit with
everything I have to do the new opening
of the show and I don't like doing that
new opening every
time I don't but I have to now I have to
we have to get the information right and
straight I love you guys listen start
with that you never want to do too much
crazy stuff with the liver you never
want to purge it too hard you never want
to purge anything too hard you want to
take a you know you don't want to you
don't want to go those roots when you
take care of your liver you start with
something basic like that and you're
already on your way and I'll do more
liver stuff for you I promise so we can
do more we will do more liver stuff I
know we need to I just try to cover as
much as I can with the gallbladder today
I love you I love you like you don't
even know you don't even know how much
just know take care no be well one day
at a time you can heal you keep a li
heart I'm with you bless your heart
bless your soul take care and um yeah
yeah talk to you next show can't
wait