okay
Facebook YouTube telegram Rumble we're
live
and I'm excited link is in description
on how to see me on Rumble by the way
you guys we're talking about tools for
the immune system really important time
we're at a place where hey lots of bugs
going around lots of stuff going around
got to keep our immune system strong
lots of stress things kind of breaking
our immune system down we'll talk about
the different things that break our
immune system down we're live on Tick
Tock live on Rumble live on telegram
live on Facebook Live on YouTube we got
a whole thing going on right here all
kinds of stuff right here okay I got
some oranges right
right vitamin C shock therapy right
we're gonna do some of that exciting
zinc shock therapy we're going to talk
about that we're going to do the heavy
metal detox smoothie I'm excited about
that too I got fresh cilantro here look
how beautiful that is are you guys doing
this as a leafy green are you putting it
in your salads are you having a whole
bunch of it like this you can put a
bunch of it in your salad right got some
frozen wild Blues right there Frozen
wild blueberries so we got a lot going
on I'm excited even got the wild
blueberry juice here got the Bemidji
immune system tools which is a big deal
we got some lemons as well and
this is fun because we got stuff to talk
about you guys we're talking about
building up the immune system tools for
our immune system vitamin C shock
therapy using shock therapy as well all
this is important I even have some time
right here right look at that beautiful
time that is a weapon you do your fresh
thyme tea we'll talk about that too okay
see you guys
our immune systems are under a lot these
days right everybody's are okay so we
want to keep our immune system strong
keep in mind this is really important to
know if you got any kind of symptoms any
kind or if you've got any kind of
diagnosis if you're you're someone with
Hashimoto's thyroiditis or
hyperthyroidism right or fatigue or
anything anxiety or lupus or
neurological Lyme or whatever it is
you're dealing with your immune system
is already struggling so it's already
weakened along the way your immune
system's already been weakened along the
way and then the flu comes and hits us
and knocks us down and then we're
knocked down and then
we go when we go and we go to the doctor
we get a blood test
and we get our blood drawn out of us and
then boom our immune system gets knocked
down again right down to the floor okay
so we get hit in all these ways that's
just a couple of ways we get our immune
systems down low when they start to
knock down like that right and then we
get all upset about things we get worked
up and then boom adrenals
fight or flight fight or flight fight or
flight and her immune system is dropping
then too
see then where our immune system is
getting hit hard on that as well you're
upset about something emotional
confrontation emotional stress of any
kind any kind of struggle hardship
difficulty and then we got adrenaline
running and it drops down our immune
system
so that's another thing all on its own
and then
our brain
starts to get toasted it gets toasted it
gets beaten down
right so our mind it gets beaten down so
easily these days everybody's going
through so much and that breaks down our
immune system too because that's a lot
on us right it's a lot on us so there's
a lot of reasons why our immune system
takes a hit
and there's things that happen in our
personal lives that lower our immune
system but what's the note what's really
annoying what's really annoying
is when we got enough on our plate
personally right in our life and then we
have outside Invaders
flew
anything happening in the flu family
bugs people are worried about that are
going around right and we have that
outside sources salt in the wound you
know what I mean as if we have enough
crap on our hands with their immune
systems as if we got enough difficulties
with our immune systems next thing you
know it we get hit down I got a sore
throat now
I think I got a sore throat coming on
you know yeah
I think I got a sore throat and I don't
feel good and the sinuses are getting a
little clogged up and
and I think I might even have a cough
coming on I don't know where was I uh
it's at the store
um someone was coughing next to me at
the store no that wasn't is that it or I
was at the post office is trying to get
an early Christmas gift out or something
or what was I doing
and I got a um no I think I just got a
cold coming on and so what happens is
you know we have enough on our plate and
then we get these outside annoyances
that come and get us right
so we're talking about building up the
immune system this is critical and so
important once again you guys we're live
on telegram we're live on Facebook we're
live on YouTube live on Rumble check out
Rumble look at the link in the
description if you guys want to join
that and see me there we're on Tick Tock
so I'm excited good to see you guys this
is a great day so let's start let's talk
about zinc shock therapy to start with
okay
what I love about seeing sock therapy
right if I have a friend or I have a
family member
and they're getting a cold of some kind
or flu bug or whatever's happening in
their life they're not feeling good or
up against what's going on around us
right and they're not feeling good I'm
always like zinc shock therapy man zinc
shock therapy so it's family and friends
I'm like are you doing it are you doing
it right so the zinc shock therapy I
offer my family and my friends is of
course it's got to be the liquid zinc
sulfate that's the best one there is out
there okay this is the best brand I'm
not sponsored by these guys just telling
you right off the running it's vimorgy
these in Victor I Amazon Mary e r g
y.com themergy.com that's the zinc I use
for my friends and family it's critical
for immune system stuff and if you look
at the medical medium books right
if you look at like cleanse the heel
okay and you see autoimmune in here and
you see symptoms and conditions in here
because there's almost 200 or over 200
when when you go through the book of
symptoms and conditions right you'll see
zinc is for these symptoms and
conditions there's a reason when we're
sick and we have a symptom or condition
our immune system is down it's down
that's the whole point zinc builds it
back up because we're zinc deficient
that's what happens out there we're zinc
deficient very important to know
okay we're zinc deficient because we're
up against so much we're up against
bacteria we're up against viruses we're
up against these things so we get zinc
deficient zinc gets burned up it gets
used up really quick and easy in the
body
it gets used up
fast too real fast so what I love if
someone in my family they're getting a
scratchy throat they call me and they're
not really no answer it's like aw
I got a sore throat coming on zinc shock
therapy it's really important a lot of
people do it actually Millions around
the world do the zinc shock therapy
medical medium tool to Medical medium
tools so for adults it's two dropper
fulls every three hours two dropper
fulls every three hours that's what it
is for adults children a lot less I talk
about the dosages in cleanser heal
ask your doctor if it's right for you
I'm just telling you what I do for my
friends and for my family if you're
sensitive do a little touch you're
sensitive with anything you're sensitive
with anything you're you're sensitive
doesn't matter what supplement it is
doesn't matter what food you're really
sensitive just do a little just do a
little do a couple of drops one two
three four five six tiny drops right I
got a sensitive family member I'm like
okay do a couple drops that's fine but
ask your doctor what's right for you
okay you can bring that to your doctor
and ask them I'm just telling you what's
for my friends and family I get asked
every single day so zinc shock therapy
is a great tool to knock things back
knock the crap out of stuff back is what
I mean like really I mean that's what it
can do
and I talked about it years ago it's a
medical medium tool you know when you
get run down
you're run down
your immune system is run down okay
basophils neutrophils lymphocytes
monocytes right killer cells your white
blood count right gets run down starts
to get beaten down and then
you pick something up
and a lot of people were sick with
symptoms and conditions they already
have all these different things going on
they got the Epstein bar they got the
shingles they already have viruses they
already have bacteria they already have
stuff they got strep people get strep
throat easy so we're going to talk about
the next thing that's critical Sean says
what does he mean by sensitive
well only sensitive people know that
sensitive people right people who are
like well I can't really have that
herbal tea it's too strong
um I can't really have too much healthy
food I kind of it's hot it's hard for me
I can't eat this because I get a funny
feeling
um you know they're sensitive sensitive
that's what I mean people who are
sensitive know what I'm talking about
they only can take a supplement here
supplement there right really sensitive
Sharon says what was the name of the
zinc supplement
it's vimergy V as in Victor I am as in
Mary e r g y.com it's the best sync out
there right and I'm talking about what
to do for our immune system and I'm not
sponsored by those guys
um great people okay I get to know the
the different companies that have the
best products out there I get to know
them I like having relationships this
way I can keep my eyes on things is the
product staying at its highest qualities
the product staying at its best and I've
lost a lot of relationships throughout
the years because companies would not
keep that quality they would not keep
that quality insurance you know and keep
all that Holy keep it right and they
would change because they have free will
and they can change their recipes change
their products and then I'm like I'm
done but Bemidji incredible products um
friends of mine just I'm proud to say
that because they have hearts of gold
there's a lot of companies that I've
that I work with in the sense where
making sure their stuff is good
um and so yeah they're they're
incredible they're totally incredible so
let's talk about vitamin C shock therapy
vitamin C shock therapy okay is
that's a really good one too so this is
this is a vitamin C that's amazing for
people who are sensitive to vitamin C
ascorbic acid
it's really harsh on a lot of people's
system ascorbic acid okay and this isn't
ascorbic acid this isn't like the
battery acid vitamin C out there this is
buffered in a way that's gentle on the
system so that's what I love about the
micro C and Powerful right so there's
there's vitamin C's out there that are
so
abrasive and people like yeah I'm taking
vitamin C and oh my God it's giving me
the runs or something like that I've
seen that over there well that's not
what happens here with the the micro C
okay that's the one that I recommend
right there it's the vermergy micro C
just so you notice a zinc shock therapy
we just talked about now we're doing
vitamin C shock therapy okay remember
not sponsored by these guys I'm not the
owner of the company or anything of that
sore I like making that clear you guys
know I work with the mega with the with
the juicer because you know of that
whole thing I told you guys and um
so I'm making vitamin C shock therapy
you do warm water you can do hot water
doesn't have to be real hot but warm
water is great okay I'm putting some
water in there right there two capsules
right
two capsules right there we're doing
some honey
now this is
really incredible tool really an
incredible powerful tool keep that in
mind all right and I'm doing an orange
in here too I got these beautiful
oranges right this is the vitamin C
shock therapy
it's a medical medium tool
that has turned people's lives around
saved lives okay
so I'm squeezing some orange in here
vitamin C shock therapy is a great way
to save your immune system when you need
it the most
save your immune system when you need it
the most right because you're coming
down with something or you're run down
or you're not feeling good say you got a
UTI so
family friend contacted me and said I
got a UTI coming on what do I do aw I'm
like where's your vitamin C shock
therapy do it now okay and you can do it
for two days you can do it longer if you
want every two waking hours
you do two capsules
every two waking hours so what you do is
you get the honey ready
you get the orange ready you get your
capsules ready and every two hours
you're doing it this is Vitamin C shock
therapy critical for what's happening
it's like I get calls all the time
friends and family and like get a
scratchy throat aw what do I do
um been around a whole bunch of people
that were coughing and sneezing what do
I do I'm not feeling that good what do I
do got a UTI coming on what do I do you
know I got a stye coming on
conjunctivitis I got seems like chronic
sinusitis gets worse which you know I'm
like well your vitamin C shot there be
so important right there okay so that's
what that is
now that's the micro C
emergy.com that's the one I use now I'm
asked every single day what supplements
do I take what do I do do I do the heavy
metal detox smoothie do I take the
vitamin C showing you guys what I use
and what I do this is the zinc that's
the vitamin C
all right vitamin C shock therapy zinc
shock therapy are in cleanse to heal
keep that in mind amazon.com us right
it's 51 off there and check it out it's
cleanse the heel right that's the
medical medium Book Get It Free at the
library too if you want to try to do
that I tell people all the time and go
to the library and try to get cleansed
to heal or any medical medium books free
at the library right
so I'm talking about another powerful
tool golden seal now this is interesting
because
Goldenseal is in supplements out there
okay immune like immune strengthening
supplements and so forth but they use a
speck of it
spec of it and it's usually mixed in a
formula with a whole bunch of other
stuff okay and over the years
I have seen that never work I have never
seen that work
when a speck of it is used where they
literally use less than what you see
there as a drop that's one drop right
there you use one drop it's in a formula
or a capsule with a whole bunch of other
things
I've never seen that be effective when
someone is getting a UTI a bad case of
acne conjunctivitis a stye strep throat
a sore throat a flu a cold I've never
seen that work
I've seen practitioners tell people go
take this formula go take this formula
there's a little bit of echinace in
there there's a little bit of Goldenseal
and they still get sick and they're
still running to get antibiotics for
their their UTI they're still running to
get antibiotics for their stye for their
chronic sinusitis for their lung
infection for their bronchitis they're
still running
to have to get the antibiotics because
they're taking
weak formulas
okay Goldenseal is a powerful medical
medium tool because and I can say that
because of the way
it's supposed to be used right if you
look and cleanse the heel there's a
strep throat section five dropper holes
twice a day in the strep throat section
any family member or friend that
contacts me that says aw I got a sore
throat coming on whether it's strep
throat or a cold or whatever it is
I'm like hit the strep throat section in
here
and take that Goldenseal therapeutically
therapeutically it's critical to take it
therapeutically that's the difference
right there okay because I've watched
for years talked to hundreds of doctors
over the last 30 years I've watched all
kinds of different formulas made out
there and it's usually some bad alcohol
written natural flavor ridden citric
acid ridden
formula with a drug no one realizes it a
drop of low quality
Goldenseal in it oh this formula looks
good oh I'm in the store right now I'm
at Whole Foods I'm checking out the
different stuff here this one says it's
got echinace in here and this one says
it's got gold and seal in here and
libelia in here and a couple other
things it's like good luck
good luck you just pissed your money
away good luck if something's got to get
done it has to be done right so what I
like to use Golden sealed how I like to
use Goldenseal is therapeutically and
when it comes down to your immune system
and immune system issues and building up
the immune system it's critical to use
it therapeutically so important
UTI boom therapeutically
sinusitis a boom therapeutic lip Okay
cold flu boom therapeutically right
concerns about any kind of flu family
going around right now and everybody's
locking their doors and scared about
boom therapeutically
that's what I love about Goldenseal so
if I got
you know into a jam starting to get
something or a tickle in my throat I've
been flying in Planes I've been visiting
family visiting friends whatever I'm
doing running myself down writing the
books on two hours of sleep
I do the golden seal last night
I do it every night before bed last
night I did six dropper fulls before bed
that's what I did last night
six dropper folds before bed
and that's what I did I took one two
three four five six
I don't have anything going on
I feel fine don't have nothing happening
don't even have a sore throat
but I'm keeping my immune system strong
is what I'm doing I don't have a reason
to take it I don't need to take it I
feel the same as I always feel
I'm blessed I feel good
okay but I still took six dropper fulls
before going to bed last night
and sure I may do that for like a week
and then take a few days off three or
four days off and then I'll do it for
like a week again
Claudine says suffered for 20 years with
hot flashes two weeks on your morning
cleanse with heavy metal detox smoothie
my hot flashes are gone thank you
incredible quality amazing
I just want to say something about
medical medium stuff okay just a little
heart to heart you guys
and
people don't come to Medical medium
information
right first
it's rare
they get sick
and they go to a doctor
they stay sick they go to another doctor
and you gotta have a doctor you got to
have doctors doctors do some great stuff
and you need them for a lot of different
things they get sick they go to a doctor
again
then to another one then to a natural
doctor then to another type of doctor
and then another type of practitioner it
takes a good amount of doctors for a lot
of people a good amount of Specialists
for a lot of people to finally break
down enough get beaten down enough have
enough time pass
where they got to go in for the heavy
duty stuff medical medium information
medical medium books medical medium
knowledge was all about the sickest
people
that have been sick too long
it's not about
what's happening out there where there's
a lot of different practitioners and
doctors and not handling the real 666
people they're just handling people that
are not so sick and they're learning
tips and their online learning tips and
their Googling tips and they're doing
their thing mm info
was for the people that had enough and
they're like you know what
I've already been to 10 doctors I've
already been to three neurologists I've
already had the MRIs in the CAT scans
I've already had more blood taken from
me than
than anybody I've ever known I've
already done all this
and I heard about medical medium I've
been I've been not wanting to do it but
I finally got his books and I realized
it makes sense I've never heard this
information before
and now I'm healing and that's what mm
info was about for years it was about
people coming into my office for over 35
years after they've traveled around the
world and had the best access to the
best doctors even people on private
planes and loaded with all the money in
the world and finally knocking on the
medical medium dorm being like we are
desperate we don't usually talk to
someone who hears from a higher source
to get our information but right now
we've done everything where we've been
through it all what can you do and I'm
like it's gonna be what it's going to be
things you have to do it's going to be
the medical medium tools
but you got a chance to heal
golden seal therapy therapeutically was
never on anybody's radar it's in medical
medium tool ask your doctor if it's
right for you anything you pick up from
here you can ask your doctor
okay friends and family they come to me
for help
and I give them that knowledge and say
use that Goldenseal therapeutically six
dropper fulls three times a day five
dropper fulls twice a day four dropper
fulls four times a day you got something
coming on you got your UTIs and you got
your uh BV right bacterial vaginosis you
got your bladder infections right you
got your kidney infections you've got
your styes you've got your eye
infections your nose infections you've
got your bronchitis whatever's happening
got your bad acne
therapeutically that's the difference
right there and that's what you don't
hear all these years from the naturopath
from the holistic doctor from the
acupuncturist from God bless them all
but you don't hear this stuff you might
hear from somebody you should try to be
on an immune system formula I saw it at
Whole Foods I saw it at the health food
store here here's the brand and it's got
this in it it's got this in it it's got
this in it good luck good luck because
it's got that much gold and seal it's
got no zinc in it it's got that much
Goldenseal if you're lucky in the whole
formula mixed with a whole bunch of
other stuff and that's why people they
stay lost and they don't know where to
go and it's sad
so anyway we're talking about Goldenseal
that's the Bemidji golden seal and when
you have a powerful version of it
it takes it to a whole new level and
that's what's incredible you guys this
is important information
this gets people out of trouble is what
it does it gets them out of trouble and
that's what's amazing about it okay so
go through another immune system builder
right here
which is cat want to run that one
by everybody Lyme disease the world of
Lyme disease and Lyme symptoms changed
because of medical medium information
putting out cat's claw out there all
these years now that's an important one
to know lime doctors now bring in cat's
claw that's mm protocol
and it's actually gotten out there
around the world right but me
I'll use cat's call for friends and
family
if they got something cooking that's
going on strange nerve pain or some kind
of symptom or some kind of tingles and
numbness or something going on with them
neurologically I'd be like are you on
your cat's claw
you know and Cat's Claw is great for a
lot of different protocols I talk about
that too
Taylor Rain I suffered from Interstitial
cystitis for months
no doctors could give me any answers one
month of following your advice and I am
completely pain-free thanks to God for
leading me to you that's incredible and
that's how it happens with medical
medium information it's people been
through a lot and they've seen a lot of
people throughout the years someone just
doesn't first get sick and I'll go oh
I'll go to that guy
the medical medium guy
um he hears his information from above
and I'll go to him first
only a handful over the years here and
there they're like no I'm gonna go to
this guy first because I don't I don't
want to go to the doctor but this don't
that's only stuff but really it's the
majority of people have to just I guess
they have to go through the ringer
and you got to go to your doctor you
have to because you know it's good to
get good to see your doctor and have
your doctor look at you and take take
this information these tools to your
doctor ask your doctor about them
that's fine that's fine so we're just
giving you a little recap real quick so
vitamin C shock therapy with the microcl
showing you guys there's two capsules
every two hours every waking two hours
got a family member that woke up in the
middle of the night and they were up for
a few minutes
right they texted me I happened to be up
I was working on the book I said do it
again I said yeah but I did it all day I
said do it again
in the middle of the night get the two
capsules out and do it again you're up
you're awake do it again they did it
went back to sleep they got that extra
one in it's important so it's an
incredible information talk about zinc
shock therapy
zinc shuts down bugs shuts it down bugs
are allergic to zinc something you'll
never hear out there
it's mm info bugs are allergic they're
sensitive to zinc zinc destroys bugs
pushes bugs back so it's not just about
zinc actually restoring your immune
system which it feeds your immune cells
that's what it does but it slows down
the bugs they get docile
they actually get docile so when you got
that cold or flu family or whatever bug
that's out there swimming around and
everybody's worried about you got these
different bugs you hear something going
around some kind of tummy bug whatever
it is
zinc slows it down and then it levels
out the immune system so it doesn't
overreact or under react
see how important that is really really
important
all right so let's talk about some other
stuff let's
talk about metals
you guys got anxiety
got medals
guy's got some depression
you got medals
you know somebody who's bipolar
they got medals
know somebody with ADHD they got medals
know somebody schizophrenia
they got metals
you know somebody that's got
depersonalization
they got medals
you know somebody who is just basically
struggling emotionally but there's no
answer to why
got some metals Metals cause a lot of
trouble a lot of problems okay you know
somebody with neurological Lyme they got
viral issues
and they got metal
you know somebody with eczema psoriasis
they got viral issues and they got metal
metal
keep that in mind toxic heavy metals are
the ruination of a lot of lives
they literally shape Who You Are
in ways we don't want to even be you
think somebody wants to be bipolar do
you ever meet anybody they want to be
bipolar I'm just curious
and if you guys run into somebody who
wants to be bipolar
like no no don't worry that I got a
friend they're bipolar they want to be
bipolar
I got a friend who's bipolar they're ups
and downs and their Mania they go into
mania they want Mania no they don't
no one wants to be bipolar
oh do you know somebody that wants to be
I got a friend
who's got a lot of anxiety and I'm like
get the medals out
get the medals out do you know anybody
who wants to be anxiety written by
crippling inside you guys know anybody
who wants anxiety
right no one wants anxiety
that's the metals talking the metals can
literally reshape and change someone's
life in a way they don't want
metals can even speak for you when you
don't even want to speak metals can
control us and create this mind control
over us
do anybody who wants to be depressed
like they want to be severely depressed
they want to be suicidal
do you know anybody that wants to be
suicidal they actually want to be I
don't know anybody that wants to be
suicidal
the medals can make people suicidal
one thing I don't like about toxic heavy
metals is it breaks down the immune
system
we got enough breaking down our immune
systems you guys we have enough
we got hardships we got the adrenaline
pumping we got the adrenaline surges we
got all kinds of crap on our plate we
got enough struggles we got enough
issues and problems with all kinds of
people throughout our lives we get
enough stress when we're driving a car
we get enough stress when we're
registering a car we get enough stress
in general and then
we get these outside sources we get the
metals toxic heavy metals and then we
get the bugs and then we're all of a
sudden getting another bug and then
we're getting the flu and cold then we
got more metals and guess what
it starts to break down the immune
system so it isn't just everything else
out there it's the metals that break
down the immune system too and that's
really important to know
doing a heavy metal detox movie
today's like an immune system building
day and that is something we should
celebrate really because it's important
to protect your immune system it's
important to take care of yourself you
guys by the way we're live right now
telegram we're live on Tick Tock 11
Facebook Live on YouTube live on Rumble
Okay so
and I just want to let everybody know
link is in description if you want to
hook into the whole Rumble thing too
right link is in the description check
that out so we're doing heavy metal
detox smoothies so wild blueberries
not cultivated blueberries
Wild
okay
an adaptogenic food
incredible adaptogenic food immune
system building because it feeds cells
strengthen cells you see that color
right there what's that crazy color you
see that crazy deep rich blue
anthocyanins
right
we're going to make sure we get those in
us so we're doing two cups of Frozen
wild blueberries whoa look at that look
at that
amazing how incredible is that
it really is it's incredible right
um
so let's do this let's throw a couple of
bananas in there let's do that
such a great food incredible food
glucose for the brain that's what
bananas are glucose for the brain right
throwing two bananas in here we're doing
the recipe a little bit we're going to
talk about the different ingredients why
this medical medium tool gets the metals
out how it's the only tool that gets the
metals out of people I love how people
are like oh try this heavy metal formula
uh is your bipolar gone no
try this heavy metal formula that
there's some other guys got some podcast
doctors got because he just learned
about metals because the medical mediums
doing all the metal work all these years
so he learned about it he's got his own
formula check it out does it get rid of
your anxiety anxiety under
depression
no
two bananas in there medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie
and heavy metal detox cleanse has turned
lives around has gotten rid of
depression in people crippling
depression got their lives back got rid
of anxiety crippled anxiety got rid of
bipolar OCD
do you know anybody that wants to be OCD
do you guys know anybody that wants to
be obsessive compulsive disorder to the
point where they can't even walk or talk
they got thoughts visiting their minds
circulating their minds just driving
them insane do you know anybody that
wants to be OCD
no one wants to be OCD no one wants to
have OCD
Metals causal Metals cause it
okay
so let's talk about OCD for a couple of
seconds too we're making the heavy metal
detox smoothie right we got the wild
blueberries in here a couple bananas in
there
we're going to talk about OCD for a
second this is fun
it's not fun if you have OCD
breaks my heart so many people suffering
to a degree with it it's just it's just
brutal
beware though okay
they're changing OCD around where
anybody who has anything they'll say
it's OCD now though it's really sad what
they're doing out there and I have to
talk about that okay because what
they're doing is they're saying if
someone's even anxious they're saying
that's OCD it's like no they're they're
anxious well see these are different
kind of thing so if you'll see this
pencils pencil is a neuron so that's a
neuron inside your brain right neurons
inside your brain okay
that's your head that's half a brain
right there
that's a neuron this pencil
that's metal
that metal is in the middle of a neuron
okay now electricity goes to the neuron
and it travels down the neuron when you
think of thought so when you're thinking
of thought like hey
this is what I'm going to do today I'm
going to make this my best day this is
going to be a good day I'm going to do
some cool stuff I'm thinking of thought
right now
and then all of a sudden some thoughts
you don't want to think you start
circulating right it's a vicious cycle
that's happening and you're in stuck in
this OCD land okay what's happening is
electricity is going down the neuron
and then it's hitting a piece of metal
on the neuron
microscopic piece of metal but it's
hitting it on the neuron
then
it's going back the other way when it's
not supposed to
at the same time you're thinking a
thought another electrical impulse
electricity is going down the neuron
while that other electrical impulse is
coming back
they meet right here
and then they explode
that's OCD right there
just so you know metal can change your
life the direction of your life
it can change how you live your life it
can wreak nothing but Havoc I love
getting metal out of people's heads
important this is this is Advanced
Medical medium information okay
I love getting Metals out of everyone's
brain really important our brain gets
saturated with metal
okay
wears down her immune system and it
breaks us down so here we are we're
struggling with our OCD and we're
getting really upset
we're getting upset
it's exhausting us
we're wearing down our adrenals
when we have bipolar we're getting upset
we're exhausting ourselves and we're
wearing down our adrenals when we have
crippling anxiety we're getting upset
we're exhausting ourselves and we're
wearing down our adrenals and our immune
system starts to break down
Metals break down our immune systems
very important to know okay
let's talk about me
it makes Incredible tool that has
changed lives
I'm recapping on the smoothie for a bit
we got bananas we got two cups of Frozen
wild blueberries right we got that let's
go into the next one cilantro
cilantro by itself
can get some metals out some
but when it's mixed with the other key
ingredients something happens that
changes everything
so
put some cilantro in there
we got that now
what I like to do is you guys know about
the wild blueberry juice okay
and I told you I am working with these
guys all right because I don't I don't I
don't want this to disappear out there
because it's that incredible so that's
the Wyman's wild blueberry juice right
they pressed the wild blueberries into a
potent form so what I do is I put the
wild blueberries in there
but I do a shot
of that blueberry juice
I just can't help myself right I'll do a
shot of that you know
that's incredible stuff
if you don't have the wild blueberries
then you got the wild blueberry just use
the wild blueberry juice don't have the
wild blueberries
then I'll do the vermergy
wild blueberry powder if you can't get
the Frozen wild blueberries
do the wild blueberry powder right so
I'll put some of that in there
in there too
the amount of anthocyanins we're talking
about right here like we're talking
about medicine now now we're in
medicinal
you know I love when I hear out there
people are like well that's medicinal it
is
I'm scratching my head because what
you're showing me over there ain't
medicinal
I see it all time out there it's like no
no this is Madison I'm like oh really it
is
this chocolate's medicinal I'm like
really because chocolate has caffeine in
it and it breaks down your adrenals and
lowers your immune system how is
chocolate medicinal when breaks your
immune
I want to know his apple cider vinegar
is medicinal over here oh it is because
guess what you won't have teeth left
when you're older because that apple
cider vinegar will dissolve your teeth
from the inside out
and how good is that going to be for
your immune system when you have no
teeth left down the road right
it's important to know like I hear it
all the time well that's medicinal oh it
is because I'm scratching my head over
here a little bit because that apple
cider vinegar is going to dissolve your
teeth I call it the teeth dissolver
because that's what it is
it's like okay anyway this is medicinal
that's what we're talking about here so
we got
the cilantro in here we got the
um
blueberries so now
we're talking about spirulina okay
I put one cup roughly one cup of
cilantro in there by the way okay now
we're talking about this uh the
spirulina now Okay so
spirulina gets Nettles out remember this
you can make a rhyme out of it if you
want
spirulina gets Metals out
Chlorella
doesn't I know that doesn't rhyme
but
it's something to remember chlorella
doesn't get Metals out spirulina gets
Metals out it's so important to know you
know why
is I can tell you now
and you'll know now
but then you'll see out there a lot of
people don't
and you'll see they're like gorilla
chlorella that does it chlorella I'll
give you a little hint or a little
talk about chlorella I've seen it
almost killed children
because it's so Russian roulette with
bad bacteria
that's number one
I've seen people react from chlorella to
an allergic reaction where their throat
closes up
and they almost die
I've seen that for 30 plus years
I've seen
people throw their guts out
on their bathroom floor for weeks at a
time until almost dying because of
Chlorella
that I've seen
but I've never seen chlorella fix
somebody's bipolar fix somebody's
depression fix somebody's OCD fix
somebody's depersonalization if
somebody's crippling anxiety fix
anything
that I haven't see
that's the difference
and it doesn't remove metals very
important to know so I like a good
quality spirulina it's the best one on
the market
putting a teaspoon in there that's the
Bemidji one right
that's the best one there is if you just
got on here and you're wondering if I'm
trying to sell Subs I'm not sponsored by
Bemidji
okay oops almost lost that one now the
barley grass juice powder now this is
important to know
not barley grass
barley grass juice powder I put a
teaspoon in there it's the specific
blend that gets the metals out
in the medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie it's the barley grass juice
powder the spirulina
it's the cilantro
it's the wild blueberry
right and then
it's the dolls now today I got the dose
liquid right so that's the Bemidji dose
liquid which is incredible so I'm
popping that in
I don't know if you had a chance to
check that out but this stuff is
incredible it's absolutely amazing so I
just threw a shot of that in there
um so the memory dose right
liquid so right now I have
the power five in here
the power five I still got one more
thing to put in
but I got the spirulina I got the barley
grass juice powder I got the wild
blueberry I got the cilantro and what's
the fifth I got the dolls in there now
got the five
right
then orange goes in
so put some orange in there squeeze in a
little bit of that if you got an orange
and that doesn't have a lot of juice you
can put two orange squeezes in you know
you can also peel the orange and put the
r a whole orange and a lot of people do
that it's perfectly fine so just want to
answer that question because I know
everybody
Chris you seem fine to me
power five right
so I'm putting a little these are small
oranges I'm just squeezing a little
extra Orange in here this is what I'm
doing there we go
now
when it comes down to immune systems you
know what I like
I like what works
there is so much misinformation about
the immune system and what works and
what doesn't out there
it's
even contagious that misinformation
I like things that have a track record
of working I like things that have a
history of working
I like things that have a history of
saving people's lives
I like things that have a real history
in changing so many lives it's
indisputable
and that's what I like for the immune
system
okay
I got this rigged up right now I'm gonna
turn this on
my hand over it
so let me escape
foreign
we're at a place in time in history
where immune systems are under assault
and under attack like never before
keep that in mind
that's where we are right now we're at a
place in time where our immune systems
are just under assault I got a cup right
here so I'm all set gonna pop this in
foreign
there's more actually than than what's
in this glass right here so I just
filled it up to the top
with that
the medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie right there
a little recap on what's Happening Here
and I still have one more tool to show
you because I have some fresh thyme so
guys don't go anywhere if you want to
catch that right there if you just got
on here we're live on telegram live on
Rumble we're live on YouTube live on um
Facebook we're live on Tick Tock we're
live on that as well
I want to talk about some things that
break down our immune system
this is going to be one of the most
important things you take from today
even if you're somebody that doesn't
have the medical medium tools
this is important okay
you want to definitely listen to this
right
what's happening right now
is people are getting taken advantage of
they go get their blood tests and too
much blood is drawn
when too much blood is drawn
they lose their CBC
they lose their white blood count
is what they lose
very important their white blood count
to kill ourselves their immune system
your immune system parols
your entire body
protecting you so that you don't get
brain infections see that you don't get
other infections so that you stay
healthy
the majority of your immune system
is circulating throughout your blood and
blood vessels and organs and glands
important to know
and what happens is when you get too
much blood removed
they remove it a portion of your immune
system so you're now more susceptible to
getting the flu the cold the UTIs
conjunctivitis the bronchitis and
anything else that you're dealing with
including sending you backwards into
chronic
mcfs lupus neurological lime or anything
else
people already have low immune systems
that's why they're sick to begin with
and then they get more blood drawn and
then they get sicker and then they get
more blood drawn because they got sicker
and no one's picking this off this is
something that's critical and then as
they get sicker they get more blood
drawn and then they get sicker more
blood drawn
see the Vicious Cycle
do you know why so many people died of
neurological Lyme in the last 40 years
they were bled to death
by their doctors
but the medical industry 27 vials 25
vials another 14 vials with a specialist
another 10 vials with another specialist
another doctor pulling another seven
vials another doctor pulling 40 vials
another doctor pulling 30 vials
and they lost your life
happens with a lot of people with cancer
too
you get sicker they pull more blood
sicker they pull more blood sicker they
pull more blood I'm saying this because
if you want to protect your immune
system going on into where we're heading
on to and everything else with this
winter and all that's happening
learn
about medical medium podcasts at Apple
podcast learn about the blood draw
vampire episode
learn how to protect yourself so you
know what to tell your doctor and you
know how to get the blood drawn
this is a critical piece of knowledge
I'm giving you for free
you notice how these lives are all free
it's all I do I don't take it to a
private platform and then charge for it
and everybody gets a ticket and they buy
or whatever it is and next thing you
know it you guys got to come to a big
event or something online or whatever it
is I do it for free
and I don't believe
in what they say out there that you have
to pay for it in order to honor respect
it and appreciate it I don't believe
that that's that's basically talking
stupid to people people aren't like that
I believe people know when they're
getting something that's incredibly and
powerful and for free and they know and
they appreciate it and I know you guys
do too I know you guys appreciate it
so let's talk about blood for a little
bit
they only need to take this much blood
right
that that much blood
to run your A1C and a a a a nutritional
panel a thyroid panel
you see what I'm saying they can find a
speck of blood on someone's pair of
jeans that was in a shallow grave 40
years ago from a murder scene
make a serum out of it
and get more information from it than
you can possibly imagine
think about that
but they will bleed you to death and
lower your immune system this is an
immune system building episode this is
about how to sustain your immune system
too
not just build it not just get it strong
not just fight bugs and fight problems
that I've been talking about all the
different conditions this is about
getting Metals out building up your
immune system this is about protecting
your protecting your immune system and
this is about sustaining your immune
system all of this
and the blood draws are a big one for
sustaining and protecting your immune
system I believe in blood tests I
believe in going to your doctor
but I believe in doing it right and
careful
because they've been trained to please
you to death
and that's why half the people with
neurological line in the last 40 years
lost their lives and died that's why
many people with multiple sclerosis lost
their lives and died throughout the
years that's why many people with ALS
lost their lives and died many years
that's why people with Hashimoto's got
worse until they got worse until they
got worse that's why everybody gets
sicker they've had their immune system
removed from the blood test over and
over and over and over again check out
the podcast so you can learn more about
how to protect yourself what to do all
that's important okay
now
do a little recap
and we're talking about building up the
immune system zinc shock therapy that
one right there an incredible weapon
incredible tool zinc shock therapy I
talked about that recap on that two
dropper fulls every three hours
for two days or three days or whatever
you need to do you'll see it in the
medical medium books and information if
you don't have cleanse to heal consider
getting it someday amazon.com us I don't
set the prices my publisher does it's on
amazon.com us it's 16.99 it's 51 offer
try to get it free at the library
consider having this powerful tool in
your hand a guide
a guide so making making time tea
so I'm going to turn the kettle on you
guys don't mind okay so I got this
little tea kettle right here I'm going
to turn the kettle on get that baby
running a little bit right
and we're gonna make some thyme tea
get in a cup
right now I have a pitcher here because
we can make thyme water you know what's
incredible about time water wow just
throw some time in there let it sit in
the fridge
so instead of drinking water every
single day you're drinking thyme water
that's an immune system builder an
immune system enhancer an immune system
protector
I am
stays in the bloodstream
for a longer duration than other herbs
paroling
your body looking for Invaders
and hindering those Invaders
that's what time does so that's the time
water I got the time T getting going
here
little time t
fresh thyme
put a few sprigs of time in there
just like that it's fine right
now you can do a couple things with that
I like honey in this
a little bit of honey
okay you can put a little bit of lemon
in this too
right
okay time water sits in the fridge
overnight just so you know
I just put lemon I just put a little
honey
right
and I got the hot water in here and I
have the fresh thyme
if there's nothing
you take from these lives right here
but this
I'm proud of you okay
if you don't take anything from here if
you're like uh whatever I'll do the time
okay the fresh thyme tea I'm proud of
you
one step at a time if you need to that's
okay all right so let's talk about time
for a little bit it's the
repeller of bugs
so
you got the bugs going around you got
the flu viruses you got the cold viruses
you got the plague viruses you got all
the bugs going around everything's
floating around
and when you have this in your system
you're helping to repel and destroy
those bugs these bugs are allergic to
time
phytochemical compounds in time are
antiviral and antibacterial so time has
antiviral antibacterial compounds
keep that in mind
you put this inside your body and the
bugs that keep everybody sick and all
you guys sick
don't like time
they don't like time
so time is an amazing tool it stays in
the bloodstream longer
so when you have your time water every
single day you're keeping the
phytochemical compounds that are
antiviral antibacterial you're keeping
them in your bloodstream longer and
longer and longer and you're keeping
them there so then now you're creating a
little bit of a shield a little bit of
an extra protector so if you were gonna
get sick you're gonna get sick way less
than you would have gotten way worse
keep that in mind
because it was sitting there Fielding
your bloodstream keeping Invaders from
exploding out of control
and that's
what I love about it that's the time
water you got the time T right here
see you guys
quick recap vitamin C shock therapy
right talk about that two capsules every
two hours waking hours
Right medical medium vitamin C shock
therapy micro C that's the one that I
use when I recommend okay that's the one
that's incredible
right zinc shock therapy we talked about
that two dropper fulls every three hours
a couple of days two days three days if
need if you feel like you're coming down
something talk to your doctor what's
right for you I'm telling you what I use
for my friends and family and for myself
personally if you're sensitive with any
supplements or anything else do a couple
of drops every three hours
ask your doctor what's right for you
okay
Goldenseal therapeutically you guys if
you just got on here watch this live
from the beginning wherever you can I'll
post it on YouTube if you like the video
on YouTube or wherever you guys thumbs
up if you can all right I'm posting it
on Rumble so you can watch it on Rumble
posting it there posting it on YouTube
I'm posting it on telegram I'm gonna try
hopefully my tech skills work
anyway
and then re-watch if you can learn how
learn about the therapeutic uses of
Goldenseal that's the beverage golden
seal not sponsored by these guys but the
stuff's incredible guts of energy Dulce
Atlantic dolls that blows my mind when I
found out about that recently I was like
what because I heard you guys talking
about it I was like what that's
incredible incredible I put that in the
smoothie
so pumped
um I talked about the power of the wild
blueberries getting the metals out why
this is an important episode you guys
should watch it from the beginning
talked about the wild blueberry juice is
an option I talked about the vermergy a
lot of blueberry powder right
so the vitamin C the zinc everything
anyway I'm heading off to do another
live believe it or not and I'm going to
click on telegram I'm going to click on
Instagram I'm gonna click on tick tock
and I'm heading there in about 10
minutes I just got to get my crap
together clean up this mess we're going
to talk about the immune system again
you never know every time I do another
live it's never the same
uh who knows I might mess up really bad
or might drop something or
who knows I might get a phone call too
and I might get a visit from Dr Nesbitt
I love you guys
so I'll see you guys soon okay we're
shutting things down and turn to tick
tock IG back on and telegram back on