with Miranda Kerr I guess is thanks for
joining us today that's a great day
we're so happy to be here we're gonna
talk about a couple of cool things
having metal detox smoothie Miranda does
that she there's the celery juice and
this is great health as well that's what
I say and I'm so happy that I get to
come on here and chat with you about all
the wonderful things that we're both
doing and they are like educating people
about so that's really important for
people to know well you've always caring
about like what people put on their
bodies you care about like it's like
your core organics it's about like
skincare that doesn't have bad chemicals
in it so it's unified organic yeah
because what you put on your skin soaks
into your bloodstream exactly it's
really important that we're conscious of
what we're doing and putting on our skin
and make an educated choice about it
yeah yeah and you've always known this
stuff for years and that's what's so
cool because your lines been out for a
while now yeah it's really established
because it's so healthy for the skin and
so it's like you know a lot about what
people should do and you know I remember
we were talking recently and you're like
no I don't like the scented candles with
the chemicals and there are some simple
things that people actually don't
realize and when you understand and you
can see what what is you know if you
read the ingredients and whatnot on the
back of any household goods what's in
your hair shampoo what's in your
products that you're putting on your
skin then you make an educated choice
and say okay well I'm gonna have that or
I'm not gonna moon it you know yeah and
it's like how we are with our food like
I try my best to eat healthy and organic
as much as possible and make educated
choices about it and I feel like that is
the best you can do really no I know you
you eat really clean and that's what
I've always admired like you're doing
them the heavy metal detox movie yeah
yeah I nearly mentioning how people
think it's gonna be this like really
harsh detox or something but it's not
yeah this is very gentle smoothie that I
love and I have every morning the heavy
metal detox amazing with your it's your
recipe I love it and I actually have to
even be a bit of a bigger bigger one
than
that's a small one with my celery juice
in the morning I have 32 ounces cool
that's perfect I tell people I started
like this yeah 32 ounces I'm doing so
much yeah and you know everyone in my
family is drinking celery now even Flynn
no way Evan Evan loves e celery he's
like he didn't in the beginning he's
like oh it's probably not gonna make a
difference and now I see he even tells
his friends celery celery you've got to
get on it's so good it helps just with
like the brain fog with energy levels
with just health in general I know every
now and then you'll hear out there like
there's some naysayers saying don't
drink celery juice you don't want a
juice celery you want to keep the fiber
and I'm always like no no no what this
is an herbal this is an herbal power
right here it's a table medicine
alkaline system yeah fast though like
fast versus slow alkalinity it actually
alkaline this quickly and that's
something that happens too that's why
people get relief with acid reflux
almost immediately
yes and all of that actually when I was
younger I had a little bit of acid
reflux and I think it was emotional at
the time because I had lost my boyfriend
he had passed away instantly in a car
accident and I had to worry and concern
and that had brought like kind of you
know how emotion you have a loss I've
talked about that in the medical meeting
books they talked about that in medical
media book one and they're some of the
other medical media books that like when
you get that great loss and and
something so so hard and a struggle like
that it's it could really hit you hard
too on a whole nother but I wish that I
had known about celery juice back then
because it would have really helped like
soothe soothe my digestion and now it
does every day which I'm so great well
you've been doing it long term too
that's what's cool like and I tell
people I tell you guys out there all the
time and I tell other people I run into
all the time you just don't do it for
just five days don't do it for and to
seven days and you're done and every day
every day yeah and you're doing every
day for a long time now
for a couple yeah that's really cool and
this made the biggest difference and
continues to make the biggest difference
to my health and I thought I was healthy
before I met you and you have taught me
so much more than what I even thought
you know I even thought was even out
there and obviously every day we're
learning more and more and sure and
that's obviously what life is about but
it's these simple things like the celery
juice like having the banana and
actually potatoes yeah I love
everybody's afraid about that I love the
fact that you're really all about
potatoes and incorporating like potatoes
steamed potatoes into your diet and not
being afraid of the cards yeah
because they've also been like since I
met you a staple in my diet that's
incredible and the potatoes have been
really helping me as well that's amazing
it's very soothing yeah you know and my
cleanser heal book that's gonna be
coming out you guys
that book I mean potatoes play a big
role in that it's really important
because there's you can mono eat with
potatoes they're so good for you for
healing problems with the digestive
tract and the intestinal tract and
they're so soothing but meanwhile it's
funny they're like hated out there
they're hate and what I always find out
there is they're usually hated by people
in the industry that don't know what
causes chronic illness so it's like wait
a minute if you don't know what causes
all the different conditions out there
that women are suffering with the
fibromyalgia and the chronic fatigue
syndrome and and like rheumatoid
arthritis and the Lyme disease and all
these other things that are now becoming
mysterious like even Lyme disease is now
a mystery to the industry because it's
autoimmune now they say so with all of
that it's like and then we're gonna hate
on a potato I've seen people get their
lives back from those potatoes I mean
potatoes and yeah like really really
helpful especially for digestive issues
oh yeah the steamed potatoes and what
are some of your recipes that are so
yummy you've got a whole bunch of them
and they they have the potatoes in them
yeah I mean there's that I think we have
a whole bunch of them exactly there's
all kinds of ways you can make them and
steamed potatoes are liked I know
everybody likes to bake
potatoes yeah and it makes it fun yeah
right but Dean potatoes I'd they're
quite addictive I feel yeah really
nourishing they're filling yeah and
right before I came here I was at an
event and then I packed because I always
pack my food in the car so I packed a
salad I had steamed potatoes and then I
just wrapped it in a little seaweed roll
yeah and I was able to eat it on my way
here to see you and it was easy it was
easy it was easy
yeah very easy and you don't have to
worry about it going bad so it's easy to
you know travel with because everyone
these days is on the go whether or not
they're going to work or running getting
on an aeroplane no not you didn't take
them with you you could steam a bunch of
them the night before you can have them
in the fridge take them with you what I
like about this the potato is it's got
l-lysine in it and l-lysine
is actually what knocks down all of
those viral issues that everybody's
struggling with with all their different
conditions
you know eczema psoriasis and like the
fibro the CFS and the lupus and and
that's why it's so important to have
those potatoes they're actually a
medicine which is really cool nobody
really knows that they just think oh
it's bad and what they're really
thinking or what they're really
associating the potato with is all the
sour cream the butter cheese you don't
want to be any more so that's really
cool because that's what makes it work
well you know what I asked so fine about
the potatoes is so funny that we expect
us to be talking about potatoes is is
really cool yeah you don't know what
you're gonna know what's gonna know it's
gonna bother and the potato is great for
like food poisoning when people get food
poisoning and so many so many people out
there I hear it all the time you see it
out there well I said this restaurant I
got food poisoning or I'm really sick
and I don't know what it is and it was
food poisoning and I noticed I'm it
won't notice well spirit of compassion
has told me this going back decades now
is it's one of the most quickest ways of
healing and recovery from food poisoning
is using it yeah just like steamed
potatoes yeah you can also blend them
right make like a potato soup
after you've been through the heck of
the total like up sets of the food
poisoning for a good few days and you're
just coming out of there and your
stomach feels all sick and you feel like
you're now you're just you're you're
looking for help and what do I have do I
have a pair of cycle I have this at that
you're just dealing with leftover
foodborne illness and then you bring in
those potatoes as your recovery food a
little bit at a time and it can bring
people back I've seen so many women
struggling with food poisoning issues
where they can't eat foods and and
actually get comfort eating really
anything they're struggling for months
after food poisoning I've seen some
people where it's like six months
nothing is right they have gastritis
they have bloating they have all these
things after it they go and I've always
seen potatoes be that answer to help
bring people back so it's so cool and
same with the coconut water right yeah
coconut water with bananas yeah you
taught me yeah that's the best yeah just
make a shake blend it now the
carbohydrate here I am breastfeeding
mothers gonna eat again well that's how
you build breast milk yes stolen it's
like carbs build the breast milk yeah if
you take a snack you know I've seen this
over the years with so many people that
have come to me looking for help
had doctors talked to me about this I've
had and where there's difficulty
building breast milk with women hmm you
know after birth and what happens is the
trainer's help and yeah that's exactly
and and any kind of any kind of food
with glucose because breast milk breast
milk is basically glucose so that's what
it is
it's a carb it's a carb drink it's sugar
water and there's very low fat very low
fat and breast milk
exactly and really low in protein that's
the breast milk is it's low protein it's
low fat and and it's filled with sugar
water yeah so breast milk is so if you
and there's so many women that were if
they go like where they're just all high
protein no car but while trying to build
breast milk they lose the breast milk so
to bring the bring breast milk back it
saves me like know you got
bananas in you got to bring potatoes in
but not as a great yeah so it's really
important that's really cool yeah like I
don't like on a day that you're eating
healthy does you honestly every time I
talk to you it's like you're always like
no no I'm still I'm still on it I'm
still doing it I'm still you know this
is what I'm having I'm having you know
the salads that you have in our books
all those recipes where you can make
even the the mock cheese sauce yeah yeah
that's really good that tastes so good
even though there's no cheese or dairy
in it and I just really feel like you
can make yummy foods that are nutritious
and delicious and that's what I'm all
about and especially with feeding the
kids there are so many wonderful like
vegetables and salads and things that
you can incorporate into their their
diet and even my little one hot who's 21
months he has his celery juice and asked
every day for it every morning an empty
stomach is it these little sippy cup B
celery juice he has coconut he's always
like oh and you know when like when
babies want celery juice and toddlers
want celery juice and I mean it it's
really remarkable because you know it's
like they can they're there yeah what's
like the intuition of a baby you know at
that and blueberries the frozen
blueberries yeah every morning heart has
his blueberries and he gets it all over
his fingers and I just let him make a
mess because I they're so good for him
and everything his fingers he's mouth
everything gets blue and I'm like okay
time for mommy to wipe your hands yeah
the wild blue yeah yeah it's the it's
that literally the richest blue there is
and any fruit on the planet
yeah it's the wild poop in this movie he
actually likes this movie too
that's incredible yeah somebody's good
cuz it's got the blueberries in there
coconut have you got a little bit of
dolls you
like spirulina barley grass banana yep
banana
exactly it's so perfect yeah and the
reason why you know like I get always
get asked this question like why why is
this heavy-metal detox smoothie
constructed like this and for one is in
order to get a nutrient into our cells
you have it has to be glucose that
drives it into the cell so nutrients
like if we take supplements all day long
and we you know because there's some
great supplements out there and there's
different things or some foods that you
think are nutritious because you're
totally maybe supplemental you take my
b12 this much might be 12 under my in my
lemon balm my tongue my goodness I have
it in my bag I'll have to do that
yeah well that's what's cool if you're
doing it every day and you like miss a
day okay it's fine yeah I haven't been a
today I'm doing it every day but I miss
it yeah oh they'll do it as soon as we
finish it what's your dosage anyway um
the b12 I'm doing to drop offals ok cool
you're sticking with what I wanted okay
good
is it for dropper fools once a day i hat
orders do I have um for twice a day I'm
trying to remember now I'm boosting once
a day maybe I could do should I do you
can do two Fabri falls twice a day you
can do yeah and the celery force and the
celery force which keeps like our brains
sharp I mean yeah I don't even need to
sleep like I don't know I was just
finishing a book deadline I don't even
need to sleep with that I'm sleeping
like four maybe five hours a night and
to be honest I've never felt better
that's because I'm eating healthy and
I'm taking care of myself and you know
I've always said it's about a balance
and I like to have like 80% healthy and
20% indulgent but you've been mentoring
me to be more strict with myself which
has definitely been paying off in the
way that I feel my energy levels and and
health but your you know what though you
like it you get committed you get
dedicated to it other people I work with
it's just like wait a minute what are
you
stop stop all the burglary well I like
you no wait you had shrimp that wasn't
on the program shrimp isn't on the
program yeah then and so and you're
always like you know you're always like
on it so that when I do a check-in la
what are you doing what's going on
you're like no um don't worry I'm good
yeah because I really noticed the
difference and look as I said life is a
balance it's about being educated making
those choices having healthy choices the
celery juice is really just like it
takes things to a nice level yeah it
just takes things to that whole other
level of health and wellness and I'm
just so grateful for that so thank you
well look it's spirit of compassion I
wouldn't I wouldn't know about it I
would never know just these sweet celery
juice because everybody like mocked that
what they called a vegetable they
thought that things just crudité you
know that it's just chopped you know you
chop that anything yeah you can chop it
up into a salad I guess put a little in
a salad you know you can ya put in a dip
basically so so you know and but it's
like for me it started in 1975 when I
was this little kid and and spirit of
compassion was like this is gonna be an
answer right here for a family member
that had a struggling back problem and
it fixed it and then Wow
and then spirit compassion was like you
know there's just like I remember spirit
compassion trying to convince me because
I was just like you sure I should keep
on recommending celery juice and I was
eight and nine years old and 10 years
old Spears like you know you have to
recommend this because this is going to
be that that that basically that
safeguard for people's health like no
other that's ever happened on this plan
it's going to be that that tool that
takes everybody to next level protects
them helps them recover if they're doing
something good for themselves this will
help take them to that next level even
more so and even if they're not doing
anything good for themselves it's gonna
help them yeah if you do it every day
it's an everyday thing I think don't you
think it's important this in every
it's like brushing your teeth it's true
exact on expect to have clean teeth if
you don't brush them it's like yeah
consistency I really feel is important
like and I feel like a lot of people
might go on it for a little bit then
they go off it but it's really important
to maintain the celery juice one little
thing you can do yeah right it's one you
know it should be like part of your life
you should just like when you're taking
showers exactly this should be in there
just like anything like anything you do
you put gas in your car you're always
gonna put gas through always decelerate
just whatever it is something that you
know you always do in your life and
whatever that is but celery juice should
always be a part of it like yeah
brushing your teeth like all of that
it's so important and I forgot to remind
everybody if you like this video thumbs
do give us a thumbs up but the bottom
line is what celery juice I find all the
time you know miranda is that people
will be like well I tried it for seven
days or I did it for 30 days and then I
stopped doing it and I noticed I was
actually feeling better from it so the
stop effect when people actually do it
just long enough and then they stop it
and then they're just like whoa
something changed I gotta go back on it
but actually it actually reminds you to
go back on it it has an ability to
remind people to go back on it how much
do you drink celery juice a day do you
know me yeah 64 ounces is what I try to
do okay wait no 30 like today it's been
this plus it was 32 this morning okay
so it's probably not I don't know I
don't think that's 64 today but there's
a lot of days where I'm like I'm like 16
ounces like I don't have it in the
fridge I take one bunch out that's all I
have and I run it through and I got like
I got 16 ounces which is the which I
like to use that is the bottom line for
people but yeah the bottom line is empty
stomach first thing in the morning empty
stomach first thing in the morning and
if you want to have additional salary
throughout the day you can just do the
empty stomach
'banahna oh no it doesn't have that's
still really helpful just don't put
anything in it do you have what do you
find it like that all that your friends
can I add lemon I'm like no I am celery
yeah what about a carrot I might know
everybody wants to put something in it
or mix it with something oh my god my
celery cheese put add parsley in there
and it happened and that's ok but it's
not gonna give it would it it's not
gonna let it do what it needs to do to
help us recover and help us get to where
we need to go yeah but you're really
eating amazing you oh you know you're
really eating really cleanup you're
doing 32 ounces that's mind-blowing a
lot of you guys are probably now doing
32 ounces some of you guys are doing 16
but 16 is always that like hey you know
that's what you need to have it run
through the body get up to the liver go
up into go up into your brain clean
everything out and send up heavy metal
so the heavy metal detox movie can
actually pull out the metals even easier
and can you tell me more about the lemon
water just like because being doing that
lately as well just cut your lemon water
yeah 32 ounces one lemon
perfect why you wake up in the morning
like all night long your liver is now
working it's working for you so whatever
you did if you if you're on a high-fat
diet if you're doing lots of fats during
the day and people are like I'm not on a
high-fat diet well if you're on nut
butters nut butters lots of avocados are
good for you it's just that we eat a lot
more of them than we should and that's
what happens and so your nut butters the
avocado you're on all the coconut oil
then you're then maybe you're doing some
dairy maybe you're doing some goat's
milk whatever it could be and or chicken
and so you're doing too many fats
throughout a day and then hey look if
you're not struggling with anything and
you're doing all the fats then your
liver will just kind of hang in there
for a while until it gets sluggish down
the road then you'll get your first
symptoms and then have to lower the fats
but what happens is that the lemon water
is there to flush out those poisons and
toxins that get built up by the liver
ready to deliver into the system ready
to get out so every single night it's
like there's a there's a workshop going
on and your liver a bunch of elves are
in there and they're just working on
getting all the
without packaging up getting them ready
and then that 32 ounces of lemon water
and it's really important that it's 32
ounces somewhere around there unless you
can't do that and I totally get it so do
less I do it I make sure I bought a 32
ounce bottle so it's always like 32
ounce bottle this specifically for my
water with lemon yeah I bought another
32 ounce like empty bottle so why you
reuse them every day
that's perfectly for my celery and then
I have another 32 ounce bottle that is
for my smoothie and I labeled them so
that I know it every day thing that goes
in that goes that's incredible yeah that
that's like everybody should be doing if
you can oh yeah yeah I don't even do
that yeah I just it's a mess in my
kitchen it's just yeah have my like you
know celery juice bottle and it's in the
32 ounce so I know I'm exactly a my 32
ounces water bottle and my the heavy
metal detox smoothie which isn't it
isn't fully eight thirty trances it's
like whatever the recipe is yeah I just
sometimes you know it just fits well in
there it does yeah I can shake it and
add a little more coconut water if it
gets too thick that's perfect which
likes of one of your favorite medical
meeting books I have like a bunch
because you and I haven't we have a
photo with the holding the thyroid using
foods I feel like the liver rescue it's
good also your fifties that the first
one yeah that's the first one yeah
that's the one that tells a little bit
about my story if you don't know about
it and my dog and my dog was drowning
and in the ocean and I went out there
and it was a powerful story because so
many people are always like that that
story of what happened is just it's just
unbelievable so I'm really blessed that
actually survived that event back when I
was younger but anyway to talk about all
kinds of cool things and the liver a
grocery as well because I feel like
people don't understand also was it
apples
when your honor I was pregnant with
because I spoke to you and I was
pregnant the last two pregnancies yeah
but the last one it was just I was
craving apples like all the time apples
apples that's incredible you know
well the apples have like electrolytes
it's not like the celery juice
electrolytes but it's really powerful
electrolytes and people underestimate
the apples it's actually plus plus the
thing is they cleanse you the apples are
cleansing that's why it's part of liver
rescue it's part of it just it helps
clean everything out of your body and
it's important when you're pregnant to
have apples is important when you're
breastfeed to have apples to because you
know all of those foods are important
it's like I'm always asked like is the
heavy metal detox movie safe for
pregnancy for breastfeeding yes you know
like if I'm if I'm actually like making
a baby or if I'm breastfeeding or not
the answer is it actually makes the
breast milk cleaner it it's what's
cleaning the breast milk so that's the
whole thing and you're getting the
protein from this really narrow
oh yeah there's tons of protein in
spirulina it's really a high protein
food but it's also a you know like a
cleansing food not the proteins in it as
the cleansing part but it's a cleansing
food word it pulls out not only metals
but other toxins so that breast milk
gets cleaned so you know why your baby I
have yeah you while your baby to have
the cleanest breast milk so that's why
it's so important to use that while
breastfeeding and being one when you're
pregnant it's amazing to have it then
it's just really a perfect food and then
the glucose in it actually to help with
the breast milk so it's a win-win it's
what about the polygraph oh yeah that's
that's another that's another world so
high nutrients barley grass cheese
powder is so high in phytochemical
compounds so we're talking about
antioxidants that are not even
registered yet out there science
research doesn't even know what's in
barley grass use powder as far as the
different antioxidants that aren't
discovered and same with the spirulina
there's antioxidants undiscovered same
with the wild blueberries and these are
the very thing that helps us to not age
fast these are the things that actually
help us for babies to develop and
it's incredible yeah thank you it's just
Freddie
spreading all of this information well I
said well in helping people well what
we're we're in it together you're out
there helping people you got the corner
organics the skin line so we're doing
amazing work and well that's what it's
all about what it's all about health as
well
you guys remember it thumbs up and
subscribe and and Miranda Kerr me we're
gonna sign off and we love you much