medical medium here we're talking about
all kinds of different stuff with health
because it would be great you're
somebody that's got chronic illness
you've been sick for a while some
symptoms that you move forward this year
you do some healing you can do it
there's ways to do it one of the
problems out there is that people don't
know that there are options to heal that
there are ways to heal there a lot of
noise out there a lot of confusion and
people they don't always take the right
path because they don't know something
else is better and something else is
there for them so they can move forward
and heal because that's what it's all
about it's about getting better there's
a lot of talk out there there's a lot of
stupid talk out there there's a lot of
cheap talk out there there's a lot of
all kinds of garbage talk out there
about try this do that fear chaos shock
awe try this take this magic bullet This
Magic Bullet and then people end up
doing what they've done in the last 10
20 30 years they end up learning like
everybody else does in the past is they
end up sick and sicker over time but
they tried this magic bullet they tried
this thing they tried that and they
stayed sick and it's all fun and games
until you're somebody with the chronic
illness and you're suffering and
struggling I'm Anthony William the
medical medium guess what Cafe Gratitude
medical medium collaboration there is a
cleanse it's the wellness reset cleanse
at Cafe Gratitude in January January
20th you can order a cleanse they will
have it ready for you it is unbelievable
they'll deliver it to you and so forth
Cafe Gratitude you guys medical medium
collaboration so I just wanted to tell
you how excited I am about this how
incredible this actually is so Cafe
Gratitude amazing amazing healthy eating
restaurant they're in La I don't know if
you know about those guys right but we
did some events there do you remember
that was really fun they have medical
medium dishes the menu you should try
them out they got an incredible Nory
roll dish they got a potato bowl that's
amazing you might have tried it before
anyway they're doing a cleanse for
people who want to heal get better get
stronger it's the wellness reset Cafe
Gratitude January 20th it starts let's
talk about what's in there a little bit
okay wait till I tell you about the
pizza party coming up January 15th 16th
I'm going to be there meat and greet
which is going to be incredible and it's
going to be so fun right we'll talk
about that too um let me get a knife
really
quick cut a lemon you don't
mind cuz I didn't put any lemon in my
tea and I kind of want a little bit of
that in there you guys there we go nice
so the wellness reset so check this out
when you get this cleanse when you order
this cleanse from cath gratitude okay
let's talk about what's going to be in
here check this out and the price is
insanely low which I don't even
understand because of what you're
getting this cleanse is incredible so
you get the celery juice to start out in
the morning you get the heavy metal
detox smoothie it's another thing after
that you get the Cravings shifter shot
think about that right there it's part
of the cleanse the Cravings shifter shot
okay then you get the spiced squash soup
that's after that then you get the brain
Soother juice think about how insane
that is think about that that they're
offering this then you get the healing
broth soup the healing broth soup I mean
my God they're doing this the dreams
shifter shot is in the cleanse the
Estonian stew and the massaged kale
salad that's in the medical medium
cleanse Cafe Gratitude starting January
20th they're going to offer this I just
want to tell you guys how
insanely Incredible Cool and healthy and
amazing and fresh all this is this is
really exciting so you this is how it
works right you go you're like I want to
have that cleanse they get it ready for
you they make it for you they have it
for you every day fresh you pick it up
or they deliver it to you okay if you're
in the area they deliver it to you and
then you have it all done you got your
shifter shots you got your hmds you got
your celery juice you got your healing
broth you got it all brain Soother juice
you have it all and you can work on
healing and that's what they're offering
there I am blown away let's talk about
the pizza party Cafe Gratitude medical
medium collaborated on healthy pizzas
medical medium
pizzas at Cafe
Gratitude they're going to be offering
those medical medium pizzas January
23d and they're going to be on the
menu pizzas freaking pizzas man pizzas
I'm GNA say it over over pizzas pizzas
pizzas pizzas seriously this is
mindblowing so I hope you guys are
pumped about that I got a friend lives
in Europe they're
flying in February to have the pizzas
they they they actually like trying out
pizzas different places around the world
they're taking a trip just to Cafe
Gratitude in early February pizz on the
menu for these pizzas they're going to
stay a couple days and eat them both
days and I'm going to tell you right now
these pizzas are incredible and healthy
though like really healthy but taste
unbelievable do you know what I'm saying
like you can get a pizza but it's going
to have a lot of stuff on there it
probably isn't that great it's going to
have some strange oil in there whatever
it is you know how it works or you're
going to get a pizza and it's going to
have all kinds of crazy stuff on it this
is different these are incredible tasty
delicious pizzas I'm going to be in La
January 15th 16th um coming right up
coming right up around the corner like
coming right up like what a week what is
it a week a week and a half I'm going to
be there I hope you got a ticket because
those are Pizza nights right there so
the Cafe Gratitude medical me
collaboration popup dinners we're
releasing the pizzas there for that
night but it won't be
there until the 23rd every day if you
want to buy pizza it's the pizza party
the events are sold out it's the 15th
and the 16th what you got to do is you
got to catch the next one if I do
another one but you can join the weit
list so check that out look for the weit
list right the Cafe Gratitude medical
medium popup dinners weight list the L
is in the bio and in the description of
this video that's where you can check
out the link and you can get on that
weit list because you never know you
someone might hey someone might get busy
something might happen they can't make
it and all of a sudden a spot opens up
and boom you got it and you're going to
be eating pizzas with medical Medium
you're going to be eating pizzas with me
and it's going to be fun so this is
going to be a killer event really
incredible these pop-up dinners I can't
say enough about it but here's the good
news if you can't make that popup dinner
even though they've been sold out and
you can't get in somehow it's okay
because the pizzas are going to be on
the menu and I'm going to be stopping by
Cafe Gratitude a lot because I do want
to eat these pizzas while they're on the
menu so I'm excited yeah pizza party
that's right it's going to be really
really worth it and fun so I want to let
everybody know about that right there
and when you think about it though
medical medium pizzas on the menu at
Cafe Gratitude I promise you
this they are
so so mm approved they are so mm
approved I'm serious about that these
pizzas are Beyond mm approved check out
the other dishes on the menu too they're
still there they sell people go in buy
them all the time but get them while
they're there while they're in Cafe
Gratitude the nor the potato bowl make
sure you do that so not only is this is
what's interesting too not only the
pizzas but a
cookie a medical medium cookie is going
to be on the menu
too what yeah it's going to be really
good all
right CT Toba says I'm so excited ADW
I'll be there with my daughter for the
pizza party whoa you got tickets you got
in you got into that popup yeah we're
going to have a we're going to have a
blast we're going to have a light
blast so good that tea is delicious
right now so anyway but the cleanse I
want to just give you one last reminder
January 20th Cafe Gratitude okay the
wellness reset the cleanse is going to
be there they're going to make it fresh
for people how incredible is that
pre-orders start January 17th for the
clay pre-order start January
17th for the
cleanse
okay so how do you heal how do you
heal sick you got a symptom you're not
well you go to the
doctor right everybody goes to the
doctor how do you heal you go to the
doctor they offer you this they offer
you that depending on what they are who
they are what they're into with
conventional alternative and then you
work under healing
right but what if you got a whole bunch
of mystery symptoms and you go to the
specialist now and another specialist
and then you're getting your blood drawn
and then you're getting more blood drawn
and then you're trying this and then
you're on two medications and it's hit
or miss and then you're getting some
side effects and then you're to the
alternative doctors and you're trying
this gut cleanse and you're trying to
change your microbiome and now you're
trying to do something else and then
you're back to this doctor and that
doctor have you been on that Journey
Through The
Years and exactly what did I just say I
said through the years how many people
are sick with symptoms conditions and
it's been for years years exactly it's a
long time when you're sick and you're
not well and it's a really hard time for
a lot of people and you guys know that
but there is a way to heal there is a
way to move forward because your body it
does want to heal and here we are in
this new
year we need to get that to happen
ignite that get that access
accessibility of your body getting what
it needs to your body cells working on
your healing process working on moving
forward jumping
forward fast there's a way to do it now
what you'll see out there is there a lot
of different Magic Bullets left and
right popping up I don't know if you
guys see it every day now but I do out
there and there's a Magic Bullet every
10 seconds out
there did you know that olive oil can do
a whole bunch of things for
you did you know about salt pills and
what it can do for my
man did you know did you know your gut
microbiome needs a whole bunch of
bacteria that's why you need this one
now did you know did you know you need
to drink the right water because that's
been your problem all along you're not
getting the right water did you know
that if you've been you know doing
processed foods you're getting these
food chemicals so you better try this
charcoal cleanse did you know this and
this did you know you need fish oil for
your brain because that's what's
important did you know you need eggs cuz
that will fix it all it's all you needed
all this time was just some protein from
eggs such a healthy food you didn't know
that you didn't know that that green tea
and coffee is actually good for you and
maybe it'll stop you from getting
prostate
cancer you didn't know that you know you
should be eating chocolate once a day to
crank up your oxytocin did you know you
need to do this and that to crank up
your dopamine hey you might need these
electrolytes for this and that and
that's what you hear all day long out
there that's what it is you need this
Pearl powder you need this stuff you
need that stuff you need this closet you
need this magic bullet Magic Bullet
Magic Bullet Magic Bullet Magic Bullet
everybody getting sicker sicker sicker
sicker five years from now mark my words
boom we're talking everybody's going to
be getting sick and we're talking
another
200,000 Carpet Baggers are going to be
out there try this try that try this
investors here investors there try this
brand try that thing try this guy you
could try this this you could try this
and it's going to go like this on and on
and on and if you're not that sick you
might improve if you get rid of the
garbage clean up your diet a little bit
take a little bit of this and that maybe
take some
B12 which nobody took medical medium got
that word out there you need B12 and
then you might get a little better but
there's going to be a massive massive
wave wave of sick people and this year
it's going to be a tough one so you got
to have the right information you got to
know how to move forward there is a way
to heal there's going to be a lot of flu
bugs later on this year there's going to
be a lot of weird bugs later on this
year everybody's screaming about what's
floating in the sky right
now everybody's freaking out about one
thing or another and I'm not saying
what's floating in the sky is a great
thing I'm not saying that at
all I'm just saying everybody's getting
sicker it's what's really happening
you'll see you'll see and you'll see why
do you think health is taking over why
do you think every single model and
celebrity and every single Sports person
is trying to push something in the
health world because they're struggling
with symptoms too because everybody's
getting symptoms and everybody's getting
sicker and sicker but you don't have to
get sicker and sicker you don't have to
you can can heal and avoid all that and
and really
can swim through that
current that everybody's up against
right now of all the shock and awe and
Magic Bullets being thrown at them left
and right the crazy thing is is years
ago when there was some Magic Bullets
around then and nobody got better when
shil hit the fan nobody got better
everybody with chronic illness who had
thyroid diseases Hashimoto everybody
with fibro lime disease neurological
lime they took XY never got them better
fic minerals that was the next thing
back 20 years ago never got anybody
better it didn't and it was the next
thing and the next thing and next thing
and that's how it went but now we're in
a Land of there are hundreds of things
and hundreds of Magic Bullets and you
could swim in that stuff and sit in that
stuff for a really long time if you're
struggling
and you're sick with some neurological
problems so what are you doing for your
health like what are you doing because
what
I know is you have to have these
landmarks these foundational Staples you
have to have these solid
foundations
critical critical they have these solid
foundations and you got to stay with
these solid foundations and you got to
hold with them
because you need something there that
works so if you want to try all the
out there or try the different
things and whatever flashy new thing
gets thrown at someone every single
person is being thrown a flashy new
thing sure you want to do that that's
great but you better have some
foundational tools you better have
something
there a
landmark there that's holding you strong
while you're trying trying to heal and
being thrown off left and right not
enough protein not enough
protein deficiencies
deficiencies you should be drinking out
of copper pots and copper you us using
copper utensils and wearing copper
jewelry and drinking copper thermoses
that's your answer it's not your answer
that's actually dangerous but that's
what I mean you should be freezing your
ass off you should be taking ice baths
you should be you should be putting
yourself into ice shock
no bad bad bad bad bad point
is point is you better have some
foundational tools so no matter what
you're doing you got something that's
helping you while you're getting pushed
into other things or pear pressured into
other things or tricked into other
things you need to have the core
foundational strength in your
healing so that you can hold strong and
then move forward especially with the
bugs to
come I mean four years
ago right it four years ago
now or is it more than four years ago
now right when the bug hit the town
there's going to be
more they're coming they're on the
way and you got to have that core
Foundation it's got to be
there so I came on here to say look this
is the start of the Year just wanted to
say hi to everybody also let you know
about the Killer Pizza party because
that alone is really
exciting but I want to talk about some
tools and I want to talk about the
foundational tools and I've said that
years ago too you needed the
foundational
tools very important for healing okay
for one simple some foods to avoid
simple I know you don't want to hear
this I know I get slammed every time
every
time and I'm ready to take a hit again
I'm
ready I'm primed I'm ready this
year and I'm not messing
around but I want to tell you one of the
foods to avoid is the eggs I know when
people hear it they start freaking out
and then boom everybody body's on board
you know eggs are good for you you need
the protein they're filled with vitamins
and minerals they're filled with choline
they got everything you ever need it
it's eggs it's eggs it's eggs but I
promise you this whether anybody likes
it or not no matter how much crap I
get if you got chronic illness if you're
somebody that has a
symptom I promise you this those eggs
aren't going to help they're going to be
a monkey on your back and they're going
to hold you you down on your healing
process even if you keep them in there
and you're bettering you're getting a
little better with your illness because
you're doing a bunch of stuff and you
keep them in
there it's going to
eventually you're going to be back to
full circle or 180° however you want to
say
it because eggs will feed what's coming
and what's in people people still don't
realize it all the different pathogens
that were actually raised in labs and
manufactured
by classified medical research
science many many years ago they used
eggs to do it all the suffering people
have right now is from the herpes
viruses it's from the herpes simplex one
herpes simplex 2 it's what creates
cancer it's all the
viruses it's the epscene bars that end
up creating cancer it's all the
different bugs that end up creating
cancer and what happens is is that all
these bugs feed on something that people
don't realize it was what they were
raised on and it was eggs so that's just
one foundational tool right there you
throw everything else away and you just
say you know what I'm holding off on the
eggs you're doing yourself a
foundational
favor that alone right
there sure you want to go grab the Magic
Bullets left and right and everything
else but that's the big one right there
okay that's the big one
viruses feed on toxins equals cancer
viruses Staying Alive because they feed
on eggs so they can feed on toxins and
create cancer there you
go important to understand how it
works and right now we're heading into a
place where a lot of people are getting
sicker and sicker it's going to happen
faster and faster and you're going to
read more things about it and see more
things about it and there's going to be
a thousand more Magic Bullet companies
and Magic things and Magic Bullet this
and this to try and they're just going
to come out and be like Oh try this oh
no try that oh no you need to be doing
keto oh you need to be carnivore now oh
you need to do this you need to eat lots
of eggs oh you need your fish again or
your fish oil and it's going to go back
to this again and then the same old crap
happens right where you got the wars
between the plant-base and the carnivore
or keto and animal right you see this
now and I talked about it before did you
see how bad it's getting plant-based
movement
I'm on look I'm I totally support
plant-based I told this told you before
I also supported somebody's doing an
animal protein thing because there's
tools you can do medical meme tools fit
in both both places so you can do your
healing right but man the vegans whether
vegans know it or not they're asleep
right now on the plant-based people
they're asleep right now they're just
getting destroyed out there the
movements being destroyed it's the
saddest thing I've ever
seen okay and eggs are part of how
they're destroying it that's what's
crazy cuz no one wants to give up their
eggs on any level to come for food their
eggs they don't want to give up their
eggs no way that's one foundational tool
stay away from those if you're
chronically sick cuz I promise you they
are going to get in your way I don't
even have an egg prop with me right now
but whatever all right another
foundational tool okay that I've talked
about forever stay away from canola oil
and now some people out there like
canola oil is bad for you
I'm a health leader and I'm telling you
canola oil is bad for you I'm a health
influencer and I'm going to be the first
to say canol oil is bad for you really
been saying it for three and a half
decades or more canola oil is bad stay
away from it when you can where you can
foundational toour right there don't use
it you hear about seed oils right people
freaking out about seed
oils
okay have I been a big fan of seed oils
no that's the whole thing of course not
and I've been I've done stuff in the
books about canola oil and so forth all
right and that's one thing you can stay
away from is canola oil that's a big
deal right there all on its own the
other one
corn I know it feels fuzzy and warm I
know corn you know feels so good it does
feels great I know a lot of people feel
that way about it's comfort food they
love it's just sit there with you know a
whole bunch of popcorn organic popcorn
of course or of course it's organic
popcorn staying away from corn right
there foundational tool right there you
guys I can hand you the golden ticket
you could smack it right out of my
hand
whatever you know I can do that I can
hand you the golden ticket here here's
the golden ticket you can smack it right
out of my
hand remember that used to say that
years ago I can hand you the golden
ticket you know
right I can tell
you stay away from the eggs here's the
golden ticket
boom so these are just a few
foundational tools here's another one
right here Dairy I don't care about
kefir
yogurt gone if you're sick with chronic
illness cheese
gone that's
right dairy products
well yeah I do goats
milk still if you're sick it's not going
to work because there's stuff in goats
milk dairy cheese kefir yogurt all the
dairy raw dairy sure raw dairy there's
raw dairy people that're like raw dairy
raw dairy he's so stupid that medical
medium he's just talking about Dairy he
doesn't know he's talking about
pasteurized Dairy what a dummy he is he
doesn't know about raw dairy really I
don't duh
the irony I knew about raw dairy before
you've discovered raw dairy in the last
5 years and now you're eating it and
feeding it to your family I knew about
raw der a long time ago try decades ago
when maybe you weren't even born yet or
you were three years old I knew about
raw da it's still going to feed the
pathogens because once again no one's
really kind of like really locking into
the pathogen thing right now talking
about parasites a little they're talking
about you know they're talking about
this and hormones again back to the
hormone thing where it's all hormones
that's your problem it's all
hormones that's how I know it's not just
Spirit of compassion but that's how I
know how sick the world is getting in
the next 5 years because they're not
even they're not even on the pathogen
thing really yet they're talking about
hormones again dude that was talked
about 30 years ago everybody was sick
boots McGee it's amazing listening to
your podcast yesterday from 2020 and you
predicted so much we're experiencing now
thank you thank you for for thank you
for saying that okay because right now
the media stick psychics that nobody's
even known about like saying oh the
psychic saying that this is coming it's
like uh yeah um pretty much a world war
is eminent anyway
eventually so thank you it's nice to see
that you know you heard from the past
that stuff and you're talking about it
now um what kind of tea are you drinking
right there lemon bomb lemon bomb lemon
bomb
with a little bit of lemon in there and
some
honey okay
so so Dairy it's another one there too
these are just a couple things chocolate
caffeine oh my God the beatdowns I got
for ripping apart caffeine people you
see right now in the health movement
right that are getting some air time
places people you see right now they got
a lot of bread they got a lot of bread
they've hired agencies and promotion
people they got they got a lot of
they're getting a lot of PR they're
getting all the stuff and they're out
there people in the health movement you
see out there
okay they they were all for caffeine
just a year ago two years ago drinking
it themselves every morning wake up in
the morning hey honey yep where's the
coffee and now they're starting to utter
it a little bit like caffeine's
bad and they're drinking alcohol too I
notice you'll see see some alcohol's bad
for you alcohol's bad for your brain
really because I put it in the books
that alcohol's bad for the brain but
anyway alcohol is bad for the brain now
so you see some people meanwhile they
were just drinking wine a couple of
years ago they had they had their
Revelation their Epiphany that like now
don't don't drink alcohol anymore and
shock and awe that person said don't
drink alcohol
whoa those are Basics those are easy
ones right there you know you shouldn't
be doing caffeine you know if you're
sick with chronic illness you shouldn't
be doing caffeine you shouldn't even be
doing chocolate you shouldn't be do
shouldn't be doing
um uh coffee green tea
matcha but people do it anyway should be
careful with chocolate if you're sick
with chronic illness but it's really
hard to break away from that and I
completely understand it see I'm not
judging anybody it's not about judging
anyone cuz I get it life is hard it's
easy to go to chocolate and caffeine and
coffee and cheese and eggs life is hard
totally get it foundational pieces
though you can take
them smack them out of my hands fine
either
way that's what you can
do I just found a golden ticket here you
can take the golden ticket smack it out
in my hand medical medium morning cleans
talk about that a little bit treat your
liver good treat your liver good
let's talk about the morning cleanse
just for a couple of seconds here
morning cleanse lemon water boom move on
to some celery juice boom you can have
some fruit plain old fruit which is now
allowed it's now allowed in the keto
diet and morning cleanse is in the book
cleanse to heal you can have some fruit
now which is allowed in the KE keto
diet remember when you know you weren't
even allowed a green
apple anyway the point is keeping off of
fats in the morning no bacon no eggs no
butter no milk no avocado no cheese no
oils no olive
oil keeping the over fats away and do a
morning cleanse which leads me to
this you can be somebody that rips apart
being off of the overt fats but just so
you know you're never going to really
truly cleanse as deep as you need to if
you're doing overt
fats so at least catch a morning cleanse
so you can do a little bit of cleansing
because that's what it does it gives you
a daily cleanse when you do the morning
cleansing you do your your lemon water
you do your celery juice you do your
hmbs how about that and then you do if
you want to do some fruit sure if you're
starving and you're really hungry do
some potato steamed potato no oil no
cheese no nothing on it and then
afternoon you can bring in your avocado
whatever you want your nuts your seeds
if that's somebody that you know if
you're somebody that eats that your fish
or whatever it is if you're somebody
like that or your animal protein person
do it afternoon don't do it in the
morning that's the morning cleanse it's
just a quick rundown of the morning
cleanse somebody that's really
struggling testinal tract problems all
kinds of issues do the mono cleanse
which you'll see in the books as well
the monoc cleanse monoc cleanse is
reversed Crohn's colitis IBS so many
intestinal tract disord gastro pris
reversed it and move people
forward try the antibug cleanse so you
can kill off all the bugs inside of you
okay and then the heavy metal detox
cleanse right
here
boom reach deep into those metals and
pull them out I'm going to tell you
right now
you know what's funny
okay medical medium heavy metal detox
has been around for a long long
time I've gotten so many people better
reversed so many different conditions of
people got people out of wheelchairs
okay it is an
incredible detox the heavy metal detox
it has a it has a track record it has a
street cred it saved lives
people have literally rid their
depression their anxiety their
depersonalization it's put people on the
map back into life and then someone gets
jealous that's in the healing World
somebody
who was sued for stealing somebody's
money somebody who doesn't even have a
doctor's license anymore and then
they're running ads 24/7 runs running
ads 24/7 they're using the their family
to do it all kinds of like fake
testimonials and they start ripping
apart things like cilantro they start
ripping apart things like spirulina
maybe you've seen some of
this meanwhile what were they really
doing just a few years ago
nothing and what were they really doing
a few years ago they had anything to do
with he heavy metals
nothing the system set up right now it's
rigged for failure for people so they
won't heal and the one thing I want the
reason why I'm saying this and bringing
this in because the traps out there are
set you you can like me you can hate me
I don't care I mean I hope you like me
but what am I going to do you got your
own free will you don't like me what am
I going to do but one thing's for
certain whether you like the way I look
don't like the way I look you like you
know what I mean one thing's for certain
this
works and has gotten people out of
wheelchairs not just one person
hundreds and
hundreds something that can never be
done out there and this industry doesn't
like that that's why I'm always attacked
that's why I'm always right that's why
I'm always censored attack Shadow band
you name it everything that's ever
happened and then people trying to talk
but one thing's for certain you do
the right tools you heal I mean take the
books to your doctor ask them what's
right for
you but I know what's in here moves
people forward and moves the needle and
gets them better if they do it right
meaning they just don't do it one day or
they don't do it just do it one week and
they do it half ass one week and then
they're eating all this chocolate not
telling anybody and they're eating all
this other stuff and they're getting
blood taken out for no reason left and
right and they're doing you know and
they're getting all kinds of
stuff and all this stuff's happening
then it's going to take takes some time
you got to get on it you got to work it
you got to put this into motion and you
got to heal and you can heal for
2025 if I was a fly on the wall the fly
is going to come back by the
way if I was a fly on the
wall and I can see what people are
doing they're doing
unbelievable if I could look at their
credit card receipts their credit card
statements if I could look at their
restaurants they're eating in what
they're buying at the grocery store what
they're eating while they're drinking a
celery juice 3 years ago for a month or
something if I can see what people are
doing and I can to some
degree fin wall
can so can
unfortunately a lot of people don't tell
the truth and they won't say what
they're really doing what they're really
eating and that's another thing that
happens because that's how social works
that's how people work
but the heavy metal detox has turned
lives
around and it works it works and if
someone's pushed away from it because of
a campaign trying to lead people to
whatever they're selling or whatever
crapping hes they're selling whatever it
is and they miss out on a chance to heal
cuz now they're afraid of cilantro and
now they're afraid of something like
spirina or they're afraid of something
and they don't know what they could they
don't know how to heal you just send
them down to track and they're going to
be stuck for another five years after
they paid thousands and thousands of
dollars for programs chrisa Ritz it
helped me so much that hmds cleanse and
celery juice I had brain fog it is is
gone and I had mood changes my moods are
more stable my health has improved a
lot and that matters having the right
stuff so back
to back to some foundations okay if you
can just bring in the hmds into your
life if you can do just do the morning
cleanse if you could just do the celery
juice the hmds the lemon water every
single morning what that can do for you
these things matter they do and then you
got the brain shot Therapies in the
brainsaver books I mean I know many of
you guys live by them I know many of you
guys have tried them but they're mental
health
tools they are mental health
tools healing is
possible there's a way to do it it's in
our
hands the brain shot therapies help
physically and mentally both physically
and
mentally truly
powerful so it's go to a couple couple
other things here
so all
right why do you have to have these
foundational tools because some people
are under a lot of stress their adrenals
are pumping they're doing fight or
flight you know anybody in fight ORF
flight know anybody that's up against
that periodically fight ORF flight
right so the foundational tools are
critical you got to have your zinc you
got to have your
B12 you got to have your micro C you got
to have your vitamin C you have to have
some foundational tools and I've talked
about this over and over again you have
to have those coupled with being
cautious on some of the foods that will
feed a problem the one thing you're
going to get with the medical medium
food is you're going to get lots of
it lots of
it have you ever known medical
medium information to be portion control
where you're only allowed like three
berries you're only allowed like two
strawberries in a blueberry you're only
allowed like two 1 o of chicken 2 ounces
of chicken you're only allowed like you
know like half a potato only and that's
it
but you'll run into that everywhere out
there you'll run into that everywhere
what you're going to notice in
2025 is a whole crap ton of people
getting sicker looking for
help and you're going to see a whole new
barrage of
programs membership sites for
information pay you have to
pay all kinds of different re R treats
you're just going to see tons and tons
of that it's going to be the money
suckage
year for health on the planet the money
year go to the library get the book out
for
free learn how to
heal get the right information the real
information that has healed other people
get into the 369 cleanse because it's a
lifesaver
Lifesaver 369 simplified 369 original
Advanced 28 day cleanse got the other
book over there behind there 28 day
cleanse look into these things go to the
library get the book for free for free
learn how to
heal
okay A W can anesthesia
and mental metal implants trigger mental
health episodes as well psychosis and
similar breakdowns maybe months later
would that be more immediate it could be
some immediate and months later and
years
later and that's why we have to take
care of ourselves have those
foundational tools and do the healing we
need to do and move
forward so I know a lot of people are
freaking out and you'll see that on
social everybody's just freaking out
about like you'll see it out
there food chemicals food
chemicals food chemicals are bad I've
talked about them in all the books
processed
foods it's not why everybody is getting
dangerously sick and sick and sicker
it's not unfortunately that's not the
reason I know they're looking for stuff
like that but what you'll see the
industries do is you'll see them
still hide from the pathogens and the
metals see little bit of the metal stuff
creep up because they're learning the
medical medium information right all the
metal information I put all these years
but you'll see them skirt around the
pathogens once again and they'll try to
just look for these other you know
things and they'll try to do shock and
awe this food chemical this die number
three this die here this thing
here you're going to see a lot of that
why everybody's looking for reasons why
people are sick and at the same time
whether it's accidental it's accidental
or purposely could be accidental they're
not seeing the real reasons why people
are sick and
suffering so one problem with the flu
and the Sea that's coming again over and
over again the RSV and the neuro
virus and the
SS and all the other different ones like
the bird bugs the problem with all these
is if you don't have your foundations
intact and you're not cleaning out some
of the garbage getting some of the
metals out knocking back some of the
pathogens it becomes too much of an
overload too much of an overload
2025 going to be a year where we're
going to get a wave a bunch waves of a
lot of bugs going to be coming
through and people aren't taking care of
themselves properly and knocking down
the bugs that they have in them living
in them all the time and that's the
perfect
storm for all that stuff Uma a w where
have you been okay okay okay
okay get
ready I'm only going to squeak out an
inkling of this information right here
and inkling of this
information okay if you're
interested you know how you guys have
been asking for Spiritual information
from
me you guys I don't know you guys
remember they've been asking about like
spiritual book or spiritual information
or spiritual right I don't know if you
guys have been asking that but I think
you
have
well I got a book
that's going to happen in
and I got something else that's going to
happen in
2025 and I just hope I hope to
God that I did the right
thing
by putting in
print and in audio possibly
um
information that comes from
so that's going to answer a lot of
questions about a lot of things and I
know I sound kind of hesitant right now
and kind of reserved and I'm like
talking in like cryptic
code but holy crap do I have something
for you guys
guys and you know my concern is my
publisher
right my Publishers behind me
100% they're so excited about it it's a
medical medium book medical medium
project our Publishers really pumped
about it they can't wait they're really
really excited and they know what it's
about had meetings with them
it's going to knock your socks
off a lot of people have been asking
about afterlife a lot of people have
been asking about Darkness a lot of
people been asking about a lot of things
for many years and the 35 plus years
I've been helping out people I've had
people of the highest powers on this
planet that's just billionaires people
that have immense power that have asked
me a lot of private questions about what
happens in the afterlife what really
goes on all those
things and I and I did it I put together
probably one of the
most profound books from s so my
publisher is going to be releasing and
um and it's not for faint it's not for
faint ears or faint
eyes I'm just letting you know what you
read and what you hear may be sh
shocking because it's not what people
really know it's not what people know
it's what people understand I'm just
letting you guys
know I think I did you're
right I'm nervous some of you might be
like this is what I can't handle this I
don't want to know these things I don't
want to know about all this stuff some
of you might be really pissed at me
because you might be like how how can he
put this out there because but then I
don't know maybe you can grow from it
maybe if you're really pissed at me or
angry at me because I'm going to release
what I'm going to release maybe you'll
find some forgiveness in your heart as
time goes on and maybe you'll understand
why I put this information but it's
questions that I've asked all during on
my spare time in the middle of the night
talking to Spirit of compassion when I
opened my eyes for a couple of minutes
and I say but wait a
minute why does someone go there when
they die wait a minute no so that how
come this happens wait what Angel comes
where when then like and I ask these
questions and I am letting you
guys look I don't know what's going to
happen I think that you
know life is
short like a
blip time goes by quite quick fast
and I'm putting this information out
there if you can handle it you can
handle it if you can't handle it I
apologize but I I did it my Publishers
behind me we are rocking and rolling for
2025 I'm finishing it up right
now my Publishers
waiting you know hey house penguin
random is
waiting I'm just letting you
know um so was one thing I wanted to
tell
you think I need anything I need a cup
of tea for
that I can handle all of it Colleen said
oh man I don't know I don't know if you
can handle all this I don't know Ser
seriously guys I'm like
nervous yeah wow but you know what I
could take a licking and keep on ticking
and I could take a
beating and you know keep on hanging in
there I came from hard KNX I was raised
hard KN workingclass
family and
um you know
and I got some skin on my
back I got some whip marks on there from
life but I got some skin on my back and
if someone you know people don't like
this because it's so so
intense you know so what other things
are happened in 2025
preparing something because I think it's
about
time some
people I've been as nice as I could been
handling as good as I could been as
friendly as I could for the last couple
years but I'm working on packaging
up
quite a
situation to uh
settle settle things
properly being nice kicking back but
2025 is going to be quite a
year who
knows so you guys I'm just letting you
know but here's what's really
crazy
so this spiritual project that I have
it's just a about ready for
2025 it's going to be the
first and there's going to be another
one shortly after that because there's
that much information coming from above
but I'm just for warning
you when the time comes pretty soon I am
going to you know basically say I'm
going to do a disclaimer of saying if
you can handle
this you can't handle
it I
understand anyway you guys we're talking
about health 2025 talking about healing
can you heal yes you can can you move
past your symptoms yeah can you heal all
of those mystery tingles numbness aches
and pains ringing in the ears dizziness
achy feet achy body fatigue neurological
lime yeah neurological lime anything
like that Ms and all these different
things can you heal yeah you can can you
get out of wheelchairs yes you you can
cuz it's been done before and you can
foundational tools are critical learning
what to avoid is a big piece of it
that's a big part of it learning some
tools for a foundational base making
sure you got up B12 making sure you got
some zinc making sure you're doing the
right things I'm just throwing a couple
of things right there making sure you
know how to protect yourself with golden
seal make sure you know how to protect
yourself with olive leaf make sure you
know how to use the right stuff
propolis and getting the best stuff you
know always check out the medical medium
talks about all the different things
because you want the best of the best of
the
best and then you want those adaptive
adap genic tools you want the really
powerful tools for adapting
right anyway so much to
do cold white
spring I hope I hope you either I hope
you're cool with what I'm
releasing again if you're not I hope you
forgive me because it's going to blow
your mind it's going to blow your
mind
anyway it's that intense and it's that
powerful there's that much information
but there powerful Tools in there but
wait till you know what it's about I
can't say too much right now but who do
I want to say
everything all right so remember medical
medium pizza party medical medium pizza
party Cafe grat itude collaboration Cafe
Gratitude medical
medium January
23rd medical me and pizzas are going to
be on the menu there healthy pizzas mm
approved across the
board I mean heck like I worked with
them on the crust like it is like legit
this is going to be just unbelievable
and there's the medical medium pizza
party popup dinners
January 15th January 16th I'm going to
be there get on the waiting list if you
can if you're able to watch
this um if you're able to watch this
from the beginning watch it from the
beginning but keep in mind I am going to
live stream J uh January 15th and
January 16th the popup dinner parties
I'm going to live stream those so keep
in mind so you know where to go to look
for YouTube okay Rumble so going to be
live streaming the meat and
greet the light
blast this is going to be it's going to
be unbelievable and check out the
wellness reset I'm holding it right here
because this is it you ready the
wellness reset
okay January 20th you can order it at
Cafe Gratitude the wellness reset there
it is right there I'm trying to hold
this piece of paper up front of you
right there Wellness reset you see that
all
right celery juice heavy metal detox
smoothie Cravings shifter shot that's
that's crazy that's
crazy Number Four Spice sash soup you
get then you get a brain Soother juice
then you get a healing broth soup dream
shifter shot stoni and stew massage kale
salad can can you imagine if you want
those are extras right there if you want
them can you imagine if your doing this
cleanse you did it for one day two day
thre three can you imagine if you do
this cleanse for four days 5 days six
days can you imagine if you take on this
cleanse seven eight n days can you
imagine did you hear what's in there and
you do that for nine straight days or
three
days and in my opinion it's freaking
inexpensive for what it it is and what
they're doing and what it takes to put
it together and get it to people it is
unbelievable all right I just want to
tell you about that you
guys keep in mind here here just a
little
message if you're somebody that's
struggling and you're struggling with a
chronic symptom you've been to doctors
you've been trying to get you've been
trying to heal bring this information to
the doctors bring the medical medium
books ask your doctor if you can do the
heavy metal detox cleanse get the metals
out
properly and watch your life change
watch it change seriously ask your
doctor if you can do um some celery
juice why watch your life change 32 o
celery juice every single morning 16
ounces every single morning then you go
boom heavy metal detox cleanse youat a
little fruit after if you're hungry boom
lunchtime right do some steamed potato
and some spinach or steamed potato and
some lettuce Boom the afternoon drink a
little bit of lemon water have some
honey tea ginger boom you just you just
move
forward and
heal and the the heavy met detox puns
with the extractor oh my
God you want to move fast
fast
anyway Fen over
there please help if you have any remedy
for
recurring ration
hives so check out like check out the
mono cleanse take the monoc cleanse to
your doctor okay check out cleans of
heel get the book if you don't have
these books I feel really bad I mean all
these all these medical Bibles here and
it's incredible what's here the advanced
information and people their lives
changed with these books get the cleans
of heel book go to the library get it
for free if you don't want to pay $16
$20 for it on Amazon I mean it's on sale
right now at Amazon I saw it it was like
it was ridiculous the price for
it you know get the book take the monoc
cleanse to your doctor do the monoc
cleanse for a few weeks if your doctor
approves ask your doctor what's right
for you and
heal rise with
melum brain shots are game changers
can't live without
them yeah they really are game changers
that is no joke Nicholas Russell over
there mm is not restrictive it's
liberating and that's the thing there
are people out there that were like told
to eat four blueberries that was all
they were allowed to eat half of a
granny smith apple then they were
supposed to in mitt fast all day long
then they had to eat nothing but like a
piece of meat just sit that's it piece
of meat with nothing around it no
vegetable like the amount of
restrictions people all the different
diets and gloves bone
broth that's a
joke someone's probably G to get mad at
me right now kayn says mm has helped my
family so much my 10-year-old is
enjoying listening to your live and
learning the mm info and becoming
empowered that's just that just put a
smile on my face
that's so cool listen you know that's a
whole another thing like bone broth that
whole thing every time I hear once in a
while somebody's like I'm trying bone
broth out there I'm like oh my God like
yeah go ahead do a fat bowl of soup do
fat soup like with vinegar in it like
okay do bone broth do fat soup do animal
fat soup with with vinegar in it okay
okay
sure sure what you'll do is get so
deficient down the road so sick down the
road you might be okay for a little
while because your adrenals are
likeu your adrenals are like that was
not a real swear your adrenals were like
you're doing all that bone broth and
your adrenals are freaking out and so
you feel kind of high on it a little bit
and you're eating kind of light and
you're doing this this this bone bone
broth soup this fat soup this bone
marrow soup and then all of a sudden 3
months later you're doing something else
because guess what you're you're you got
a rash now a year later you're like why
do I have all this seim on me now what
the hell's going on I was doing great
for a while in my bikini I was doing my
bone broth diet it's the same old
it's like around and around we
go that's what it
is f says thankful came across your
information after got
Ron uh after I got Rona yep hmds celery
juice vimergy vitamins and minerals save
my life and I've helped and helped my
family that you've helped your family
that will listen and heal too but
there's a lot of resistance to
lifechanging Foods food's a tough one
people love their food you know how it
rolls right my mom is eating more fruit
because of me and medical medium
information as she was told by her
doctor to not eat too much fruit that's
still happening out there God
my God heavy metal heavy metal detox
cleanse the heavy metal
cleanse with the extractor smoothie wo
is so powerful that has that has been
the cleanse that has helped me for so
the most amazing the extractor extractor
cleanse that's
powerful you know all right passionate
mm healing
says they got brain shots on the
menu
boom you guys it's been a great little
talk I hope I have inspired you in some
way I am at your service I am I think
I'm going to be bringing back the fly on
the wall this year and uh Bryce might
make an appearance the robot protein
robot the science robot might make an
appearance but it is pretty
claustrophobic to be in the science
robot
metal uh uniform that was really hard
make sure you are on the medical medium
newsletter please make sure and the
telegram by the way you guys I know I
haven't done a telegram recently but
check out if you haven't seen check out
the last 30 telegram messages that I did
do they're really inspiring really
healing good information
make sure you listen to those on
Telegram and I'm going to do more so I'm
going to get on telegram probably soon
and
um this year it's going to be great
we're going to do a lot of healing a lot
of stuff and I'm preparing you for
what's to come with the new medical
medium book my publisher is going to be
releasing medical medium podcast new
episode each
week There's an
episode each week
Have you listened new episode out today
it's about cleansing check it
out I'll see you guys
later can I have some
tea
chain you guys I appreciate
you this is going to be a good year