[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is it is
decades ahead head of what's out there
now I'm kind of giggly today as I've
always said who has 10 or 20 30 years to
wait for answers for example the show
today we're talking about
UTI UTI urinary tract infections yeah is
this an important topic yeah you better
believe it is it's really important
we're going to cover this it's really
important and you know there's a lot of
reasons why it's important for sure and
I'm giggling because I was I was
remembering right before I got on to the
show was remembering so many stories if
you UTI over the decades where I'd help
people try to prepare so they're not
heading on a plane and you feel that UTI
coming on so they're they're not I mean
there's nothing worse than that and I
feel bad and I'm not I'm not laughing
I'm I'm giggling because I remember so
many times I've been able to to you know
to stop it from happening and that gives
you relief and so I'm laughing now
because I'm excited about giving people
relief
and and that makes me happy because you
know I've I've spent so much time trying
to prepare people to so it would not
happen you know like you people that get
them all the time so to try to get rid
of them and so they're gone for good and
there' be this process where it takes a
little time you know all of a sudden you
have less UTI than less and finally
they're gone for good and I've been able
to help so many people over the decades
and I remember you know there's always
this good feeling like the pressure is
off when not only did their UTI get
better without using antibiotics but it
would get get better and go away for
good and it gives you this relief this
like oh thank God the person doesn't
have to suffer anymore in their life and
that get gets me giggly because that's
what it's all about it's is getting
people that relief of any kind in all
these different illnesses we talk about
so I'm excited about today today you
know I was like Hey UTI okay this is
great um so it's really important to
know so listen I just got to tell you
something this is I say this at the
beginning of every show for a real real
important reason you know the
information on this show here you can't
get anywhere else it's not possible and
if you did get it anywhere else it came
from me originally whether anybody likes
it or not so it's really important to
understand the information here doesn't
it's not backed by interest groups it
doesn't come from in interest groups it
doesn't come from medical funding with
strings attached it doesn't come from
botched research with the thumb on the
scale because there's money behind it
because that's what happens with almost
every study I hate to say it you guys
when it comes down to chronic illness
especially any s any study that's done
there's somebody putting a thumb on the
scale I'm sorry it's just the way it
works I know this for a fact I know
people in the field in the Science World
I know you name it and I've heard and
seen it all I know how it works there's
no persuaded belief systems with the
information that I'm giving you there's
no private panels of influencers that
you guys have no idea exist in
alternative medicine all throughout
alternative medicine to have something
come out a certain way so it can then be
to Al used in a certain way it's just
how it works investors invest in all
aspects of alternative medicine and
conventional medicine and guess what we
are free from it you need to know this
if you're a first-time listener it's
that critical to know trust me it is
that critical to know because it's
important no private panels of
influencers no health field payoffs and
no trendy traps those nasty trendy traps
that confuse people to stop them from
healing taking advantage of their
vulnerabilities of being sick for a long
time and not knowing what direction to
go and sucking them in with trendy traps
there are so many of them at this point
it is endless and it is actually
sickening so that's a whole thing there
so I'm just telling you this Joe does
not have any of that it's the only
Health show out there in the world
actually that is pure and untampered
with the information that's here it's
Advanced it's a clean Source it was
given to me as a gift since age four
I've been using it ever since to fight
for the people and fight for your rights
of healing and fight for womenkind and
Mankind to make sure that we have better
lives and that's what the gift was given
to me for and you just need to know that
before we start so we're going into
UTI let's talk about that a little bit
you know you're you got your bag packed
and you're heading off maybe a family
member is driving you to a um to you
know to the airport and and you feel a
little bit of UTI coming on and you're
like darn it I know this feeling I felt
this before and I'm feeling it again and
I'm about to hop on a
plane okay and or or you're about to go
on a bus or you're about to go on a
vacation with someone or a trip or a car
trip or it's a big family night out and
you're getting a UTI or it's a dinner
party or you have to go to your boss's
house for a party or you have to go
whatever it could be or hey you're
you're you joined a bathon so you're
going to be biking you're going to be
riding a bicycle with you know a
thousand people and you feel that UTI
coming on you're like not now and you're
like already looking for the cranberry
juice you're already looking for the
cranberry
juice and yeah for real like how many
people have ever felt this how many
people mostly women not men but mostly
women have this have this experience and
the same thing with BV bacterial
vaginosis the same thing there it just
starts coming on it could be before a
cycle it could be right directly after a
cycle just pass and there it is it's
kind of coming on and there's discharge
and you you're going to the doctors
doctor's not sure if it's UTI or if it's
you know or if it's BV or if it's a
yeast infection and yeast infections
being thrown in there left and right
what is this all about anyway what if it
is a bacterial infection
what what kind of bacteria ah nobody
really knows how do you like that isn't
that funny that the labs don't really
know isn't that funny you go in there
and you got this kind of infection
whether it's mild or starting or
possibly yeast or not or what it's just
you know hey nobody really knows I'm
just being honest that's just how it
works I've talked to a lot of urologists
over the years too talked to a lot of
them and you know that basically the
protocol is is basically the bottom line
is here just take this antibiotic and
and go off in your way and we'll see
what the lab says or we'll see what a
culture says and and but what kind of
bacteria is really going on for a UTI
for real urinary tract
infection and is it just yeast as yeast
infection these are all the important
questions and it's all important to know
how things work so let's cut into it a
UTI is bacterial you ready for this you
ready for
this a yeast infection no this isn't
someone's going to say oh okay duh it's
bacterial UTI okay isn't it bacterial
you can just hop on line and look a
yeast infection is
bacterial that's right that's right a
yeast infection is bacterial if you know
that already it came from me originally
I'm the first person that actually put
that out there years
ago exactly a yeast infection is
bacterial bacterial that's right really
important to know this really important
yeast will be present many times when
bacteria is jacking up when bacteria is
is you know working its way up to the
surface when when bacteria is flowing
when it's growing when it's
proliferating when it's
evolving that's right and what will
happen is yeast will try to beat it out
it will try to beat it out because yeast
its job is to gobble everything that
shouldn't be around so that bacteria
doesn't take over so when you have
symptoms of a yeast infection and you go
on to the doctor and you're on a yeast
infection um treatment what's really
happening is there's a bacterial
infection that's
underlying and that is the problem right
there that there's that's why the yeast
infection comes and comes and it keeps
on coming and it over and over get
another yeast infection n another yeast
infection that's because bacteria is not
being dealt with another yeast infection
that's because it's bacterial it's
bacterial there's a a bacteria involved
another yeast infection there it goes
that's how it works that's how it works
and you know for years for years you
know UTI have always been a mystery a
mystery to research in science I'm just
telling you right now they got a couple
of treatments they pump you up with
steroids if it gets really bad and they
pump you up with tons of antibiotics
whether they do it IV both steroids or
antibiotics IV or whether they they
administer it orally that's that's
basically the treatment and whatever Hit
or Miss whatever happens if it finally
subsides and it eases
off and you know you're able to you're
able to get through it it it could come
back again you could get the bleeding
the whole bit we're going to talk about
why the bleeding comes what the bleeding
is of course it can run into the kidneys
it could be it could start from the
kidneys it could start from the urea
thre the Ura it can start from it can
start from
anywhere and can start from the bladder
you know bladder infection of course
could be all three areas could be just
one area nobody really knows I mean a
real serious kidney infection a
bacterial serious bacterial kidney
infection doctors can most most of the
time be like okay no this is in the
kidney it's actually the kidney this is
it this is severe let's do you know lots
of antibiotics let's do a treatment of
steroids let's try to get this under
control but what is that bacteria that
even gets to that point for some so many
people out there what is it in what kind
it's strep it's strep a cacus it's strep
that's what it is it's the strep throat
that we had at one time in our lives
it's the strep that gets in the sinuses
it's the same strep that causes
sinusitis for so many people it sits in
the cavities and the sinus cavities and
sits in there and it gets in it just it
works in the it works in the canals of
the sinus passages it gets in there and
it stays in there for years for so many
people who get chronic sinusitis chronic
allergies sinus infections and and
anything can tip it over you got some
hay fever anything that triggers it
anything out there Foods or whatever it
could feed the bacteria the bacteria
your immune system can be you know
overrun by so many contaminantes out
there that the bacteria can just start
taking
over and so and that happens really
common with sinusitis people with
sinuses sinus problems but that same
bacteria that's in our system and it
just isn't strap a through
H okay it used to be a and b
now we've come to a place where at least
science and research is at least at
least acknowledging more groups of strep
I was telling people about more groups
of strep when I was eight years old
hearing it from Spirit okay I was also
told by Spirit at 8 years old that there
would be so many groups of strep that
you couldn't even fit it in the alphabet
you would need more than one alphabet to
actually fit it all in
okay and guess what we're up to H and
I'm going to tell you right now we're
far past H and maybe they're already
tacking on a couple more hi JK maybe
they're about to head there but that's
how many different groups of strep never
mind the mutated varieties in every
single group that science and research
have no idea
about so many varieties of strep and
it's everywhere it's on public toilet
seats it's on the public toilet handle
it's on restaurant door knobs it's you
know you walk into a restaurant you know
what I do when I walk into a restaurant
you know what I do a first thing I ask
Spirit if there's anything on the handle
that's the first thing I do I say to
Spirit there's anything on the door
handle spirit says no if there's no flu
virus or there's no nothing on the door
handle um then then I'll just I'll grab
the door handle but I'll always grab the
door handle underneath the door handle
in a spot that not everybody thinks to
grab it and then I also asked Spirit did
someone think to be kind of like tricky
too where they can you know grab the
underneath the door handle did someone
already do
that you know and and it you know I'll
get the first thing I'll ask is Spirit
okay and you know and I'll grab the
underneath or I'll take my pinky I'll
open the door with my pinky underneath
it because the last thing I need right
now is another variety of strep or some
other variety of strep or anything you
know that could have got could get into
me or whatever the last thing I need is
is any variety of strep and I've been
fortunate and I'm strep free and I've
been very happy and fortunate about it
but he gets in almost everybody and
everybody everybody everybody in so many
different ways and not just UTI not just
sinusitis and sinist problems but strep
throats sore throats that aren't
diagnosed as strep throat because they
can't find the strep on the surface
because it's not your first strep throat
so then you still have these sore
throats you get these random sore
throats you get run down which also
means there's an Epstein bar present
somewhere in the body
somewhere and so it's easy to pick up
strap they can pick it up anywhere so
you can pick it up with physical contact
with people and and everything like that
and that's another thing too is that so
many people have different varieties of
strep and it's and here's the problem so
many people have been on so many
different antibiotics and different
kinds of
antibiotics that they their strep could
be antibiotic resistant that's another
thing too so you can have all these
different antibiotic resistant streps
floting around where they're they're
resistant to one type of antibiotic but
maybe not to another but then you got
people that have had strep in their
system all all through their lives
causing all all kinds of symptoms like
lots of acne cuz strep is actually
behind acne cystic acne is caused by
strep I'm just going to tell you right
now and you know when you have this kind
of strep in the system and it's in there
cooking people take antibiotics they
take antibiotics for a flu virus they
take antibiotics for bronchitis and all
of a sudden the strep gets fed a new
antibiotic then it upgrades itself this
is how it works and sometimes we have to
use antibiotics we're in crisis Zone
we're not taking care of ourselves we're
not taking the right supplements to take
care of our immune systems we're not
eating the right foods and so we end up
just like in an emergency situation or
like oh my God dear Lord I got this
infection or some my eyes blown up sty
sty are strep that's what causes a sty
you know the IAI that's
strep and not only that you guys sibo
that's strep that's strep in the gut
that's not just overgrowth of bacteria
that's overgrowth of strep that was fed
antibiotics along the way from childhood
on in some capacity and if it wasn't
antibiotics actually literally
administered treatment from a doctor
prescribed and you've taken it was
antibiotics you received from the water
supply or antibiotics you received from
food I mean not every single person has
eaten a piece of chicken that's organic
antibiotic free I'm sorry but that was
just recently that it's mostly out and
still all the restaurants Stock the
regular chicken that's loaded win
antibiotics so nowh no matter what you
get the antibiotics in you so they're in
there and they feed strep and then we
end up with something like a
UTI a lot of time also sexual contact
you know a new partner or something and
you know and and bugs bug normal bugs
like strep that that are everywhere they
just pass along and then a person gets
their first
UTI or their second kind after they
haven't had them for too many
years so it's just around and you know
sorry about the story I know I did that
long story about the grabbing the door
handle but that's true and then the
bathroom handle I actually just take my
wrist and kind of use my wrist around
the door handle or something you know to
try not to touch the bathroom handle I
mean maybe it's I'm I'm a little too
much with that but the thing is is I
know what where bugs are anyway cuz
Spirit tells me when I sit on the plane
I know if there's merca on my my plane
seat I know if there's you know I know
if there's tuberculosis you know cuz
someone coughed and sneezed tuberculosis
all over my my airline seat and I can
ask spirit so you know it so yeah of
course it's something that had been
given as a gift to know through
throughout my life and it it's helped me
but I realize you guys don't have that
so you know to bring handy wipes and
stuff like that bring handy wipes always
have the handy wipes it's really
important but the bottom line why does
it matter because you can get strep on
your finger and stick it in your eye and
have a sty and it could be your first
sty for the first time and then after
that a year later you have a UTI and
have no idea why or how you got that
UTI because what it was it started with
the sty and it went into the body and
into the system and it got down to where
it got down to this is how it
works so it's not about fearing life
it's not about that at all it's about
knowledge is power it's about knowing a
lot it's about knowing everything it's
about knowing all the things you need
cuz guess what's worse than not not
knowing what you need to know I'll tell
you what's
worse is not knowing what you need to
know gu that's what I'm trying to
say so you need to know what's what's
going on I think I mixed it up there a
little bit just bear with me you need to
know what's going on because there's
nothing worse than not knowing that's it
that's it that's it talking too fast
talking way too fast somebody I think
someone did a comment while back was on
social media and they said he talks too
slow he talks too slow and so I was like
oh God you know it's the second time I
heard I talks too slow and then and then
I picked it up a little bit it just
naturally happened I guess and someone
say he talks too fast I can't listen to
him all right okay go back to yeast
infections yeast infections candida
other types of yeast there's a lot of
different varieties of yeast there's a
lot of different varities of fungus some
some are really mean and nasty and some
are just friendly and nice and great
some friendly nice cute special fluffy
light and Airy fungus which isn't bad is
there to stop
bacteria it's there to stop bacteria it
could be irritating could be agitating
could be problematic but it's there to
try to gobble up
proteins and other things like that
other things like bad hormones and
proteins that are in eggs and other
things and all this that find their way
into the bladder and they find their way
into the vaginal area and they just find
their way all over the place and and the
yeast wants to just start eating it up
and gobbling it up because if it doesn't
guess what's going to feed off of it
it's going to be strep that's what's
going to feed off of it when yeast is
present strp is present it's in there
somewhere it's in the
system that's the whole thing when
someone is exploding with candida in
their intestinal track that means strep
is rampant Pro proliferating and going
crazy also in there
too so that's why the candid is freaking
out because it's trying to gobble all
the bad fats everybody's eating on these
high trendy fat diets it's trying to
gobble all this crazy
stuff it's not trying to gobble fruit
it's not trying to gobble
vegetables but it's gobbling all this
other stuff because it's trying not to
let the shrep like ignite and
proliferate and grow and just and and
and move and vastly you know Cruise
through the
system so very important to know how it
works same thing yeast infection same
thing with BV it's all strep related yes
it is and the groups of strep are now
way past the alphabet we have including
two alphabets but science and research
is so behind it's unbelievable
especially with chronic illness anything
to do with chronic illness it's so
behind don't get science confused don't
get don't get confused about the good
parts of science don't get confused
about what they do with with like like
mathematics and they try to create uh
parts and they try to they try to build
things and they try to create better
equipment for diagnosis and everything
else don't get confused by that science
versus chronic illness where science
research knows nothing about I'm sorry
they know nothing about chronic illness
we got over 250 million sick people in
the US alone 250 million with symptoms
and
conditions okay and I'm just going to be
straightforward science of research
doesn't even have their finger on the
pulse they still think autoimmune is the
body attacking itself it's unbelievable
if you want to learn more about that get
thyroid healing my book thyroid healing
if you don't have my books here's some
someone said this the other day that
said why do I need your books I can
listen to your radio shows I that that's
that's that's unbelievable because the I
can't cover a fraction of what's in the
books in these radio shows I just can't
it's not even possible so thyroid
healing talks about the autoimmune great
mistake that we have right now that's
going on that that you know someone I
think someone was saying to me like I
I'm kind of upset at you and I said what
are you talking about you're upset at me
what do you mean and they said well my
body is attacking itself I said what and
they go my body is attacking itself and
you're wrong because my body's attacking
itself I was diagnosed with an
autoimmune disease and my body is
attacking itself how dare you say your
body's not attacking
itself and it it would it just blew me
away actually it blew me away it totally
did the body attacks a virus not the
body tissue not the not the body cells I
talk about it in great detail in thyroid
healing and I've talked about it on
shows too it's not attacking a single
cell in the body your immune system is
working for you it's not working against
you on any level it gives people
tremendous tremendous tremendous relief
and gets them healing especially what
they know what to do with their automine
especially when they know how to heal
their thyroid finally especially when
they know how to heal themselves from
lupus especially when they know how to
heal themselves from ra and everything
else so when someone gets all upset
because they they like the fact that
their body's attacking itself I I don't
get that
one I don't get that one I really don't
so I was just like okay okay all right
fine sorry sorry your body's hacking
itself okay
fine you know you know the thing is is
is is
uh the thing is that when it comes down
to chronic illness like I was saying
very little is known about any of it
there's plenty of fancy
names okay and but you have to
understand something the science and
research behind chronic illness and what
is out there and the studies and whatnot
that are out there and everything they
are paid for and they are funded for all
the wrong directions for all the wrong
reasons that's the way the system is
built and guess what it funnels itself
down to UTI and urinari tract infections
you better believe it it really does
where are we today with UTI you either
get an antibiotic or you get a steroid
and see you later hopefully it goes away
someday that's where we are chronic
illness with science and research go to
an alternative doctor he might give you
an herb or two he might give you some
cranberry extract he might give you
something might she might give you this
whatever but in the end they're still
not going to know it's really strep and
it's it's in it's in it's in the system
and it's deep in the system and it has
to be warded out it has to be weeded out
it has to come out of your system you
got to kill off the strep you got to not
feed it and that's another thing you got
to learn to not feed the strep in order
to get better from UTI
UTI okay that keep on coming and coming
and coming the bacteria is feeding off
of something it really likes whether
it's feeding off of something it really
likes inside the liver whether it's
feeding it's feeding off of something it
really likes it's coming from other
places the kidneys you know and and
because it's it's all getting through
osmosis all you know the way the body
eliminates both the intestinal tract and
the kidneys and there's fuel for the
bacteria to
thrive and here's the
thing the yeast with yeast infections is
just kind of a little outer
sign then you got strep ins inside okay
inside the reproductive system then you
got it inside the
gut and it that's how it
works and then you have a little bit
inside the liver and and that's how it
works it's not scary there's nothing
scary about it in fact it's great
because when you know what's up we're
going to do some strep killing we're
going to kick its butt we're going to
knock it out of the system you're not
going to have to deal with the sty
anymore you're not going to have to deal
with the sinus infections anymore you're
not going to have to deal with the UTI
all that will minimize and minimize and
minimize and be less and less and less
you'll get the antibiotics out of your
system you'll get them out of your your
your um your liver you'll get them out
of your spine the antibiotics will start
leaving your system so they won't even
be able to feed the different varieties
of strep that are mutated that that are
actually mutated because of antibiotic
use for you know over the century so all
this is really
important and you know so let's talk
about severity of UTI okay um sometimes
it's just a burning sometimes it's just
a burning
itching um sometimes it's a little bit
of pain um urinating in general with the
bladder sometimes you can have like
bladder spasms going on where you're
feeling bladder spasms sometimes you can
have achy kidneys you could have
achiness all over the body you could
have a fever and different levels and
different kinds and different kinds of
strep cause different kinds of UTI and
then you could have the bleeding too
which is
rupturing rupturing of tiny micro blood
vessels cap lares that are rupturing and
they're rupturing because of a bacterial
overload and so the bacteria is causing
rupturing in the little blood vessels
next thing you know you're urinating
blood
everywhere so there's different levels
of of how this could work some people
they can also just get a really bad
kidney strep infection for the first
time it comes along with the worst case
Amano they ever had and maybe they're in
college or something or it's summer time
and you know after after college is over
and it's summertime and then a lot of
women young women go through this where
they have the worst the first UT UTI in
their life it's the worst there's
bleeding there's kidney infection
there's fever they're they're at their
pediatrician and if they still have a
pediatrician most most people keep their
pediatricians all the way until they
like 20 now and then you know and or
they end up at the ER they end up with
an antibiotic some steroids they'll stay
a night in a hospital if the fever's
High um and then they'll go home and
then that's their first you know kind of
weird UTI with that weird UTI is that's
a strep infection
100% so I'm trying to give you all the
different scenarios before you know we
got a little time we got a little time
to burn as far as the I got plenty of
things we're going to do for UTI but we
have a little time to talk about the
different scenarios the different
severities and levels and then there's
just regular like I said before it's
just a little pain a little twitch a
little nerve twitch um um little spasm
when urinating a little itch a little
burn um you know there's that too and
there's that rundown feeling you can get
with it too you can get kind of run down
your throat gets a little kind of horse
it gets a little uh little sore while
you're getting like a
UTI um happens with women a lot when
they have their cycle right after right
before their cycle they they get a UTI
and it could happen each month and it
can happen every six months but it does
happen and it happens more than anybody
knows and it happens all the time it's
it's like if you if you can count how
many from mild to severe UTI are
occurring or East infection UTI are
occurring just across the country at any
given time you wouldn't believe what it
would be it would be it would blow your
mind and then if you know tack on sinus
infections and also lung infections too
there's a lot of lung problems people
have where they have a chronic cough
they go to doctors they take tons of
antibiotics and they haven't had a flu
they haven't had a cold or anything and
they got this chronic wheezing chronic
cough chronic lung problems that's also
strep that sits inside the lungs for a
lot of different people and that's a
different variety of strep
and that strep just incubates in lungs
while you're taking antibiotics for it
and whatever and it get just doesn't get
it's becomes immune to different
antibiotics and that's a different kind
of strip but those people also get U
periodically throughout life it's it's
it's it's just all in our system and so
now it's time what do we do and how do
we you know fix this how do we get
things
better why does
cranberry why does cranberry work why
does cranberry work it must have worked
at one point for
someone right cranberry juice or
Cranberry extract or cranberry pills or
something it must have worked at one
point for
somebody keep in mind cranberry is a
fruit cranberry is a fruit keep that in
mind really important any fruit helps a
UTI any fruit there's a reason for that
the sugars and fruits can't feed any
bacteria can't feed any virus can't feed
any any yeast can't feed anything the
sugars and
fruits they can't feed anything bad but
what they do is those sugars bond to
bacterial killers they bond to bacterial
killers and that
bond is what knocks out bacteria that's
what knocks out bacteria so for instance
Elderberry syrup incredible for UTI
taking Elderberry syrup got to get a
really good one high quality one and you
know you you get an Elderberry syrup you
take a tablespoon Elderberry syrup you
know one one tablespoon twice a day one
tablespoon three times a day to help
knock that UTI but that's not the only
thing you could use it that it's a
really mild UTI that could probably
work and but the sugar in Elder
berries is what does
it the sugar wild blueberries work
better for UTI than cranber
does wild blueberries do they work
better any fruit helps um knock out
bacteria any fruit any all the way up to
bananas so the fruit hating world is out
of control more than ever before in
history right now for no reason for no
reason you know listen to the fruit fear
show listen to that so you know what's
going on it's actually it's Sinister
it's actually Sinister so but that's
cranberry knocks out
bacteria and because antoin and not just
that other phytochemical compounds that
are
antibacterial attach themselves to the
sugar and it's this this sugar and the
antoin or the phytochemical that kills
off bacteria attached to the sugar enter
cells easily they enter organs easily
they enter hard to reach places where
strep hides and
incubates and that's how it works strep
tries to burn burrow itself in the
urethra it tries to burrow itself in the
urinary tract it tries to burrow itself
in the in the in the inner sides of the
of the gallbladder nobody knows that
nobody knows a strep makes pockets and
that becomes
cystitis down the road intercal
cystitis that's just that's from years
of having strep years and years and
years of having strep in the wrong diet
and having the wrong diet and the strep
feeding off of dairy and feeding off of
eggs or feeding off of a P of cheese on
a pizza from 20 years or feeding off of
you know goodies or feeding off of high
fat foods even if it's healthy trendy
high fat fat even if it's just straight
keto high fat that's somewhat healthy
whatever it is Strep loves lots of fats
it loves lots of fat and it loves lots
of it loves lots of also other things
that are in Foods it loves what's in
eggs it loves what's in that stuff it
loves what's in corn it loves what it
actually loves Woodson actually with in
corn that's different than fruit
entirely different corn is different
than fruit it loves Woodson
um a lot of these things loves what's in
pork and so you know so when you have
pork when you have bacon and you think
Bacon's healthy or something you're
having bacon that's just that just keeps
strep around forever and eventually you
get the you get the cystitis you get the
interstial cystitis and this the
bacteria build little pockets from
Little Scar Tissue Pockets start
building and the strep hides and these
are cells that are hard to reach for
anything and then when you dump in
Cranberry you dump in Wild blueberry you
dump in Elderberry in your system and it
and and it goes into cells in hard to
reach places excuse me hard to reach
places and it gets in there deep and it
starts pushing out the bacteria starts
knocking it out it starts getting it out
of there another thing that's in fruits
like cranberry W blueberry and
Elderberry and I'm just saying those
three never mind a whole bunch of others
I could be saying just tons of fruit
whatever papaya whatever you know what's
in there lots of vitamin C heavy loads
of vitamin C guess what bacteria hates
it hates vitamin C with avengeance with
everything it's got it hates vitamin C
because vitamin C not only feeds your
lymphocytes your basophils your
monocytes your neutrophils not only does
it feed your immune system to go after
strep and identify it tag it and and bag
it not only does it have that ability to
do all
that but What vitamin c does it's
poisonous it's a toxin to bacteria it's
actually highly toxic to bacteria only
That's What vitamin C is highly tox
toxic to bacteria so when you have
cranberry juice what's in cranberry
juice you got this this this special
vitamin C that's just just in
cranberries that's just in Wild
blueberry that's just an Elderberry that
vitamin C is a toxin highly toxic to
bacteria so these are some of the
reasons why it works because people
don't know why it works and they just
don't
know so that's what's happening there
that's what's going on okay so another
thing to understand when you're dealing
with um when you're dealing with
bacteria strep causing UTI is you don't
want to feed it so back to those Foods
you got to be on the no Foods if you're
in you know if you're into uh if you're
a big animal protein person then try to
do the animal proteins that that that
don't feed strep and try to keep it
lowfat lots of leaner versions and not
too many I would honestly if you're
somebody dealing with UTI I would try to
get off the animal protein for a little
while and try to do something like the
28 day cleanse or try to do something
you know my first book or try to do
something and listen if if you're a
vegan and you're plant-based and you got
UTI get off the nuts just limit them
they're really healthy but limit them
limit your fat content don't eat so many
avocados don't eat so many nuts and
seeds don't me eat too many oils and and
you know be cautious also of strange
grains you know a lot of vegetarians
they eat you know they still eat um
different you know they eat like um
Sprite of Buckwheat and they eat all
kinds of other things that they eat and
and that's fine but it's it's at the
same time too many grains too much of it
is not great for a UTI so that's another
thing too so if you're a macrobiotic you
know and all you do is eat GRS you know
try to bring in more fruit and
vegetables and leafy
greens and limit the grains um
especially the bad grains especially the
bad ones all the gluten all the gluten
varieties but here's the thing though
it's it's it's like this and if you're a
vegetarian just don't eat the eggs don't
eat the eggs don't eat the cheese time
to be if you're vegetarian you don't
like meat and you're afraid to eat meat
or it's not in your belief system or
whatever it is then you you should go
all the way plant-based I I'm you just
should you should be getting rid of the
eggs and get rid of the dairy if you
have
UTI if you're dealing with sinusitis if
you're dealing with lung issues if
you're dealing with sty if you're
dealing with
sio get off the eggs get off the dairy
go plant-based if you're vegetarian I'm
just being honest it's it's not about
what side I'm picking on it's about
what's right for the problem and that's
what I'm trying to say I'm I don't I
don't I'm not sucked into a belief
system I'm not sucked into a belief
system where you can't eat a grain or
you you you you you can't eat a piece of
chicken if your heart desires or if you
or if you're all plant-based or all raw
I don't I all you whatever you want to
do but I'm going to tell you right now
what you should do when it comes down to
what's wrong with you in that moment and
with UTI animal products keep them down
low none of the dairy none of the eggs
all that just throw all that out if
you're eating meat I would probably
consider just knocking that back keep it
down to real small portions at different
times and try to do other things and you
know bring in other Foods bring in sweet
potatoes bring in more of those bring in
Winter squash bring in regular potatoes
because guess what those don't feed
strep either none of that feeds strep
but if you have a high high fat diet
really high fat content what you're
every what's a high fat diet it's high
protein just look out look out for that
it's hidden under the word high protein
then that's a high fat diet so you just
got to look out you're having more fats
than you even know and they're in the
bloodstream they're in the body and they
take on the intestinal lining they they
Harbor strep and you just got to min
minimize if you're vegan and plant-based
you can't be doing four avocados a day
unless it's the only food you have then
it's totally fine if you got meaning
like you can do four avocados a day but
if you got UTI and you got strep and you
got all the strep related stuff then
back it down to one avocado a day back
it down to one and a half AV as a day
unless you're having a get together in a
party then you know go to go go crazy
with the guacamole if you're paleo or
you're somebody that's totally in high
protein animal protein you shouldn't be
eating animal protein three times a day
no way you if you got strep if you got
UTI if you got all these different
problems sorry it's never going to go go
go go away completely 100% you got to
you got to lower your animal proteins I
hate saying that I'm sorry but it's true
I don't care what fancy doctor what
fancy belief system or trend is out
there right now saying you know stay
away from all fruit you should just be
eating tons of animal protein I don't
care what it is if you got UTI they
don't know what the hell they're talking
about and guess what that's is how it
works in the industry nobody knows what
they're talking about so here's the deal
is yeah I'm sarcastic a little snarky
today you know but here but but like I
said I I like having people not having
the pressure on them I like people being
being getting the relief I want people
better I want people to not have to
worry about that UTI that's going to
sneak up on them during their wedding
day you know I'm I'm just you know I'm
I'm or when they're the most important
moment in life they're about to give a
speech somewhere and they're getting the
worst UTI they've ever had I've seen it
over and over year after year out there
in the old days I've seen it and even
now people getting those UTI and they
sneak up on them and and it just messes
them up they can't have fun they they're
going to a movie theater with friends
and they got a UTI that's a problem and
they're just they're not even watching
the movie because they're in agony
whatever I've seen it I've seen it all
including some severe cases that got
really bad in people and they've lived
like that and they didn't have to
anymore cuz they got the answers they
knew what to do so with the diets you
lower your animal protein to once a day
that's what I would do if you're a big
animal protein person big animal Pro you
lower it down to once a day keep it
small portion bring in more fruits bring
in more vegetables leafy greens and
we're going to talk about some herbs and
vitamins too if you're if you're plant-
paste and you're vegan um or raw just
lower the fats don't do the oils maybe
just a few hemp seeds are fine maybe
just one and a half avocados a day maybe
a teaspoon of coconut oil somewhere in
there on on a salad or whatever it is
you can you can heat it up and put it on
a salad but you know just try to do much
more fruit try to do more fruit
different kinds of fruits try to do
other things too um if you're Raw it's
going to be all raw if you're a vegan
that eats cooked it's going to be some
Cooks to too the vegetables and
everything
else I'm not picking
sides I'm seeing what's really going on
from what has been given to me as a gift
so that people can find their way and
have the answers and know what's causing
problems and know how to heal them and
let me tell you something okay you know
Spirit told me when I was younger that
that was really important it was
important to have that sight but I
didn't think I was the only one in the
industry to have that sight and it's
still to this day with with everything
that I'm seeing out there day and day
out and the new books coming out and the
new literature and what's on the
Internet it's like oh my God everybody's
still blind and I want you to be able to
see and know what to do for each
condition and these these radio shows
we're going to be doing there these are
going to get really intense and we're
going to do more and more of them and
we're just going to be rocking the truth
and putting the truth out more and more
like never before
for so the bottom line is this what else
can we do for UTI one thing is
everybody's got a zinc deficiency yes
they have a zinc deficiency and the zinc
attacking zinc is also been a trend oh
it's going to get rid of all your copper
oh you're not going to have any copper
oh you can't take zinc you're going to
lose all your copper first of all I
can't tell you how wrong that is number
one we have so much copper in our system
it's the one mineral we can't get away
from we have so much of it it even gets
us sick there's so much copper in food
I'm talking about levels of toxic copper
in food not to mention good copper in
food there's so much of it abound you
can't even lose it if you want it to in
fact you need to get rid of some because
it can keep you sick and knock down your
immune system and it hurts you copper
actually hurts you it doesn't help you
it hurts you it's an IT copper is
riddled on every conventional piece of
of food that exists on the Planet
riddled in Copper never mind even
organic food has copper in it naturally
copper is not deficient in our soil in
fact it is it is overabundance and
copper is a serious problem too when you
have too much copper your liver builds
up all this copper it causes eczema
psoriasis it causes all these problems
with people so when people out there
would you hear it from everybody oh
watch the zinc oh it's going to get rid
your copper another another theory that
was paid for somewhere with some thumb
on the scale while back and some study
put out there why because if you become
zinc deficient you get sick and I I
believe I
believe that keeping everybody sick is
probably on somebody's agenda out there
in the world and I have good reason to
believe CU I got a source that tells me
and it's
spirit Spirit tells me and not just that
I got other sources too and anyway the
bottom line is the bottom line is copper
it you know when you take zinc and you
take the right kind of zinc the zinc I
talk about the zinc that's on my website
if you go to my website and you go to
the supplemental directory I don't I
it's not that I'm selling supplements I
don't I try to get you there where you
need to go you go to my supplement um uh
directory you find the right kind of
zinc you build your immune system up and
you'll have less UTI and less UTI
because guess what when you when you
have the zinc in your system the strep
is going to lower and lower and
naturally lower it's not going to be
able to function it's not going to be
able to do what it needs to
do and that's what I'm talking
about guess what strep can feed off of
though can feed off high amounts of
copper so it's it you shouldn't be
afraid of a little bit of zinc the very
thing that actually helps stop strep and
stop the UTI I've seen it save people
from Agony actual Agony it's one it's
it's deficient in the soil there's no
zinc in the soil I don't care if it's
the best organic farm there's no zinc in
the soil oil there isn't zinc is gone
been
obliterated been obliterated because of
f Fallout from World War II from the
from the you know the
bomb okay that's still in the air coming
down every day every day it never came
down it's still up there just floating
around the atmosphere just floating
around just floating around floating
around and dropping slowly Non-Stop and
what it does is that Fallout in the in
the minute forms that it's dropping
non-stop in all the fields and all all
the even the organic fields and
everything else what it does is it
cancels out zinc gets in the soil and it
cancels out zinc science and research
doesn't realize that that Fallout is is
diminishing zinc to the point of of not
being in our in our in our food supply
so don't be afraid of taking a little
bit of zinc if you're sensitive just try
to switch off maybe to a good capsule I
got a I got a capsule zinc on the
directory too the liquid one is the one
I like the liquid ones the right
kind so and just don't run off and get
any old zinc it might be loaded with
citric acid or something they put like
two parts citric acid in some of those
zinc bottles it's the worst thing I've
ever seen or it might be loaded with
something else or it might not be a zinc
supplement it might be a zinc with 20
other minerals so you're getting like
this much zinc but 20 other minerals
just try not to get confused and pick up
the wrong thing CU it's not going to
help but you need that for the UTI you
need the zinc okay so that's number one
number two let's do some herbs I
Bright's a great one for UTI ibite is a
great one propolis that's a great one so
ibrite propolis okay lemon balb that's
amazing that's a that's amazing one for
maintenance you could be on that as a
maintenance to actually fend off strep
so that you don't get a UTI or any other
type of thing I'm talking about so
that's a great one all right I like
licorice root on and off you can do that
for
UTI that does help with strep it does
help and then and then um let's see what
else olive leaf that's a great one to
have the Elderberry I talked about
before Oregon grap root Oregon grape
root that's a good one for
UTI couple of dropperfuls of that twice
a day and dosages wise you can go look
you can talk to your practitioner talk
to your practitioner about dosages talk
to your practitioner whatever but I mean
if if it was me and I had a UTI which
I've never had in my life but if I had
one okay and and I you know and I hope I
never get one and you know if I but if I
did have one I'd be doing like two
dropper FS twice a day
of the orgon graef rooot I would do
probably when if I had the UTI in the
moment I'd probably be doing like four
dropper fulls of golden seal golden seal
three times a day I'd do three dropper
fulls twice a day a lemon balm I would
do you know olive leaf two dropper FS
twice a day I would do one tablespoon of
Elderberry three times a day yeah sure
i' I'd probably take a cranberry extract
why not I'll probably be eating up in my
wild blueberries
too vitamin C I'd be doing six eight
capsules of Ester SE twice a day and if
you're sensitive and you can't do these
dosages of course I'm not saying to do
these dosages at all this is just what I
would do but if you're sensitive
whatever you go to your practitioner you
take one capsule of vitamin C you take
five drops of of lemon bomb if you
want but but I would be doing all those
so so you're getting the list down I'm
trying to think is there anything else
in the list that'd be really good you
got the vitamin C that's a big
deal that's a a big one you can do monol
Lauren sometimes that helps sometimes it
doesn't but it's worth throwing in in
there if you're really dealing with or
suffering with UTI in a bad way you can
definitely do that throw some monolaurin
in there that's okay um sure absolutely
nettle leaf that has a maintenance to
help keep strep back nett Leaf is great
that's a good one um turmeric that's a
great one for UTI too it can help keep U
Back turmeric is a great one ccin or
cumin or however you want to say it
that's a great one also for
UTI so these are some of the options um
I like Oregon grape root like I said and
um I like the golden seal I like the
olive leaf I like the lemon bomb I like
the
ibrite okay and the Elderberry you know
bring all those in and they can really
help the propolis that's a big one too
like I said earlier that's a big one and
you know what happens is it if you have
one coming on you just Hammer everything
you bring it in you bring it in and then
you when when it's gone you can keep a
maintenance of a little bit of zinc a
maintenance a little bit of zinc maybe a
little bit of Elderberry and some lemon
balm keep maintenance as you're cleaning
your Foods up making sure you're not
eating Foods if like I said make sure
you're not eating too much fat if you're
on a high protein animal diet lower them
bring in more fruits and
vegetables okay I love it how the
experts now the other experts out there
whatever so-called experts I love how
they pull this where they're starting to
see finally for the first time ever in
the history of their their practices and
what they're doing they're seeing that
people are getting better by remove
first of all they see when you remove
the dairy and the and and the gluten and
they see people getting a little better
but then they realize they're lowering
the animal proteins a little bit some
some belief systems are shifting and
they're actually lowering the animal
proteins and they're bringing in just
more more more vegetables and leafy
greens but they're lowering the animal
proteins and and Eureka they think they
struck gold because people are getting a
little better and a little better yep
you know what I was doing that 30 years
ago 30 years ago
there are people out there right now at
the age 60 65 that have lived great
lives because they got that information
30 35 years ago from me okay you you the
thing is the experts don't know it's
because they're lowering the fats they
don't understand it when you lower the
fats the fats the high fat feed bacteria
and viruses and they hide bacteria and
viruses so what I'm saying is if you
still want to be on high protein just
lower the amounts if you still want to
be plant-based lower the amounts of nuts
and seeds lower the amounts of um of
fats in other ways and oils and stuff
like just lower bring it down bring in
more fruits bringing more leafy greens
bringing if look if you're if you're if
you're not all raw and you're cooked
then bring in cooked vegetables bring in
potatoes and they could be really
helpful and keep the bacteria down so it
can't eat and Thrive it can't eat and
Thrive so look the bottom line is it's
about you getting stronger healthier
about you avoiding calamity
it's about you know avoiding adversity
in your life it's about just getting
away from the bad lands and getting into
the good lands and moving forward and
knowing what to
do so you know when it comes down to ETI
and when it comes down to yeast
infections too you still want to do
these things you still want to do these
things because the this because there's
an underlying strep Factor going on with
bacterial vaginosis yeah it you know
that that too you want to do these
things to get that bacteria down and you
want to do the foods and get the foods
better and better the the most the most
bug feeding food there is is eggs it's
the most bug feeding food on the planet
it feeds every bug that isn't good is
what it does it feeds every single
variety of
strep it the strep was actually raised
in Labs a long time ago and somehow got
out of the labs and into our bodies
that's interesting that's
interesting that that strep was raised
and guess what it was raised on it was
raised on egg that's what it was raised
on that was his food
Choice guess what's in some antibiotics
egg believe it or
not and there's all kinds of things in
antibiotics petroleum you know engine
oil you name it that's all that's
actually all in antibiotics the
petroleum the engine oil you name it
it's not that you can't take an
antibiotic in a crisis situation because
you've gotten there it's about doing
everything else so eventually that
crisis situation doesn't come and hit
you and goes away and you see it go by
and you You Kiss It Goodbye you said bye
and you wave It Goodbye so it's gone and
gone for
good and that's what you want to do
that's what you want to do and if you're
worried about getting a UTI someday and
you've never had one and you might have
something else cooking like a little bit
of sibo you think your doctor thinks or
believes or you got something else going
on like a little bit of gastritis
because gastritis is also something
that's caused by strep some of the it's
chronic gastritis and bloating
constipation bloating gastritis all that
has strep behind it if you think that's
what's going on let's start going
anti-strep and start knocking this stuff
down and we can do it simply if this is
too overwhelming and I've given you too
much you start small and you start with
the good stuff you take away one thing
you take away the dairy you take away
the eggs you you take away the gluten of
course you take away you know you lower
your you lower your intake your fat
intake whatever side of whatever side of
the world you're on in the food belief
system Wars whatever side you're in
you're stuck in or you want to be in or
you feel good in whichever one some
people they don't feel good in it
they're just stuck in it some people
feel amazing in there now I talk to
plant-based people and they're like I've
never felt better in my entire life I've
been sick for 30 years I went
plant-based I can't believe it I've
gotten everything better it's the
greatest thing in the world so they
don't feel stuck in it and then you got
people that are in some other belief
system or they're in a belief system and
they're they're not feeling good they
did feel good for a little while and
they're not feeling good anymore and
they're stuck in it because they can't
get out of it whatever it is just lower
the fat intake so that the strep can't
feed off of that hide or pilate
underneath perate I can't say the word
now can't you know
grow underneath underneath those
layers underneath that fat that gets
Caked Up in the intestinal tract in the
walls and turns rancid and putrid it
gets inside the bladder we urinate fat
out of our body we urinate fat out of
our body we actually do and what happens
is it builds up in the bladder lining
and it Shields strap all the time
something to think about okay just one
day at a time take it one a time youve
got an arsenal of some things to use you
know what to do we're on the right track
I'm with you I stand behind you 100% I
love you guys thank you for being on the
show with me today let's hit the next
show let's do it I love you take care
bless you God bless you okay bye-bye