[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now as
I've always said who has 10 or 20 30
years to wait for
answers and answers for pots you know we
need answers for
pots um so many people suffer for with
with it it's it's unbelievable what what
they go through you may be one of them
and you may have a mild rendition of it
you may have a serious rendition of it
either way this is the only Health show
so here where the information doesn't
come from medical interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched up research with the thumb on
the scale medical lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems which
is sucked into every part of alternative
and conventional medicine private panels
of influencers health field payoffs or
trendy traps the information here is
pure it comes untampered with from a
clean source to me higher source I call
Spirit of
compassion and that's very important to
know about and you're going to know that
when we talk about pots why this has to
be pure information and why it can't be
agenda driven information that's
contaminated both conventionally and
alternatively in the world that there
I'm talking about doctors doctors are
the greatest thing in the world and
surgeons sure doctors you know the best
thing ever you can do is you know you go
to your doctor when you see your doctor
whether it's a naturopath functional
medicine doctor regular MD specialist
immunologist hematologist oncologist
whoever it is and now you stick your
hand out and you just say listen thank
you I appreciate the fact that you
dedicated your life to helping so many
and being there for so many and day in
and day out and I really I just really
appreciate it just thank you thank you
whether you're healing whether you're
working on healing whether you're just
went to your first doctor whether
whatever it is
because um and same to the nurses and
same to the nurses actually nurses are
critically important for sure I've known
uh hundreds and hundreds of them over
the years and it's and you you know and
and listen it's about the information we
talk about on the show medical medium if
this is the first time that you've come
to the medical Medium show um what I
mean by pure information I mean this
information hasn't been misguided by
funding or something you know that's
Twisted it or something like that for
example autoimmune autoimmune we're
talking about pots right and pots is
considered an autoimmune syndrome
autoimmune disease autoimmune condition
right that's what is considered well
first of all
autoimmune isn't even right the body
attacking self isn't even right and that
contamination from that misguided theory
that became
law that has poisoned poisoned literally
the medical systems both alternative and
conventional and I I had to write a
chapter about it in the thyroid healing
book I just couldn't help myself I had
to I had to because it's still that
poisonous toxic and still it's ruining
people's lives in many ways you don't
think it is oh it is if you're new to
the show and don't realize this no it is
cuz if you think your body is destroying
itself creating your illness causing
your illness attacking yourself
attacking your nervous system whatever
it's attacking if you think that's what
it's
doing that's not going to help you
heal it's going to kick you down a
notch because it's wrong to begin with
it's not even
correct and and if it was correct it
still would it still would kick you down
a notch of course it would but it's not
correct it's not even real we're going
to talk about why and how it's not real
and everything else it's important to
know the autoimmune great mistake I call
it the first great
mistake of all time the first great
mistake and you'll see in the thyroid
healing Book You'll see there's a whole
bunch of great mistakes that I that I
write about that I clarify that I
Rectify that I clarify very important to
know that very important to know because
when you read them you'll see oh my God
this is a great mistake oh my God I
understand now it's important to not for
your healing because great mistakes that
are corrupted that Ru the gamma in the
health field these great mistakes they
stop people from healing they stop
people from healing darn right that's
what they do and if you don't know that
that's not good you got to know that
it's important to know that it's really
important to know that an autoimmune the
autoimmune Theory the great mistake of
autoimmune because it was created
because the medical industry doesn't
know what causes pots
it doesn't know what causes lupus it
doesn't know what causes Ms it doesn't
know what causes Hashimoto we know what
causes those but the thyroid healing
book I I put it right out there so the
world will change so that you take the
book and you tell somebody about it so
that you bump into somebody like look
you got to get this book because you
need to know what's going on or here
borrow my book so somebody else
learns and because because the the body
attacking itself isn't it isn't a a
fact what's fact about it it's it's a
misguided theory that became law that
part is fact but it attacking the body
isn't fact and it messes people up
especially with pots that's why I have
to talk about it a little bit the
autoimmune
theory was being funded in the 1950s
this is when women were filing in like
an army like like file filing in like
soldiers that just came out of a war
zone a war zone they were just fatigued
sick couldn't function
migraines central nervous system
disorders brain fog confusion filing in
left and right into doctor's offices out
of nowhere out of nowhere ever before
like never before in history in fact
never before in history filing in
filing
in and they were filing into the
doctor's offices with complaints that
were all mystery and because these women
were mostly in their 40s and their 50s
and they were all on that edge of the
hormone change and everything doctors
said well Dr said first of all there was
never ever changes in people before this
in 1945 1950 before this women who went
through the change felt better they felt
better they had more libido they had
less headaches
they had less problems they had more
energy they could exercise more they
felt better they lost weight all these
different things happened like that were
all good then by 1945 it
changed because there was a something
was simultaneously happening during the
change it had nothing to do with the
change there was a virus that incubated
and had a shelf life of 40 years before
it came out and it was a virus the early
epan bars of 1900 1890 1892 1889 1901
1905 five that virus that exploded got
into people got into women very early
on and men but it got into women caused
the first
eruption of sickness that's never before
been seen first eruption of chronic
illness symptoms what did the medical
industry do they they try to sell it as
a hormone thing of course they did
because they were already developing
hormones perfect
timing sinister Sinister timing that's
right but you know what else developed
what else developed was yeah was a study
you know looking for things so there
were some good-hearted doctors and they
were looking for things they're looking
well they didn't think it was hormonal
so there was some good doctors that said
well you know we don't think this is
hormone related they couldn't find
anything they couldn't find a pathogen
cuz they didn't know where to look and
they didn't know how to look because
because they couldn't find a pathogen
they didn't understand pathogens they
still don't to this day why am I talking
about this because I'm talking about
pots pathogens pathogens yes we're going
to talk about pathogens related to
pots so these doctors were looking for
pathogens couldn't find any but what
they found was an
antibody which they claimed as an auto
antibod the body creating an auto
antibody to attack itself causing
symptoms in the
1950s it got funded and became law it
was a theory there was no evidence
whatsoever that an antibody or a auto
antibody attacks anything in fact they
couldn't even see that it wasn't even
humanly possible or
visible what a screw up of all time it
became law it was funded just like that
so back to the beginning of the show
it's like that thing I say at the very
beginning the information here is pure
it wasn't backed by trusted old
grandfathered medical funding laws with
strings attached in panels of
influencers and thing tanks it wasn't
it's not that information it's pure and
it's clean and that's why you're here
because you're going to learn about pots
today so what happened was the theory of
autoimmune was
birthed and it became law and no one
ever went against it no one ever went
against it that just assumed it was it
and then people who go to medical school
they just get taught whatever and they
out they go they just process them and
stamp them out out you go out you go
okay you just graduated okay you're good
do your internship okay out you go yep
that's the theories okay here's all the
bum theories here you go that's how it
was
done still
is right when it comes down to these but
there's good stuff they learn in medical
school but they you know where they
learn most of their stuff they learn it
in practice when they wake up and they
go to their first practice day and
they're like who why is it so different
what are all these problems people have
they didn't even talk about this in
medical school wait a minute what what's
going on and they got to learn you got
to go in the trenches and you got to
learn and the best medical doctors in
the world do that and then they and then
decide they want to get interested in
something and they go into a specialized
field and they dive in and they can't
get funding because the funding is
corrupted because no one wants to know
about what's really causing pots no one
wants to know what's really causing pot
so these doctors can't get these
immunologists can't get funding but if
they want to play around with genes and
autoimmune theories they could get all
the funding they want because that's the
belief in the law if they want to play
around with jeans you know why doctors
are going into jeans so much it's the
only thing they can get funded for how
about that how about them apples how
about them
apples yeah it's important to
know someone said to me the other day
you've been doing a lot of ranting and
raving about stuff I said yeah it's
critical for people to know because
you're going to blame theirselves they
going to blame their health they're
going to blame their bodies breaking
down they're going to blame it on Old
theories and they're going to get hurt
and this person said you know what I
didn't think about it that way I go
that's because you're not suffering with
pots you're not suffering with something
that's why you're feeling fine you go to
the golf course you play golf you feel
fine okay you got a little high blood
pressure you got a little bit of
cholesterol doctors don't know why I
know why it's because your a liver
problem that they can't
find but you got nothing going on so you
just go play golf and you're okay but so
you don't you don't really like my
ranting and
raving cuz you know you're not in a bed
and then when you get up from your bed
you almost fall over and pass out and
you get dizzy in Vertigo and you can't
exercise and you can't go and live the
life that you want to live right now
and you okay that's not your life so you
don't have pots you're not dealing with
something you go out in the golf course
you go drive your car around all day
long you feel
fine yeah yeah you take your high blood
pressure medicine medicine because you
don't want to quit eating all the wrong
foods and you don't want to quit you
know putting too much fat inside your
liver causing High you know high fat fat
liver that's developing a pre pre pre-
fatty liver doctors can't find yet and
that's what's causing your high
cholesterol and high blood pressure you
don't want to eat better but you know
you're doing great so you don't want to
hear my ranting and
raving but my ranting and raving what it
is what it is it's things that you have
to understand you need to know a little
history so you don't just you don't
destroy yourself with the bad Theory and
not heal one of the ways you heal from
pots just like you heal from other
misguided labeled
illnesses one of the ways you heal is
knowing what's wrong obviously and
what's causing it the other thing is
what to do for
it but also shed away and dispel the
bull the lies the theories that were
grandfathered in that get in your way
and that's the other piece of it darn
right that's the other piece of it I'm
talking about you better believe
it
and and this is critical to know so here
we are we're going to get down to the
bottom what causes dis
atomia disauto atomia
sorry we're going to get down to the
bottom of a postural orthostatic tacac
cardia syndrome we going to get to the
bottom of that dis autonomia comes in
different shapes and sizes it comes in
different shapes and sizes different
different levels of disautonomia
different L levels of it different um
different you extreme to mild the whole
B you might be suffering with it and
you're listening to the
show you might be
suffering and and and struggling with it
it's a struggle for a lot of people it's
really difficult I mean you know you
know and if you you might have a loved
one with it you got to take care of your
daughter with
it and it hits a lot of young women why
why does it hit a lot of young
women why it does hits men too but hits
a lot of young women there's a reason
for that there's a reason for that there
a lot of Epstein bars I said it Epstein
bars that get into women really young
when they're young causing early monos
that sometimes aren't even detected
mostly aren't even detected they go to
another phase in another stage and they
end up getting the nervous
system inflamed and it gets diagnosed as
pots they get all the symptoms
pots except Steen bar the one thing I
have to Grant the one thing I have to
Grant the medical
industry with is they actually think
there's a correlation with a viral issue
they don't know what kind of virus they
don't have a clue they don't know what
they're talking about as far as what
looking for a virus they don't know any
of that but I have to give them credit
we're credit is due they affiliated
gilon Beret sometimes
lupus and a viral
condition into it a little bit the big
mistake is it's not the viral
issue they hang their hat on they hang
their hat on the body attacking itself
they're big nasty mistake negligent
Mistake by accident through default of
being taught this by the system by the
industry their their mistake is the
great mistake of autoimmune in the body
attacking itself pots is not the body
attacking itself but they do have one
thing they caught on to is
viral there is a viral correlation they
don't know how what why and I got to
give them respect and I got to give
them thankfulness and honor and and and
glory to that glory be because they
they're figuring that
out but here's what's happening you got
a virus that's causing the problem
that's attacking the body can I tell you
the difference between knowing your
body's not attacking itself versus a
virus is let me tell you the
difference you got control back because
we can stomp on a virus we can kick the
crap out of a virus over time we can
beat a virus down over time we can beat
it we can beat it we can do things like
take lemon bomb which is
Melissa and Melissa doesn't take any
crap at
all Melissa can kick the life out of a
virus because she doesn't take it she
does take any crap doesn't take any heat
from anybody you can't mess with her
that's one powerful herb one powerful
herb right there you take lemon bomb
long enough and you just slowly squash
and beat down that bully and beat down
that bully and beat it down until it's
down to the ground because when you know
you got a bug causing the problem and
you know your body is protecting you and
not hurting you you start turning around
your pots over time darn right that's
the power of it I had somebody say to me
I had a practitioner say
practitioners said to me a while back I
remember it I'll never forget it they
said okay so you're saying you're saying
Anthony that it's not the body attacking
itself you're saying it's a virus
attacking the body wasn't that going to
scare the
person I
[Laughter]
said I said I'm going to tell you right
now let's pretend you're the patient and
and this practitioner doctor said okay
I'll pretend I'm the patient I said come
on serious seriously put your hat on put
your thinking cap on become that patient
become that patient that you see and he
said all right all right I'm doing it
I'm doing it I'm the patient I got these
symptoms I said let's do more than that
you got these symptoms which you can't
feel because you don't really have them
I said to the doctor I said but you got
these symptoms but you got other things
going on you can't work anymore so you
got to give up your practice he goes oh
that's that that sucks that's what he
said to me he said that word so I'm not
trying to say nasty words he just said
that word and I said yeah you lost your
practice cuz you can't work anymore and
he said all right okay okay that that
that hurts I go that hurts huh you don't
have any you don't have any symptoms I
said but that hurts doesn't it and it
goes yeah yeah that hurts I gu okay and
then then people they kind of think
you're a hypercondriac too so you got to
you got to f file for disability and you
got people that think you're
hypercondriac you got to lean on other
family members for help and financial
help and everything else and to get food
and all kinds of other stuff and he's
thinking about all these things and he
goes oh my God I go yeah this stuff
hurts doesn't it goes yeah it hurts I'm
really feeling it I'm just I feel for
the people that go through serious pots
and other the other illnesses and that
have labels just like that lupus and so
forth and everything and he goes he goes
all right I said no I I want you to take
this seriously cuz I am and I'm not
liking this I go yeah I know I go and
then you have a relationship the
relationship is really difficult because
you feel like you know you feel you feel
kind of torn the relationship you're in
because you just you just don't feel
good all the time and you feel bad for
your partner and so he goes oh my
God like yeah people go through this
this is real and he goes okay okay okay
let's get to the point I said okay well
here's the point okay just say I'm the
doctor doctor of course I'm not a doctor
I never went to medical school everybody
knows that I'm not trying to be a doctor
everybody knows that everybody knows
that I'm the medical medium I that's
that's just what I am whatever and um I
go you know I go I'm the doctor he goes
okay you're the doctor Dr Anthony I go
yeah just pretend I'm a doctor he goes
okay I'm pretending okay I'm here and
and I said Jack he said what I said Jack
I have to tell you something and he said
what I said your body is destroying
itself he goes it is I go yeah it's
attacking itself he goes and he stopped
he was shocked for a second he goes oh
wait a minute oh okay no I know what
you're doing I see what you're doing I
go no Jack Jack you got all these
symptoms you got pots you got all these
problems and your body's attacking
itself and he goes all right yeah okay
yeah okay I got you and that's what I
tell people because that's autoimmune
it's autoimmune I go yeah I go it's a
attacking
itself I go how does that feel he goes
you know what he said it it doesn't feel
good I get it I know what you're trying
to do I said all right Jack Jack Jack
Jack listen your body's not attacking
itself I need to tell you the truth he
goes all right what's the truth I go you
have a virus that's been in your system
a long time and that's what's causing
problems and inflaming and attacking the
body he goes all right he goes is there
anything we can do go of course there is
why don't we go after the virus he goes
you know I got some good ideas to go
after a virus too I am a doctor I'm not
100% alternative but I'm partly
alternative and I'm mostly you know an
MD regular conventional because but I
got some ideas I go yeah we're going to
go after the virus he goes that sounds
amazing he goes his life changed his
life changed he wasn't sick we were just
we were playing the
roles he his life changed from that then
he went back and he started looking up
the law of the autoimmune law and then
he was on the computer and then he was
sending me all this stuff and all these
old documents of how it was just a
theory and how they don't even know what
that auto antibod is doing and
antibodies doing they have no clue and
he's sending me all this data on how it
falls through your hands like
sand excuse
me I just drank a whole thing of celery
juice and you know he was liter Al like
it fell through his fingers like
sand and he couldn't believe
it he couldn't believe it it was just an
old grandfathered funded idea that was a
concept that's poisonous and from there
on out
everybody he doesn't say the body's
attacking
itself never he never ever tells his
patients they file in he never tells
them their body's attacked backing
itself ever
again that's right that's
right instead he goes after
pathogens he goes after pathogens and he
doesn't mess around and one of his best
friends now is Melissa the girl that
really doesn't take any crap and she
knows how to kickbox big time and she
kicks kickbox
is Epstein bar right down to the ground
and that's what lemon balm does that's
what Melissa does and you
know and that's just one thing that's
just one thing we can do the point is is
it matters so let's talk about pots
let's talk about the whole thing this
autot Tomia is um is is another theory
circulation to the nerve
circulation um slow vein draw going up
the body um you get up too fast your
heart
races but what's really happening what's
really happening it's a viral condition
100% it's a viral condition that sits
inside the liver it's a viral condition
that's been sitting in the liver for a
long time producing producing a
tremendous amount of
neurotoxins
neurotoxins pots is a neurot sorry is a
neurotoxin
disorder chronic research with chronic
illness chronic illness in science
research medical research and science
research with chronic illness is so far
behind it's it's it can make someone
depressed you know someone said to me do
you ever get depressed I said yeah I do
I do get depressed they're like what the
Anthony William gets depressed what are
you talking about yeah I get depressed
all the time they're like you need to do
something for that I go yeah I do and
they go what I go I talk about what gets
me
depressed in my books and in in in the
radio shows I said what are you talking
about I said yeah it's a fact that
medical science medical research is so
far behind on chronic illness it's the
most depressing thing I've ever
seen it's set it saddens me deep in the
heart deep in the soul every single
day and it's it's it's it's a it's it's
that part I have to bear of it of
knowing how behind it is it's so behind
it's maddening it's so Antiquity it's
maddening it's so Antiquity it's so
antique that just the newest experts
today putting out books meaning whether
it's on thyroid or anything else it's
it's it's so sad to even see it and
that's the newest in what year are we in
where still the body attacking itself
stuff it's still misinformation it's
still theories it's still it's
unbelievable everything and that that I
mean and anything in any Arena and you
know natural medicine is great it's just
chronic illness it's still behind it's
depressing
suppressing
so with when it comes down to pots what
it is it's a neurotoxic disorder it's
100% neurotoxic related neurotoxins
caused by the Epstein bar the Epstein
bar one of the varieties that causes
pots one of the varieties out of the 60
plus v varieties that causes pots that
is the cause it's Epstein bar and
Epstein bar sits in the liver produces a
tremendous amount of neurotoxin that
neurotoxin floats around it swells up
the nerves so you can't exercise it
swells up the nerves so you get the
brain fog it swells up the nerves so you
can't focus it swells up the nerves so
the heart Works harder the liver pushes
the blood out of the out through the
liver up to the heart making it as clean
as it can but when there's too many
neurotoxins flooding the flooding the
bloodstream the neurotoxins go into the
heart and they Tire the
heart they Tire the heart heart
palpitations are part of this a Gunk
collects a debris collects in the mitro
valve and other valves creating
different varieties of eutopic heartbeat
ectopic heartbeat and Pals heart palps
it's an Epstein bar related
symptom the one thing I love though one
thing that gives me hope is they at
least realize that gilon Beret could
have something even to do with pots
thank the Lord because
and uh I say that because gilon ber is
an Epstein bar illness gilon Bret is
Epstein bar it's an Epstein bar illness
so someday and my hopes and dreams and
in my heart they're just going to
override the
stupidity and it's going to come
together and we're going to know finally
what's wrong with people so we can help
more people than I can help every day
I'm just one guy what if everybody knew
the truth
things that change and maybe we could
beat out the funding machine and all the
nasty stuff behind it all we can beat
out that bureaucracy that's involved in
the medical worlds both alternative and
conventional that just you know and the
reason why they want us and you know
what they'll just throw pots right into
genetics big time if your Epstein bar
came from your parents or if you're
sensitive to Epstein bars because you
happen to have a lot of mercury in your
system and then your daughter you know
has the Epstein bar and and she has the
Mercury and she develops a symptom
similar to poan St
genetic that's an evil evil machine I
talk about that more and more each day
more and more each day the problem is
here's what's hard when you put out the
truth and people already invest their
lives into the nontruth they're going to
fight for it they're going to fight for
it tooth and nail they're going to fight
for it man because they just put their
work into it so when this guy
put his work in the funding and all the
funding goes into some autoimmune theory
that that like I said this Dr Guy know
that Jack said that that's even a theory
that they they never even proved the
auto antibody the auto
antibody is an antibod actually produced
by the immune system to only go after
one thing the virus never the body the
virus so go it's geared only go after
the Epstein bar and only the Epstein bar
but it needs help it needs more than
just that we we need the herbs we need
the nutrients we need the foods to go
after the Epstein bar to we need to do a
whole campaign against it so back to
what I was saying when you invest into a
nontruth like autoimmune or you write
books about genes because you're
invested and you're you're interested in
these these topics so you write a whole
book on it and you invest your life into
it it's you can't just turn that off and
go with the truth you can't just say oh
okay wait a minute all right all right
you know I can't you can't put on the
brakes that's one of the problems so
when nontruth is out there to such a
saturation and everybody's got all their
money invested in their time their books
you name it about autoimmune books left
and right and it's all wrong information
it's all autoimmune books by the piles
out there just buy the truckloads and
they invest in that you think they're
going to just shut that
down and and and and admit that they
made a mistake even if they learn the
truth no and this is why nothing gets
done and we just can't get there but you
know the truth and we're going to work
on that we're going to work with that so
here's the
deal the deal is with pots it's about
going after the Epstein bar virus you
can recover I've recovered lots of
people and what I mean lots of people
over the decades hundreds of people with
pots recovered them so they actually had
their life back so they can get out of
bed and say oh my God I'm actually going
to walk five miles can you believe that
I'm going to go walk 5 miles and I I'm
going to feed myself in between it all
and I'm going to be able to do what I
need to do I'm going to go take a shower
people with pots can't shower it means
it's they just they they lost a day they
lost a day in their life cuz they
showered that means they're dizzy
they're worn out that means they're back
in bed because of a
shower they lost a day can you imagine
right I'm sure some some of you probably
do imagine because you're going through
it you lose a day and the reason why is
cuz when that water hits your head and
nobody knows this this is another this
is another truth that just doesn't exist
out there I mean nobody knows it
nobody's nobody knows that Spirit knows
and here's what happens when the water
hits the head all the nerve endings all
the nerves that go up around the skull
on the outside of the brain they all hit
the inside of the skull there all these
different nerve endings those nerve
endings are filled with neurotoxins from
the have being so viral so long having
the epine bar in your system so long and
those neurotoxins
those
neurotoxins they inflame those nerves
those nerves become inflamed from the
virus from the viral nerv neurotoxins
it's not the body attacking itself so
when you have water hitting your head
and it's hitting it's hitting those
nerves and the vertigo could come the
dizziness the imbalance you get out of
the shower you're like oh my God let me
just get to my my couch or my bed that
was it for the day you're lucky two
hours later you can get you're so weak
you can get up that's that's that's a
version of
pots the reason why the heartbeat raises
when you get off the ground or you get
off the bed and your heart jumps up 30
beats per minute just from standing up
or 40 beats first of all the heart jumps
up for everybody no matter who it is if
you are laying down and you get up your
heart's going to jump up a little bit
anyway but for people with pots it jumps
up a lot higher the reason why is the
heart's working harder because the
amount of saturation of poison in the
liver going into into the bloodstream
going into the nerves the nerves being
inflamed and nerves being inflamed and
the neurotoxins inflaming everything it
it makes it hard the heart heart has to
work harder and then you take pots
somebody with pots and you put them on
an asinine trendy dumb diet I know I say
you know probably not the best thing
sometimes yeah I told Spirit when I was
young that I can't
change I'm going to say stupid things
once in a while spirit said that's okay
as long as you got the information right
spirit said that's all right I said I'm
also going to you know be
sarcastic and spirit said that's okay if
that's what you have to do Anthony to
deal with this and survive this gift
that's what you have to do this gift for
the people to survive this information
that's coming through I said yeah I'm
going to be sarcastic and I'm not going
to be always you know I don't know my
words aren't going to be always so
perfect I'm not a scholar I didn't go to
Harvard and
but what happens is when you put
somebody with
pots on a diet that's
trending that's trying to fix everything
out there it's not a good thing if you
what I'm talking about a diet that's
trending a low carb diet a low carb diet
now with pots you don't want to use a
carb that could feed a virus so you
don't want to use chocolate cake to feed
a virus you know lard inside the cake
you got lard in there you got wheat
gluten you got preservatives you got
something in the fondant on the top of
the cake fondant made out of
preservatives dyes and
chemicals natural flavorings unnatural
flavorings preservatives you name it got
fondant on there you know I I was
actually over a family member's house
and they had one of those shows on one
of those cake making shows so I think
there's a couple of them out there they
had one of these cake making shows on
there and I was watching it they were
you know they're playing around with
tons and tons of fondant you know and
they're doing I don't even know if
that's what you call it and they're just
you know they're just doing all this
kind of stuff in it and and and and I
said to Spirit I said hey here's your
favorite spirit says I hate when you
watch these shows and I said and spirit
do say hate spirit says a different word
and that I'm just voicing out what what
the word equates
to and spirit said yeah and and you know
because of what's in those fondant
what's in the and then what's in the
cake because can feed it can feed a
virus like Epstein bar nobody knows that
nobody even to this day nobody knows
viruses eat anything it's only coming
from Spirit and if you hear it out there
it came from me one way or another and
you know and the thing it's always
important to know that so you don't get
sidetracked onto a whole different place
of of information that's also got
misinformation just riddled in it and
anyway the chocolate cake is a carb bad
carb it's got bad fat in there also bad
carbohydrates in there there but these
low carb diets are a nightmare for
somebody with pots because people with
pots their adrenals are tired their
nervous system is is in desperate need
of glucose which is sugar which is
carbs their liver can't handle fats
their liver can't handle fats I'm
telling you right now
secrets and and you put them on a high
fat diet and take away all their carbs
it's like if it's bad for somebody with
pots of course the good part about that
diet is you're taking away the bad
processed foods the fried foods you're
taking away cheap sugar you're taking
away stuff like that which does matter
for somebody with pots but you also
leave them without what they do need to
heal even if they experience better
symptoms at first in order to heal
completely they're going to have to have
a carb this is one of the great mistakes
of alternative medicine right now is the
low carb Trend train which is absolutely
Ely ridiculously
wrong so it's important to know this
that means fruit is an answer to someone
recovering with pots fruit is antiviral
antibacterial yes it is whether anybody
likes it or not it is and I'm going to
tell you now not just fruit but you got
the leafy greens but that's not a carb I
get that but the starchy vegetables are
okay too a little bit of potato that's
right sweet potatoes that's right um
sweet potatoes winter squash once again
that's right and these are really
important for that and you got to keep
the animal protein down somebody with
pots you got to minimize it it's even
good even to go off it completely with
somebody with pots but you got to
minimize it you do if you really like it
you still got to minimize it you got to
make because you got to make room for
these other foods that are antiviral not
because I don't like animal protein for
somebody it's because you want to get
rid of these foods that are antiviral
and you never want to eat eggs with pots
and you never want to eat bacon with
pots you never want to eat dairy
products with pots these feed viruses
the bacon is so high in fat that it'll
just wreak havoc but the the eggs the
dairy products will feed Epstein bar the
virus that causes
pots it's not just that it's the weak
gluten feeds epin bar it's too much corn
feeds Epstein bar which is bad with p
thoughts or any kind of disautonomia any
kind of
disautonomia
seriously and that's important to know
so we got to be careful we got to be
careful with the
foods one of the greatest things for
pots ever is celery juice now it's not a
calorie so if you drink a celery and
don't have any calories man you're going
to hit the wall but when you drink
celery the mineral salts count for
repairing the central nervous system in
the brain for somebody with pots I got
to finish my celery juice right here and
I got it in my
hand and um I've been bringing my celery
juice to the show a lot more a lot more
meaning in my hand like a fresh glass of
it I drink it in the morning I don't do
the show in the morning I do the show
obviously my time you know my time in
the uh afternoon over here in the US and
you know and and but I'm asking my
assistant can I have some juice now for
the show and um because it reminds me of
how powerful it is too you know what it
does the mineral salts subgroups of
mineral salts undiscovered by research
and science because instead of putting
instead of putting $500 million in
figuring out what's why celery is a
miracle cure you take $500 million and
stick it into genes once more so you can
insult people in their hereditary
traits it's amazing it's amazing
sick but you know the celery reboots the
central nervous system but it's not
enough you need to have a sugar you need
to have glucose see the nervous system
demands glucose which is guess what a
carbohydrate that's right that's right
that's right for those high-fat trending
you know people out there high fat high
fat high fat I get it I get it listen I
get it if someone who eats a regular
standard American diet filled with all
kinds of garbage pizza and everything
else they want to lose weight they want
to start getting in shape they don't
really have any illnesses that are ser
ious or or confining them so they go to
they go to a a grand scheme of a high
fat trending diet they get rid of their
processed food they hop on the treadmill
and they start working out every day
they think they found the holy Grill I
get it and I'm happy for them because I
want them to quit the processed food in
the garbage but if they developed a
health problem or had a real health
problem behind it all that's not going
to be the answer in the end they got to
lower the animal fat lower the high
protein down the fat down in the diet
and raise the fruits and vegetables on
the other end of it and that's what
what's happening you'll see some of the
trending higher fat diets being more
vegetables and they allow you more
berries and more green apples because
they're starting to realize that people
are getting a little better the more of
that you add in and then when you add in
most of it and you're getting majority
of it all the fruits and the vegetables
and the green juices and lots lots of
those carbs that everybody's afraid of
you heal from neurological
disautonomia conditions like pots and so
forth and celery juice combined with the
fruit like banana can actually heal
somebody with pots banana kills Epstein
bar and it restores the nervous system
with somebody with pots so then you can
actually heal
them but Banana's taken away all the
trending diets take it away out of
ignorance out of ignorance due to a
mistake that was made about 10 or 11
years ago from a popular popular
practitioner Doctor Who wanted to sell
his fruit in a pill so told everybody to
stay away from the fruit itself that
it's cancer
causing and it got through the it got
through the web it got through the
system but so I've recovered people with
pots to a full capacity where they're
exercising no symptoms whatsoever ever
again by putting them on Epstein anti
antivirals Epstein bar anti-in bar viral
herbs supplements and foods and got them
on the celery juices and banana
smoothies every
day and got them enough calories through
that lowered their fats where they only
had a few seeds or or a little bit of
avocado here and there a little bit of
coconut oil and have recovered them from
pots completely so they can then do what
they want down the road if they want to
bring in more this if they want to bring
in more salmon they can bring in more
salmon they want to eat something else
they can eat it and they get their life
back they knock their Epstein bar all
the way down to the ground and in book
one I got the Epstein bar chapter in
there about Epstein bar and the thyroid
healing I really talk about Epstein bar
like I've never done in the history of
any I've ever
done and
um yeah so it's important to know that
you got to yeah you keep the fats low
you got to do the antivirals what do you
need to do little bit of zinc pots is a
tricky thing when someone gets so weak
they can't handle taking anything or
even eating things sometimes because it
takes energy takes neurological energy
to digest neurological energy to eat
neurological energy to take any
supplements I understand take a little
bit by a little bit if you got a good
practitioner get some help but you need
to be on the right kind of B12 you need
to be on the right kind of
methylfolate just go to the directory
that medical medium.com if you don't
know and you can you can show your
practitioner the
supplements that are just listed there
so you know the right ones to take I
don't sell them they're just just there
for you to know and you can do a little
bit of the B12 a little bit of the
methola but lysine I've seen lysine be a
miracle for people with pots lysine L
lysine LS i n e I've seen it be a
miracle for people so L scene I've seen
a little bit of licorice frot be
life-changing for some people with pots
the lemon bomb that's Melissa I've seen
that really be life-changing seen a
little bit of cat's claw be life
changing of people with pots cuz it goes
after epine bar vitamin C if all else
and you can't do anything and you got
pots and you got a condition of some
kind based around it if you can just do
vitamin C and only vitamin C I'll be
happy because vitamin C gets rid of the
Epstein bar over time takes time if
you've been in it too long it's okay
you're going to get better we can get
you better I've had people couldn't even
get out of their bed their heart would
go crazy they get out of the bed they
could barely get enough energy to get to
theed bathroom and pee and then come
back to
bed and have recovered them Spirit
recovered them with the
information I can't give myself credit
because it's it's it's Spirit bottom
line I have to always remember that one
time I uh claimed it was all me Spirit
taught me a good lesson in the garden I
told you that story it's in book one had
the neighbor over neighbor was telling
me how he doesn't understand how I knew
what was wrong with the wife his wife
how she couldn't walk for years and
spirit said it was arsenic in their
water and their well water and nobody
knew
and and and he tested and the well water
had some arsenic in it and and then we
did Heavy Metal detox to pull out the
Arsenic and over time she walked for the
first time in a long long long time and
I was in the garden bragging he said how
do you know these answers how is it
possible how do you know you're not even
a doctor I said I know everything
there's nothing I don't know I know
everything and never forget it never
ever forget it I'll always be right I'm
right everybody's wrong and never forget
it I took two steps I stepped on a rake
like a one of those ho rake things in
the in the garden it flipped up backward
smacked me in the face and it knocked me
clean out I was out cold 100% knocked
out I didn't even have time to see stars
that's how fast I was knocked out as I
was waking up my neighbor was standing
over me he was just looking at me I had
some onions still in my hand that was
pulling out of the garden and Spirit
then said remember this I'm always right
you're always wrong I'm always right
you're always wrong and spirit knows I'm
not always wrong I got my own ideas and
I got my own thoughts and I could be
right about something but Spirit was
making it clear when it comes down to
this this part in my life spirit's
always right and I was wrong and I T I
would learned the lesson so I got to
give Spirit credit cuz I don't want to
step on another rake in the garden cuz I
do like the garden whenever I get it
chance once in a blue moon um so listen
you take it one day at a time with pots
you have to have faith number one the
faith and the hope and the faith and the
hope and you also have to have the truth
that your body's not attacking itself
you got a bug in you it's been in there
for a while big deal meaning your
symptoms are a big deal I get it but the
bug isn't you not we knock it down one
thing I learned from Spirit right from
the beginning and I'm going to tell you
right now one thing I learned from
Spirit right from the beginning is when
you know what's wrong inside your body
your body kicks it up a notch when you
know it's a bug your immune system knows
it's a bug as well it already knows it's
a bug your immune system that's why it
even creates an antibody to go after the
bug not to go after you to harm you or
to hurt you ever but it knows it's B but
when it knows you know too and the two
things combine the soul the heart of
someone and the spirit of someone
combines with the knowledge of knowing
it's a virus you're going to squash and
your body's squashing guess what happen
guess what happens come on guess I know
some of you are but not everybody is
yeah you win the battle you destroy the
virus you knock it down your immune
system gets even stronger that's what
happens all of that and the
above and uh and never forget
it never forget it so cucumber juice is
great too you can do that look do teas
herbal teas very helpful for for pots
any kind of herbal tea you like you can
do a little bit of golden seal for pots
periodically I do like that that's not
bad at all you can do that um and and
and that's fine and but what I like what
I like for pots is anything onion if you
can handle any kind of onion any kind of
like a chive or a little bit of a
scallion very helpful for pots um eating
every 45 minutes for pots is critical
meaning s something eating something
snacking on something every 45 minutes
whether it's a banana and a celery stick
whether it's a handful of nuts and seeds
and a celery stick whether it's an apple
apple and a handful of seeds whether
it's Apple handful of hemp seeds whether
it's an apple and a cucumber cucumber
slices and apple whether it's you know
juice if you can find some juice
whatever it is eating every 45 minutes
to an hour snacking and grazing is
critical for pots critical sitting up
when you can sit get up when you can
walk when you can it's never going to be
perfect at the beginning take walks one
of the reasons it gets harder with pots
is because it's like kind of it's very
similar to other kinds of nervous system
disorders because it's it's neurological
to Epstein bar related what happens is
you lose muscle and your body's not used
to doing anything because you were
inhibited prohibited from doing
anything so excuse me so you were
prohibited from doing it
anything and what happened was you know
it it doesn't help it kind of works
against you and that's perfectly fine
because if you do too much you're going
to pay for it I get it you're not going
to be able to do good function you're
going to be wiped out taking a show
wipes you out stand when you can when
you can walk a little bit when you can
each day it helps retrain the body while
you're healing if you can't do it you do
a little bit at a time I I knew somebody
all they could do is just draw draw they
could sit up for a half hour and draw
and then they had to go back down
absolutely but that sitting up and
drawing for half an hour made a huge
difference it was the beginning of their
healing process and when you add
everything else into it a little bit by
little you heal and you move
forward so yeah so that's where we are
with pots we're coming to the end of the
show check out the Instagram you know
with everybody's stories check it out
and uh Facebook I'm on there fooling
around all the time on Instagram and I
think somebody said somebody said on
Facebook one day they said is this
really you and I I typed back yeah it's
me with a heart you know oh oh here's
what's really funny somebody said this
can't be Anthony a guy said this can't
be Anthony on Facebook because Anthony
would never do hearts what are you
kidding I love doing the hearts I love
the hearts heart emojis I love those the
red ones love those I love those and you
know so on Facebook that's what I do I
do the heart emojis I do the happy faces
do other things too I'm on there I'm in
there if you see I don't answer a really
serious in depth question it's because I
can't answer it because it would take I
can't do a whole thesis some some people
they ask me a question I'm like wow I
know what the answer is to that question
but it's going to take probably about 10
minutes 15 minutes and it's going to
probably take like a page two three
pages of writing and um that's hard to
do that's hard to do so just know that
I'm there though and I try to answer
questions that I can that seem to be
brief enough um it's hard for me to do a
a very very long you know a very long
whole thing a thesis on an illness or a
big chapter on an illness it's hard so I
try to give you directions like go to
this go to this radio show go to this
whatever I try to do things like that so
listen just know that I care I stand
behind you 100% when I was given this
gift I thought it was for me but it was
originally intended for you 100% Spirit
taught me that the gift that was given
to me is for
you that's the whole point I got your
back I'll keep on watching your back
we're going to do the next show and the
next show we're going to have a good
time remember half the battle knowing
what's wrong the other half is knowing
what to do the rest will come together
and then shedding away the great
mistakes get the thyroid healing book as
soon as you can because I actually did a
chapter on each great mistake the
important ones right now that you need
to know to shed away so you can heal
100% and eventually get there or heal or
improve or get somewhere with your
health anything that's critical and
important important so make sure you get
that the book and you check that out so
uh have a good night and uh take care
and I'll see you soon I love you guys a
bunch and um bless your
heart take care do some celery juice
okay bye
now