hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and as decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who is 10 20 30 years to
wait for answers the information here on
the show the only show that doesn't come
from
agenda driven groups so agendas you know
like interest groups and medical
interest groups and medical funding with
strings attached bot researched
researched with the thumb on the scale
all the time lobbyist medical lobbyist
internal Kickbacks persuaded belief
systems private panels of influencers
Kickbacks payoffs trendy traps in
alternative medicine that's right is
your mind blown in alternative medicine
that stuff is in yep that's right times
have changed it wasn't like that years
ago years ago years ago alternative
medicine was s sa L it was saintly I
mean don't get me wrong the doctors and
practitioners doing alternative medicine
are saintly they're
saintly absolutely I call them saints I
call them saints chiropractors
naturopaths K you know kinesiologists um
you know uh acupuncture acupuncture you
know acupuncturists Oriental medicine
doctors uh massage therapists um I mean
if I forget any don't that doesn't mean
I don't like the group um of course you
know all of them all of them cranial
sacral therapists are really great
everybody everybody's working
everybody's doing stuff does anybody
forget Homeopathy right homeopaths right
I love it love it functional medicine
doctors you know people that are joining
forces you name it they're Saints and
medical doctors I feel are Saints too um
yeah yeah absolutely medical doctors of
all kinds uh pediatricians you name it
Specialists Saints and um but but the
industries aren't St Lee they're not St
Lee that's the whole point that that's
what we have to understand here and
alternative medicine used to be the
industry first of all the regular
medical industry the conventional Med
medical industry was never saintly and
going all the way back hundreds of years
it was never saintly it was never a pure
place um the doctors are the doctors are
let's not let's not mess that that up
let's not mess up that because that's
the doctors are I mean honestly like
angels and and you know and what happens
is that you know alternative medicine
though the the medicine the the the
industry was
saintly it was always pure in the
1800s the late 1800s the herbalists the
naturopaths that developed the nature
medicine nature
medicine you know that was that was
definitely and in the 1920s it was still
cleaning it was still 30s 1940s 50 60s
and then we got into the day the day
we're into now today today's age and I'm
sorry but alternative medicine the
industry has is slightly tainted because
these groups that I just mentioned are
all kind of in there so information
getting out there isn't always as like
it was back in the 1950s 40s 30s in
alternative
medicine and you know and always
remember that you
know when it comes down to the
practitioner itself that's different you
know that's different than the
practitioner the Healer the doctor
they're they're Saints to me every
naturopath you go and visit any
naturopath you go and visit just
remember there's probably hundreds of a
hundred easy hundred if not hundreds of
naturopaths that went to prison for no
reason just for waking up in the
morning putting on their their white
coat and helping people not because of
anything that harm or anything to happen
to people because the conventional
industry
ostracized and and privately went after
all the naturopaths in the old days all
the chiropractors in the old days when
medicine you know wanted to dominate
when conventional medicine wanted to
dominate and own it all and they didn't
like the they didn't like the nature
medicine rising up in the late 1800s and
early
1900s I mean there those doctors were
hung they were hung by their feet and
beaten and and you just need to know
that so when you go to your natural path
just you need respect and
honor where we've come from and how far
we've come it's like
unbelievable and you go to your
chiropractor you need to respect that
you need respect if you go to your
healer you need to respect that and if
you go to your conventional doctor you
need to respect that too of
course it wasn't wasn't the doctor's
faults it was the industry it was the
industry it was the industry I know you
know I know I'm going on a tangent about
this but it's important to know to have
that kind of respect when you go and see
your your healer when you go to see your
naturopath now I have naturopaths tell
me they say you know I'm I'm doing
everything I can I'm doing my best
helping out my
patients and he gets this Ang angry
patient that just you know that just is
is is upset about something and he
doesn't like the the naturopath or
something like that the naturopath is
like I don't know what to do I'm I'm
doing everything I can I care I got
compassion I want the person
better we have to have respect to for
our our doctors or naturopaths whatever
kind they are functional or not or
functional whatever you know natural
everything we have to be because man it
wasn't easy it wasn't easy to we you
know that old thing where when I was
when I was a kid you know grandfather be
like when when I was a kid I had to walk
9 and 1 half miles in the snow 9 and 1/2
miles in the snow to go to school to The
Little
Schoolhouse 9 and2 miles in the snow 0
de and all I had was these knitted
little gloves with holes in them and all
I had was these old boots and they got
filled with water and slush and Frozen
and I got frostbite every time I went to
school all winter long and I dropped my
books in the snow and the ice
and you know well that's that's what
it's like with what happened the history
of what happened so when you see your
naturopath like I'm glad you're here can
I shake your hand today I'm glad I know
I'm consumed with all my stuff I'm
consumed with as a patient I'm consumed
with my pain and my my my Agony and my
symptoms and my lyme disease and my you
know Epstein bar and all my stuff and
I'm consumed with it my fatigue and I
know so but can I shake your your hand
today just thank you for being here
thank you for being
here um all right let's we're talking
about we're talking about acid reflux
today acid reflux that's what we're
talking about I mean right I mean it's
interesting I think that's interesting
asset reflux I think it's
interesting asset reflux what's
interesting about it we're going to talk
about it we're going to cover
information that nobody knows nobody
knows that's right right nobody knows I
wake up every morning I say the spirit
okay what else what else are you going
to tell me that nobody knows that I
don't even know what else are you going
to tell me spirit says well you know we
I keep you around as long as we can keep
you alive aw we got to keep you alive aw
as long as we can because I got things
to tell you for years and years and
years to come and nobody knows I said
all right all right I'm okay putting on
my pants all right putting on my shirt
time to go time to go to work let's get
it down let's get it down let's get it
in these books and let's get it down you
should check out the thyroid book
thyroid healing to check it out did you
order it did you order that book oh oh
my God you're going to learn more about
the thyroid and it's more than just the
thyroid you're going to learn more about
chronic illness than I think you've ever
known seriously if you don't have that
book you're going to love it you I
didn't let you down I I know I didn't
let you down I also wake up in the
morning say did I let him down or I go
to bed at night did I let anybody down
did I let him down did I let him down
did I get everything I need to be in
that book for this book I know I'm
working on the next one but I did get
did I get everything I needed on this
one and um it's important and if you
haven't gotten medical medium book one I
I don't know what to say I don't know
what to say why why haven't you gotten
it oh all right all right all right all
right acid reflux we're going back into
it we're going to town on it so what is
acid reflux a bunch of acid building up
in the stomach burning your esophagus
causing esophageal spasm going up
causing Scar Tissue causing waxing and
waning wear its hair at the bottom of
the esophagus down there by that lip
down there I mean causing other things
that create you know other names for
illnesses the scar tissue growing and
things like that I mean what is acid
reflux I mean it's a heartburn the hell
is heartburn the hell is it is the heart
really burning no probably not it just
burns up there no definitely not but it
just burns up there in that area right
feels like it's up in the chest like
whoa am I having a heart problem you I
feel out of burning what's this pain
feels like gas pains gas pains are very
strange I'm going to tell you something
about gas pains gas pains can do the
darnest stuff
they can you can get a gas pain by your
neck by your neck you can get a gas pain
up in your shoulder way up
high seriously get gas pain up there
how's that possible no see nobody knew
this nobody knew
this how's it possible to get a gas pane
way up there at top of your
shoulder you know and how's it possible
to get a gas pain way up high like that
up your neck
I said that already I know I know thanks
for by the way I wanted to thank you
guys for something I want to thanks for
just bearing with me bearing with my
silliness my
sarcasm my um annoying annoyance
whatever that is and um and just thank
you for seriously thank you for just
bearing with me thank you for just
listening it's an honor to have you here
it's an honor to be with you and I just
want to say thank you for I never say
thank you enough to you guys there's no
way I don't don't say thank you enough I
I really don't think so anyway so how do
you get a gas pain up in your neck like
whoa a cramp up there a pain and where's
it coming
from that's how strange the the
gastrointestinal system is that's how
strange that's how Elusive and and
mysterious our intestinal tract is by
the way your intestinal tract is
mysterious you get a gas pain up
high absolutely you can get a gas bubble
the top of your colon say on the left
side left side of your colon your left
your left arm right at the top there
right in the corner of your
colon you know right there at the you
know that spot there left side right in
the rib area right around the spleen you
can get that you can get that gas bubble
there and it can cause pain all the way
up to the top of your neck that's why
that's why that's how weird the nervous
system works the frenic nerves p h r n i
c a very sensitive nerve responsible for
so many different problems with
neurological problems well anyway that
frenic
nerve um sitting there by the ribs there
rides up rides up through the chest goes
up through the left side of the chest
and there's a frenic nerve on the right
side top of that colon on the right side
rides up the right right side of your
chest and that frenic nerve there two
frenic
nerves right they're hypers sensitive
they could be really hypers sensitive in
a lot of people you get gastritis and a
gas bubble gets trapped up in that Cor
corner on each corner of the colon not
the small intestinal tract the colon on
each Corner left side corner right side
corner underneath the ribs right there
and man you got like Sparky going on
like like oh my God like it could it
could spark up those
nerves cause a spasm cause pain going
all the way up sharp pain jagg of pain
all the way up all the way up the chest
through the kind of heart region the
other side too uh right up through the
neck give you cramp get give you kind of
cramped up that's just a gas bubble
could be tiny too if it's a toxic gas
bubble if it's a toxic gas bubble could
be tiny I got celery juice with me now I
have celery juice with me a lot but I
have celery juice with me purposely on
this show today CU this is acid reflux
show I got celery juice here why would I
have celery juice for acid reflux who
who who cares who would know what what
like what does that have what does that
do what does celery juice do it does all
lot I can't wait to tell
you so there's a lot of mystery in our
gastrointestinal tract there's a lot of
lot of mystery and all that on every
level you know so mysterious that nobody
even knows what happens to food once it
enters the stomach I say that a lot I'm
going to say it again and if you're
brand new to the show I'm going to tell
you something right now right
now 500 years from now from this day
they're still not going to know what
happens to food when it enters the
stomach they're still not going to know
no one's going to know there's going to
be theories and more theories the enzyme
factor is a theory yes enzymes exist
they do play a role but what they do is
theoretical nobody knows what they do
nobody knows what they
do seriously even when we have a theory
of they break down food they cause you
know they cause a gastric breakdown of
food they help assist in digestion
Theory because we don't know there's no
way to measure it no way to weigh it
nobody can measure it nobody God knows
what happens inside the stomach when
food's dropped in there God
knows yeah God and if you don't believe
in God it's fine the universe universe
knows okay and and it's going to be like
that for 500 years 700 years a th000
years 1500 years 2,000 years and if we
haven't blown this planet to nothing by
then if we haven't blown it into Smither
and Ash and boulders burning Boulders
and we hav't literally nuked it and
wiped it clean by then if we haven't
burned it to just a just a ball of
nothingness by then we're still not
going to know what drops inside our
stomach we're still not going to know
and don't think I Haven an asked Spirit
when the world does end or if it does at
all I have many times and I do have
secrets about if the world is if it's
not when if it is or if it's never or I
have secrets to all that I am going to
do a book on that down the road but
there's just too much medical
information in the way there's too much
medical information there's too much
chronic illness and it needs to be
addressed and I just I got to push off
the fun stuff I have to push off the fun
stuff I have to push it away push it
away
so the deal is the deal is that um
because we don't know what happens to
food in the stomach we're not going to
know what foods really do help and
change what's happening down in there
like when you put celery juice in the
stomach and I'm going to take a little
sip I feel my I feel my acid reflux
already going
away I don't have any acid reflux but if
I
did it would start fixing
it what is acid reflux let's go into
that let's go into
that it doesn't mean I took another sip
of celery juice it doesn't mean I can't
get acid re flux if I'm under tremendous
stress someday like I'm always under
stress
anyway deadlines and stuff like that I
got to get the information out to you I
got to get all the blog blog articles
out to you I got to get all these radio
shows done I got to get the books done I
got to you know I got to be of help and
service any way I can in between it all
in any way
possible
and and doesn't mean you know I can't
get some stress and and and something
also changed chemist chemistry-wise in
the gut comes some stress happening
creating acid reflux I'm I don't want to
get it I hope I don't get it but if I do
which I could be susceptible to that
darn right someone said to me well
you're you're you know you're Anthony
William you you can't be susceptible to
anything well if I was not human if I
was if it was not human then sure I'm
human I'm just like you yeah I hear a
voice perfectly clear but if I don't
take care of myself you know some it's
Anything Could Happen
but I don't take care of
myself I mean it's just way the ball
rolls the way the ball rolls
so celery juice okay so what what what
is the bad what is this acid what is
this acid
reflux acid reflux aets those aets
aren't gastric acids those aren't
gastric acids news flash they're not
gastric
acid so when you get acid reflux and
it's always
happening news flash those aren't the
glands in the stomach creating gastric
acid and hydrochloric acid that's not
what that is that is an hydrochloric
acid burns like hell goes up the
esophagus Burns everything goes into
your throat they kind of spit it
out some people do some people don't it
can make you
cough cough and cough and coughing all
night all night long coughing on some
mucus too I've seen people
suffer I've seen people suffer or it's
just you Burns and it's rising up Burns
and it rises up Burns and it rises up
Burns and it rises up that's not gastric
acid would you believe
it but you know back to chronic chronic
illness research back to how it's so
deficient and anemic back to how you
know they can go to the best clinics the
best doctors it's not their fault
believe me it's not their fault they
just don't
know that's not gastric
acid it's an acid it's an acid produced
by something it's an acid produced
produced by poison inside the liver but
but but more than that it's an acid
produced by bacteria by
bacteria I'll say it again it's an acid
produced by bacteria you got acid reflux
there's a good
chance it's not reflux because you got a
kink and we're going to talk about that
if you have something going on that's
visible if you got something going on
like a
kink and that's what I love about
medicine too is you you get an MRI you
could get a because I can't be
everywhere to get people MRIs through
spirit I can't I tried that I tried that
for
decades and I still can't get every I
can't reach everybody I can't get
everybody done can't get the millions of
people that need help with me
personally can't do so I got to do it
through the books the
books the series the medical medium
series if you got one of them make sure
you get them all because they're all
interconnected they're all
interconnected it's
important they're they're they're there
for a reason and then here's the deal
here's the
deal if you don't have a kink if you
don't have something busted
inside I don't mean busted but you you
know what I mean you don't have because
what happens is we get wonky in there
internally we get first of all we get
hernas we get high anal hernas that
actually can cause a reflux that can
cause non bacteria related acid reflux
so if everything rolls out there's no
hiatal
hernia there's no
hernia in a weird place that maybe not
just Hiatal but there's all kinds of
hernas you can get in weird
places and uh and believe me I'm not I'm
not immune to a hernia I mean I could
pick up something stupid and heavy and
pop something out just like the best of
anybody can it's another thing too we
got to always be careful with that um we
got to be careful we get pushed into
workouts by the way that's just that's
just LED I I know I'm taking this off
track a little but not not necessarily
because if I can avoid a hernia with you
that's amazing um and then hey I could
avoid possible acid reflex then there
you go but if you're doing workouts or
you get sold into a workout thing don't
push it too hard a lot of a lot of
trainers they don't realize in so many
different ways they have people pick up
tires and stuff like that you just you
just don't do that that's so so silly
you just don't do that if you're a
trainer do offering that just stop that
stop that stop that whole thing or
you're like taking sledgehammers you
give them a sledgehammer you have them
hit a tire with it just don't do that I
can't tell you how many people get
hernas from that crap you don't even
know because everybody's doing that and
they're all getting hernas I know I know
so I hear about it all the time don't be
picking up giant tractor tires with
everything you got and pushing it over
there's nothing to prove there don't do
it do do responsible exercising okay you
do you know resistance you could do
weights you could do resistance you can
jog you can run anything you like to do
but you just just don't do things like
picking up gigantic tractor tires and
pushing them over in in in in the
workout place stuff like that oh be
careful be
careful um okay so let's go back let's
go back sorry guys let's go back into
this if you don't have a kink if you
don't have a hernia if you don't have a
blockage and those are easy to see for
MRIs and CAT scans and stuff like that
and ultrasounds
and and you know you go to the doctor
and you swallow that barium you swallow
that you know that glow-in-the-dark
material and then you go and get an
x-ray whatever it is if nothing's like
that is going on and you got the acid
reflux and you got some bacteria
Brewing could be undiagnosed bacteria of
course that's how it works I mean
hpylori can cause it but hpylori becomes
it's diagnosable sometimes and sometimes
it's not it's very elusive it it evades
andc escapes tests it tests all the time
hpylori is a
bacteria interesting Critter but
bacteria
produces an
acid produces an
acid that will trick out and mimic an
acid similar to gastric acid which will
trick out the doctor physician thinking
that this is just a tremendous amount of
acid regardless and not really know what
kind and what kind and
where bacterial acids that's what it is
that's what that acid is it's constantly
causing problems it's constantly going
up the esophagus it's const constantly
burning everything that's bacterial
acid heartburn a lot of times is a gas
bubble it's a gas
bubble and and not acid so a lot of
different cases of heartburn someone
describes like I got a heartburn I got
heartburn that you know I can't tell you
how many people they came to me and
they're like I got heartburn in the old
days like that's that's gastritis and
like maybe it is yeah it is and then
there's heartburn world oh okay now it's
burning up here okay no that that's
burning yeah no that's heartburn that's
heartburn that's that's that's that's
you know that's acid
reflux and
um so what happens is you got bacterial
acid that's not gland produced gland
produced gastric acid and hydrochloric
acid in the
stomach do you know what happens when
you're getting acid reflux from Bad acid
bacterial produced
acid do you know what
happens it means you have no
hydrochloric acid left or very little
because if you did have enough
hydrochloric acid it would be destroying
the bacteria so you wouldn't have acid
reflux yep
yep yep yes
I'm trying not to say that's right
that's
right that's what's going on there
what's going on is if you got the bad
acids and you got that acid reflux and
that's bacterial produced
reflux that's what that acid is it's
it's acids produced by
bacteria if that's going on that means
you don't have any toone to very little
hydrochloric acid but that might not be
diagnosed properly at a practitioner's
office both conventional or alternative
or functional because they think you're
filled with acid so they're thinking you
got tons of hydrochloric acid or they're
think you got tons of gastric acid
no you got acid in your gastric system
but it's coming from
bacteria it doesn't mean taking
antibiotics either it doesn't mean you
got to jump on the antibiotic thing to
start killing off bacteria because that
will just create more bacteria and more
bacterial
acid I know so there's so many people
with h pyloric diagnosed hpor did they
do the antibiotics for hpor and then
they have the worst aser reflux for the
next 10 years I see that all the time I
saw that all the
time and you know we so and I'm not
against antibiotics they're great when
when you need them for certain things I
mean there's there's things you need
them for there's no doubt about
it but we could be cautious when we use
them and how we use
them that's important to
know sip of celery juice again so here's
the deal
here's the
deal if we have that kind of problem
going on that means our hydrochloric
acid is gone so we have to build their
hydrochloric acid back up and it doesn't
mean taking HCL capsules or HCL pills
hydrochloric acid pills we need to build
it back up and that's really important
very important we need to change the
diet around too because there's
something in our diet that's feeding
bacteria whatever that is could be wheat
and gluten could be corn could be weak
gluten could be Dairy could be eggs eggs
feeds bacteria like no other you know
what even if you have your best chicken
eggs from your best friend's
backyard which is the ones to eat if
you're going to eat an egg even if you
have the BET and the the the yolk is
nice and dark it's not like Factory
chicken eggs the yolk is nice and
dark delicious
egg right I mean a coyote with would
love that
egg a fox would love that egg my God be
a fox's dream to get that kind of
egg and you know even even those kinds
of eggs which you know which are the
nutritious ones they still will feed a
bacteria and it's not the egg's fault
it's not the chicken's fault it's not
your fault I said this before actually
recently that the medical industry not
the alternative medical industry the
conventional medical industry ruined
eggs for us they ruined it as a food
they ruined it as a food
source because they used it in the lab
to feed and raise bacteria for a hundred
years now and that's what they did and
they used it in the labs to feed viruses
and bacteria to play around with bugs
and pathogens they used it as a food
source I don't care what anybody tells
me they're wrong if they say no that's
not true and they're wrong if they say
that bugs don't eat anything they're
wrong wrong wrong I don't care if you're
a scientist saying it I don't care
you're wrong I don't know I don't know
why you don't have the right information
I don't know how that happened I don't
know if it wasn't just taught to you or
what it wasn't told to you or your
supervisor didn't tell you at a lab or
something whatever happened or there
wasn't a study on it that you could read
but you're wrong bugs feed off of things
food food food like we feed off of food
and eggs are one of them and it's not
that this would have never happened if
they didn't use egg they used corn too
corn they ruined corn on
us corn is delicious totally screwed
that up the medical industry ruined that
on us and then they grow all the GMO
medical corn on top of it and they
ruined it even more and they ruined it
it was corn eggs and even some Dairy was
used to Corn eggs mostly but these are
the things that feed the bugs they feed
the bugs so you know so diet matters so
that's important to know so we got to
build up the hydrochloric acid we got to
clean up the liver a little bit cuz the
liver is not functioning that great if
we have acid
reflux that's going to be a big part of
it too might have a fatty liver
developing pre fatty liver might be
pre-diabetic for a lot of people with
acid reflux they have this pre
pre-diabetes not pre-diabetes pre
pre-diabetes and then guess what guess
what there's pre pre pre-diabetes
interesting huh pre pre pre-diabetes PPP
diabetes that's right nobody knows that
either
and that is happening in people so
that's going on with their liver and
that's what's happening it's all liver
caused and then you got you know weak
digestion because if the liver is
getting beaten down then the liver
doesn't produce the strong bile so that
means your stomach has to
overproduce hydrochloric acid your your
stomach has to overproduce hydrochloric
acid and wears it out wears the stomach
right out exhausts the stomach's gastric
ability to produce the proper kind of
acids because the liver's so burdened
and and so constantly having to spit out
all that bile to digest tons of protein
and tons of fat in everybody's diet the
liver weakens and breaking down breaking
down it breaks down is breaking a word
it could be and you know here's the
thing with all that
happening and then what goes wrong is
the stomach the HCL starts to then
diminish starts to WAN starts to fall
back
the glands in the stomach can't produce
the stomach can't produce anymore and if
you're not drinking celery juice and
you're not taking care of yourself you
can't even build your stomach acids back
up you can't even clean the liver up and
build it back up and people go on even
higher protein diets and they wear their
liver down more even if things gotten
better in their health in other ways
they're still breaking their liver down
they're still setting themselves up for
the worst hydrochloric acid deficiency
and they're setting themselves up for
down the road WEA the time they're in
their 50s or 30s or 80s or whatever
whatever it's going to be they're going
to have that acid reflux kick up because
that bacteria is going to grow bacteria
is going to grow and when it grows
produces bad acid your Hydrochloric
acid's too weak you don't have enough
hydrochloric acid to kill off that
bacteria and remember that hydrochloric
acid blend is a seven blend that's that
only Spirit knows and release that
information I talked about that in the
first book I'm going to talk about it
again in the next
book
and
so and what happens is that seven blend
three of that seven could be diminishing
so then practitioner doesn't even know
somebody's hydrochloric acid is even
low so we have to build up the HCL to
kill off the bacteria so the overgrowth
doesn't happen and I'm not just talking
about sibo small intestinal tract you
know bacterial overgrowth I'm talking
about bacteria that's just not that's
just in general sitting in the
dadum
and then sitting in the in this in the
stomach pouch the bottom of the pouch
there's this well there a well at the
bottom of the
pouch stomach pouch it's a little
well okay and there's this little spot
too that dips
down and and stuff collects in that
little spot it collects there right
there that's where bacteria loves to
grow right in that little spot do you
ever go to the beach and it's low tide
and there's water in this one little
spot but yet there's no water in that
spot that's how what it's like there's a
little spot in the bottom of the
stomach little spot little little patch
in there it's almostly you know a little
spot and right there at the bottom of
the corner there it's you know little
spot lots of things can grow in there
bacteria loves to grow there especially
if somebody's got a weak hydrochloric
acid the bacteria just spawns and grows
right there and when it does it spawns
and creates acid not hydrochloric acid
no not the seven blend no not other
factors in gastric acid from glands
no it spawns and grows an ugly mutant
foreign acid that mimics acid stomach
acid hydrocor whatever mimics all the
acids and that's what it does and that's
the bacteria right there that creates
that and sure you can have sibo too
which we did in the sibo show which is
all strep a cacus that's defin and that
strep can get in there too and strep in
the small intestinal tract if it's high
enough can create a lot of acid
absolutely and that can spew up into
dadum and push up even further into the
stomach and somebody could have a lot of
acid going
on
yeah it's all it's it's all fixable
though it's all fixable it's all we can
all work on it we can all get it better
we can all do things about it we can all
get it in the right place we can get rid
of acid reflux but what I like about
doing the show on acid reflux is you
know you're covering a few things you
want to get the liver a little bit
better you want to knock down
bacteria right talked about kinks in the
gut kinks in the intestinal tract I
hernas different kind of her we're
covering a lot of
ground so it's not just this thing where
okay I got acid reflux let me find a
pill for it let's see if
aw has you know has some kind of pill
the magical natural pill because I got
this acid reflex no it's more than that
it's the information because it empowers
you strengthens you and then we'll do
more than just a magic pill we'll do
some different foods so first of all
what not to eat just go to my what not
to
eats you know and in in all the
books and uh that's really a big deal
that's a big deal for getting rid of
acid reflux if your animal protein lover
lower reduce it because you're just
going to max out your liver with all
that animal fat and you're going to
force your liver to produce extra bile
salts to break down that animal fat and
you're going to weaken your hydrochloric
acid because your stomach's going to
have to overproduce hydrochloric acid
once again and just exhaust itself kind
of like adrenals when adrenals get tired
and all of a sudden you get a bad
experience it happens to you and then
your adrenals don't have anything else
to spit out so they just shoot out
whatever they got left and they're
really exhausted you know like when a a
girlfriend breaks up with a boyfriend or
a boyfriend breaks up with a girlfriend
or or anything anything that happens in
Life or you walked into the office one
day and someone who's trying to steal
your job
is talk to the boss and set you up for a
fall whatever I've I've seen it all I
mean it's just it's it's just this world
is is this world is
crazy this world is crazy and you know
next thing you know
it next thing you know it you got you
got you know you got you got hit the
adrenals got hit adrenals got weakened
well it's the same thing with the
intestinal tract you dropped too much
animal protein down too much animal
protein too much animal fat down in
there and same thing if you're a vegan
you drop too much nut fat too much
coconut oil oh my God I saw somebody eat
like a half a jar of coconut oil and
they gave themselves pancreatitis and
they were a vegan and they gave
themselves pancreatitis this matter if
they were a vegan or a meat eater if
they're a meat eater and drank a whole
bottle of coconut oil yeah it's possible
they can give themselves pancreatitis
too and just for the record meat eaters
get more pancreatitis than any
vegetarian or vegan has ever gotten in
the history of medicine I'm going to say
that not cuz I'm standing up for vegans
right now and I'm trying to knock down
animal protein people that's not it at
all I'm just telling you right now
pancreatitis is from animal fats from
pork more people get pancreatitis from
pork than anything else anything else
Bak bacon ham pork roast whatever that
is pork chops uh ribs more people get
pancreatitis in cases of pancreatitis
from all that pork and all that and the
burgers and all that stuff even if it's
grass-fed burgers and all that butter on
their lobster whatever it is more people
get pancreatitis that way than vegans do
eating too many nuts or a half a jar of
coconut oil I've seen meat eaters drink
a whole bottle of olive oil thinking
they're going to flush out gallbladder
and liver which you can't and it doesn't
work and they do that and they give
themselves pancreatitis because they
also had a steak the night before I've
also seen vegans drop a whole bottle of
olive oil down and give themselves
pancreatitis and then the night before
they had you know a big nut pie so it's
like seriously like you know whatever
but the bottom line is
um you know we got to reduce that animal
fat if you're in the Animal product
world and we we just got to reduce the
fats so that the liver is not
overburdened if you want your acid
reflux to go away you want you don't
want that liver overburdened I'm telling
you right now if it's overburdened
what's going to happen is it's going to
overproduce bile it's going to try to
make bile so damn strong it's going to
weaken the liver it's going to push out
so much bile and when that happens when
that happens the the liver weakens and
then what happens the stomach over
produces the hydrochloric acid it burns
itself out Burns it out like a
star Burns it out like a rock star when
rock stars get burnt
out and I'm you know I've known a lot of
rock stars over the years I've helped
out a lot of rock stars over the years
and they get all burnt out you know and
so it's it's and that's what happens
your hydrochloric acid they you know it
burns out and so you want to kind of
restore that so how do we store that
what do we what do we do what are we
trying to do well you know I I
antibacterials don't I mean they we
shouldn't disc guard them natural ones
herbal ones a little bit of golden seal
once in a while will lower a bacterial
load in the gut a little bit of golden
seal once in a while little bit of eona
golden seal it does reduce that little
bit of Elderberry syrup once in a while
cats CLW a little bit of cats claw here
and there if you ever want you can lower
and reduce that bacterial stuff a little
bit of oregano oil oregano oil time tea
time time water time tea the stuff I
always promote in the books like
life-changing foods you can you can
lower you can
lower the uh bacterial
load lemon balm lowers the bacterial
load why does peppermint tea help with
digestion nobody knows you know I was
talking to an herbalist a while back too
a well-known one and they were just like
I love what you do I love what you do I
I I I learn a lot even as an herbalist
you
know he go let me ask he goes let me ask
you this question Anthony let me asked
this gu I'm like what and he's a really
nice guy really nice guy and he said he
said peppermint tea peppermint tea you
know it it it works really good with
that bacteria in the stomach I'm I'm
guessing because you're telling me the
bacteria is the acid reflux so the
peppermint tea it
helps with the acid reflux how's that
possible that is it that I go because
it's actually knocking down bacteria he
says no but herbalists know that that's
not one of the antibacterials peppermint
te herbalists know that that's not
really one of the main that's not an
antiviral antibacterial herb I go yes it
is it's an antibacterial herb nobody
knows that it's like I'll be darned I'll
be darned I'm going to be talking about
that on my lectures that's what he
said and you know he's helped a lot of
people he's helped a lot of people I
mean just in his whole career being an
herbalist he's helped a lot of people I
love herbalists you know the thing is is
this is that is that is because that
peppermint alone peppermint tea does
diminish bacteria certain bacteria in
the in the gut meaning in the top in the
stomach in there so that one helps the
lemon bomb like I said before peppermint
oregano oil capsules we know that one
does right olive leaf olive leaf
capsules olive leaf tinure of the right
kind make sure you go to you know if
you're going to get a supplement go to
medicalmedium.com I don't sell the
supplement but I but I we created with a
lot of time and energy exhausting and a
lot of money involved to create this we
created a um um a directory for you so
that you can know what is the right one
cuz we kept on hearing we we didn't do
it for a long time but we kept on
hearing from so many people like I got
this supplement and I'm not getting
result because that supplement is
actually garbage or I got this
supplement and it just burned my throat
yeah because it was loaded with citric
acid or whatever it is so finally we had
to create a
directory and that's what we did and uh
and someone said to me why don't you
start selling supplements so you can pay
for some of this stuff I said I'm not
going to sell supplements I'm not I'm
not going to do it I just I can't I
can't something in me I just can't do it
I said there supplement companies they
sell them I don't want to do that I'm
about getting people what they need the
information they need I got to stay the
Integrity has to stay
there you know um so here's the deal
here's the deal see there's all these
different things you can take and use to
knock down that bacteria which is really
helpful and and we can do
that and that you know licorice root all
on it all on its own actually does that
too licorice root knocks down some
bacteria in fact licorice
root is like a miracle for acid reflux
because it's knocking down so much
bacteria and also viruses in the
intestinal tract but it's knocking down
so much bacteria licorice root licorice
tea licorice peppermint tea is a godsend
for acid reflux why it's knocking down
bacteria you
guys bacteria that creates the bad acid
and if you've heard that before it came
from me originally I'm saying that
because I have to keep it straight with
with with honoring spirit that put the
information out there A lot of times for
years I put a lot of information out
there I taught a lot of people through
spirit's wisdom not through my wisdom
spirit's wisdom and stuff did get around
and if you say oh I think I heard that
before well trust me that one came from
spirit I have to always honor spirit
Spirit doesn't care Spirit doesn't care
I just I care about honoring spirit I
just I have that kind of respect for
spirit so you know here's the
deal um celery juice now we can do the
food celery juice is critical aloe vera
water aloe vera gel you can scoop it out
the leaf and eat it if you want I
remember I was traveling one time and I
told my assistant I said get me an aloe
vera leaf get me an aloe vera leaf
and she was like okay I'll get you one
and she got me a bunch of them and you
know and I was around a bunch of people
at the time I was around a bunch of
people people that weren't you know they
knew who I was but they they weren't
used to being with
me and everybody was you know getting
their food out we were having lunch and
all that and I grabbed a leaf an Al of
leaf I cracked it open and I took a
spoon I sliced it open so it was It was
kind of open where I I then took a spoon
and I divided at the flaps and I just
scraped inside the leaf and I just ate
the whole Alo leaf that was my lunch
that day and everybody looked at me like
like even though they knew of course and
they know and everything else and there
that's the whole point I mean they knew
if they're me you know with me they knew
but they were still so surprised I'm
like why are you surprised they're like
what I just never seen anybody do that
for lunch I go yeah I'm doing that
because the flu it's flu season right
now it's flu season people have
pneumonia out there it's flu season it's
traveling I was hopping on a plane on
and off planes or whatever and you know
what this Alo does it kills bacteria and
it kills viruses so if I happen to
accidentally ingest or inhale a a neuro
virus which is a flu virus which is a
stomach flu virus and it gets on my
tongue and it goes down my throat and
gets to my stomach and fires up the
worst stomach flu ever I got some aloe
sitting down all around in there and
that's bacterial and viral
killing that's why people's acid reflux
drops
substantially
substantially when you use aloe water or
aloe
juice yeah it's another secret weapon
but what's the goal what's the goal it's
killing off the
bacteria that's the goal the other goal
is getting the liver better getting this
hydrochloric acid stronger and that's
where the Cel juice comes up with the
with the the hidden subgroup mineral
salts that rebuild your hydrochloric
acid
that rebuild and restore glands in the
stomach that produce HCL in the seven
blend the mystery 7 blend nobody to this
day knows about except for
us so and that that right there is why
you do celery juice you lower the fat in
the diet I can't say it enough I've been
saying it more and more because people
are like hey hey medical medium I'm on
this new diet it's low carb it's high
protein I'm like no that's not what I
said I said you know the low fat they go
no there's no fat in it I go what are
you eating they a chicken chicken twice
a day um in the morning I had two eggs I
got this great holistic practitioner
they got me on two eggs in the morning
they got me sugar-free I'm on chicken in
the afternoon I'm on Chicken in for
dinner I'm on a few of these these
vegetables I'm eating a salad I said
it's all fat all your calories are 100%
fat coming from all that oh no no the
chicken's not fried I go no that's not
it the chicken's loaded with fat inside
the flesh no no it's a chicken breast no
I I know that no no there's no skin on
it no that's the fat is in the chicken
breast that's the calorie so you can
function so you can walk and talk you're
getting a calory CU if you took that fat
out you'd fall to the ground and you
would
dissolve and and they be oh I go yeah
that's still a liver problem your your
your your acid reflux is getting a
little better cuz you took away all the
chocolate cake that was feeding the
bacteria too with all that crap in the
chocolate cake you took away some of the
processed food which was feeding
bacteria but you're still burdening your
liver with fat and when you do that your
acid reflux will come back it will stay
there it will come back it'll come back
on a rainy day and bites you in the butt
I almost said something else bites you
in
the yeah in the
butt and it's going to get you you can't
do that so do the do the chicken once at
the end of the day day make sure your
lunch has a little bit of avocado which
is a little better it's a little better
of a fat a lot better of a fat a little
bit of avocado maybe put some different
fruit in your salad maybe some more
cucumbers lots of tomatoes oh my
practitioner says night shades no no no
no no no no you have tomatoes they have
its own V they have it it has its own
vitamin C that could save somebody's
immune
system that's what the tomato has you
can't mess with it get an heirloom
tomato get whatever get a good tomato
don't get a bad tomato don't eat you
know and and so yeah you get tomatoes
and cucumbers on those salads you get
some potato Believe It or Not steamed
some potato you have a fruit smoothie in
the morning now fruit I was told to stay
away from fruit my practitioner told me
to stay away from fruit it's bad n your
practitioner is only telling you that
because he heard it from somebody else
he heard it from somewhere else and I
know where the original Source came 11
years ago from a doctor that brought it
into the industry because it was to sell
his fruit pills he didn't want people
eating fruit I remember the day it
happened and it's just spread like
wildfire and now clinics even say in the
health world oh fruit's bad it'll feed
cancer no it doesn't fruit doesn't feed
cancer corn syrup feeds cancer processed
table sugar feeds cancer beet meaning
GMO beet sugar feeds cancer beet
processed GMO sugar
um Dairy feeds cancer eggs feed cancer
like no tomorrow they grow fibroids they
grow tumors they grow benign tumors
benign cysts they grow eggs grow tumors
of all kinds cancers of all kinds feed
everything under the sun as eggs they
kept cancer alive in Labs back in the
1950s by putting eggs in with them
Christ but yet no but you know they all
be like oh fruit will feed cancer it
doesn't feed cancer you know what fruit
does it kills bacteria that causes acid
reflux you just can't eat a fruit
pie on top of a steak the body fights
itself cuz the fruit just wants to do
right while the steak wants to just do
wrong not saying you can quit steak if
you're a steak eater I'm just saying I
can't put the two together the fruit is
a bacterial
killer and it wants to rush through your
stomach through your dadum through your
intestinal tract it wants to rush
through it wants to push through it
wants to drive all the way through and
it wants to kill everything shouldn't be
there and save everything that should be
there so when I hear misinformation it
drives me insane it drives me insane I
mean when you hear the misinformation
that's been out there and rampant and
took off like lightning it's one of the
reasons why you guys I had to stop doing
personal
consultations I had to stop to write the
Books because it got so bad Spirit
stopped me spirit said look you're
working on people day in and day out in
the offices you're working on people day
in day out you work 24/7 you're doing
seven days a week but we got an
emergency out there and I said what what
now I like what I'm
doing me and many others and
practitioners and doctors and all this
we help people hand in hand foot by foot
we help them right here and spirit said
you got to stop right now you have to
get this information out with everything
you can it's all going in the wrong
direction out there spirit said it's
getting bad it's including fruits being
picked on God given created fruit
natural fruit to actually stop Cancers
and stop disease and Save your liver and
save your stomach and save your body and
save your brain antioxidants and stop
you from aging all inside fruits it's
getting bad Anthony and you got to get
to it you got to start taking my
information and writing it down in books
you have to stop the trendy traps that
are F that are produced by agenda driven
monsters out there in the world Monster
Machines I mean out there in the world
and that's why that's what happened I'm
just giving it to you
straight all right take one day at a
time you know one day at a time
and we can get there so listen I hope I
gave you at least some information on
acid reflux I hope I gave you at least
some you know just no I care I'm with
you 100% you know when I was given this
gift when I was a child I you like I
said and I told you before I thought it
was for me I was convinced eventually
since you know my parents would be like
he was giving this gift he's gifted was
iing I had it all in my head that I was
gifted and spirit said this isn't your
gift I didn't give you this gift for you
this is for the people you're going to
have help this is a gift to them and
that's what spirit said and I was like I
had a hard time with that for a little
while I was like oh crap then what is
this whole thing you know as a kid like
what do I got why do I got to do this
just want to ride my skateboard I just
want to you know I just want to play
basball anyway I love you dearly take
one day at a time bless you bless you I
care about you greatly all right Forge
ahead heal Forge ahead and keep on
healing for me
bye-bye