hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now and when
it comes down to psoriasis eczema cystic
acne yes it's information ahead of
what's out there now and I mean that in
fact today I'm exposing first time ever
in history
I'm making public what causes psoriasis
what causes eczema so this is where it's
found right here you're not going to
hear it on the internet you're not going
to see it on the internet you're not
going to see it in any book out there
written anywhere you're not going to
find it anywhere or at the doctor's
office it's going to be here today and
so if you're tuned in stay tuned in
because you need to know this
information it's really important and
I've always said who has 10 or 20 or 30
years to wait for
answers and you know so some of the
stuff I'm going to be talking about
today is going to take 30 years for
medical research and medical science to
find out what causes psoriasis what
causes eczema so um do you have 30 years
to wait for that to get those answers to
know to be there at the head of the time
and that's why I'm here that's the whole
point of why I'm here so you can have
that information and why we're doing
this show um so yeah life is precious
there's no time to spare let's get
started in healing now today's show is
about healing acne azema and psoriasis
we're going to try to get those all done
I'm going to do I'm going to do my best
it's a lot it's a lot of stuff I might
have I might have thrown too much into
this one but I'm going to try to cover
what I can especially exoman psoriasis
and then acne we'll do what we can and
um well we can always do another show if
I don't get enough done on it but we'll
see we might be able to pull it off the
real causes of this chronic skin
condition and it's all still largely
unknown in medical community ities in
fact what's really funny you look into
it and you'll see it is unknown so so
many millions of people are suffering
with no clear answers in this episode I
will reveal what's really behind skin
conditions like exim unisis and even
acne and how you can begin to heal
pretty cool um so you know remember to
go to my website too I wanted to mention
that medicalmedium.com where you can
sign up for my free healing p path
resource source which I've dedicated
hundreds of hours into creating so you
could have the foundational tools and
information you need to start healing
now I made sure to make it completely
free so everyone would have access to
this information right away just go to
my website and sign up today for that
instant access a little bit about me if
you don't know who I am or you know
what's happening here and this is your
first time you know with the show and
everything else started at the age four
heard a voice perfectly clear just like
someone standing in the room it's
different it's not like channeling it's
not like that kind of thing this is like
you hearing your friend talk in real
time in your ear so that's how it works
and because of that it's been this thing
where I can get the information for
people no matter what I'm doing doesn't
matter if I'm tired exhausted doesn't
matter if I'm run down doesn't matter if
I you know if if I'm upset or if I'm sad
about something spirit will provide the
information at all times nonstop no
matter who's around me what's going on
and because of that that medical
information that's ahead of ahead of
medical research and medical Sciences
time I've been able to give that
information since a child to people I've
dedicated my entire life doing this
literally doing this and only this my
entire life and so that's a little bit
about me I've helped tens of thousands
of people heal find the information they
need like we're doing on this show so
let's go let's go into the eimos
psoriasis let's start talking about that
right now because I know we have to get
this done um so if we're going to talk
about Xmen psoriasis though I have to
tell you something first of all fasten
your seat bels get ready for this
because I'm releasing some serious
information in this show this is really
serious if we're going to talk about
Xmen psoriasis then we have to clear the
air about the great auto immune mistake
once again I talked about it recently
you guys know okay the reason why I have
to talk about this is because aom and
psoriasis are they're classified and
listed as
autoimmune which medical communities
believe it's your body attacking itself
so Medical Research Medical Science
believes your body's attacking itself
autoimmunity so you know look if I went
to the doctor because of a rash on my
arm that was chronic and I was diagnosed
with eczema or
psoriasis and was told my body was
attacking itself I would leave the
office to feed it I really would now if
that was the truth if that's just really
how it worked then okay fine I at least
it's the truth but it's not the truth I
I it's not and I can prove it in many
ways including helping people heal in
all the years I put into it including
the information I have that's Advanced
you'll see you just hang in there we're
going to learn about it all um you know
if I drove home from that doctor's
office of course I would feel let down
defeated your body does not attack
itself and the fact that I have to bring
this great mistake up of autoimmune
multiple times with almost every illness
I have to cover shows me how many of us
have been let down misled been given
misinformation and truly this is really
that serious and how serious this really
is I mean think about it and there's
very little known about what causes
eczema for example so think about it if
you even look up what causes eczema it
it's unknown so how is it even possible
to blame your body and say it's
attacking itself destroying your skin
that your tea cells are destroying the
skin when it's unknown as to anything
about the disease or illness or
condition whatsoever in medical research
and medical science think about that one
think about that is that unbelievable
just kind of think about that for a
couple of minutes exactly so when you
know someone says to me what does the
big medical medium know about you know
Medical Research Medical Science I'll
tell you I have the answers from spirit
thank God and I've been able to help
people thank God and it's that important
because what's the what's the opposite
what's the lad the lad is unknown
meaning cause of illness and disease
unknown and we're going to blame it on
you that's the latter what what's the
difference there you want to go that way
so when someone challenges you or
challenges you on what you're doing to
take care of yourself and all the good
stuff you're doing for yourself they
challenge you what are you going to are
you going to say okay so I'm supposed to
do the latter it's unknown and my body's
attacking him itself and that's it so
that's what you're supposed to do I mean
come on so we we have to we have to come
we have to be just honest we have to be
honest we have to be clear there has to
be Clarity there has to be understanding
there has to be compassion with this
there has to be all of this so there's
very little Unknown about what causes
azema for example in the in the world of
medicine it's thought that your genes
once again are fouled up or all miss
combobulated or bumbled okay like your
jeans are all messed up so that's
actually the other option they have they
think it could be your jeans listen
that's one of the other great mistakes
that I covered recently and and before
you can't think it's your jeans whatever
you do you think it's your jeans you're
just going to get in trouble because
it'll break down your immune system it
will break down your immune system and
and one of these days we're going to
cover the whole methylation issue the
MTHFR gene mutation which is actually
going by storm raging through all the
alternative doctor's offices right now
and even conventional and functional
that is a confusion now yes there is a
methylation problem that we have out
there but the gene mutation test is not
what it's cracked up to be I'm going to
have to expose that to help everybody
out so we can move move forward that's a
whole another thing it's about the genes
anyway so you know basically another
thing that the medical communities think
that causes exmos orasis is
allergies some kind of allergy to
something I mean come on talking about
throwing darts at a barn that I mean
really um same with psoriasis it causes
unknown um it's either your genes or
it's your white blood count your te-
cells that are attacking your
skin yeah nice Theory nice Theory look
I'm sarcastic I am I have to admit I'm a
little more sarcastic today because I'll
tell you why I'll tell you why we'll
talk about why I'm sarcastic it's it's
coming up look this is once again Theory
no real answers and the best it gets in
medical research and medical science is
cause unknown so let's blame you and
your body that's why I'm sarcastic about
it because it's being you're being
blamed so let's blame your genan once
again that's why I'm sarcastic because
you're being blamed think about that
today is the day we air out the
truth about psoriasis and eczema and
also we will try to cover some AC acne
today cystic acne if we can so I know
the you know if you're suffering from
that we're going to do our best as far
as eczema and psoriasis goes it's a
whole different level of suffering if
you are a loved one or friend is dealing
with it you know different illnesses and
symptoms of conditions people who have
created who people who have been dealing
with suffering at different times and
levels in different ways exen psoriasis
is a different
ballpark so we all suffer from these
different illnesses out there we we you
know different diagnoses conditions
symptoms but examen orasis creates a
suffering that sometimes just can't be
matched and and this is why I have a
snarkiness about me and and some sarcasm
about everything because I've seen the
suffering I've seen it for years I've
seen it for decades if you've had eczema
and it's been pretty bad or flared up if
you've had um psoriasis you know what
I'm talking about the itchiness is
unlike any other the pain on the skin
unlike any other the burning the
swelling in many cases bleeding is
unlike any other okay that we've dealt
with or deal with you know think of the
worst case of poison Ivy but then
imagine it being
chronic you know so this is this is a
piece of it this is a piece of the deal
of of why I get kind of snarky of why I
seem like I have an attitude at some
times because you know it I've seen the
suffering I know what it is I know it's
what it's about and I've had to help
people recover and you know when when
when the answer out there is only cause
unknown it's your genes or maybe an
allergy and your body's attacking itself
and that's all we're given it's not
enough it's just not and you know fine
fine if it we can't blame anybody if
that cause is unknown but we better at
least be honest and get out of denial
medical denial that that it's you know
that they don't have the answer so we're
blaming you that has to be fixed it has
to be we have to say look we don't know
what causes all this but we have to stop
blaming the person we have to because it
breaks down their immune system that's
what we just talked about in the last
immune system show is we talked about
that very thing breaking down the immune
system with this this
misinformation so um there are different
levels of psoriasis and eczema you know
mild rash crack cracking in the skin
different levels of itching different
levels of bleeding to mild and to
releasees s um so and the thing is is
one of the things we have to understand
this is important this is an important
note there are hundreds of varieties
meaning it's not just always the same
it's not just different levels there's
different varieties of examon psoriasis
different different shapes different
sizes different patterns different
different way it's laid out on the body
different levels of of um you know some
even if some is some eczema or some
psoriasis is really extreme it may not
bleed some does you know it's so many
different varieties it's not just like
oh that's eczema you know that's an
umbrella word for a 100 varieties of
eczema I'm not exaggerating on that by
the way I'm not 100 varieties of eczema
I am not exaggerating that is serious I
mean that's how many different varieties
there are as far as with exim alone and
psoriasis it's not just pla psoriasis
and and serotic arthritis you know and
different psor that involves with um
arthritis and non- arthritis and
everything else and not even just that
there's there's not those two varieties
or three varieties we're talking there
is over a 100 with psoriasis
2 that's how many so we have to kind of
do we just we just have to be open to
this and to know this we can't just bury
it and hide it like it doesn't exist now
the reason why it's not talked about so
much is because it'll confuse the bear
it'll confuse everybody and they'll be
like well what is it there 100
medications then how come there's not
100 medications for 100 different
eczemas the reason why it's the only
medication for eczema is an
immunosuppressive or a steroid so they
no one cares in the Medical Science and
medical research world no one really
cares to identify different kinds the
different shapes different sizes all the
different varieties because they're just
going to give a steroid out anyway or an
IM immunosuppressive uh drug they're
just going to hand something out and
sure you know these things can Aid at
different times when we're we're in
crisis when we don't know how to deal
with it when we don't know how to handle
it and we don't know what we need to do
for it of course you know the we we
could use these things at different
times in our life and I've seen them
help people when they couldn't be helped
because they weren't they weren't given
the information they weren't given what
they were supposed to do but the reason
why a 100 varieties is not
identified is because that very reason
is because they don't have anything to
offer it's just one drug or two drugs
and that's it so why go crazy and trying
to really look into this with research
and Science and fund and funding and
getting a lot of immunologist on board
and figuring things out it's just it's
just not worth it for the industry so um
but it's worth it to get the answers and
to get us in a better place so let's get
down to the truth you know fasten your
seat belts I'm with you on this ride and
we're going to get down to it so if you
just logged on we're going into it right
now and if you just logged on you got to
go back and and to the archive and hear
the beginning of the show you have to so
the real cause and the foundation to it
all ecam and psoriasis stems from the
liver but it's more than just the liver
and I'm going to explain so we have to
kind of have our thinking caps on
because this is going to get a little
bit more complexed um spirit's
information can can do that I try to I
try to deliver spirit's information in
the best way I can um to try you know
try to over complicate something so we
have to hang on for this one that's what
I mean by fasten your seat belt so the
truth is it stems from the liver that's
where the cause or that's where it all
begins it's a liver condition the reason
this is not on the radar of medical
research and medical science is because
it's not a liver disease okay so you
have to understand how Medical Research
Medical Science Works um if it's not a
liver disease that's easily detected
with what they use already and not
creating something to detect what's
really happening then it's not on the
radar but it's a it's a liver issue it
stems from the liver that's what causes
this condition but we're going to go
into it deeper it's more than that okay
and and what happens is when you know
the doctor tests your liver function he
sees it's normal that doesn't mean there
isn't a problem when they're checking
for like liver enzymes cuz that really
doesn't play that much of a role into
psorasis or EXA until things have gotten
too bad and I'm going to tell you what
plays the most role what plays the
biggest this biggest part of it so like
I said if the doctor finds you know
liver enzyme and the function is going
good it's not going to be enough to
uncover the deeper more complicated
issues regarding the liver that creates
eczema and psoriasis or both or one of
them I've seen people with both so what
is wrong with the liver of someone who
is dealing with eczema and
psoriasis what is
wrong well it's a specific group of
toxins that are not known to
Conventional or alternative medicine and
will not be singled out for at least
another 30 years or
more but everyone
here I'm sure doesn't have the 30 years
to wait for even the discovery so we're
going to learn about this today right
now this specific group of toxins is
called a dermatoxin that's what it's
called a dermatoxin that's what they're
going to call it down the road
dermatoxin now you know that a
dermatoxin is a toxin that surfaces only
to the skin and injures the Derma the
Deep Derma tissue okay that's what the
dermatoxin is I've talked about
neurotoxins a lot neurotoxins come from
viruses such as Epstein bar virus or
shingles or hhb6 or ceglar virus and
others neurotoxins inflame and affect
the nervous system in the body causing
fatigue anxiety depression pain tingles
and numbness burning Etc okay that's a
neurotoxin so that's different so I want
you to know that so you know spirit's an
expert at neurotoxins and has been
talking about neurotoxins long before
they were talked about I remember being
10 years old and telling someone they
had neurotoxins from Spirit neurotoxins
that was like basically an alien ship
Landing because never mind 30 years ago
telling somebody that they're allergic
to weed
that was like an alien ship Landing okay
because meaning talking about blowing
somebody's mind out 30 35 years ago or
more and so um so just imagine saying
neurotoxin out of a 10-year-old and
that's that's what I'm saying it's it's
but dermat toxins this is a whole
another game now I'm releasing this
first time here today and you know I
thought about it and I said you know
everybody just needs to know so the
dermato toxins go to the skin it's
different than the
neurotoxin so I talked about the
neurotoxin for a second I have to go
back to that a little bit just so you
know there's a difference the
neurotoxin is a virus that's eating a
specific food it likes it could and or a
specific type of metal like for instance
if a virus like Epstein bar um feeds off
of mercury it goes to bathroom releases
a neurotoxin it's like a methyl
neurotoxin and that neurotoxin causes
all kinds of tingles and numbness it
causes all kinds of other stuff
depression anxiety it inflames the
nerves causes
vertigo you name it and that's what it
does okay so that's a neurotoxin so
dermato toxins are different they go to
the skin they don't go to the nervous
system so deep underneath the skin in
the Derma at the bottom base basically
it starts there's it's like a dermatoxin
acts as a
Venom and these toxins are highly
inflammatory the skin tries to release
the Toxin and may crack and bleed in the
event that it's trying to do this it's
trying to eliminate the Toxin and that
even hurts even more okay that's how it
works the neurotoxin is created by a
virus like I told you that you know
epine bar that eliminates the poison
it's neurotoxic a
dermatoxin is also created by a
pathogen but here's the difference so
understand this so we have the liver
remember when I said that I said the
liver is where it all stems
from okay well the liver has a pathogen
in it it doesn't have to be a specific
pathogen that's what's interesting about
this with psoriasis and um eczema so a
pathogen sits in the
liver and it's a
and it creates a
dermatoxin by consuming
copper you got to understand that by
consuming
copper that's how examen psoriasis is
created it's from a bug consuming and
eliminating copper you won't find that
on the internet you just won't find that
there and you won't find a lot of things
that that I've discovered on and off
over the years to with Spirit through
spirit and this one here you're not
going to find there either and but this
is the real root cause I mean this is
exactly the root cause it's a pathogen
that is consuming copper wait till you
hear this in the
liver
okay and that
copper is also in the liver due to
pesticides and herbicide exposure
that are not
new so I repeat not new so okay sure if
you go and eat some conventional produce
um which we're going to talk about next
show by the way I think the next show if
you eat conventional produce and there's
some residue somewhere in there like if
you have some grapes and it's on the
skin of the
grape and you have that
pesticide you know it can add into it
over time but it's not the root cause
it's from copper and a
pesticide from Generations past it's
from your
parents parents it's from your
grandparents
grandparents okay that's what it's from
it's from
DDT starting from
1874 that's what it's from okay
and even though DDT was was really put
into high use in
1939 it's its forefathers were from 1874
and being used and being used widely so
you have to understand this goes back to
1874 prior 1874 psoriasis and and and
and um psoriasis and eczema was rare
when I mean rare barely existed and what
existed of it was from copper poisoning
from copper
pipes copper
pipes and things of that nature that
were just being developed you know
basically um and the industries copper
exposure copper poisoning from the
industries but the Xmen psoriasis
boom came out of the pesticide World
starting in
1874 okay and has been passed down from
our parents parents to their parents to
their parents and sometimes you know
depending how long someone lives it
could be a more than a few Generations
depending on I mean you know if they
haven't lived that long in certain
aspects of the family line then it could
be multiple Generations between 1874 on
and even earlier and so this is the root
the root it's also why babies have
eczema they have copper in the
liver copper in the liver and the
pathogens from the parents and from the
parents and it from being passed down
now the problem here is the copper stops
the pesticide or the old DDT from
degrading it stops it from degrading
This is complicated stuff basically the
copper stops the rest of the pesticide
from minimizing and minimizing and
minimizing so that it becomes less and
less so exen cisis Fades away our world
it doesn't fade away because the copper
stops it from degrading and every
generation pass
down you see how it works so and then
when there's a pathogen consuming copper
in the
liver including copper we can collect
even more you know from copper pipes in
houses drinking water out of copper
pipes or if we're getting too many
pesticides in us that still have copper
in it to some degree if we're adding to
it it doesn't help we're adding new
stuff to it but it's mostly from old old
times it's passed down generation to
generation this is the confusion of
medical research and medical science
saying it's hereditarian your genes that
that's the
confusion I mean that's how it
works this is simplistic really I mean
we're just not there yet so let's suffer
for another hundred years for I mean
that's really medical research and IAL
science can't come down to the basics
they do it with heart surgery though
I'll tell you and they can REM remove
aneurysms out of the brain good and they
can fix broken bones like they never did
before and they could put a lot of
screws and a lot of rods in you that we
need and a lot of you know a lot of
titanium rods they can do amazing work
so you know and if your gallbladder is
about to explode because you haven't
taken care of yourself and you're eating
too many fried foods and yeah I mean if
we need the gallbladder out they're
they're there and they're ready so don't
get me wrong when when I really get
snarky about things but when it comes
down to chronic illness and the
suffering we have problems we have holes
in the whole whole thing there's cracks
in the sidewalk everything is slipped
through and that's what we're really you
know airing out so we'll talk about this
copper thing again so this is from old
Generations passed down this is from DDT
from Generations passed down the copper
keeps the DDT from degrading and other
pesticides from
degrading and this is how it works so um
and if we collect outside sources it
doesn't help and if we're hard on our
liver anyway so say you're someone with
exra examon orias and you end up getting
a pre- fatty liver because of your diet
on top of everything thing it only makes
it worse and compiles it and makes it
more
difficult and that's the problem there
so
what here's here's also how it works so
I told you about the the hereditary
factor and and how it gets passed down
from relatives and relatives and that's
how we get the same issue okay and um
but there's also it also works like this
um when the when the toxin surface to
the
skin everybody's different so a lot of
times the patterns change and pathogens
are sometimes different in different
people too so in a family line you can
have a different pathogen in the liver
consuming the copper and the old
pesticides that won't degrade from
generation after generation after
generation and will get different
markings on the body the reason why
someone has these little spots tiny
little spots with eczema another person
has large patches another person has
entire one patch it's just all red just
everywhere another person has like
skin-like leather because it's all there
another person has you know one type of
psoriasis that flakes off and and breaks
another kind doesn't do it at all but
just you know swells up it's all these
differences matter to how much of what
variety of pesticides in the liver
mostly containing to Old DDT from the
old days let me tell you about what they
used to do with DDT in the old days um
they used to spray it in the streets and
they used to wash the streets down with
it that's what they used to do they used
to wash the parks down with it they used
to spray the entire parks while the kids
were playing in it that's what they used
to do just with trucks just come by with
a truck and hose the entire park down
while kids were CH children were playing
in the suds and bathing in the suds of
it that's what they did not only was it
all over food like pesticides are today
you know which are bad of course the
pesticides today are bad Not only was it
over food but it was considered a
nutritional supplement so if it was on
your Apple then you were going to get
healthier you there were signs in the
markets with a child eating an apple
okay and and a can of DDT spray next to
it saying DDT is good for me so we're
talking about it was it was out of
control that's our psoriasis and ezema
problem of today that's the big part
that's developed over the years now of
course our pesticides today they're
they're no better and they add to it and
add to it it's just that we're not as
saturated with them as much for the most
part unless you're getting your lawn
sprayed and you're doing other things
and getting your house sprayed with
insecticides so if you're someone with
eimon the first thing you got to do you
have to eat as organic as you can I mean
do you do the best you can that's I mean
w with the ability that you have that's
the first thing you do second thing you
do is you make sure there's no
insecticides being sprayed in your
house don't worry about the ants you
leave the ants don't worry don't worry
about the ants okay and just or whatever
it is okay just don't worry because it
can be a lot worse you keep on getting
those sprays inside the house so that's
a big deal
too um all this matters now the reason
why there's different levels of it like
I said is there's different levels of
the pesticide different levels of the
ancient DVT from our forefathers there's
different levels of copper and they're
different pathogens so it makes up for a
complicated process for medical research
and medical science to ever really
through they don't like to go there it's
just way too much funding way too much
money to figure out the different levels
of what people have in their liver what
pathogen is creating it and what the
outcome is on the body so it's best to
just say you're you're at fault you got
stupid genes okay and that's pretty much
what it is and or you um or you're just
you know it's your body attacking itself
why not why not tell everybody that I
guess you know so
exactly right so um so a little bit more
about how this works um you know the
alternative world of health so
functional and alternative world uh
believes that it's autoimmune and the
body is attacking itself and um even
though the alternative world is smart
about everything meaning smart about
everything in the sense where hey
processed food has to go away you know
you go on healthier Di diet there's
healthier your vegan diets there's
healthier your P paleo diets where you
take out all the garbage you take out
the fried foods you take out everything
else you know there's a a food War
actually going on out there I did a show
on it I'm going to do another show
there's a food War got all the Paleo
people and you know meaning the leaders
of the Paleo movement and they're just
they just hate the vegans and you get
all the plant-based people exactly
vegans and vetetans all plant-based
people they they hate the Paleo people
there's a big war out there um and it's
not about that you know I I do know that
you know some paleo diets are helping
people they take out the processed foods
they take out the McDonald's they take
out the fast foods they take out
everything else and people start getting
better you know and I know that there's
the plant-based plant-based world where
you know everybody's taking out
everything and and they're getting
better they're getting better it's
wherever you feel you have to go to if
you're not getting the results in one
angle and first of all you got to give
it you know a longer test p you have to
give it longer time and don't give up
early on trying something new um and you
know and you can find your way um and
but eating healthier matters no matter
what and we're going to do a lot more
food talk especially with the
life-changing food book we're going to
talk about you know all of it and I
actually laid out in the life-changing
Foods book a really good chapter on what
not to eat and why you shouldn't be
eating it with what illnesses you have
um and that's whole another area now
when it comes to psoriasis and it comes
to eczema your better angle to
go is actually not just no processed
foods so it's not just hey keep the
processed foods away keep the fried
foods away keep the wheat away when
you're dealing with Xmen resses you want
to go all the way over you want to go
more
plant-based um and like I said that
doesn't mean I don't like paleo diets
that doesn't mean I don't like you know
whatever eating all the different diets
that are out there it's not about what I
like in the end it's about what's right
for the person what's right for the
illness it's what's right for what's
going on and what spirit says that's
what matters the most because if I start
thinking of what I like then that's a
different story people won't get what
they need it has to come from Spirit so
when you're dealing with psoriasis and
eczema you really want to go towards a
little bit more towards the plant-based
angles if you're into a lot of animal
products you want to lower them it
doesn't mean you have to get rid of them
all together depending on who you are
and how severe it is the reason why I
say this is because in order for the the
liver to release copper and get the
copper out and release deep pesticides
that are in the liver you got to have a
little bit lower fat so you can do just
a little bit lower fat you have to lower
the fats in your diet you know the 28
day cleanse in the medical medium book
has really helped thousands with examen
psoriasis thousands with examen
psoriasis because it took out the fat
the high fat including a lot of the
plant fat and it made it so the liver
can recover release copper release
pesticides and the pathogen can actually
just start to uh break down and have
nothing to do anymore because it doesn't
have any food to eat and that's how
psoriasis and eczema clears up um in
people um once it's cleared up and
you're in a great place then you can
move forward and you can if you want to
do a healthy paleo diet or you know a
little bit more animal protein cuz
that's what you like or that's what
someone told you as best you could try
different things you go in different
directions um but in this situation it's
important different situations different
illnesses different complications with
People's Health you got to do different
things um so it's uh it it's that
important as far as the balance of it
all and that's what we're going to we're
going to talk about a little bit more um
the thing is is that with xon and
psoriasis is that there's Cycles it's
cyclical so it runs Cycles a lot of
times when someone's involved you know
they're in that aimen psoriasis it
becomes like it starts to clear up and
then 3 weeks later four weeks later you
might be one of these people that are
experiencing this it starts to then come
back a little bit more but less and then
starts to clear up come back until
finally it gets cleared up all together
so anyone healing from it right now
realize it's going to kind of come and
go a little less it's going to be
cyclical it's going to be doing this
thing until finally It Go goes away
completely it's something to understand
on how it works and then you know you
get it cleaned up and you can bring back
other foods but I recom I'm going to go
over Foods now to what really works um
for exen psoriasis wild blueberries they
clean up the liver they bind on to
Copper they're a big deal I talk about
wild blueberries all the time papaya
huge one huge one for eimos
orasis that's a big deal too um pear s
that's a big one silly pear you know
those are really a big deal watermelon
that's also really important lettuce
Roma lettuce green leaf lettuce red leaf
lettuce butter lettuce lettu uses are
incredible for psoriasis and eczema what
this means is is if you have say a
healthy standard American diet but a
healthy version you want to start you
know minimizing anything like the grains
you want to minimize any kind of wheat
you want to minimize any any kind of you
know heavy meat you don't want pork if
you want to do you know some lean meat
or some like turkey or chicken or fish
and and bring it down see how it goes
along the way you know you don't have to
go crazy or all the way if you don't
want to but if you're suffering that bad
you've been living this with this for a
long time I would do the 28 day cleanse
I would stay off of all animal products
for a little while in your life and
really start cleaning this out and like
I said it's just you know for the
process and then you can go back to
doing what you like or what a good
practitioner recommends um so spinach
big that's a big one kale that's a big
one arugula that's a big one Sprouts
that's a big one Sprouts clean the liver
they help heal the liver that's
incredible important so avocado is
actually good too watermelon seeds so
when you eat watermelon you want the
ones that are seed watermelon seeds are
incredibly important sweet potatoes
winter squash that's a big one too um
incredible FX monis hemp seeds that's
another one berock root that's another
one too avoid all grains avoid dairy
products listen I I understand the
grass-fed beef butter thing I think it's
the healthiest butter on the planet I
understand the yogurts I get it but
we're talking about psoriasis we're
talking about Eczema we're not talking
about food Wars and food belief systems
okay so you have to understand that so
anyone out there who's like really big
on something like their grass-fed butter
don't get mad at me because it doesn't
mean I don't like it it just means this
is something that you know with the
aasis it can't be there if it's there it
doesn't help the exis go away that's all
um so you want no Dairy no eggs eggs you
don't want with examen sasis it'll keep
it around forever and it it'll keep the
copper in the liver and it'll keep the
old pesticides going all the way back in
the liver they just won't go away really
important to understand so um no canola
oil you know that no canola oil that's
got to go and like I said before you got
to lower the animal proteins if you need
the exis to go wave in more you have to
eliminate them for a while in your life
you could bring them back later it's not
about the belief system it's about
what's right for the moment at the time
in your life always have to remember
that people get really
upset if I start leaning on one side or
the other or whatever it is it's not
about that it's about what's happening
in your health and what's needed in that
moment if you had a kidney disease if
you had a kidney disease or if you were
on dialysis I would have you remove all
animal protein because animal protein
kills the kidneys when you're on
dialysis it's about what you need and
then if you're somebody and you don't
you know and and you can't you know you
can't you have so many food
sensitivities and you can't eat anything
and you got to live off of turkey
absolutely then you live off a turkey
I'm for it until the body calms down so
I'm in there with you no matter what
it's just about what we need for what we
need and I have to express this because
um you know we do we do every now and
then get someone saying wait a minute
wait what is he talking about okay so
you know there's acne which I didn't
cover a lot didn't cover at all today
want to talk about cystic acne the cause
is Strep that's the cause it's the
bacteria strep strep a cacus that's the
bacteria that causes acne so when people
say well it's hormonal it's it's not
hormonal it's actually strep it's just
that hormones are steroids and when
they're out of syn or they're raging
whether they're out of syn or they're
raging okay they break down the immune
system and strep grows rapidly so when
we're hormonal in different ways in our
life whatever that angle may be the
strap a caucus if we have it in our
system um proliferates it actually grows
in high abundance and that's so when
we're going through puberty or we're
going through when're we're going
through puberty we're having a serious
metabolic change in the body we're
actually the immune system is is not
getting stronger it weakens for the
moment actually through puberty it's
another reason why Epstein bar and mono
come come so heavily handed in puberty
and after because we lose all our zinc
we lose our immune system when we go
through hormonal changes um same thing
with pregnancies our immune system drops
during pregnancies acne comes acne comes
after delivering a baby acne comes when
we're pregnant a acne comes when we're
ovulating acne comes during periods and
and menstration it's all because these
are times when the immune system abs and
flows and drops and lowers and the strep
that's in the body raises it's a it's a
balance that happens all the time time
cystic acne is chronic strep from your
strep throat you had when you were 3
years old that you didn't know about
from that ear infection you had when you
were 5 years old and it sits in the body
and it causes the cystic acne so when
you're dealing with strep we want
different supplements you want zinc
that's a critical one when you're
dealing with STP you want um golden seal
periodically go to a practitioner talk
about how you can do some golden seal
periodically go to an herbalist um you
want time time tea when you're dealing
with acne you want um you want lemon
bomb lemon bomm tea lemon bomb tinctures
alcohol free you want lots of lemon balm
and you can lower your strep you want a
little bit of maybe some some Cal silver
Sovereign Silver actually that's the one
um so silver hydrosols the high quality
ones you want a little bit of that in
your life you want lots of vitamin C
lots and lots and lots of vitamin C and
foodwise you want to you want to work on
some of these Foods you want the wild
blueberries you want lots of lettuces
you want avocado you want to stay away
from all grains all Dairy all eggs
canola oil
soy you want to stay away from all of
that with acne so that's really
important it's different from psoriasis
and and eczema psorasis and eczema you
really have to lower the animal proteins
um to get the best
results and but acne you don't have to
lower those animal proteins see so it's
all about what you have just like I was
saying before
um supplements for for examon psoriasis
aloe juice fresh aloe leaf so you b aloe
water I talk about that on my blog you
can go check that out the zinc that's
incredibly important ala so alal opaque
acid um B complex
MSM that's a good one um curcumin so
cumin or curcumin people say it
different way turmeric turmeric saying
it in all the different different ways
and languages so everybody kind of knows
and um those are great as well skull cap
tincture like natur aner skull cap skull
cap tincture alcohol-free is great for
examen
psoriasis um herbal teas colula
peppermint rose hips rose petals nettle
Leaf lemon bomb chamomile berock root
incredible for examen psoriasis and good
for acne too but ex examen psoriasis
it's really good um you can get rid of
acne there's no question get rid of
those Foods you're supposed to get rid
of um keep them out of your diet for
long term a good couple of years
seriously and you know get the zinc get
the different you know get the th tea
going all the time get the lemon balm um
get you know little bit of silver in
your system you just work with it and
you'll see and the golden seal and
you'll see work with the herbalist too
and you'll the acne will start coming
down um because it's about knocking down
that strap and lowering that strap I'm
going to do another show on acne uh I
promise I will and we're going to go
into it even deeper we're going to go
thoroughly all the way from the whole
thing with the oil of how the Medical
Science medical research just calls it
basically an oil buildup meanwhile they
they give out antibiotics left and right
because someone must have figured out
it's it's it's bacterial think about
that how many antibiotics are offered
for cystic acne so let's just be honest
once again and realize its strep and not
just oil sebum oil that's just sitting
up there under the skin so uh we're
going to go into that detail that'll be
fun we'll be kind of we'll be kind of uh
fun with that one and um but listen I
know that anybody who suffered with
examen psoriasis and even cystic acne I
mean I I realize it I mean it's it's
difficult it's it puts people through a
lot it pushes people to the edge um
psoriasis and E eczema can get better
and will get better I've seen it happen
it happens all the time on my Instagram
page people are actually getting rid of
their iasis you can take a look surf
through my Instagram and you can find
people contact them find out what
they're doing they're probably doing the
celery juice on top of it all the famous
celery juice that that I've that Spirit
has offered us and um so you can you can
get help there's no question um so we're
coming down to the end of the show we
we're we're we're getting here look um
the bottom line is with like for
psoriasis and xma just know that my
heart pours out for anyone who's dealt
with it or dealing with it right now I
understand I get it um I know the
suffering involved you can't sleep you
can't function half the time I've seen
this for decades with people what they
go through I stand behind you 100% we
can clear it up we can heal we can move
forward your body's not attacking itself
it's not how it works go to my website
medicalmedium.com you can sign up for my
free healing path course my free healing
path resource I dedicated hundreds of
hours to making this thing I don't don't
want you not using it oh my God you
should use this seriously it's got all
the functional to tools it's got 18
essential steps recorded by me there
audios to actually walk you through the
healing path and that's the way to go
know that I'm here for you know that I
stand behind you 100% um I give you all
this good stuff on Instagram too check
that out Twitter Pinterest you name it
everyday fruits vegetables information
nobody knows and daily Inspirations to
move you forward in healing because it's
all about you it's all about you healing
I stand behind you I'm with you on this
I know what it's like to be told hey you
know this is what you got going on
meaning like I've seen it I feel it I
feel the pain of others and the
suffering so listen we're going to do
this together we're going to move you
forward it's not your fault you didn't
create it you didn't make this happen
you're not a faulty person you're not a
bad person you didn't do anything wrong
your body can heal and we're going to
move forward together have compassion
for yourself take a deep breath have
compassion for yourself know that I love
you know that I stand behind you and
we're going to do this together bless
you love you bye-bye