first month anniversary on Tick Tock
since I've been a dietitian
uh-huh you know I do it Rd here
you saw that I know
I know thank you for paying for my
registered dietitian School you and
Daddy have been really so helpful
I know my Tick Tock page is growing I
talk about protein
uh-huh
yeah I know Mommy I know Mom I know
protein is like the most important thing
ever it's why I became a dietitian
uh-huh
yeah
okay I have to go to work I think I'm
going live on Tick Tock right now
okay bye
love you
okay so as I was saying before
this has protein in it and this is this
is meat and it has protein in it are
these here I have to say that Rd here
because it's really important when I
graduated from registered dietitian
school they gave us all this for our
class
and they said that you have to learn how
to identify when someone's protein
deficient or they're not protein
deficient and you can do that by looking
at this scientific measuring tool that
they gave us
at dietitian school and they got like
I think my dietitian stuff is really
paying off on tick tock and I okay
come down
Okay so
this is a measuring tool to show how
much protein one is getting and and
dietitian School were taught that it all
depends like your facial structure and
everything
determines how much protein you actually
receive
and how much B12
I can't believe how much I learned about
B12 and registered dietitian school they
said that only the meat eaters can have
B12 and get B12
B12
okay
um
this is really important that I want
everybody to know on my Tick Tock page I
can't wait to make small videos out of
this on my Tick Tock page
oh my God like cheese
I want you to know that it's so
important it's a staple that every girl
should be on yes
um how old am I I just saw a comment I'm
24 years old and yes I just graduated
from registered dietitian school I want
to go into how cheese is so important I
have I have four ounces of cheese per
day and in The dietitian handbook guide
where is it
I've been doing this now for I guess a
couple of months I just graduate
graduate Grant I think
I have my handbook guide right here that
they gave us at The dietitian School
Rd here I know right
and they say that cheese is
fundamentally one of the most important
things that you can actually get in you
exactly a whole bunch of us graduated
and we're killing it on Tick Tock now
so cheese is probably one of the better
things sorry I got a phone call coming
in
you see
hold on
hi
yeah now I I know I'm in alive I know
Todd
I know I thank you for being so
supportive okay I'll see you later okay
that's just my boyfriend just don't
worry
his family had celiac
and they're all like Celiac people his
whole family his mother has Celiac is
Dad has Celiac and he says he has Celiac
and I told him that you have to get as
many eggs in you as possible and as much
cheese and he's on an 100 egg diet an
egg white diet right now and so I've
been really helping my boyfriend and his
family with their Celiac now I what I
really like is chicken
I eat chicken three times a day every
day for the protein chicken's the most
important and I just want to say one
more thing
that's really really important is that I
don't want anyone to think that they
can't indulge because I've noticed that
there's Eating Disorders out there being
started by people who have like they
think they've run the gamut in social
media and they actually they actually
like tell people to stay away from so
many things but you have to treat
yourself because it's called moderation
and balance and so what I recommend is
some chocolate cake once in a while or
you have an eating disorder and so I'm
just telling you I learned a lot from my
dietitian school and I have a lot of
experience too because you know when I
put in my resume now that I've been
doing this since I was like 11 years old
I was telling my mom what she should eat
or not eat I have so much experience and
what I did was on my website now in my
Tick Tock handle I talk about how I've
been doing this for like 10 years
even though I'm 24 years old I've been
doing this for 10 years and I'm so
accomplished and I went to school and
dietitian school I just want to show you
what happens with this tool here this is
a tool you when you graduate they give
every single Rd there this very tool it
determines how much protein how many
carbs if you have too many carbs it
changes the structure of your face if
you have two not enough protein it
changes the structure of your face and
you can get really sick and protein
deficient
I think that's it for this
episode of Samantha Samantha's Rd
channel on Tick Tock
um there's so many of us out there
fighting for people and getting benefits
to them I think um anyway thank you so
much I have to take a phone call now I'm
so busy I'm a busy Rd and I have to go
foreign
anyway we're talking about neurological
symptoms today you guys we're going to
cover tingles numbness aches pains
different kind of neuro symptoms even
touch upon migraines neurological
migraines we're going to touch upon a
lot of the different Tremors shakes
ticks spasms cranial nerves which is
really important too you got cranial
nerves that really affect everybody in
so many ways try geminal neuralgia
all kinds of different problems people
are up against
and so I think it's really smart to
touch upon neurological symptoms I want
to do a little q a stuff too so I want
to be open to that as well
and so I want to begin with is what
happens is that
practitioners
and doctors people in the health
movement
never ever connected the dots between a
symptom being neurological if you're
somebody that's experienced enough in
the last 10 years 15 years maybe you've
been sick 20 years in your life
and you've been sick with different
neurological symptoms you probably went
through the whole guessing games Channel
seeing a lot of different professionals
and health professionals a lot of
different doctors and as it's happening
none of them knew that your symptom was
actually neurological not even believe
it or not like panic attacks back then
10 years ago or more a panic attack was
never considered to be neuro or
Neurological on any level and this is
important to know because now that the
time is changing things are changing now
and what's happening is people are
realizing through medical medium books
and medical meme information because it
was being put out there through these
books about how neurological symptoms
like give you all of these different
things like we feel these different
things from cranial symptoms cranial
nerves to vagus nerves to all kinds of
different things so I want to cover that
right now a little q a how many people
go through tightness of the chest
and it's unexplainable they have this
tightness of the chest going on kindness
of the throat kindness of the chest how
many people have ever gone through that
they feel like they can't get a deep
breath and they're having a problem
getting a deep breath right so that's
actually Vegas nerve related stuff if
your doctor rules out everything that
they are looking for if they're looking
for something and they rule it out and
they're like look you got anxiety let's
put you on some benzos let's send you
home with a benzo you can take an Ativan
a Xanax whatever it is and they send you
home with that and they're like do this
for a while see how your anxiety gets
see how your Panic gets see how your
tightness of your chest is in the whole
bit right and they rule out pretty much
everything else they do blood work they
look at you but they can't release
everybody's saying yes right there
exactly that's what you have lately too
I'm seeing all that
so what is missed in the health world
it's a big deal
vagus nerve issues now you'll hear more
about vagus nerve issues now a day right
you'll hear more about it but what
people don't realize is why do we get
symptoms that are vagus nerve related
why and how how does it even happen so
what medical mean information brought
into town years ago was that nerves
swell nerves actually swell they become
inflamed there's a reason why they
become mysteriously inflamed when you
haven't had an accident or an actual
physical injury or anything like that
there's a reason why nerves get
mysteriously inflamed and that's viruses
viruses such as Epstein-Barr being one
of the leaders everybody's got
Epstein-Barr at this point in the world
spreading fast but it's not just about
everybody's got Epstein-Barr you know
everybody's got Epstein-Barr 80 in just
about that it's everybody's getting more
than one variety of Epstein-Barr and
that's what's happening out there so
it's like there isn't just one
Epstein-Barr that means if you have
Epstein-Barr you can't get Epstein-Barr
again that's not true you can have one
Epstein-Barr and get another
Epstein-Barr and get another and another
and another all different varieties some
Milder
some more annoying some more aggressive
but you can get a lot of different
varieties of these viruses and these
viruses release something I call a
neurotoxin it's when the virus eats
something it really likes
like an egg
and then peas and poos
waste out of the virus
that floats around your body and is
highly highly allergenic to the vagus
nerves
right there
one of the most important things you can
learn to empower yourself
is vagus nerves swelling getting
inflamed
because there's something toxic a
neurotoxic compound that's saturating
the nerve
that's touching the nerves creating them
to spasm
creating them to twist a little creating
them to swell and get more inflamed and
this leads
to a lot of different symptoms and
conditions people are suffering with
okay from intestinal tract pain
stomach problems intestinal tract pain
okay that alone because the vagus nerves
are inflamed to tremors
to spasms and ticks
to tingles and numbness on the body
and not just the Vegas there was getting
inflamed but the phrenic nerves that run
down each side of the chest here
the the phrenic nerves can get inflamed
and swell too which give people a lot of
different issues as well both the
phrenic nerves and vagus nerves can
inflame Korean tightness of the chest
that's unexplainable by any physician or
any doctor out there mystery symptoms
that are plaguing people out there all
the time
and so what is critical to know is that
people walk around with lots of
different bugs in them different viruses
now the thing is here is that the health
movement years ago you could even hear a
word like nobody even knew virus what do
you mean what does that even mean no one
talked about it didn't exist
in the Natural Health move it it was
just about eat better stuff eat better
books eat better this it was about how
wheat was genetically altered
that wheat was hybridized that wheat has
changed in this world that was pretty
much all you can actually get back years
just more a little over 10 years ago was
just wheat's genetically altered Wheats
hybridized wheat's causing our problems
gluten is causing our problems no no
information on how gluten is causing our
problems on any level
but that's what you would get you would
get eat better books to stay away from
processed foods
to stay away from fried greasy foods and
that's what was given to us pretty much
all around that's all you can do it's
like years ago you got sick
it was like well maybe it was that fast
food diet doing it maybe it's just
hybridized wheat I've been eating every
day
in this gluten
but that's pretty much as far as it went
and then you had millions of people on
the planet suffering with all kinds of
symptoms conditions including thyroid
conditions many of you guys got thyroid
problems right doctors checking out your
thyroid your numbers don't look good
and they're like Hashimoto's all of it
and then there's the mystery symptoms
the fatigue so I want to go into that a
little bit too when someone has a viral
load and that viral load is feeding on
what it wants like say eggs and cheese
and dairy I'm just showing you a little
bit here in that viral load
is getting high because
a virus is feeding off of eggs
and devouring the eggs
and then releasing neurotoxins
neurotoxins are flooding the entire body
and then the vagus nerves swell up
and now we're in fatigue where we feel
like we have sandbags for arms we feel
like we have sandbags for legs we have a
hard time getting out of bed we have
what medical mean information States as
neurological fatigue
so I know that so many of you guys have
dealt with neurological fatigue out
there where it doesn't make sense why
are you tired someone will be like
you're lazy and back years ago it was
like you're lazy
you're you're bored you just want to be
on the couch you don't want to get out
of bed
you're just this is just who you are and
people took the hit every day day in and
day out for their neurological fatigue
but what's really happening is you got
the viral infections the viral
infections are releasing all of these
different neurotoxins including some
neurotoxins the neurotoxins are landing
on the nerves
in the body and when they land on the
nerves
they swell and inflame the nerve very
important to know because if you don't
have answers you're lost you're in the
dark you're searching the web
you're checking through social and
you're trying this and trying that and
doing this and doing that when the
answers aren't even clear to why you're
even struggling or suffering on any
level
so I want to get into the brain a little
bit the brain stem
the vagus nerves come out of your brain
stem
so do other nerves too like trigeminal
nerves many people you guys might be
dealing with this is nerve problems in
the neck in the jaw in the face facial
nerves
right around the temple
nerves around the eyes
nerves in the back of the neck back of
the head
so you're dealing with cranial nerves
facial nerves that are inflamed
trigeminal nerves that are inflamed all
from different viruses and viral
infections so I want to get into that a
little deeper we'll leave Epstein-Barr
for the moment we'll pop back into it
let's head into the shingles virus
the shingles virus
is growing fast out there more and more
people are getting different varieties
of shingles they're wreaking havoc and
one of the things the shingles virus
does is create trigeminal neuralgia
facial nerve problems and different
symptoms people get where your teeth
hurt really bad your teeth hurt really
bad your jaw hurts really bad you're
going to the dentist over and over again
you can't really get answers they're
drilling your teeth they're doing root
canals or maybe they're just pulling
teeth because it gets so bad you're on
medications you're struggling you're on
gabapentin
because that's what they put everybody
on when you have jaw pain neck pain and
it's unexplainable and you're struggling
so much they throw you on gabapentin
right so many people have been on that
and I'm not saying don't be on it or be
on it and just do what your doctor you
know what's right by you and your doctor
of course your doctor's guidance
but so many people are giving so many
medications like gabapentin and benzos
to try to help them with the
neurological pain
and their neurological symptoms but yet
the answers aren't there
the answers are not there the well is
dry
and it's we're we're not getting an
answer and so people have to understand
something shingles can rash out
and shingles can also not rash out
you can have two just separate accounts
of shingles one can rash out and they
see push tools and then you have the
nerve pain another never shows its face
never Peaks its ugly head
it just stays there on the nerves and
you're walking around looking to try to
get botox injections both Botox
injections in your neck in the side of
your neck right and the nerves near your
brain stem nerves in your spine the
nerves in your neck like you name it and
people have to go and they have to seek
this and look for this Botox in their
facial nerves because they're in that
much Agony and that much pain and
they're walking around but what they
don't get are answers to What's
happening and how it's happening so
in the medical medium book I don't know
if you guys have the medical medium
books on here many of you guys do right
but that's cleanse the heel this is
brain saver okay they're on sale at
Amazon right now these books are
incredible for giving people answers
turning people's lives around it'd be
one thing if I said that when it did not
happen but it did there are hundreds of
thousands of people going into the
millions just on brain saver alone
around the world getting answers and
cleanse the heel is one of the most
famous books in health worldwide right
now because of what it's done for people
bringing people's life and health back
and so I'm just showing you this so I so
you know that there's actual protocols
that you can look into to actually get
some help with so let's cut into this a
little bit more I want to talk about the
shingles virus here's a question right
here
Nanny news right there on IG no more
gastric acid after celery juice
explanation points after 25 years every
day so amazing when I think about that
right now you're going 25 years
with acid attacks gastric wise 25 years
you're doing celery juice now and it's
gone think about the power of that and
how incredible that is right there The
Ballad says on IG medical medium has
healed my chronic constipation
nothing makes me happier than to hear
that because chronic constipation is not
a joke it is brutal it really really can
bogs somebody down it can really set
them back it can torture them in many
ways and I'm so happy to hear that I
can't tell you how how that makes me
feel let's say
um goodbye
Guinness says thank you for this live aw
you have made my day so much lighter
with the laughter sending blessings your
way you liked our Rd that's our
residential Rd
that we actually have now we have an RD
that actually you know comes on here
before I come on so that's great it's
great she's amazing
um see Mary just said knowing this info
has changed everything for me and all
the tools we have so thank you so
thankful so you guys
I want to cut a little bit more deeper
into the soul a lot of people have the
shingles virus wreaking havoc creating
inflammation in their trigeminal nerves
and their facial nerves
causing untold amounts of pain and
sorrow for people they have to be on
gabapentin they have to be on benzos
they got to be on Xanax they got to be
on antidepressants doctors recommend a
cocktail of like antidepressants plus
Gabapentin plus this plus that I'm not
saying take those no I'm not saying
don't take those I'm saying listen to
your doctor whatever your doctor does
for you and whatever guidance you want
by your doctor I'm just saying the
reality of The Facts of what people are
on and what they go through and how
difficult it is and that's not even the
amount of people that are actually going
and looking around for answers and
they're trying this like they'll go and
try ionized water like alkaline ionized
water that stuff just makes things worse
because of the metal plates leech metal
I tell people stay
a million years
I would never touch in a natural water
machine and a million freaking years I
would never let that stuff poison me and
poison my brain leeching off those metal
plates at a million freaking years never
and so I'm saying that people are then
searching for answers and they're
looking for all these different things
if you're trying that they're trying
this meanwhile they're suffering they're
struggling it's really hard and they
don't have answers so I want to go a
little deeper now
there are people out there suffering
from so many different low-grade viral
viruses and viral infections that
they're dealing with a combination of
different varieties
and
some varieties are the Epstein Barr some
of the shingles some are hhv6 some are
simplex one some are six plus Simplex 2
and they're dealing with multiple
problems in multiple viruses
they'll have an Epstein-Barr and a
shingles they'll have an Epstein-Barr
and they'll have set of megalovirus
they'll have that plus they'll have
something like strep and that strip
will work along with the Epstein-Barr
virus so they'll have a combination of a
few different things bacteria plus
viruses
and then these things are what gives
people all these different crazy
neurological symptoms as they live their
life
so they wake up in the morning and their
problems not gone it's still there and
then the next day they wake up in the
morning they still have ticks and spasms
they still have aches and pains they
still have fatigue
because until you get the answers to why
these nerves are inflamed and learn that
these nerves are inflamed from these
viral infections can you actually
address them and do something about it
and so
it's important to know the medical
medium info was just about like taking
away everybody's food far from it it's
about giving you options you never
thought you could use or do and then
having those options to help heal the
body
everybody has a choice to make they can
eat the things they want they have their
own free will but if they're really sick
it's good to know why it's okay to
remove something let's take eggs for an
example
viruses love eggs it's their favorite
food
out of everything if someone was to say
aw I'm gonna
I'm gonna take all your food away from
you but I'm just gonna leave you a few
options I'm Gonna Leave You this roasted
chicken I'm Gonna Leave You this
chocolate cake I'm Gonna Leave You this
cheese and I'm Gonna Leave You these
eggs
and they said that's all you're gonna
have you're gonna starve to death unless
you choose one of these unless you
choose eggs or cheese or chicken
or chocolate cake
and weeks go by and I haven't eaten any
of those and I have to make a choice and
I know I have to make a choice I'm going
to tell you right now I'm not going to
choose
the egg
the last thing I would ever choose is
and you'll see out there people saying
eggs are so good for you eggs are
important eggs are filled with protein
you should have all the eggs you want
you should never not eat eggs the egg
yolks are good though egg whites are
good
you should be on eggs you'll hear that
all day long out there everywhere
but that's the last thing I would choose
because
if there's ever a bacteria or a pathogen
or anything in the body the egg will
feed it if there's anything in there the
egg will feed it and that's important to
know
cheese and dairy will feed viruses and
pathogens
and that's another thing too that feeds
viruses and pathogens the chickens not
my favorite go-to because it's so high
in fat people don't realize that it's at
the highest in fat but it's actually
something that's not my go-to right and
chocolate Cake's not my go-to because I
don't want to destroy my adrenal glands
I want to protect my adrenal glands I
want to keep my adrenal glands happy and
I don't want my adrenal glands jacked up
on all that caffeine and then I don't
want to be addicted either so that
wouldn't be my go-to either but
regardless I wouldn't choose the eggs
so I want to go into some more symptoms
conditions how many of you guys are
dealing with ticks spasms
where you have them on your body all the
time you feel them in your arms you feel
them in your chest you feel them in your
your eyes you feel them around your eyes
you feel them on the sides of your face
okay
so many people are dealing with a lot of
the different ticks and spasms
so ticks and spasms can be a combination
where you're dealing with low grade
viral infections but you're also dealing
with toxic heavy metals and that's the
next thing I want to go into a little
bit
it's one thing to have viruses inside of
us creating neurological symptoms
through inflammation caused by
neurotoxins being released from the
viral infections so viruses eating foods
that it likes such as eggs and then
releasing neurotoxins that get onto the
nerves and inflame them it's one thing
to have that it's another to also be
high in toxic heavy metals without
realizing it and a blood test does not
determine how high you are in toxic
heavy metals nor do a hair analysis or a
urine analysis will not determine how
high you are in toxic heavy metals that
is an important understanding if you
want to heal because you can be thrown
off your game
you go and you get a test or a hair
analysis for toxic heavy metals doesn't
look like it's a big problem but you're
struggling with symptoms and conditions
you don't think you need to do anything
about it but here's how it works toxic
heavy metals burrow themselves deep
within organs
deep inside the brain
deep inside the liver
they sit in there and they're not
available
to be drawn out of the blood they're not
easily available to be taken out of the
blood for an analysis
for a viewing
they hide and they stay dormant and
that's what metals do they can stay in
your bones and never show up in the
bloodstream when someone's getting
tested on any level
biggest reason behind autoimmune
and chronic health conditions like
neurological symptoms
is toxic heavy metals
and viruses and pathogens
toxic heavy metals and viruses and
pathogens
it's the biggest combination
viruses tend to like to feed off of
toxic heavy metals the more toxic heavy
metals somebody has the more neurotoxins
the virus can produce making somebody
feel like that got chronic inflammation
brain inflammation they feel like they
got sandbags on their feet their arms
they can't function and the brain fog is
out of control
and you guys know you guys have dealt
with brain fog you've dealt with all
kinds of different issues different
symptoms different problems someone just
said on IG I'm literally loving this
with a laughing face I'm loving being
here you guys and talking to you guys
I'm trying to do a presentation for you
guys here today as you can notice I have
the props out and I have the anatomy
and I'm just trying to present the best
I can
I want to cover different symptoms and
conditions while we're still here
Helene says so happy to attend this live
so happy you're here
you're over there on YouTube amazing and
then someone just said f u
C I won't say the last letter okay let's
get back to it
on IG
how can you detox from heavy metals good
question heavy metals don't just leave
heavy metals don't just get up and leave
hey I'm gonna get up now I'm a toxic
heavy metal and I'm going to get up and
I'm going to walk on out of that
person's body maybe that person can Will
me out with their mind maybe that person
hey that person's willing me out I'm
going to be a toxic heavy metal and
leave the person's body and that person
is going to manifest me right out of the
body just like that and hey if I try all
these different things maybe that'll
help too maybe some zeolite will help
maybe something else will help maybe
something but it's not it's not
Metals don't go and they don't go with a
lot of the trendy crap that's out there
they don't remove metals
it's not how it works
in order to truly get Metals out of the
body you need five ingredients that I've
talked about check out the heavy metal
detox smoothie
check it out when you get the chance
if you look here at brain saver
protocols
heavy metal detox cleanses in here
Advanced heavy metal detox cleanses
there's a heavy metal detox smoothie in
here too
so you'll see the ways to get Metals out
and guess what
this heavy metal detox smoothie and
cleanse is the most known and popular in
the world of Health for getting Metals
out because it works so much so that so
many people have ripped off
ripped off
the ideas
right they'll take one ingredient two
ingredients from the heavy metal detox
smoothie and then they'll add something
they want to sell or something to it
but this is by far hands down the way to
get Metals out I've said it so many
times over the years and so many people
got their lives back after they got rid
of their metals
Ian Lampson said what about emotionally
charged shakes okay that's really a good
point
okay let's hit it
if your nerves are inflamed like your
vagus nerves
endophrenic nerves and they're inflamed
an adrenaline surge occurs
them nerves are gonna light that up
did you hear that bleep
them nerves are gonna light the freak up
that's what they're gonna do that's what
they're gonna do that's emotionally
charged shakes emotionally charged
nervous system conditions
when you get jacked up because you're
getting emotionally triggered you're
getting triggered by something happening
something that's out of your control
someone said some stuff about you maybe
it's family maybe it's friends maybe
it's co-workers whatever it is maybe
someone's just talking crap and talking
smack and you had enough and you're just
finally pissed and it hits you and
you're just charged up and now you're
just shaking you feel it internally you
feel it in your hands and your knees you
just feel it and you're getting those
emotionally charged shakes
you have to have sensitive nerves for
the most part for those emotionally
charged shakes
sensitive nerves
but
you could be somebody pretty solid
pretty tough
and still get them
but if you're somebody who's really
sensitive you've been through a lot
you're been chronically sick you have
neurological symptoms already you're
dealing with a lot and then you get a
jab at you then you get a trigger at you
oh man you can be going through ticks
and spasms you could be spasming
everywhere you can be shaking you can be
sick your stomach can be flipping you
can be a really really feeling it when
you get an emotional jab an emotional
hit you can really feel it and it could
be a really hard
really hard
and I've seen people go through that
it's really difficult for a lot of
people you can be somebody that's more
solid meaning you're not that sick
you're not that chronically sick you
haven't had enough problems with that
you haven't had that much go on and then
someone gives you a jab someone triggers
you and you got the you got the
emotional shakes you got the emotional
shakes
it's not tanking you it's not taking you
down to the ground
depends on what the news is depends on
what it is that's triggering you what
I'm trying to say is if you're sensitive
and you're hypersensitive and your vagus
nerves are inflamed and your phrenic
nerves are inflamed and you're going
through a lot you're gonna feel it
you're gonna get jacked up from it your
nerves are going to move a little bit
more and they're going to shake a little
bit more they're going to Spas them a
little bit more and you're going to
struggle
reason why
because the adrenaline is going to flood
your system and it's going to touch
those inflamed nerves and those inflamed
nerves are going to go on fire and
they're going to light up they're going
to just light right up
because that adrenaline's just going to
go someone pisses you off
adrenaline just do that like out of the
adrenal
adrenaline just
and then you've got this blend of
adrenaline and I talk about the medical
meaning books it comes out and it's like
it could be a fear-based adrenaline it
could be an anger-based adrenaline it
could be a sad based adrenaline and as
it's coming up coming out it's corrosive
and that corrosive adrenaline lands on
the nerves and if your nerves are
sensitive you're going to be feeling it
and damn that trigger is going to feel
like it's taken you down and taken you
out
cold white spring nobody knew anything
about Metals before the first medical
medium book I have to agree in fact I
was talking to a practitioner the other
day
a well-known practitioner
who's been around who saw everything
before the first medical medium book
came out and that well-known
practitioner told me ain't nobody knew
anything about Metals aw that's what
they said nobody knew anything about
Metals before the first medical medium
book came out in 2015 I concur greatly I
agree and I will even say in
in British English
indeed
anyway
okay
indeed indeed
yes
us Royals we're talking really good
English
language the proper kind
indeed
okay
I just want to say this
nerves can heal
your central nervous system can heal
your vagus nerves can heal your phrenic
nerves can heal your trigeminal nerves
can heal your nerves
can heal
they just need the things they need and
they need time they need some patience
but I understand because when you've
been sick for a long time
and you've been down and out for a long
time patience this grows weary and grows
weary and patience Thins and it Thins
and it Thins
and I understand
I totally get that I do
so even when you've been given an answer
and you've got a direction if your
patience has been out and you've
struggled long enough it's hard to just
say you know what I'm gonna do this you
know what I'm going to commit and I'm
gonna make this happen but I'm promising
this that your nerves want to heal every
single one of your cranial nerves it
causes all the different symptoms
conditions and problems wants to heal so
many people have hearing conditions
they're dealing with like cochlear
nerves so many people are dealing with
so many different nerve problems have a
glossal nerves with taste and tongue
problems and mouth problems you're
dealing with facial nerves facial ticks
and spasms trigeminal nerves
optic nerves too so many people
have uh optic neuritis and they're
dealing with inflamed swollen optic
nerves deep inside their head and
they're suffering from double vision and
all kinds of other issues that are not
explained
and they got lesions on their optic
nerves from all kinds of neurotoxins
from viruses
Emily harridan says could you please
talk about working out while trying to
heal your nerves I feel well enough to
work out and Miss cardio and strength
but need to heal post
plaque tight chest in Tim Okay so
first of all walking if you can walk is
critical anybody
anybody walking is miraculous
it is powerful don't underestimate it on
any level if you're somebody that
wasn't sick at one time in your life and
you're a runner
your Avid exerciser
you do weights whatever you do you might
think that walking is chump change but
it's not
walking
is one of the most powerful ways to
exercise while you're healing with
chronic illness and you're dealing with
sensitivities and chronic issues and
neurological problems
chronic fatigue syndrome and
fibromyalgia walking's a big one that
alone is incredible swimming's another
one too
I know that a lot of pools are hemmed
out big time
they're coming out
they got a lot of anti you know
fungicides in there
for fungus like you know they got a lot
of different you know chlorine High
chlorine levels So It's Tricky but any
kind of swimming in any kind of
situation that's cleaner than that
without the high chem is also really
powerful too walking
swimming
these are two options right there that I
always tell people they should be doing
depending on each person you might be
somebody that's able to start doing some
resistance training
you might be somebody that's doing just
baby steps with resistance
rebounding another great one
it's another thing too cold wide spring
no one is talking about rebounding back
in 2015 and before very few it was one
of those niches that was tucked away and
it wasn't for chronically ill it wasn't
for the chronically ill was it for
anybody it was just one of those things
the mini trampoline they called it
and I talked about it in the medical
medium Book 2015
I talked about rebounding that's another
one for The Chronic chronically ill it's
a great one it could be rebounding for
one minute a day
with counting it you're watching the
minute and you're rebounding for one
minute they gotta understand something
if you're somebody that you're not sick
you're not struggling you might think
this is a joke when I say one minute a
day of rebounding but when you're
struggling you just got off a mattress
Island walking to the bathroom is an
exercise
keeping a pedometer on you is actually
not a bad idea if you're somebody coming
back from chronic illness just seeing
how many steps you take in the house as
you're recovering
you're like okay you know what I took
500 steps today sounds like a joke it's
not a joke for somebody with chronic
illness you could barely take a shower
500 steps is a miracle so I'm saying I'm
taking it Taking us down to that area
and moving us up maybe there's somebody
that just deals with a little fatigue
and you're fighting for it you want to
do your run and you want to do your
cardio you want to do your weights
incredible if you can do that incredible
rehab Takes Time coming back from a
chronic illness it takes time and
patience
so rehabbing from that takes time any
steps you take any walking you do
standing upright so I want to say this
for people who are really sick and
chronically chronically ill they've been
on mattress Island Medical medium term
mattress style and now I hear people
saying it out there
mattress Island
it's okay if walking around your house
and in your kitchen and standing upright
is your exercise because you're laying
flat so much so many people they're sick
for a long term they lay flat all the
time or they lay flat they lay sitting
up right they lay sitting up in their
bed like this
so
standing that alone is an exercise for
somebody who's been bedridden somebody
that's been on mattress Island standing
walking in their house keeping a
pedometer counting the steps all that
matters nothing is small time
50 steps for somebody could be big time
500 steps could be big time keep that in
mind now let's go a little bit more say
somebody they just have some aches and
pains here and there they're trying to
control it with whatever they're doing
out there
right
they can run
they can do some resistance training
they can do some workouts they can get a
trainer whatever it is fine that's great
if you're somebody coming back and
rehabbing some rebounding swimming if
it's possible if you have the resources
the option
riding a bicycle stationary bicycle
walking on a treadmill walking outside
all of that can count all of that is
helpful
and that's the start
it's hard to go just from being in
mattress Island straight to an advanced
yoga class
it's hard to be on mattress Island and
move to an advanced boom a 10 mile run
really really hard gotta have patience
and you get to take one day at a time
and you gotta baby step it for your
recovery
Steph says you say don't let your feet
leave the trampoline when rebounding why
you have much more gravity occur when it
doesn't leave you're utilizing
and manipulating gravity
when you keep your feet still on the
rebounder
you would think it's the opposite you
jump off the rebounder you're gonna have
more gravities you're coming down not
true
because you're you you have lost control
the minute you jump on the rebounder and
this is this is SOC information
okay giving it to you right here
the minute you purposely try to leave
your rebounder you're not in control
anymore
you're not in control anymore
you can do it if you want
that means you can't manipulate gravity
with your own body's Force
you're getting less of a workout when
you leave the trampoline when you leave
the rebounder and you leave the mini
trampoline and you're going up and
you're doing the jump up you want to go
up high off there you just lost control
and you're not now you're you can't
manipulate gravity anymore with your own
Force
with your own body's Force
you've lost control
you get less action happening within the
body less results
less blood flow less lymphatic drainage
less everything
so if you're somebody and you're leaving
your rebounder and you're going up up
down up down like this your lymphatic
system isn't going to be benefited as
much hardly
but when you keep your feet on that
rebounder and you're going down and
you're still stay on that rebounder just
about and you're not really going off of
it you're now controlling and
manipulating gravity itself you're using
your body's Force to do it you're
focused you're concentrating your brain
is actually wired to what you're doing
you want to jump up off that trampoline
and be off the ground your brain all of
a sudden stops working
it stops navigating
you're not able to manipulate gravity
anymore you're not using more
introskeletal muscles and you're not
draining your lymphatic system the way
you should you're not getting anything
you're not getting more play so that's
why it's important to keep your feet on
top of the
mini trampoline on top of the rebounder
important tip
you're welcome
oh
game changing info saying Sue says
I'm honored you think so
thank you for being here
anyway you guys
this concludes today's live I just want
to let you know I'm on Tick Tock check
it out
follow me on Tick Tock when you get a
chance I've been verified on Tick Tock
even though it was verified on Tick Tock
years ago
and had an account that almost had a
million people on there
and now after
poof it disappeared on me many many
months ago we are back on tick tock
we're verified once again and we're on
there so check me out when you get a
chance because I want to eventually do
some exclusive stuff on there telegram I
do exclusive audio messages have you
been checking out the Pride and
Prejudice messages on Telegram
check out Telegram
I beg of you to check out my Telegram
page
telegram account right and sign up to
the medical medium newsletter by the way
I'm talking about how Pride and
Prejudiced the 1995 version
is extremely healing on the nervous
system especially if you're somebody who
struggled with chronic illness on any
level
but I go into more details and how
angels are present during the filming of
The Pride and Prejudice 1995 version I
go into detail on telegram please listen
to the last few telegram messages that I
left the audio messages go search for
them and find them and get caught up on
Pride and Prejudice and what I was
talking about with that Judith says over
there on YouTube Titan Titan of the
chest would happen at night in bed
thanks to you that is gone
laughs
foreign
just a messenger of the information
turning people's lives around
in this world and I'm happy to do so
Kelsey box says see Kelsey aw I
absolutely love watching the healing
tool you told us about
the angels are so amazing yeah The Pride
and Prejudice is a healing tool but not
just the book The Pride Prejudice book
by Jane Austen not just the different
versions that have come out in film no
it's the filming it's what happened
paranormally
would happen Godly
supernaturally what happened during the
1990 1995 Pride and Prejudice
all right
you guys incredible I'm Julie Tuesday
144 says I was able to get off Xanax
by doing the brain meditation
brain meditation
I still listen to the morning cleanse
emerging melatonin magnesium and b12 so
I was able to get off Xanax by doing the
brain meditation the morning cleanse
demergy melatonin magnesium and vimergy
b12 forever grateful
incredible
just incredible
Okay so
Jenny
Jenny says I was prescribed Gabapentin
five years ago for CRPS
could not move my knee no solution from
traditional or alternative medicine
it's hard
was told I am stressed
because it was my thoughts
I've been four years on medical medium I
am healed
I'm actually getting choked up on that
on that comment that you left Jenny
because
people just don't understand unless
they've been through it
wondering Wishin says my nine-year-old
son has vocal and physical ticks
school really sets him back but the
heavy metal detox movie and B12
helped so much especially when we do it
every day
amazing
gold white says the new people coming in
now they have no idea what existed back
before 2015 they have no idea what a
what a desert it was and they also don't
have any idea that if they get sick
enough the answers still aren't out
there
you guys it's been amazing it's been an
honor I want to do more of these I want
to cover symptoms conditions
I want to bring our
registered dietitian out if you guys are
okay
I mean she's pretty cool and she's
pretty hip and she's
she she was really she was at the top of
her sorority
and um
and everybody loved her the University
I think she was forgot what the sorority
she was in but she's a registered
dietitian now and boom she'll be here
once in a while
India says books recommended for lupus
foreign
that's a book right there for Lupus
medical medium book one New Edition new
edition
very important
now I realize
that our registered dietitian that's
going to be coming on regularly hasn't
put out eight
Bibles have turned people's lives around
in the world all these years this last
decade but regardless she's got good
information about protein
anyway you guys
I'm honored
and um crispy perspective says yes bring
her back
we certainly will
be careful what you asked for and wish
for
careful what you wish for
can I juggle these eggs before we go
um
book for arthritis
osteoporosis
honestly I would still do medical meme
New Edition I would do cleanse to heal
pick one for the other
cleanse the heel
so light they're only pamphlets
meanwhile no they're heavy
heavy poundage their Bibles packed with
information
to get your life back they are not
pamphlets and they're not books
talking about eating better
get familiar with these books
but for Alopecia cleanse the heel
so that
had the shakes lately all right guys
know I love you
and please take care of yourselves take
one day at a time do not beat yourselves
up if you got a symptom or a condition
that's nagging
keep focused
try not to get distracted love you guys