[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what out there now as
I've always said who has 10 20 30 years
to wait for answers to their illnesses
life is precious today's a different
show today's about compassion that's
what today's show is about and I I
really am so happy you're here for this
this is a special show and you know I'm
not talking about medical illnesses or
diseases but yet this relates to this
because it's part of it if we don't have
compassion for ourselves and we don't
understand what what even compassion is
if we don't know how to be compassionate
within our our own beings and the ones
around us how are we going to heal it's
a it's a part of healing all of the
illnesses it's a part of healing all of
the diseases it's a part of healing our
conditions and symptoms it's critical
really critical now please understand
with this show what's going on here I
never claim to be a big Guru I never
claim to be um you know an enlightened
one I never have I'm a student of spirit
I'm a student of spirit when I'm talking
about compassion I'm reteaching myself
in this moment along with giving you any
information I can from Spirit spirit's
been teaching me about compassion and
and and giving me all the information
since I was a child before I can even
pronounce it I'd hear the word from
Spirit and I couldn't even pronounce it
I'd be like comp what is this and
I'd be like and I would and I would have
to say the word and and it doesn't mean
I have enough of it it doesn't mean I've
worked hard on it or I'm compassionate
enough to myself I try I work on it I
work on with everything Spirit has given
me and I and I Pat myself on the back
when I can and I need you to to do that
too and I need you to learn about
compassion because it's so critical to
your healing it's so critical to knowing
what compassion even means because if
you don't know what it means it's it's
hard to even touch it or grasp it and
you know some people might argue and say
well you either have it or you don't
some people have it or they you don't no
no no we all we all can access it we all
can access compassion we all have it in
us somewhere it just needs to come out
and we can create it if we don't think
we have it in us we can create it we can
learn about it and that's the big thing
and so you know it's so I'm learning too
from Spirit all the time with compassion
I'm learning too too and and because
because yeah because I get busy I do
things I'm always listening to Spirit
about information for people doing
readings and everything else both
emotional and compass with emotional and
spiritual and physical but the point is
is that you know I can also I can use a
dose I can use a dose of spirit's
information about compassion meaning a
full show after the show I'm going to be
like yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I need to
do more of that with what Spirit wants
us all to do I need to do more of this
what Spirit needs us to do because
because you're never there's never you
know it's there's never enough there's
never enough where okay that's it that's
all you need you're compassionate one
time of your life and that's all you
need and you move on and that's it no
it's never enough we have to be we have
to be more invested into understanding
and and and knowing compassion so let's
go into this I'm saying this because
it's so important this whole thing this
is I'm really excited about this show
really excited about the show now I know
that that many of you that know my book
The First Medical medium book I talk a
little bit about compassion because
spirit is that source to begin with and
spirit has always known that I'm flawed
I'm flawed in many ways Spirit has
always known that I am and you know I'm
a human being SP you know Spirit chose
me to have the gift not because I'm this
uh miraculous person that's not it at
all the irony is not because I'm the
smartest person because I'm not I'm not
the smartest person you guys probably
know that by now and and spirit when
Spirit chose me to have the gift when I
was a child it wasn't because Spirit
thought oh here's an enlightened one to
have the gift that wasn't it Spirit gave
me the gift because Spirit knew that
there was something inside of me and it
wasn't compassion it wasn't compassion
Spirit knew excuse me that there was
something inside of me that could hang
in there for the ride that's why I was
chosen there was something inside of me
I had a tough Edge that there was
something that would stand the test of
time in order to be able to give you the
information to be the messenger to give
people the information with chronic
illness to get them the information they
need to heal and spirit my my throat's a
little horse I've been talking so much
lately so just bear with me Spirit knew
that I could handle it or had a
possibility of handling it because when
you get this gift when you're a young
age you don't want to live you don't
want to stay here you don't want to be
here
anymore so you don't want to you don't
want to be here because it's too hard
it's too hard to constantly see all day
long or wherever you're going as you're
growing up everybody's suffering and
it's tooo hard to see their illnesses
it's too hard to live with that Non-Stop
and to hear Spirit Non-Stop and to hear
a voice from the outside of your ear
going into your ear Non-Stop and never
ending because it's always there meaning
spirit is always there he's always
giving me the information whether I like
it or not so there were it wasn't
because I was an enlightened child that
I receive the gift just don't get
confused with that it wasn't because I
was going to be a guru or I was a guru
and I was a chosen one no not at all it
was because the people who do get given
this gift over the centuries don't make
it too long I almost didn't make it
because you don't want to be here with
this gift because you can't function as
a normal human being you get the snow
blind which is the light blindness
constantly because you're doing readings
all the time you can't you can't be in
public places too too long because the
readings will eventually just be too
much and too much much too much there's
so many reasons I mean I could name list
100 reasons why it's difficult but
that's not what this is about I'm
talking about the whole thing about why
I got the gift and how I have to be the
messenger of compassion for you the
messenger of spirit's compassion so that
you have a chance to move forward and
you have a chance to do what you need to
do and take care of yourselves and look
out for your loved ones it's all part of
the same thing about getting the message
and information about what's going on
with health so you have that information
knowledge is power and in The Compassion
situation The Compassion moment here
that's knowledge is power too it it
means that much it makes that much of a
difference so when I was younger it
didn't mean I had any compassion when I
was a child and growing up turning into
a teenager I had to learn about what it
was and what it was what it meant of
course I felt bad for people I felt
their suffering it was difficult I still
do now with every bit about it but
tapping into the compassionate side a
part of what unconditional is that I'm
going to go into is is is is was a big
key for me and I've done that on and off
with everything I have and I've done
that and I've did everything I can in
that realm but I still need work too we
all do Spirit knew I was flawed when I
was given the gift in the sense that you
know I wasn't this this enlightened
being Spirit knew that that wasn't what
it is Spirit knew I was tough that I
could handle I could handle the beatings
I could take a beating a real good
licking I could take a kicking I could
take the crap kicked out of me and
that's what Spirit knew that I had that
I possessed I could get stepped on and
and and and stand back up and dust
myself off I could be pushed I could be
pushed aside I could be pushed on the
ground I could be pushed around I could
be bullied I could be smacked around
Spirit knew I was tough Spirit knew I
could handle it when I was born Spirit
knew what soul I was and who I was
Spirit knew it may not be great
Enlightenment Spirit knew I might not be
the greatest revered Guru in the world
Spirit knew all that Spirit just knew I
was going to be a good messenger a good
messenger and spirit knew this Spirit
has compassion towards me has compassion
towards me knows I've had it hard knows
I didn't have it easy knows what my job
is in this lifetime to try to finish out
in this lifetime with the best capacity
I have and the best ability I have to
get you the information I can and spirit
knows that Spirit has compassion for me
and I have to realize that that Spirit
actually has compassion for me and it
matters to me I have to have comp
compassion too for myself for what I've
been through what I struggled through
for what you've struggled through for
everything you've gone through I have
compassion for you I do I do I do I've
worked on it since a child I haven't
been perfect it doesn't mean I've had it
all the time and every minute of my life
but I've worked on having it and I want
to tell you all about it a little bit
you know when I was a child and
compassion told me so compassion which a
spirit told me that compassion
is the understanding of
suffering that's what spirit said to me
compassion is the understanding of
suffering what does that mean it means
you you know compassion means that you
understand somebody's suffering that you
you at least understand it I've known a
lot of people out there they don't even
understand somebody's suffering meaning
like what get up go go to the doctor
what are you doing oh you're making it
up oh you're just weak oh it's all in
your head whatever it is and they're not
tapping into comp comp passion when they
do that that's the first thing
compassion is the understanding of
suffering it's a big one compassion is
the
soul the soul of so many things it's the
soul of Truth and honor and purpose it's
that
powerful compassion is the soul of peace
and joy and and it matters now you have
to understand you know
it this is about having compassion for
yourself it's not just about having
compassion for others that that can
happen that can happen naturally I need
you to have it for yourself and I'm
going to talk about that a little bit
you know Spirit told me that God is love
and that is ancient and we know that we
know God is love you know God is love
now whatever God is to you some people
say well you know what God to me is
something different God to me is a light
in this guy God to me is a Creator God
to me is the universe God to me
everybody's got a different thing going
on but whatever that is okay it's love
God is love but this is the important
thing I have to tell you about that's
powerful God is not love
alone God is unconditional love you know
that you know that right and the human
mind us us humans will always put
conditions upon our love you know that
you know we'll put conditions upon the
love for others you know we'll put
conditions upon the loves the love for
ourselves there's going to be conditions
on even the love for ourself we can't
help it that's what US humans do okay we
we think we can feel unconditional
love but if we do feel unconditional
love that means compassion was alongside
of our love see
see unconditional love is compassion
plus love put together it's both of
those it's compassion plus love put
together that's what unconditional love
is that's the human version of
unconditional love God's unconditional
love is much bigger than that I'm sorry
to say that but much bigger much bigger
much bigger than that God's
unconditional love is bigger than than
human's unconditional
love but even hum hum have a whole
difficult problem we have a whole
difficult situation we can't T we can't
tap into that unconditional love ever
because we're wrapped up in love without
the compassionate side mixed in because
that's what makes things unconditional
is when compassion is then ignite it's
it's when it's combined when it's joined
it forces into love when compassion is
both with love that is
when it's a human's version your version
of unconditional love that you can have
that's when it's us our version of
unconditional love you can have so I
know that's really intense this is a
deep show this is no joke I'm going to
give you information from Spirit I've
wrote some of this in some of the books
too and life-changing Foods I've talked
about this about what's going on like
compassion is not empathy right you know
that because if I've I've written about
that compassion is not empathy empathy
is is something that has expiration date
you know like a carton of spoiled milk
you know if someone has been suffering
for a long time and you have empathy for
that person it could wax and Wayne it
could sour over time it has an
expiration date
unless compassion is really in there see
because compa empathy is not compassion
but we confuse that so what we do is we
have this whole thing about love we love
ourselves we follow in love love love
love love
love but and then we have empathy mixed
in with it but it can go sour it has an
expiration date even with people that
are in love it just it can die you I
can't tell you how many people who have
been ill for a long time and their story
has been like they had their family
rallying for them they had their friends
rallying for them they had people
rallying for them and they kind of
dissipated it dissipated whether it's
months or years later because empathy
has an expiration date even if they love
you it has an expiration date compassion
is not sympathy don't get confused with
sympathy too it's another whole problem
I've written about that's because
sympathy has strings attached it has
strings attached that's what that is
it's like alone it's like alone
compassion doesn't have strings attached
compassion isn't like a loan or a bank
loan or you're loaning something or
you're loaning somebody a lawn mower or
you're Lo somebody a shovel so they can
shovel their driveway there's a string
attached to that you feel bad that your
neighbor can't shovel their Drive shovel
their porch out because they their
shovel broke so you give them a shovel
you kind of you see I'm sympathetic to
that here's a shovel here take this
shovel but don't keep that shovel don't
don't keep keep it that's not yours I
want that back someday that's what that
is that's sympathy we can't get that
confused with compassion that means that
you don't have compassion about your
neighbor not being able to shuel out
their porch stoop you do you're not it's
not about compassion there it's about
sympathy we can't we can't get that
confused with oh that's a compassionate
person they want they want that person
to be okay there no we got to be careful
with that it's not really what it
is it's like when you lend somebody that
sympathetic ear you know when you lend
them that sympathetic ear there's an
understanding that she or he the other
person will lend that favor back someday
we lend that sympathetic ear back
someday I owe you one you owe me one
that's what sympathy is that's not
compassion you owe me one I gave you
that I gave you that I listen to you
when I listen to you at that time you
owe me some listening that's sympathy
that see there's a difference there I
know this is heavy duty I know this is
like
I know I'm hitting you hard with this
stuff and and look look I I'm hitting
you hard with it but I'm I'm re reesing
it myself if that's even a word I'm
digesting it all over again constantly
from Spirit I have to I'm a human I'm
like you we're all we're all like each
other you know so the whole thing with
sympathy is like I owe you one you owe
me one and it's a it's a it's a tricky
one because if you have a friend that
nurtures somebody during a breakup so if
you have a breakup if you broke broke up
with a relationship and someone nurtures
you it's there's an understanding there
it's
transactional that means you better be
doing that for me if I have a breakup
you better be doing that for me
compassion has no strings attached
there's no I owe you and you owe me
compassion is doesn't have a cell by
date like that boiled container of
milk when you received compassion
there's no loan shark there's no bank
loan there's no lone shark or somebody
with a baseball bat that's going to
break your legs if you don't come up
with that lot of money that you
borrowed compassion won't hunt you down
like a rat and snap you in a trap
compassion won't do that compassion
won't want you back with interest with
interest interest paid I want you back I
want to own your soul and I want
interest on top of that
compassion is not like empathy and
sympathy and those aren't bad things
they they have their places don't get me
wrong they have their
places but compassion is nothing to mess
around with it's a whole different game
and it isn't a game that's the whole
point because empathy and sympathy is
like a
game compass is not a game it's not it
is something different it's
vital compassion can even be
contagious compassion is
lifechanging compassion opens up the
heart compassion con can change the soul
of someone compassion doesn't
necessarily reside in somebody's
Soul it doesn't always reside in their
soul like oh that person is just their
soul is filled to compassion no it it
can fill it can restore a soul it can
heal a soul compassion is more powerful
than our souls
themselves than our than our souls
themselves you need to know that
compassion heals the heart it can fill
the
heart some of us have compassionate
sources deep within us and they've
gotten buried along the way they've
gotten buried they've gotten dumped on
and we can tap into that compassion
Source some people don't have compassion
that's deep inside them but they can
still get it they can still get it and
restore it or they can Infuse themselves
with it they can receive it they can
ingest it they can take it they can have
it inside of
them and you know when I was young and
when I was a child Spirit knew this guy
here this guy here he needs he needs
work there's no doubt he there's work to
do for this guy there's no doubt meaning
he needs self- transformational work
there's no question he needs
Enlightenment there's no doubt but we're
picking him we're picking him for one
reason he can hang in here with this
gift he can listen to The Voice every
day as a child and not lose
it and not lose himself he can still he
can still hold on to himself and hang in
there even if it's by a thread even if
it's by a thread I almost left a couple
of times you know the story about my dog
when my dog went out into the ocean and
I went out there in that cold water and
and I and I knew I knew I I knew I was
going down I knew I was done for and I'd
never even know you guys now I'd never
even be able to do what I do I'd never
be able to whatever if that happened and
I would only only people that would have
known of me and my information from
Spirit and the messages would have been
been the people in the first 19 20 years
of my life and that would have been it
but I I've I stood the test of time and
I'm here a lot of times I thought about
hey this is too hard but Spirit knew
there was something inside of me now
spirit said the the re the real test
after that is going to be getting this
guy to build up his compassionate
reserves and I've had to work on that my
whole life and I just want to share that
and have you do that too why not why not
and you know what I bet you some of you
if not most of you or many of you or
would ever probably have more
compassionate reserves than I've had or
have you probably would blow me out of
the water and many of you are probably
lacking it and diminished it or
diminishing in it even way way way under
me diminishing it of it and need a
refill I need a refill all the time so
that's why this is such a powerful
powerful powerful show and I love this
when we become Frugal with our
compassion when we become withholding of
it that's not good
either that's a really difficult thing
that can happen we treat our compassion
like it was like we were rationing it we
were carefully rationing
it that's not a good thing either when
we micromanage its
distribution we come become trapped with
barriers when we micromanage our
compassion I'll give you a little bit of
compassion but it won't give you a
little bit of compassion I won't I'll
give this person just a little bit maybe
I'll give this person some another day
maybe I'll just only give a little bit
to this person maybe just a tiny bit
when we rash it maybe I'll only give
myself a little bit of compassion I'll
just give myself a tiny pat on the back
how about that a little tiny Pat not a
big Pat right not a big Pat just give
myself a little you know you know that
isn't good either we get trapped like a
rat in a trap we get trapped like a
raccoon in a in a in a one of those
metal traps when you're trying to get a
raccoon out of your garage you're trying
to get a raccoon out of your garage you
know it's we get get stuck because what
happens is we ration it we ration it on
ourselves and there's a barrier there's
a
barrier so this is just a little bit of
what I'm going to talk about with
compassion we're going to go into some
other stuff too we're we're we're
rediscovering compassion within
ourselves we're rediscovering it if we
have it already in there we're going to
reignite it if we don't have any at all
I've run across people people they don't
have a speck of it a speck of it and I
and and I was supposed to feel good
about myself because I had a good hunk
of it inside of me lots of
compassion and then I've run across
people with zero compassion so you would
think I would walk away saying whoa ho
ho ho whistling
away happy because I'm so loaded with
compassion and proud of myself and and
no I I I felt terrible terrible for this
person or the people I've come across
with no compassion inside of them and I
felt kind of like okay kind of guilty I
had so much what do I do what do I do
how do I what do I do the first thing I
was was having compassion for the person
who didn't have any at all and I try to
instill what I could and spread the
message because it's that important and
when someone someone's dried up from it
or doesn't have any of it at all it's
sad it's truly sad so you know look hey
do you have a cup of tea herbal tea this
is intense this is really this is really
you know this is tough stuff this is
tough stuff so let's get into it a
little bit so I was saying
earlier God is love right we know that
we know that and but God is not just
love alone God is unconditional love
know
that the human mind which is our minds
puts conditions on everything on
ourselves and on others we can't help it
we can't help it there's no
question we think we can feel
unconditional
love but we can only feel unconditional
love if we've tapped into compassion
alongside of our love they both have to
be
there compassion plus love that's our
ver version of real unconditional love
that's our version of it this is going
to be intense right here okay this is
you can't find
peace unless you have some
compassion you can't find peace unless
someone
bestowed generously compassion upon
you peace for someone who has no
compassion is when someone gives them
compassion I know that's intense when
someone gives you compassion it can give
someone with no compassion peace it can
give somebody suffering with hatred upon
themselves when someone hates
themselves and they hate their existence
or they just don't like their body or
they just don't like who they are or
they don't believe in themselves or
they've lost all confidence which I'm
going to cut into the confidence thing
you got to hear about this this is
intense
from
Spirit when someone denies themselves of
anything because they hate themselves so
much and someone bestows compassion
towards them you wouldn't believe what
can
happen it's unbelievable the miracle
that can
occur often when people think they have
compassion for themselves it's really
confidence So This Is Where It's Tricky
right here just look out hold on to this
hold on to this get ready okay when
someone thinks they have compassion for
themselves it's really just confidence
and that's a mistake made all the time
and I'll tell you why it's a mistake
this is unbelievable What Spirit has
taught me over the years and what I'm
about to share with
you that's what we build in the world
right now it's confidence not compassion
do not get those confused because
they're confused they're confused the
minute something goes wrong like in
someone's life like love confidence goes
away did you know that did you know that
confidence goes away so therefore what
they thought was compassion
self-compassion towards themselves
disappears completely it goes
away you can shape your whole lifetime
around confidence believing in yourself
because of your achievements and listen
there is a good thing about that too I'm
not trying to cut that in half I'm not
trying to tear that tear that down I'm
not trying to ruin that I'm just saying
you can shape your whole lifetime upon
confidence 100% where it's all about
confidence and not realize it you can
believe in yourself and in one flick of
a switch just like when you turn a light
off the darkness of self-doubt can take
its place and Destroy every last bit of
that confidence and tear it down a
lifetime of confidence ripped down
thrown down the toilet thrown in the
garbage confidence is important please
don't get me wrong we should all hold on
to it when we
can if it's all you got you hold on to
it if you have no compassion and didn't
realize it you've mistaken it with
confidence it's okay you hold on to that
confidence and you don't you try not to
let it go you hold on to it if you
can but when people hit him a chronic
illness and their confidence in
themselves turns to
zero it turns to zero it drops it's gone
it wasn't compassion in the end it
wasn't self-compassion that was confused
with confidence it was confidence it was
just confidence in whatever was going on
in their life I see it with young people
all the time I see it with college
students that get sick I see it with
people that are starting their lives
after college and they get sick and they
got hashimotos thyroiditis and they get
fatigue and they don't know what it is
and doctors are giving them all these
prescriptions and their family members
or their spouses or their boyfriends or
girlfriends are kind of like acting
weird because of it and their confidence
drops and drops and drops and drops and
there's no self-compassion involved
something else takes place self-hatred
the confidence disappears it waxes it
wanes it disappears it diminishes
confidence is important don't get me
wrong it's how we struggle through
school and get get our grades done it's
how we become good students it's how we
we we work in the workplace it's how we
try to build our careers we try to have
confidence in what we do at work but if
if self-compassion if compassion isn't
mixed in it if it's not in there in any
way all it takes is one failure one
failure okay one failure and boom
confidence is destroyed a lifetime of
confidence can be destroyed then you're
trying to get an empa an empathetic ear
a sympath athetic ear from someone a
friend or a family member to build your
confidence back up but it doesn't even
mean still compassion is
involved I'm just saying how important
self-compassion is it's a savior it's a
Lifeboat it is a life raft it is one of
those those those Circle things with
those donuts you throw into the water
with a rope on it when someone's
drowning drowning and failure and no
confidence anymore even though their
whole life was based on building conf
confidence just like athletes build
confidence in themselves and all of a
sudden they have a failure and that
confidence just disappears completely
100% but if there's no self-compassion
in there it makes it that much
harder we should hold on to confidence
whenever we
can but it doesn't have the strength of
something else you need to know this it
doesn't have the strength of compassion
please understand this this is all
wisdom from
Spirit wisdom from Spirit
Spirit you know I I'm impressed all the
time in the sense where I'm like Spirit
you just blew me away again you blew me
away again because if I didn't have you
giving me this information I wouldn't
even I wouldn't even know any of
this and it blows me away because
spirit's talking to me right now you
have to understand that as we're sitting
here all together spirit's giving me
this information I just want you to know
how important that is
too confidence is not the answer to
self-hatred spirit
says confidence doesn't give us peace it
gives us temporary
peace because the minute confidence is
broken from a failure of any kind or any
kind of struggle or loss or any kind of
struggle with our health on any level
like if it was some kind of ill illness
chronic illness or autoimmune disease or
we're told our body's attacking itself
when it's not right the autoimmune
chapter in thyroid
healing when we're told our body's
destroying itself we lose confidence in
our body and without self-compassion we
just destroyed our our peace is
destroyed that's why I call the medical
industry with their
theories their misbegotten theories
they're misguided theories they call
them peace destroyers peace destructors
that's what I call those and they get
they bleed on to alternative medicine to
the functional medicine doctors without
knowing by accident destroy the peace in
others
too but not understanding how the body
doesn't attack itself because it was
just a theory and it's not
correct we lose confidence when we get
in illness when we're sick too long we
lose our peace or peace of mind or peace
in our soul or peace in our hearts our
family members lose the peace around us
it happens I'm just being truthful but
it doesn't have to happen this way you
don't have to lose your peace you don't
have to lose all
this it's okay if you lose your
confidence but if you have your
self-compassion if you have compassion
what does that mean and I'm going to
talk about it if you have your
compassion for yourself in there a
little bit it won't hurt when the
confidence is busted in half it won't
hurt
because you truly do love yourself in a
different way not in a fake
way in a real way we're going to talk
about that in a minute man that's really
intense if there's no compassion then
your confidence drops away the damage
becomes extreme to your soul and
body if you hold that compassion
internally if you hold it
within you can lose the confidence in it
won't phase you you can lose it and it
won't phase you you can fail at anything
you can get
sick you can be let down but your
compassion to yourself
remains whether you believe in
yourself or you just lost the belief in
yourself compassion will hold it all
together it holds it all together for
you compassion helps you heal compassion
from others to you to fill that
compassion Bank helps you heal so if you
can't touch this and you can't you can't
get a handle on what I'm trying to tell
you here but you can I know you can it
doesn't matter I know you can get a
handle on this I know you can touch
compassion it's easy it's easier than
you think it's easier than you think
it's already happening right now I could
feel it right now within every one of
you as I speak and as we're talking and
sitting here right now together in this
very moment I can feel it in all of you
that it's already it's already your
compassion meter is rising towards
yourself and maybe even towards others
it's
Rising I can feel it you feel it you
feel it just just relax for one second
just
relax do you feel anything do you feel
anything you do I know you do I know you
do you feel it you have it within you
you're also receiving compassion I know
you are your bank and your meter your
compassion bank that meter that well
that compassionate well is actually
Rising inside of you right now and I
know it is and I know it is I know
you're you're feeling that I know it's
rising inside of you right
now I know that for a
fact and it's going to heal you it is
it's deep healing when that
self-compassion comes in it's deep
healing and I know it's
happening and I know it's happening what
compassion can do is it can bring peace
to to your soul it can bring peace to
your soul and I know it's doing that and
I know it will continue to do that
listen to the show after this listen to
this show listen to the recording of the
show afterwards and listen to it again
because there's so much information it's
so
intense so listening to it it's
good Another Part Of Peace another piece
of
peace is having compassion for
yourself and that compassion brings
peace to your soul it will and it does
and if if you have compassion to someone
else it'll bring peace to their soul it
will it's the
creator of Peace it is the creation of
Peace that's what compassionate spirit's
telling
me and you need to know that peace isn't
just about peace on Earth it's not just
about and this is coming from Spirit
peace isn't just about peace on Earth
you know peace isn't just about war and
violence and hatred and trying to stop
that out there that's not what peace is
just about that's not at
all peace is about having compassion to
yourself so your soul can receive that
peace it's about giving somebody else
peace in their soul through compassion
the presence of
compassion and that's really what it's
about so listen love is a big topic
these days and it's a big one and we're
going to cut through it right here a
little bit with what time we have left
we're going to work on
this
self-compassion is not self-love you
need to know the difference it's not
self-love self-compassion is not
self-love they're not the same thing
they're not I promise you they're not
you need to know this self-love is okay
loving yourself is okay it's not a bad
thing if it gets you by you use that
until the compassion comes self-love see
see self-love it's about loving who you
are and it's about appreciating who you
are and that's what's good about
selflove it's about appreciating who you
are and and loving Who You Are
and it can reach into accepting who you
are loving yourself means you're
accepting who you are okay it seems to
work
perfectly for some people that
everything is going
perfect everything and it seems to work
for some people that need a quick remedy
when things aren't going so great but
when you really go through a through a
true hardship when you go through an
illness when you get sick when a family
member gets get sick when something else
happens when struggling happens when a
suffering happens the game changes
completely you know what self-love turns
into something else self-love doesn't
mean you're granting yourself healing
through self-compassion it's not the
same thing self-compassion is not the
same thing as self- Lov at
all
self-love cannot Grant you peace alone
it's not something that can grant you
peace in your soul is self-love alone
and because I'll tell you why when you
focus on loving yourself it can
accidentally bleed over until in into
loving yourself more than anybody else
around you have you ever met anybody
like that they love themselves more than
anybody else around them and it's
evident and you know it you know it
that's what happens when compassion is
not in there that's what happens love
love just so you know this is not what
keeps two people together in a
relationship it's not love I'm going to
tell you right now it's not love that
keeps two people together when you're in
the throws of a new romance and
everything's all hot nice and the
finances are flowing or life is Rosy or
whatever love can be plenty to hold it
together to hold the relationship
together especially when it's in that
honeymoon stage love can be plenty but
when a challenge comes along and this is
why we have what we have out there right
now is so much hardship with
relationships and people when a hardship
comes
along when a challenge comes along love
is no longer strong enough to keep to
keep a relationship together because
human love is not the creator of Peace
human love can be the creator of hell
too for people I've seen it love is no
longer enough how many relationships I
love love you I love you I love you I
love you until someday something goes
wrong no matter what that is and the
members of the coup will become mortal
enemies loving another can turn into
hating the person very
fast unless unless I'm telling you right
now compassion is involved and that's
how it changes the game that's how it
changes
everything when
compassion is involved in love the
relationship ship can go through a hard
time and love won't turn into hate or
turn into non love anymore or just turn
into
disinterest it won't when compassion is
involved compassion is the
glue component it's the
glue to a
relationship it keeps love
alive it stops love from turning into
hatred or sour
grapes and I hate using grapes as a term
because grapes is such a healing
beautiful fruit it's such a healing
beautiful fruit I don't like using
grapes as a maybe something maybe we'll
come up sour
eggs sour eggs sour chicken
eggs if
you if you look at love as a fruit as an
apple compassion is its core compassion
is its core how about that that's a lot
better and same goes for self-love you
can't love yourself without having
self-compassion or it can flip to hating
yourself how many people worked on
self-love and and it flips on hating
themselves does that happen to you did
it happen to you that's easy that can
happen to all of us oh my God I love
myself I love myself I'm okay I love
myself oh my God I hate myself it can
happen too easy because self-compassion
wasn't involved it wasn't in the mix it
wasn't
there if suddenly you're facing a
chronic illness or an emotional
challenge selflove can vanish it can
disappear it can disappear like nothing
has ever disappeared before in your life
it can literally slip through like sand
in your hand at the beach it could do it
could slip through in your hand like
water and guess what takes its place
when it disapp appears when that self-
Lov disappears guess what takes its
place self-hatred takes its place just
Falls right in there it's one of the
greatest obstacles to peace it's one of
the greatest obstacles to peace with
when an athlete is
injured self- love can turn into
self-hatred in an instant I've seen it
over and over
again I've seen it the mom who could
take care of everything the mother who
can do everything she can exercise she
can run to the gym she can pick up the
kids at soccer practice she can make
dinner she can take care of her husband
and all the bills in the house and she
could run the household and she can run
and go get a part-time job or not even
whatever it is she can take care of
everything until symptoms got in the
mom's way and made her doubt
herself and made her feel like a
failure that should never happen ever
ever ever happen ever it just shouldn't
it shouldn't we have a little compassion
inside of us we get that compassion well
built up and that's not going to happen
it's not it's not if someone around us
has just a little bit of compassion a
fraction just a a fiber of compassion a
fiber a fiber it can stop that Mom from
feeling that way even if she has no
compassion towards herself whatsoever on
any level and all all she had was
self-love and that's all she had if
that's all she had if someone else had a
fiber of compassion to share it could
ignite a spark and stop that self-hatred
it can stop that self-hatred when we get
chronically ill and we get told that
it's our genes oh man you better have
that compassionate compassionate well
get started somehow because that evil
evil not
from the medical industry will try to
tear you down and make you think you're
faulty just because they don't know
what's truly behind chronic illness and
they make everything look so rosy with
all their geneticists and they make
things everything look so low with the
literature they put out that's paid for
and funded and all
rigged and they're going to make you
feel like you're
bad because that's the name of the game
it's to break down whatever you got left
in you whatever confidence you got left
in you what whatever compassion you got
left in you but compassion won't break
down under that they just want to break
down whatever self-love whatever
confidence and selflove you have inside
of you they want to break that down and
tear tear it
apart just telling you right now take a
deep breath the misguided attempts to
explain illness out
there like saying you you caused it on
yourself or it's your genes or your body
attacking itself can make you hate every
last fiber in your body they're the
ultimate peace destroyers they're the
ultimate Soul destroyers body mind and
soul and do not get suckered into it and
if you have a little bit of
self-compassion building up you pat
yourself on the back you listen to this
show over and over again and you get
that little bit built up and little bit
and some of you may have a ton of it
already and I wish I can sh I wish I
could take some of that for myself give
me some of that self-compassion I'll
take some more for myself
because I'm human too and I'm up against
all the same things you guys are against
just because I hear spirit and spirit
knows every bit of this powerful
information every bit of the information
to get you better well I use it for
myself to get me better too I use it for
myself to build that compassion at well
too that's the whole point and maybe I'm
lucky and blessed in that way because I
get to take spirit's information right
there and he reminds me all the time so
I can work on keeping my compassionate
levels there keeping it there and I
understand that so that that is great
but I can give that to you too you can
give that back to me too we can all have
this but don't let the peace destroyers
ruin your mind body and soul and don't
let them just don't let them suck you
dry have some self-compassion get it
deeply rooted if it not already
is is really
important really important
stuff so we lose touch with all the
compassion for
ourselves if we even held compassion to
begin with it can disappear when one
acre pain does
come
but we have the ability to ignite it and
Spark it we have the ability to spark it
back up it's strong it's powerful if it
was there before like I said it can
ignite faster and easier like never
before the further away self-compassion
feels we feel something's wrong with us
remember we just need to bring it back
to reel it back in to pull it back in we
just need to bring the self-compassion
back into ourselves we need to bring it
back in because the further it goes the
way the further we think something's
wrong with me something's wrong with you
something's wrong with her something's
wrong with him something's wrong with
them we think something's wrong the
minute compassion starts to drift away
and Falls away and further away and
peace destroyers like I said originally
just a couple of minutes ago can push it
away further don't let it push you away
from compassion whatever you do grab on
to it reach out pull it back in come on
and do what that Me Now call on upon the
Angels if you have to call upon the
Angels any of the Angels any of them
call upon any of the Angels now and just
get that compassion bring it back in you
can do it bring it back in the
self-hatred will go away you won't
become prey to the misguided medical
belief systems out there and also other
belief systems too that are out there
misguided spiritual belief systems
misguided all kinds of belief systems
they can't destroy your peace and
destroy you they can't take that
compassion completely way grab onto it
and Pull It in pull it in with me and
bring it into yourself right back into
your soul and into your heart you can do
it I can do it with you let's do it
together and let's bring it back in cuz
I feel it I'm reach your hand out right
now reach your hand out as we speak
reach your hand out spirit's telling me
right now reach your hand out okay
compassion is right in front of you it's
a warm comfy little blanket that's nice
and warm and cozy grab onto that blanket
you see it you can see it in your vision
it's a comfy warm cuddly blanket that's
safe that's safe and grab on to it
spirit says and bring it in spirit is
giving you the identification of what
compassion can look like so you can
actually grab it and harness it it's
that warm cup that warm cup of liquid
that warm cup that drink when you're
freezing cold and standing outside and
someone just handed you a cup of verbal
tea grab on to it grab on to that cozy
cuddly blanket grab onto that light
compassion is a light I'm giving you
every image that you can use spirit says
grab onto a light right there and pull
it in and bring compassion back into
your heart back into your soul back into
your being bring it in it's there and
you got it all you need is a little bit
do not get disappointed thinking you
don't have any just a little all you
need is a fiber all you need is one
little speck of light of it it's all you
need that's it that's it that's all you
need that's all you need just grab it
and you got it in your hand open your
hand hand out when you're reaching out
grabb onto that warm cuddly blanket grab
onto that light grab onto that warm cup
of
tea grab onto it make a fist and bring
it in and it's in your hand right now
bring it to your heart into your chest
bring it to your soul Let The Compassion
enter into your soul right now deep in
there and you got a little bit of it
already it's there I promise you it's
there and guess what the people
destroyers will not take it away when
they come and they come and they say oh
it's your it's your fault it's your
fault it's all you to blame or when you
get that injury and your confidence goes
away or you something happens at work
and you lost your confidence oh no no no
the compassion is there it's to take
over it's a take over it's to replace
confidence so confidence can come back
over time just have that
confidence but listen The Compassion is
really going to keep it all together and
it's going to make sure that nothing
nothing goes away completely and only
grows from there and gets stronger and
stronger and stronger so your selflove
turns into unconditional love for others
and for yourself it becomes compassion
and you pat yourself on the back instead
of self-love that dissipates and turns
to nothing so that relationships you
have get stronger because you have
compassion for your that person and that
person it's infectious they might get a
little compassion too you take one day
at a time
I love you guys dearly and um hey the
show was too deep just listen to it
again and again it's deep that's why I'm
saying that it blows me away I love
spirit I love you guys God bless you and
take care okay all right bye now