[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information in
both alternative and conventional
medicine in chronic illness so involving
and regarding chronic illness very
important to understand somebody said to
me the other day they said well you
don't know anything about you know
rocket science and medicine you know
rocket science and medicine I know it's
a good one and you know putting them
both together like that and I said okay
oh I didn't know I didn't know science
and research knew everything about
chronic illness I didn't know that I
didn't know they had it all in the bag I
didn't know they had it all fixed that's
new to me thanks for telling me do you
know any information about that because
this is is amazing I didn't know they
can they fixed hundreds and hundreds of
autoimmune conditions hundreds and
hundreds of symptoms that are people are
suff suffering with 250 million
Americans alone are walking around
mysterious symptoms or diagnosed with a
bogus tag and label and told that it's
genes or something oh I didn't know it
was all kind of like done and fixed and
science had it all together all fixed
great thanks thanks for educating me
thank you thank you well science of
research doesn't have it figured out
bottom line you guys know that why is
anybody sick why I mean I mean it's
unbelievable I say this all the time I
run into young people all the time that
have been convinced entr trenched in the
fact that science and research is so
Advanced that technology is so Advanced
and they're using all their devices and
everything else and they're in school
and they're using devices in school and
and you know and the car's got all these
computers in it and they just they think
everything's figured out and then when
they start getting sick they're like
Blown Away young people are like blown
away like wait a minute you mean I have
to live with this symptom I just can't
go to the doctor and take an antibiotic
and it all go away and they're like
literally blow they're crushed literally
crushed and then the Awakening starts to
happen which shouldn't have to happen
with young people they should not be
forced into an Awakening at a young age
meaning like an Awakening of like oh my
God this world sucks yeah this world
sucks unbelievable it should not happen
that way for young people cuz it breaks
their Spirit it literally breaks their
Spirit wait a minute my body's attacking
myself what does that mean I'm 19 years
old I'm 15 years old I'm 21 years old
what do what do you mean my body's
attacking itself it's destroying it CS
it's destroying itself you don't have
the answers this is unbelievable you
know and it happens every day every day
Millions though of Americans overall all
ages it happens every day so science and
research doesn't have it figured out you
know what I mean I noticed the trolls
are all into like he knows nothing
science he doesn't it's science when you
see like the Clones I call them clones
you know cuz I don't like calling them
trolls because trolls I think is like a
a nice word it's like it's doesn't
describe them you know it's like
Dungeons and Dragons like trolls you
know the whole bit it's just like it's
the trolls are kind of friendly to some
degree so you know I call them clones
they're all they all their hatred is all
the same inside and they all say the
same thing so I they're like cloning off
each other something so kind of
genetically altered modified organism or
whatever it is and the bottom line is
and you know meanwhile what about the
people suffering I notice the trolls
most of them have not suffered they have
not suffered they have not struggled
they haven't had neuro fatigue they
don't know what it's like like to be in
the trenches with no answers they don't
know what it's like they don't try the
celery juice so they can actually heal
you know it's amazing how it works but I
know you guys you guys you want to heal
you want to get the information and
Today's Show is all about is about
healing the liver it's all about healing
the liver this is like this is the
information I'm going to give you run
down now Liver Rescue is the book um you
know pick up a copy if you don't have a
copy just just go to the LI I mean go to
the library if you can't afford a copy
someone said it to me a couple of times
I saw it on social media it's
unbelievable and somebody said I was
answering questions on social media and
somebody said you know I can't AFF I
can't afford a book and I said I
understand and I and I said I totally
understand of course I mean you may not
have the $15 right now that is very
possible I've seen that happen people
don't have money and you know when I
said go to the library and they're like
oh thank you I can't believe it I said
yeah and just take the books out that's
all free and get the free information
online the free everything online I
don't charge you don't have to go to my
website and pay a fee to get loads and
volumes of information on I killed
myself to get out there and write and
put together and everything else and get
the source the source that I have and
and to to give that information to me
make sure it all gets out so you can
heal make sure that you pick up a copy
somehow um I don't want anybody not
being able to have the information so
here's the deal healing the liver this
is going to be a great show and the deal
is about this is I can only though cover
certain aspects about healing the liver
meaning I'm going to cover a lot don't
get me wrong this is going to be a big
show but you still want to get the book
because this book is so huge it's so big
it's like 200,000 word count it's a
massive book so much information you got
there's so much to learn and heal and
all the different conditions in
everything I mean even the title of the
book The subtitle of the book only can
scratch a few if there was no room for
the subtitle so it's like answers to
eczema psoriasis diabetes strep strep is
behind everything like acne sibo then
you got Gout bloating gall stone
gallbladder problems adrenal stress
fatigue fatty liver weight issues cuz
everybody's got weight issues and if you
don't have a weight issue you're going
to have one later because of your liver
I'm just for warning everybody I've seen
it happen I've been in this for decades
if you don't have a weight issue now
because you're 28 years old and you seem
to be doing okay and you flipped on to
some vegan food and you're doing all
right and you're exercising or you
flipped onto a paleo diet and you're
doing okay and you're exercising and you
don't have any weight problems right now
you're going to have it later unless you
learn what to do for your liver I've
seen it over and over again everybody
thinks they're like all good and
indestructible and everything's all
happy and then they get the the weight G
no matter what later whether they're 35
or 38 and they get it or whatever
happens they still get it it's
unbelievable and so you know also on the
subtitle sibo and autoimmune disease
that's just a fraction of what's in the
book so when you know that that I can
only cover so much so this is about
healing the liver and where do we start
we start with one of the most important
aspects what's inside your liver what's
wrong with your liver to begin with we
come here with sick livers we're born
with livers that are weakened and a lot
of toxins are passed down passed down
from Generations okay then we get
exposed to toxins all through the course
of it if you think there's nothing in
your liver you're sadly mistaken and
terribly wrong very important to know
and then there's also the different
depths of the liver and that's another
thing too to heal your liver you got to
get to the core there's a subsurface
there's the surface the subsurface and
the inner core the three levels of the
liver and and where where toxins are
stored by the liver to protect your butt
so this is all information is critical
first of all the for warning everybody
because there's a lot of new people that
listen to the podcasts and radio shows
for warn you the information that always
comes from me in here is not out there
yet it's just never out there yet and
and and some of it has escaped from all
the work I've done and gotten out there
and and what not meaning like been out
there even even science has caught up
science of research caught up to speed
with a few things that I already
documented long before them and and so
so there's that information is out there
but today with you know with this and
much of the radio shows none of the in
it's all information you're never going
to hear read any books or find online
just for warning you so you don't jump
off the show and say all right let me
look into this yeah good luck cuz
exactly it's not going to be there so
there's the petrochemicals group it's
inside our liver all the time Plastics
okay so it's important to know and I
have to cover some of these
troublemakers I call it so in Liver
Rescue I call it troublemakers there's
gasoline we pump our own gas now we
inhale it you name it we didn't pump her
own gas only the gas station attend
attendance actually got poisoned that
was it only those poor guys okay those
are the ones that got poisoned that was
it they pumped gas all day in people's
cars they got it on their hands all day
they breathe it and inhaled it all day
now we pump gas now our 16-year-old
daughters pump gas okay and getting
exposure early on something that never
existed before something that never
existed before it's unbelievable so you
have to do things to care for your liver
that's why the show is called healing
your liver gasoline wouldn't believe the
solvents in there and the chemicals that
are in there unbelievable and what it
does and how that petrochemical gets
inside the liver Plastics is one of them
it's a whole another one they go into
deep parts of the liver diesel just
breathing in breathing in a delivery
truck in front of you or in front of
front of your apartment or front of your
house or wherever you live or whatever
you're doing breathing that in multiple
times in your life it goes into the
liver that's just a fraction have you
ever checked your oil and got it on your
finger one time in your life it's in
your liver another thing exhaust fumes
always inside the liver they just don't
disappear they go in the liver in the
bloodstream through the lungs and
instantly in the liver to protect your
heart and
brain because Li delivers your your your
filter kerosene if you've ever played
with that not a lot of people play with
that but still lighter fluid okay
lighter fluid yeah have you ever started
a grill have you ever started a bonfire
have you ever had fun and just squeeze
lighter fluid on a big pile of wood you
know what with a bunch of friends I mean
maybe somebody didn't do that it's all
right plenty more to go if that wasn't
your poison then there's plenty more
poison to go gas grills yeah what about
in your in your house your apartment
killing you know like literally like it
it it kills us I mean but we use it and
we're cooking at our stove we're let you
know we got the gas we got the gas
coming off the stove and we're cooking
all those gas fumes burning now you
can't run from it all you just have to
heal your liver while you're doing it
you still need to use your gas grill or
your gas stove or
whatever you can't you know you still
have to I mean there's chemical solvents
you name it I mean cleaning agents
everything carpet agents cleaning agents
it's endless paint have you ever painted
have you ever painted anything paint
thinner paint lacquer all of that it
gets in us we breathe in paint lacquer
all the time on Fresh Furniture we buy
you name it I've seen it all out there
nanotechnology sprayed on on on
furniture it's all of that and then
there's there's chemical fertilizers
which is like the neuro antagonist group
I mean this goes deep inside the liver
I'm just giving you a quick quick
rundown to this because why are you
healing your liver why are you what's
the point I mean meaning like why are
you healing your liver why would you
even want to care about your liver well
you got it the reason why you have to
know what's inside of it that's part of
it and I'm going to give you the quick
rundown this is this is a big deal
chemical fertilizers everywhere I'm
telling you right now insecticides
pesticides larvicides rodenticides
herbicides everywhere inner food in the
Parks everything sprayed on the sides of
the roads sprayed Everywhere by towns
and cities and what that are
commissioned to kill us with all the
with all those sprays and all those
poisons just so you know the chemical
companies literally use use our you know
our our government meaning like our Our
Town our local meaning local Town local
city those you know the state all that
they're spraying all that crap all on
the sides of the highway all that crap
on the sides of the road people are
spraying all that crap in their yards
then they're spraying for mosquitoes all
that crap and there you know all that
stuff floating in it's it's endless
inside the liver endless inside the
liver the chemical companies literally
indoctrinate in you know IND
indoctrinate um places and you know in
towns and cities and whatnot so that
they can just continue to actually help
kill us slowly it's
unbelievable how it works all goes
inside liver all goes inside the liver
puster DDT in the liver from long before
we were born and also floating in the
air now there's fungicides everywhere
it's on clothing you name it buy new
clothing it's got fungicides on it
unless it's some organic thing you
bought you can't hide from it all you
can try to hide from it a little bit
protect yourself you can protect
yourself a little bit but we have to
figure out how to heal the liver and get
this out of the liver so you don't get
sick so you don't get the hot flashes
later the heart palpitations the viral
diseases the viral situations all the
different things the Hashimoto because
of you know Epstein bar flourishing
inside the liver so you don't get sick
so you don't get all these problems just
everything under the sun can happen tons
of acne tons of this tons of that it's
all because the liver Harbors bacteria
viruses lots of poisons we can heal our
liver this information doesn't exist out
there it's beyond me that's why I had to
put this out there I was so sick sick
and
tired sick and tired you know I always I
I always have this like thing where I
have this hope and this Faith thing
because I have a lot of faith and a lot
of Hope and it and it seems to it seems
to take over and when it takes over I
say oh yeah no no there's going to be
some cool trendy doctors that are out in
the circuit that people all know they're
going to figure things out they're not
just going to be talking stupid about uh
you know lower carbs and here's what you
got to eat now and here's what you got
to do and then they'll take my celery
juice the whole Spirit celery juice
thing and they'll start saying it's
theirs or something whatever whatever
they do you know I sit back I say fine
let everybody do what they want to do
but but I'm thinking someone's going to
figure things out by now and they don't
and then I have to kick it up a notch
every time I sit back and I try to take
a break for a little bit and I try to
rest a little and say I have hope and I
have faith that all that you know the
the so-called experts and science and
research are going to actually be able
to figure a fraction of what I have to
deliver just a fraction I have faith and
I tell spirit let me just kick back let
me kick back and chill a little bit
because I have faith and hope and I
always get let down and disappointed and
then have to make a 200,000 word
manuscript called Liver Rescue and
literally almost put myself in the grave
doing it cuz you wouldn't believe how
hard it was to write this book because I
can't I get sick and tired of it all
it's unbelievable all right back to this
can't help it you guys
fluoride wait first of all smoke
exposure of any kind any kind of smoke
exposure it's in the liver whatever was
whatever was burning in that smoke like
plastic burning across the country
everywhere from California all the way
to Florida all the way to the East Coast
West Coast all the way everywhere
plastic burning every everywhere burning
burning burning agricultural
conventional agricultural burning
plastic everywhere it's in the air it's
smoke it's also plastic it's in our
lungs it hurts people fluoride ever get
a fluoride treatment no you don't have
to just a little bit of water in a
restaurant sure you get in a restaurant
there's fluoride in the water have you
had it yeah there's fluoride in in Soda
Pop there's fluoride in everything so
that's a whole another thing
chlorine swimming in pools all of that
chlorine gets us in just one way or
another it's unbelievable able you know
and then there's the whole thing with
the the problematic food chemical group
that sits inside the liver too at the
three different levels you know that I
talk about and I describe this in detail
in the book I can't cover a fraction of
this aspart Ane espartan right aspart
tene that's another thing too believe me
we all have a little bit in us one way
or another somehow some some way
artificial sweeteners y we all have it
in US somehow some way where is it still
sitting inside the liver has it left no
it hasn't left because we're on high fat
diets which is part of what I'm doing
with healing the liver here talking
about how you have to lower the fats in
your diet contrary to this to the silly
Trend out there of fats fats fats just
just make people sick and what happens
is it's really kind of deceiving and
Elusive where you know where you take
out the processed foods you take out the
gluten you take out stuff like that for
the first time or you take it out
seriously or you go raw or whatever it
is and just whatever it is or you just
you're you're paleo or something or
you're something that's not paleo but
you're look you know you're only eating
a little bit of animal protein and
bringing in more fruits and vegetables
now because they're finally somebody's
finally starting to figure out that
fruits and vegetables are the very thing
that heals everybody whatever it is if
you're still high fat whether it's
plant-based high fat or plant-based fats
or whatever it is and still doing some
animal fat whatever whatever you're
you're you're just still going to run
into trouble and you're not going to get
what I'm saying is in the liver ever out
and there will be a disease somehow
coming down the line whether you're 70
years old 80 years old 60 years old and
maybe does doesn't matter to somebody
who's 24 years old 23 years old because
you never think you're going to ever
turn 70 you never think you're going to
be 70 23y old will never believe they'll
never believe they'll be 70 years
old or they'll just think well I'm
supposed to live forever right it's
unbelievable so here's the deal all
right there's MSG inside our liver tons
of it for most people even nutritional
yeast the cleanest nicest funnest
nutritional yeast you can find has
glutamic acid in it naturally occurring
if it isn't even the crappy nutritional
yeast that actually has MSG literally
laed in it so either way it's it's
nutritional yeast is disastrous
everybody's pouring it on their food oh
I have people I put a recipe out on
social media and then you'll have
comments saying that recipe really looks
good but it would be so much better
easily so much better if you knew about
nutritional yeast Anthony like what how
about do you know about nutritional
yeast about it being so toxic for the
liver fill the glutamic acid no matter
what in good company or great product or
whatever it is
it's bad stuff it's inside the liver
glutamic acid MSG for Malahide
everywhere it's in it's all kinds of
stuff preservatives like the whole bit
so I mean where does it end I mean am I
boring you guys cuz I hope not I hope
I'm not boring you problematic Foods
what about those let me tell you
something about eggs eggs keep pathogens
that thrive inside the liver alive they
eat eggs it's the whole point someone
said to me and they still do here like
well no my eggs are organic they're free
range they're just grass-fed whatever it
is they'll be like you know what I mean
they're like no the chickens run wild
they have their own they're fed organic
scraps of food organic everything
they're just in the field they're
pecking away they're in they're not
caged they're free range or free pasture
whatever all of it and I say okay it
sounds good sounds amazing cuz if you're
going to eat an egg that's the kind of
egg you eat you better believe it but
see eggs were used to raise in Labs the
viruses that are tormenting everybody in
autoimmune disease on any and on all
levels that's the whole point all the
Epstein bars all the hhv sixes sevens
eights nines 10 undiscovered 10 11 12 13
14 15 16 that I actually talk about are
are are fed eggs that's how they're
they're they're alive that's how they
survive that's how they stay
alive and they've they've they've
escaped over the years in different ways
through Medical Treatments and
everything else and and they end up in
people and people pass them around on
top of it and they mutate it's
unbelievable and the liver Harbors all
these Harbors them and that's why
everybody gets all the different things
that's how they get all the different
conditions all of them they they get the
88 conditions I have listed in thyroid
healing the book thyroid healing they
get the conditions I have listed
multiple sclerosis Hashim Modas whatever
rumat arthritis Lyme disease that I have
listed in medical medium book one they
get that's where it all comes from eat
eggs you feed the viruses I'm the only
one talking about that the only one that
knows that I mean it's unbelievable and
and if you don't like that information
or you don't believe me and you want to
go on your way I got respect for you
totally 100% you could do what you need
to do that's free will and that's what
why it's why God gave us free will if
you don't believe in God but you believe
in the universe then I'm going to tell
you right now okay then use the universe
whatever you want to do okay the
universe gave you free will fine I'm
totally cool with that I respect that
100% the universe gave you free will
totally cool all right and then you want
to eat eggs you want to go on your Merry
way you don't think you're going to get
you know get a pro proliferation of a
viral infection in the liver down the
road where still won't be known by the
doctor anybody you'll just be fatigued
like like oh my God totally neuro
fatigued and just seeing weird things in
your eyes and getting little Tremors
down the road or just getting hot
flashes and weight gain and sickness and
adrenal problems and everything else you
don't think that can happen to you it's
happening to everybody including cancers
which viruses feed cancer so you want to
take care of your liver this is an
important show and you don't hear this
in alternative medicine you can't hop
online and start finding the right
information the best guys are just all
they're doing out there the most popular
guys they're all about selling something
it's all about making tons and tons of
money do you think do you think
$100,000 a week is a large amount of
money do you think a $100,000 a week is
a large amount of money right that's
that seems like a unbelievable large
amount of money well how about 2 million
a week or 5 million a week I mean these
guys out there pedaling pedaling things
and pedaling their products and whatnot
and they build their platforms to do it
so they can just sell you stuff and sell
you stuff and they can just get their
Mansions but they're not solving chronic
illness on any level or helping on any
level besides telling you to low carbs
lower carbs and eat some different foods
let me tell you something guys just
learn how to do this get off the eggs
that's one thing dairy products dairy
products okay so let's talk about that a
little bit feeds all the viruses inside
the liver cheese cheese hurts the liver
all on its own eggs hurt the liver all
on its own and then you got the hormones
that are in food the natural occurring
ones not the ones injected into animals
totally feeds viruses not only that
burdens down the liver and sits inside
the liver confusing your own hormone
making you someday get problems got to
be careful and then there's the high
fatty food you got to look out for the
fats I'm going to talk about that in a
little while just in case in the whole
bit and then the vinegar use be careful
I don't care if it's a v ACV I don't
care if it's ACV I don't care if it's
apple cider vinegar because apple cider
vinegar is the best vinegar there is and
if that's the one you want then yeah you
can do it but I'm telling you right now
your liver doesn't like it and you're
going to pickle your liver if you use
too much of it so just keep it sparingly
and be very cautious so you want to
these this is healing your liver all
about healing your liver this show is
all about I got to give you the rundown
on some of this stuff excessive salt use
look out that's not like celery celery
juice helps you heal from Bad salts
toxic salts that were used it's why you
can heal from celery juice cuz toxic
salts sit inside the liver stored and
then when you eat vinegar it pickles the
liver a pickle action occurs
inside the liver a pickling because your
bloodstream is also filled with sodium
so it's a pickling that occurs so you
got to be careful celery juice helps
reverse this pickling instead of
promoting it it's amazing it's like a
miracle pork products don't eat them I
don't care if it's the new white meat or
whatever do not eat them yeah that's
right someone said you're like the food
Fe I am food fear guy oh what about you
go to like the functional guys or
whoever whatever doctors and they've
like they they got a massive list of
foods and they're like you can't eat
let's see you can have a m no you can't
eat a mushroom but you oh wait you can
have a button mushroom but you can't
have this portabella you can no you
can't have cilantro but you could have
parsley wait a minute changed a week
later oh no you can have you can have
cilantro but you can't have parsley now
no you can't have strawberries you can't
have this but you can't have any fruit
whatsoever oh you can have eggs though
but no you can have yogurt no but you
can't have this you can't have that it's
Insanity you want to know what that is
I've seen people who spent thousands of
dollars with food testing of all the
different kinds that are out there go
through hell and back when really they
needed to just bring in some fruits and
some leafy green start drinking some
celery juice and literally their lives
have been changed and the Simplicity is
unbelievable and someone has has the
nerve to call me the food fear guy I'm
the guy bringing back fruit and
potatoes I'm the guy that BR brought
back potatoes for God's sake literally
potatoes which is a healing food and
then there's the people people out there
still attacking potatoes that's the food
fair group just get get the info
straight man get it straight gluten yep
look out for gluten duh I say duh
because you know what that's the only
thing that most people hang their most
experts hang their hat on but that's
like literally a joke compared to what's
what's going on you got to know about
the other stuff and then there's the
pathogens that sit inside the liver all
the different viruses all the different
viruses that I mentioned earlier the
bacteria the foodborn toxins that we
take for Granite that are there hurting
us take for granted and even mold sits
inside the liver and then the chemical
in indust the chemical domestic Invasion
I call it the aerosol air fresheners the
spray bottle air freshers colognes after
shaves the perfumes all inside your
liver the hairspray plug-in fresheners
scented fresheners scented candles hair
dye I mean then there's the personal
hair dye talcum powder conventional
makeup spray tan nail chemical I mean
you could still take care of yourself
but you got to get the more natural
stuff conventional cleaners you have to
at least take care of your liver so this
isn't bury deep down your liver
conventional lry detergents fabric
softeners Dyer sheets dry cleaning
chemicals I can't even stand there's so
much going on and then big Pharma Pharma
group okay all this stuff's in our water
supply never mind like we use it
antibiotics of course if you had it at
one time in your life it's still in your
liver it never left anti-depressant
still in the liver an anti-inflammatory
sleeping pills biologics regular
immunosuppressives prescription and
fetamines which is a whole bunch of them
I won't name the names opioids statins
blood pressure medications hormone
medications hormones thyroid medications
steroids and even the pill contraceptive
which sure if if you need to use the
pill it's your right to do it whatever
but here's the point you got to take
care of your liver so you can clean out
a lot of the old stuff the old
contracept the old pill that's actually
been trapped in the liver it's that's
the whole point it's like you can use
your statins you've every right to do it
but you got to you got to get the you
got to get the statins out of the liver
while you're using it if women want to
use the pill sure but you got to get the
old stuff out of liver if you're going
to use a thyroid medication because
that's how you you because you didn't
read thyroid healing and you don't know
how to heal your your thyroid yet and
you're going to your doctor and you have
to be on thyroid meds then then that's
your right then you do it but but but
you work on healing the liver to get the
old thyroid medication out of the liver
it's your right to use hormone
medications it's your right to use blood
pressure it's your right to use
anti-depressants it's your right
absolutely all of these medications all
of these things from Big Pharma it's all
your right to use if you want to use but
listen why don't we take care of the
liver so we can get some of the old
stuff out so the liver can actually
handle the new stuff going in women who
take the pill for years they take the
pill for years and years and years but
no one 's teaching them work on your
liver work on cleaning your liver out
work on healing the liver work on you
know work on getting that out of the
liver doesn't get bogged down instead
they're either taught to starve
themselves and then eat high fat diets
in between and go keto or something
that's what they're taught meanwhile
livers are getting more toxic than
there's epine bars sitting inside the
liver and young women have to they
suffer later on it no one's looking out
for anyone no one is looking out for
anyone it's unbelievable womenkind is
not protected at all still to this day
not protected at all in health it's
unbelievable what's happening and how
it's been happening it's it's just
beyond me and you know what making you
guys experts you know or you making
yourself experts by actually taking this
information you know and the whole point
is is is unbelievable and you don't have
to pay to become an expert with me you
don't have to pay you know you don't
have to be like I'm not not setting up a
whole thing where you got you I'm not
setting up a whole thing where you got
to give me $10,000 to become an expert
and then she it just it just get the
books and soak yourself into them I get
it when you pay for something you take
it more seriously so if you give some
like you know motivational person you or
some expert for whatever you give them
$5,000 for whatever course whatever you
want to do I respect that there's a lot
of great people out there teaching a lot
of great things I respect that but you
take it seriously because you've done
that you know this is only going to cost
you $15 or whatever it is to get the
book or just go to the library you don't
have to spend money become that expert
see the value so you can get yourself
better and everybody else better it's
amazing how the world
Works toxic heavy metal sit inside the
liver Mercury lead aluminum copper
cadmium barium nickel arsenic you don't
think it's in your liver it's in your
liver it's in your liver I mean Mercury
is still in pesticides they just spray
it everywhere they they're allowed to do
it they're allowed they got free free
immunity the chemical companies it's
unbelievable radiation still inside your
liver yeah and you can work on getting
it out believe it or not let's talk
about some things that are good for the
liver let's talk about some foods that
are good for the liver you guys ready
for that you want to do that for a
little bit but I want to talk about one
last thing and then you got excess
adrenaline stress and everything else
and adrenaline pumping into the liver
putting people at risk for liver disease
down the road weakening the liver making
sure its bio reserves break down make
sure it's make sure the hydrochloric
acid breaks down in the stomach that's
why celery juice is so critical that's
how important the liver is and it gets
bombarded by adrenaline and our young
people are getting bombarded their
livers are being soaked up and bombarded
by adrenaline on all levels because
that's what the world's about now and
then there's rainfall
exposure yeah rain filled with
everything under the sun being dumped
out of planes in the
sky and it say listen this isn't a like
fear anything it's cleaning up your
liver so you can get rained on how about
that that's what it is I I forgot to
tell you guys something I forgot to say
fast in your seat bels cuz you're going
for a ride today and it's going to be
like it's this is going to be a roller
coaster because it's intense stuff all
of this it's intense every last bit of
it so you know hey the truth is like
that sometimes and you know what this
fast in the seat belts yeah I guess
that's all I could say get some herbal
tea too maybe some lemon balm tea which
is incredible for the liver and I'm
about to talk about that in a little
bit oh my God throat's getting
dry so powerful Foods powerful
herbs powerful supplements for the liver
I'm going to tell you something right
now if you hear somewhere like oh
supplements are bad for the body they're
bad B for your health it's herbs only
herbs only herbs
only not true at all not true at all
very interesting okay I've had people
with chronic illness dying in their beds
families getting a hold of me over the
years desperate while they're laying
there laying there in agony okay and
literally all it took was the right kind
of be 12 to get that person recovering
to make the first recovery the first
literally where they can use their arms
and legs crawl out of bed and start to
heal and start to eat again and it was
just B12 by itself the right kind of B12
by itself I've witnessed that I've seen
it happen I've helped people throughout
the years do that and b12 is a
supplement it's not an herb so when you
see that on Instagram and you see that
in social media and you see that oh it's
just all about herbs meanwhile the
people the herbs are talking about are
even in alcohol they're just garbage on
top of it and you see that out there you
say something you say something if you
want because you know and chances are
they might even be selling something
whatever the CH I'm telling you now
supplements are that important and do
not ever get swindled into thinking oh
it's only herbs that help that's not
true so let's talk about powerful Foods
herbs and supplements yes and
supplements for your ever all
[Laughter]
right yeah you know I mean look I do the
radio show I do the radio show I I I I
have a lot going on I'm in the Midstream
of writing the next book for the next
year I'm working really hard I'm not
barely sleeping because I'm on a clock
of trying to get everything done and I
still don't want to toss out the radio
show because the because I mean I'm
desperate for time and energy because
cuz I'm working around the clock but the
radio shows that important and I know
that and and I know that it is and I'm
not I'm just going to keep it going I'm
going to keep it going I'm not going to
let you down apples incredible food
apples okay provides a living water a
hydration method what happens in the
liver to heal your liver you have to
have hydration apples is one of the
hydrating factors to the liver not apple
cided vinegar that's dehydrating here's
how it works the liver is in desperate
need of a certain type of hydration not
just water a certain type a living type
of water that has information in it that
comes from a fruit that comes from a
fruit for God's sake that Living Water
it takes and it actually stores it can
store it inside the liver it can help
you it can keep you from getting sick
it's unbelievable with the liver can do
with that so apples are important
apricots don't be afraid of a few dried
apricots even dried apricots absolutely
it's great when artichokes amazing for
the
liver they they contain phytochemical
compounds that stop liver
tumors so yeah you can't do artichokes
yeah you can arugula
incredible causes a gentle purging of
the liver a very thing we need with
everything I just rambled off on what
happens the livers asparagus my favorite
one of my favorites
if you know someone said I was talking
to some they like I hate a spirit they
said I hate it I hate it I won't eat it
I said what do you mean you hate it you
just don't like the taste it just go I
don't really like the taste I'm not into
it I said you mean you keep but but
would it kill you to eat some no it
wouldn't kill me to eat some can I have
it with a little something with it can I
have it with a little this on it I go
okay okay if you need to have it with
something on it go ahead they're like
all right I could can I put a little
salt and pepper on it I go all right and
they're like yeah they're like okay then
maybe I could start eating I go oh my
God I can't believe it so you really can
eat it and then they came back to me and
they're like you know what I can't live
without it now I love it I love it
asparagus is great it provides
flavonoids a type of flavonoid a rare
occurring one it actually soothes the
liver it's amazing what happens it it it
helps this there's this flavonoid that
calms down a sick liver especially one
that's spasming it strengthens asparagus
strengthen the liver immune system
purged liver I mean what happens with
this amazing DOL kelp really good for
the liver it's all part of the heavy
metal detox smoothie they get your heavy
metals out of your liver the medical
medium heavy metal detox smoothie
there's no one that works better than
that there's no heavy metal technique
remove technique that actually works
better than the medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie it doesn't exist on
the planet there's nothing better than
that one if you're interested if this
the first time listening to this show
get get the books figure it out figure
go to Medical medium.com whatever and
figure it out bananas incredible
provides a glucose for the liver that's
unbelievable okay and bananas are
antiviral anti- yeast antibacterial
antifungal foods not the opposite and
that's what you need for the the liver
the liver needs bananas berries
incredible that's a Medicine Chest all
in its own broccoli incredible sulfur
compounds that actually help stop
bacteria strep that causes acne broccoli
stops acne can you believe it brussel
sprouts yeah brussels sprouts do the
same thing okay okay we're going through
some more
Foods celery can't say enough about it I
you know what I can't even say enough
about it it's not even just the
Undiscovered subgroups of of of of
mineral salts here's the thing about
celery it's all the rage now because of
us right cuz of spirit and medical
medium and all that and everybody's
drinking it worldwide and celery's
running out Cel the celery Growers are
freaking out all of that I get it you
know I I I I brought that though to the
world for a reason first of all science
of research doesn't even know anything
about celery that's why when a dietitian
or something does this little does this
little article or somewhere some
conventional thing or alternative thing
does an article and they bring somebody
on and they're acting like a celery
juice expert when they don't know
anything about it they'll even say well
there's not a lot out there in science
and research about s of course there
isn't of course there isn't about
anything really about anything to do
with anything that's health and relates
unbelievable but here's the deal with
celery it's these undiscovered subgroups
sodium that's what it is they're called
cluster salts I call them cluster salts
I do all right I do because that's what
they are and they then what they do is
they enter into cell membranes and they
inhibit growth of viruses they strip the
membrane off of viruses that information
will be available through through
science and research 50 years from now
how old will you be then but that's when
it will be available so don't stop
drinking celery juice just because this
is the only source of information so far
celery restores the liver's bio
production I'm just giving you a little
couple couple little things the
hydrochloric acid builds back up in the
stomach glands the seven blend that
nobody knows about that I put in book
one and it's also in this book two book
as well the liver resue book I talk more
about it celery purges the liver okay
that's how critical It Is by bringing
down liver heat to a safe
level it helps dissolve Gull Stones it
can do it's I mean I could go on and on
and on we don't have the
time cherries great for the liver that's
right
cranberries great for the liver coconut
water great for the liver cruciferous
vegetables great for the liver that's
right cucumbers amazing cucumbers are
allies they're hydration they're
hydration source for the liver as well
kind of like with the Apple but it has
anti-inflammatory liver Pro liver
properties for anti-inflammatory for the
liver Danny lion greens it's another
good food do you like any of these Foods
you guys eating any of these or you you
too busy eating too much fat are you too
busy eating too much too much avocado
too many nut Butters nuts and seeds
coconut oil um are you eating too much
all that um just curious because if you
are not eating enough of this then you
know you're doing too many fats and
you're bogging down the liver if you're
vegan you're doing too many fats you're
bogging down the liver um yeah you got
to lower the fats I'm sorry about that
but you have to if you're pale or you
doing to you're worried too much about
your proteins proteins protein proteins
because you're suckered into the protein
myth the protein law and theory that was
created in 1933 to control people um
same thing with you vegans too just tell
your vegan friends you've been suckered
into the protein myth so you guys are so
anti conventional like you're anti I
noticed who the vegans is what I really
love and I love vegans I love them all I
love everybody I love paleo people I
love everybody I mean that's the whole
point you got to love everybody you got
to get them better and you got to get
them healed you got to get them to get
do the right things but I'm going to
tell you something right now I've
noticed about the vegans is they're so
they're all of course they're against
the whole animal thing they have of
course they're against the animal
killing thing all of that they're
against all that and they're against
they're against just the whole Animal
product thing all that 100% totally with
them I think you know I'm support them
100% but but yet they take the the they
take that knowledge with them on their
side they they they take protein with
them that the protein law that was
created for animal proteins to sucker
people into thinking they need protein
because of the deal the the contracts
that were made in 1933 with the with
with the how the world worked I talk
about in this book by the way and so
it's like the vegans are are literally
they want to be separate from the animal
uh protein people but yet they take the
animal protein like law with them them
and then they're all focused on protein
it's actually really sad and and vegans
don't like to be tricked they don't want
to be tricked they they want to think
they're the smartest people on the
planet they don't want to be tricked and
meanwhile they get tricked it just
doesn't really make any sense so if
you're vegan plant-based just try to
figure that out and stop worrying about
protein you know listen to my protein
radio show listen to you know see see
you know learn about it get the Liver
Rescue book so you can learn about how
you don't want to be tricked like that
and the animal protein people are not
supposed to be tricked like that either
they if they want animal proteins you
guys that's fine if that's what you want
it's fine the point is is everybody
needs to lower their fats stop thinking
about protein because the protein thing
just gets you in trouble so you end up
eating more fat and you get yourself
sick this is liver 101 right now okay
this is how we then just can't get these
toxins I just mentioned out of the liver
we're all eating fats because we're all
sucked into the protein law and it's sad
that the plant-based people are still
talking protein protein protein and
they're still all all hung up on science
and research everybody's battling
everybody with science and research it's
all bogus and all paid for so it's
unbelievable paleo people are like there
there's all the science of why this
works you know this is what they did you
know this is how man ate 10,000 years
ago nobody knows what man ate 10,000
years ago but here's here's all the
science here's how it goes here's how it
goes and then you got and then you got
the plant-based people like no no no
plant food here's the science behind it
and this is what you got to do it's this
this this and they're battling each
other it's unbelievable and there all
these hybrid diets are made from them
and then but yet they're all hung up on
this protein law and killing themselves
on high diets without even knowing it
even if they got better they're still
going to get worse way way way down the
road unless you learn how to heal the
liver and lower the fats and learn how
to do things for your liver and take
care of yourself because yeah when
you're 25 it's all cute and fun but tell
you right now when you're 45 and you're
gaining weight and no one's helping you
and you're fatigued and you can't get
out of bed anymore cuz you didn't know
you had a viral infection all these
years and it wasn't handled right cuz
you were eating a high fat diet over and
over again flipping back from from
animal protein paleo back to plant-based
back back to animal protein back to
plant-based and you don't know where to
go and you're not doing 32 ounces of
celeries use every day to heal yourself
and you're not doing all the things you
need to do or you're afraid of
supplements CU somebody said supplements
are bad even though there are a lot of
bad supplements don't get me wrong
there's terrible supplements if you go
to Medical medium.com you look at my
directory you'll see the better
supplements the ones that I trust that's
the whole point yeah the ones that do
get help people get better yeah but
there's a lot of junk out there too we
do have to worry about that but
supplements are fine garlic it's another
Powerhouse for the liver amazing grapes
great for the liver hot peppers yeah if
you like them jalapeno Chili Peppers are
really good for the liver Jerusalem
artichokes eggplants amazing for the
liver Tomatoes incredible for the liver
Tomatoes mushrooms amazing for the liver
lemons and limes leafy greens of all
kinds kale incredible for the liver
mangoes great for the liver
yeah maple syrup still good for the
liver onions and scallions oranges and
tangerines I mean oranges and tangerines
they they they provide nutrients for the
liver like nothing else papayas I mean
it goes on parsley pears pineapples Paya
dragon fruit incredible for the liver it
helps to bring liver cells back the
apple is one of the most powerful things
for the liver I said that earlier I'm
going to say it again potatoes potatoes
provide amino acids specifically to stop
and inhibit viral growth inside the
liver the very thing that gets everybody
sick in the end down the road whether
anybody likes it or not unless they're
taking care of themselves and working on
their liver and healing themselves
potatoes are that important it helps
build glycogen storage the very resource
that protects us against blood sugar
problems weight gain fatty liver dirty
blood syndrome potatoes keep the liver
grounded and stable they keep our
constitution strong radish is incredible
raw honey amazing for the liver listen
listen raw honey is incredible for the
liver it just is I just wouldn't be
afraid of it I would not be afraid of it
whatever you do
pomegranates they're great for the liver
absolutely all fruits are really but
these are some powerful ones with
information about them sweet potatoes
Tomatoes harness critical
micronutrients phytochemicals vitamins
and minerals that literally help stop
liver illnesses of all kinds they Shield
the liver they help the liver detox red
blood cells safely tomatoes are that
important and all these things help
inhibit cancer they really do turmeric
fresh turmeric incredible for the liver
and then let me not M mistake wild
blueberries there's still other Foods I
can't cover that are inside this book I
only got so much time I'm giving you
some of the power houses wild
blueberries incredible that's how we go
so supplements let's cover some of those
what's great for the liver I'm going to
give you a few just off the top and off
the running Amber is decent for the
liver I love it it's very helpful I love
it it's a great thing ashwagandha great
for the liver and I got all the reasons
why they're great for the liver they're
inside Liver Rescue you can learn about
what these things do and why they're
amazing for the liver cats Claw is good
for the liver too because it kills the
viruses inside the liver barley grass
juice powder you me like I said go to
medical medium.com and learn about the
right stuff to use barley grass juice
powder don't get confused and just grab
all some old barley grass I like the
vimer you know don't grab just some old
barley grass get the vimergy stuff V is
in Victor M E RG y that's the one I like
you know if you're doing coconut water I
like the taste Nirvana that's a good one
too if you're doing wild blueberries I
like the Wyman Frozen wild blueberries
um the whole bit I don't work for these
companies okay I mean all the companies
I recommend on my website I you know the
whole bit so this these are just better
sources so you can do the right things
for yourself um and so yeah yeah it's
just it's all important and then like
and then there's the the chaga mushroom
I like that um and you know there's so
many things that are helpful for the
liver it's incredible aloe vera is
helpful for the liver you can do fresh
aloe vera that's one thing you can do
Ginger is helpful for the liver to get
these toxins out CoQ10 I love for the
liver you know all of these there's so
many though there's a lot of them lemon
balm kills viruses bacteria other
pathogens and it helps also detox the
liver a little bit it's a great one
licorice root calms down diminishes
viral loads as well for the liver it's a
very important one that's a great one
too um magnesium is a great one for the
liver melatonin is good for the liver
you could take a little bit of that
every day not even to try to sleep if
you don't want to Mullen Leaf it's an
incredible herb nettle Leaf amazing for
the liver too all these are I mean every
last one of these that I'm talking about
are great for the liver Oregon
grapefruits a great herb so you know
these are these are some of the things
you can use to help detoxify the liver
to help heal the liver to help whatever
if you want more explanations on how
every one of these work you can
definitely get the Liver Rescue books
you can learn about which how what these
do for the liver there's a long long you
know like there's there's paragraphs of
information per each one of these so you
know what's happening and then inside
Liver Rescue I have a list of dozens and
dozens of symptoms and diseases and what
to take what supplements to take exactly
what to take to heal your liver or your
condition all the different conditions
what to take and how to heal the B12 the
right kind of B12 the adoil meth methal
Balman combin the right kind of spiralen
you got to make sure it's the right kind
can go to Medical medium.com to see
which one I use personally so there's
that too and you know and and like it's
important to know what helps sassandra
Berry is helpful rose hips rose hip tea
is helpful to heal the liver these are
important vitamin C every single day
estra C the one I use is my favorite
that's a medicalmedium.com you can you
know and then there's the zinc my
favorite zinc that I use personally
these things are incredible for the
liver wild blueberry powder my favorite
kind yellow doc that's another one that
I love you know there's these These are
so many different things that are
incredible for the liver and stuff you
can do to protect it I like a little bit
of nent iodine that's incredible
peppermint tea is helpful for the liver
too now if you can't do I'm just giving
you options I'm giving you these
different options you can use all of
these periodically you can change them
up you can do but but but here's the
deal and I'm giving you I'm letting you
know some of the supplements that are in
in Liver Rescue but what there is there
is a section in Liver Rescue which is
really great which you know which I talk
about how to heal acne adrenal problems
how to do maintenance what supplements
it take what the dosages are bloating
what dosages to do for bloating what
supplements for bloating autoimmune
disorders of all kinds what supplements
to use in what dosages brain fog what
supplements to use in dosages chemical
food sensitivities diabetes dark circles
under the ice
constipations um children's liver
problems where they're bloating and
having constipation supplements and what
to use all that you know you name it
when toxic blood syndrome exus psoriasis
emotional problems with the liver energy
issues fatigue fatty liver sluggish
liver I talk about all the different
dosages what supplements to use so I can
really really really help everyone
gallbladder infections gall stones with
supplements for gall stones gout heart
palpitations hepatitis high blood
pressure it goes on high cholesterol
hormone problem hot flashes IBS citable
bowel syndrome inflammation throughout
the body body pain what supplements to
use jaundice liver problems of all kinds
aging I mean you name it even liver
cancer you know things that people can
really get help with insomnia Scar
Tissue I mean the whole bit cysts and
everything methylation problems I talk
about it what to use what supplements
mystery hunger pandis Rena syndrome sad
sio so important sign infections UTI
supplements and what kind like for
instance the UTI I talk about what to
use like the amberry the aloe vera the
cats call the chaga I'm reading it right
here out of Liver Rescue I just opened
the book to show you just now for with
the UTI section Mullen Leaf olive leaf
and and and a few other things for
bacterial vaginosis and yeast infections
and UTI and the dosages you need it's
important to get Liver Rescue so you
know what to do and then even varicose
veins and and weight gain weight gain is
a big one what supplements to use for
weight gain and I can give you a few of
those right now since we only have time
in a show that's why I'm going so quick
with everything but still with weight
gain sparina really helpful the vitamin
B12 incredible for weight gain right
there the zinc incredible for weight
gain zinc causes weight loss it helps
the 5 mthf so the meth so the you know
the methyl folate that's a great one
aloe vera ashwag Ganda is incredible for
weight gain and weight meaning to get
rid of weight issues to get rid of
excess weight you know toxic weight
that's on our bodies the barley grass
juice powder the lemon balm little bit
of nent iodine nettle Leaf raspberry
leafes Cassandra Berry these are all
vitamin C these are all to actually help
so you can lose weight and I give
dosages inside the book so you can
actually really work on your weight loss
it's critical to take care of your liver
so and and it's critical to know what to
do with foods and STS to actually get to
get and herbs to actually get the toxins
out of the center of the liver and know
why they're even there all this
information so you can heal the liver
this is about healing the liver and
learning how to lower your fats as a
plant-based person a raw plant-based
person a vegan person a vegetarian but
whatever it is a pescatarian whatever it
is that somebody is or a Paleo or a new
variety of paleo which is basically just
reducing animal protein I see out there
and then they put a new name and label
on it the bottom line is so somebody can
hang their hat on it so the bottom line
is whatever it is you decide to do lower
the fats which means get rid of the
protein mindset a little bit because if
you keep that you'll just keep on eating
the fats and living off of them until
you get symptoms down the road if you're
not already dealing with them I love you
guys take one day at a time bless you
God bless you I'll see you next show