[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William the
medical Medium you're listening to the
medical medium radio show where each
week we bring the most advanced healing
information on chronic illness um to the
masses that's the whole point that's our
job is to make sure you get the
information you need to heal heal heal
your loved ones help you yourself people
you care about your friends and
everything else because what happens is
that when we don't have the right
information and we're dealing with
misinformation and disinformation all
the time the stuff that's circulating
everywhere in the books and the internet
and everything else we lose 10 years of
our life we lose 10 years of time we
could have gotten better or could have
gotten so much better to a point where a
higher quality of life a better quality
of life I've seen people have anxiety of
the most crippling crippling anxiety or
depression and it and if they and they
they went through it through life and
then they got it better and they got it
better doing some things that we have in
the medical medium series books and
everything else and they were just like
oh my God if I only knew this years ago
what would I've done I mean if I only
knew about the celery juice how it
reduced my anxiety and just took it down
from level eight level 10 down to level
one to level zero I mean it's things
like that the whole point is Advanced
information to make sure
that you can move forward healing and
and and actually you know beat Decades
of time that research and science
doesn't know about things out there it's
crazy look at what celery juice this is
one example of the medical medium series
look at what celery juice is doing for
Millions globally now that we've we got
it out there that we actually that
Spirit put the information out there
look what it's doing it's unbelievable
okay and there's no research in science
at all has that's attached to it
whatsoever in fact you'll even see
articles now they just totally
conventional articles and whatnot and in
media like what is this celery juice
cleanse I mean the celery juice trend is
it good is it bad what is it they don't
even have a clue no one even has a clue
it's
unbelievable and so if if research and
science is what you're relying on in
chronic illness on any level it's it's
not a really good thing it's not a
really good thing with mystery chronic
illness it's not because it's a whole
that's the whole point and that's an
advanced that's an advanced piece of
information
that's literally changing the lives of
so many and I'm talking about celery
juice for a reason because today's topic
is bloating we're talking about
bloating very important like why do we
bloat who's bloating are you bloating
are you getting bloated the whole bit
would you like to not be bloated you
know it people walk around bloated they
get so used to it they just been bloated
for years whatever we're going to work
on it this is going to it's going to be
all about bloating on this talk it's
very important so the bottom line is
you know the information you're going to
receive today is it's not it's not you
know tampered with it's not contaminated
it's pure clean information that's not
out there yet it's like that in every
medical medium radio show it's out there
in all the free information we put out
all the time it's out there in the
Articles we put out at Medical
medium.com it's out there in Facebook we
put out there all the information and
Instagram you name it it's all out there
if you're new to the show make sure you
get the free information you have to go
to my website and be like oh I have to
pay $35 a month oh wait a minute I have
to buy this $5,000 cleanse oh wait a
minute what do I have to buy all these
supplements and then buy the book along
with it and buy $1,000 worth the
supplements no what do we it's not about
that it's not we're not selling anything
besides we're giving information so you
heal and get better if you can't afford
the live a rescue book because that's
what this is all about and bloating has
everything to do with live a rescue and
the live a rescue book if you can't
afford a book whatever it is $155 or
whatever it is go to go to the library
and get it there I always say that
because I don't care please go to the
library everybody go doesn't matter to
me as long as you're healing and that's
the whole point so let's go into
bloating let's talk about this it's an
important thing because research and
sign still knows nothing about bloating
nothing it's what you're going to find
out there it's like not just the wild
west but it's really just like the
information out there is what I'm saying
is it's try this try that eat this way
everybody's got a new fangle diet a
trendy diet they got this this take out
processed foods take out gluten and yeah
that does help you take out gluten and
sometimes people lose their bloating
absolutely you take out dairy products
sometimes they lose their bloating but
it's not as simple as that for so many
people and why were they bloating if
they were bloating to gluten why why
were they bloating if they were and if
you're sitting out there saying well
what about lectin he's not talking about
lectin he doesn't have advanced
information first of all that's not
Advanced information lectin second of
all the lectin theory is completely all
wrong completely all wrong that's the
other thing in fact I talk about that in
Liver Rescue the whole lectin thing is
completely wrong there's lectin in every
fruit and every vegetable so you know
what don't eat any fruits and vegetables
don't see where it gets you see where it
gets you don't eat any fruits don't eat
any vegetables don't eat don't eat any
of that and just because you want to
avoid eltin see where that gets you I
can't even tell you how many holes are
in the lectin thing you don't even know
you don't even you got to read LI or
rescue to even know and but you know the
whole thing there's a lot of proteins
there's a lot of proteins that are more
destructive than
lectins they're way more destructive and
they're not in fruits and vegetables the
lectins are actually harmless it's other
proteins that the science and research
don't even have mapped out there's so
many proteins in in Grain in certain
grain and I'm going even talk talking
about the whole gluten thing there's
just so many proteins and and those are
disturbing because what they do is they
feed like gluten does they feed
pathogens which guess what guess what
nobody knows in the any of the medical
communities and I'm telling you that now
so you can be this is all about arming
you and making sure you become the
expert if I come off as like a pain in
the butt and I come off where you know
sarcastic or whatever it is I come off a
little Brash whatever it is it's only
because I want you to become an
expert because if I'm not a good teacher
and I don't I don't maybe I suck as a
teacher maybe I totally suck as a
teacher I'm doing the best I can but I'm
trying to be a good teacher so that you
get the information you become the
expert that you need to be and and
that's just the bottom line and so what
happens is with like gluten it feeds
pathogens it feeds viruses it feeds
viruses like Epstein bar it feeds
viruses like all the different viruses
hhv6 it feeds all that stuff strap the
bacteria and
everything it feeds all those things and
then and then now that's one of the
reasons why people bloat if you got
strep if you got a little acne and
everything and you're eating gluten or
you're eating something you're not
supposed to be eating dairy or eggs or
anything Dairy eggs whatever like I said
milk cheese butter yogurt kefir whatever
it is you know Lamb's milk I don't know
what people drink anymore sheep's milk
the whole bit it Whatever It Is goats
milk and if you're if you're
actually you know if you're actually
eating any of that and and you're
bloating up yeah of course that's
because you're you're you're feeding a
pathogen you're feeding strep in the gut
you're feeding strep inside the gut
that's the whole point so the bottom
line is it's about getting you better
it's about making sure that you're in
the right situation with all of this and
having the right information and and
that's a piece of it all on its own cuz
you know what research and Science and
everything else doesn't even know about
what's happening with with gluten alone
feeding bugs and what kind of bugs and
everything about it so it isn't just
like the gluten thing it isn't just like
that and it's more it's much more than
that we're going to go into depth about
it all because someone can eat all the
bread and gluten they want yeah if they
don't have all kinds of viruses or they
don't have a good strep in their
intestinal tract that's sitting there
feeding on it all the time you know
giving more bloating or other situations
like that or any kind of symptom
constipation any kind of cramping pain
whatever it is if if if if it's not just
that basically what I'm trying to say is
there's people that can eat anything
they want they're not getting bloating
but they eventually will and they
eventually do no one escapes bloating no
one does unless they actually
repair what has gone wrong for so many
years it has everything to do with the
liver you know children bloat they bloat
from the very beginning because of the
liver and then because of also pathogens
like strep and everything else and
children have these pathogens absolutely
and they bloat and and they get weak
hydrochloric acid very weak digestion
very weak digestion and it can happen
when you're younger and there could be
people that are not bloating they don't
bloat they don't bloat and they just go
through life but they'll bloat
eventually everybody will no matter who
it is
everybody will because you're going to
be doing something wrong with their diet
and whatever their constitution is
meaning in a sense where they they don't
have a lot of bugs their liver was
strong to begin with and their liver
didn't actually break down over the time
over the years fast enough or like some
people it breaks down because of stress
High adrenaline adrenaline flooding into
the liver and then it breaks down over
time and some people less stress with
less adrenaline you know all kinds of
different things like that uh different
resources different Lifestyles whatever
it is and whatever it is the bloating is
going to come it's going to come it's
going to it just is I've been in this
long enough over 30 years just just
practicing alone helping people just
oneon-one over the years never mind
doing the books and then years later
doing the books and all the information
we put out and everything like that that
I put out that spirit and I put out when
I say we it's you know spirit and I
putting it out the thing is is that the
bottom line the bottom line is for you
to understand one thing that's so
important and everybody will
bloat whether anybody likes it or not
unless you know what's going on unless
you know why unless you repair the hands
of time unless you repair and go back
and repair the hands of time and by
doing that is guess what making good to
the liver making good with the liver and
making sure that the diet is Right long
enough with the right things and tools
in there making sure you're healing the
right things long enough even if you're
doing some caman trendy thing out there
whatever and it helped your bloating and
you stopped this and you stopped eating
that for a little while and your
bloating started getting better whatever
it is the bloating will come back it
just does it does it does unless you do
what you you need to do unless you know
what's going really going on with the
liver the bloating comes back if you
think everybody's immune to bloating
except for you if you think people are
walking around immune to bloating except
for you you're
wrong drastically drastically wrong no
one is immune to bloating no one gets a
free get out of bloating card jail card
free whatever no one does I'm being
straight up I'm telling you right now
I'm being straight up so the bottom line
is let's let's go into this a little bit
let's talk about it when the liver
weakens okay when the liver weakens and
becomes sluggish a sluggish liver that's
right in any way such as when pathogens
like EBV and poisons like toxic heavy
metals come to visit or when fatty liver
develops it produces lower quality bile
so it's all about the
bile you know and hey look you know in
real estate it's all about the location
it's all about the location all about
the location whatever that's what you
hear it's all about that and um and with
the liver and with
bloing it's all about
bile that's what it's about so just just
remember that really important thing to
know cuz we're going into this right now
we're going to go deep into this but
it's all about that so listen the bottom
line is this is not a proud situation
for your liver when it weakens it's
not because the liver the liver lobules
these little little little cell
structures inside the liver they're all
about quality
control they're all about quality of
bile they're all about quality and
quantity that's what they're all about
so if the liver is releasing bile that's
less than that's less than it truly is a
sign that it's old overburdened and how
would you know how would you know and it
doesn't matter what kind of fancy diet
someone's giving you out there whatever
and blah blah this that diet
whatever you know diet for your blood
diet for this diet for that whatever's
going on out there is it really about
your B does anybody even know what's
going on and what's happening in there
yeah and so the bottom line is so if the
liver is releasing bile that's less than
it's truly ass signed sign that it's
overburdened that it's
overburdened so even when compromised
even when the liver's compromised it's
using every single Reserve every single
source of energy it has to produce the
strongest bile it possibly can and I'll
tell you why because everybody's on a
high fat diet I'm sorry but everybody's
on a high fat diet you don't you don't
know you're on a high fat diet call it
high protein then are you on a high
protein diet hey are you on a high
protein diet turning my head different
ways are you on a high protein
diet yeah because if you're on a high
protein diet that's a high fat diet
that's a high fat diet that's what that
is sorry sorry about this news sorry
believe me I don't I don't like
delivering I you know what when you
deliver the truth about all this stuff
and how things work every time we do a
radio show and you do it in the books
and everything else and you put the
truth out there you know it's it's scary
because yeah no one wants to know the
truth I mean who wants to know the truth
I mean unless I'm wrong I I I might be
just wrong because you guys want to know
the truth so me you know what I'm
wrong totally wrong because I know you
you want you want the truth you know I
don't know where I get that where hey
nobody wants to know the truth out there
I mean you know people don't like seeing
the truth they don't know the truth I
mean because you guys are here you want
the truth on this so you know you see so
I got a lot to learn I still have a lot
to
learn still the liver has 2,000 over
2,000 undiscovered chemical functions to
perform and some of them okay go into
the immune support and they're more
important than
bile they're more important than bile so
the bile will weaken and bile is
important but it'll weaken because your
immune system is more important
especially if you're dealing with
pathogens like everybody else and I'm
going to say it right now I don't care
who you are where you come from what
part of the planet you're on I don't
care if you're an alien from another
planet and you landed on a spacecraft
the other day you got a pathogen inside
the liver everybody has pathogens inside
the liver you can't not have pathogens
inside your liver it would be bizarre it
would be clearly bizarre if you if you
actually didn't have pathogens in the
liver because even if you had strep one
time in your life or didn't even know
you have it it's causing a little bit of
acne it's inside the liver that's just
one of just dozens of of
possibilities so lower levels of less
powerful
bile mean the breaking down of food
becomes a
problem but what kind of food what's the
problem
fats avocado oh spiles weak it's not
going to disperse it good break it down
NOP chicken oh bile is weak it's not
going to break it down good enough there
you no nope nope no grass-fed beef nope
lots of fat in that yeah there is I
don't care what anybody says right in
the lean cuts of meat plenty of fat what
do you think that juices if you throw it
on the
grill yeah you know there you go you got
there you go why does it feel
greasy and it's all greasy feeling right
some cheese big hunk of cheese God the
bile has to break that down big hunk of
cheese eggs bile has to break that down
absolutely eggs nuts lots of almond
butter bile has to Brak it down
chocolate bar cook you know cow
chocolate bar that with almonds in it
too it's got to break it down milk
chocolate got to break it down
right piece of pie he got to break down
a donut well that's unhealthier stuff I
mean whatever got to break it down there
you go cream cheese on a bagel got to
Brak it down the cream cheese the bile
there it goes again one more time the
B's cranking up what you have for back
breakfast do two eggs for breakfast or
or Smoothie with Almond butter coconut
oil in there oh bile got to break it
down it's got to disperse it's got to
disperse and go nuts the deliver got to
pound it get the get the crap pound
pound it out of it every single day okay
you got the breakfast and then what
what's for lunch oh wait snack in
between handful of almonds what's for
lunch you know exactly chicken salad B's
got to crank up again once again what's
for the afternoon big nutty granola bar
bile has to crank up again there it is
and these are healthier options all this
dinner time grassfed beef piece of fish
whatever it is oh guacamole if you're
vegan bile has to break it down that's
right that's right and that could be
kind of okay if your liver isn't
burdened already if you don't have two
varieties of Epstein bar sitting in
there that caus Hashim Modas when you're
50 years old or you don't have you know
something else going on there that's not
causing something or two varieties of
strep because you had strep throat years
ago and you get UTI periodically in your
life you got all the strep inside the
liver cyto egler virus hhp 6s which are
all in there it's Rosas when people you
know when kids get Rosas little babies
or they get Ros Olas and they get jais
because they got they got hhv6 in their
liver sitting there their whole lifetime
that's how it works and in the liver get
sluggish and SL you can kill viruses too
why do you think I put out thyroid
healing the book thyroid healing if you
don't have a copy of that get a copy of
thyroid
healing you get if if yeah get a copy
can't afford it go to the library
whatever but the bottom line is is that
all the stuff is inside the liver then
you got Mercury lead arsenic cadmium
copper nickel steel Chrome Alloys you
get all this metal titanium everything
sitting inside the liver titanium yeah
where where'd you get titanium where'd
you get that I mean is it dental
implants or is it Pharmaceuticals over
the years because they're loaded with
titanium Pharmaceuticals antibiotics at
petroleum they're petroleum based they
got Metals in it too petroleum is not
necessarily metal but what I'm saying is
they also have Metals in it too they got
all that
I mean Pharmaceuticals aren't screened
for all this stuff they even add it in
there goes into the liver fills up in
the liver detergents air fresheners
colog perfumes gasoline at the gas
station you're pumping every single day
Foods preservatives junk you've eaten 20
years ago it's all still inside the
liver every last bit of it every last
bit of it is inside the liver smoke from
a bombfire from treated wood gas grill
gas stoves and you can't run from some
of this you got to live with some of
this absolutely so you can't be afraid
you just have to help clean out your
liver it's why I did Liver Rescue Liver
Rescue 369 is in the book and everything
for people want to cleanse liver and the
whole bit and learn about the liver but
it's all sitting inside the liver all
these things and more much more than I'm
even saying petrochemical solvents
Plastics I can go on and on and on DDT
pesticides herbicides fungicides
rodenticides all sitting in the side
insecticides from bug killer sprayed in
apartments how many apartments have I
had
over the years that I I walk in and I'm
like you know what this is all I could
afford this is all I could live in right
now this is the only this is the only
place I I just got to settle I have to I
have to get this apartment this is it
right here you know it's $1,000 a month
or whatever I got to get into this
apartment let me just you know survive
here and it's filled with insecticides
and I got to live in it because it's
been sprayed a 100 times for 100 people
for cockroaches and every other every
other thing going all the way back how
many how many apartments have I lived in
like that
over the years going back it's like it
it's like seriously and the pesticide
just breathing it in inhaling
it yeah we all have that we all have and
you can't run from that so there's a lot
of things you can't run from walking in
the park getting sprayed with Roundup
Ready all the time or walking the park
with Dew on the grass and all that
Roundup Ready from the night before from
the lands Keepers all spraying all the
parks down all the time and just walking
along and what about the what about all
this crap from our parents that's still
that's funneled back down from whatever
they did in their life like smoking and
drinking or whatever it is and just all
kinds of bad food and exposure and then
from their parents it's all sitting
inside the livers getting passed down to
our livers and it builds up and all the
Mercury that's inside the liver and
everything else and then you you and
then you talk about the different
pathogens that are being passed around
everywhere you can easily pick up you
pick it up for bathrooms these days I
mean you could pick it up if you're not
careful you got to Handy wipe everything
you handy wipe your hands you got to
Handy wipe things you go to the grocery
store you're touching the carriage you
got to Handy wipe your hands you got to
you know I handy wipe the carriage
handle but then again I can't go
shopping anymore when I it's just it's
too hard for me as it is cuz readings
come through 24/7 and now I can't even
walk into a store I can't because then I
have to I have to answer questions and I
can't do that I'll never get anything
done the last door I went into I I it
took me an hour and a half to hour and
45 minutes to get out I never bought my
mangoes I never bought my mangoes
because I because people came up up and
said oh you're you know you're aw you're
Anthony Anthony William the medical
medium I got this health problem I got
this can you get I got this wrong with
me got this my sister's here here's got
this this this this and I said I can't
and and and I can't turn anybody down
because I feel bad I feel bad for what
they're going
through I feel bad so I'll sit there for
2 hours I'll sit there for 3 hours one
time I went to a store I I went to the
store I got there 8:00 in the morning
like 8:30 in the morning I left at 1:30
1:30 one time so I can't do it anymore
because I I I I'm writing the books
right now and doing everything else so I
can't do that
anymore but the point is I take out the
handy wipes and I wipe the I wipe the
carriage or
something another thing too if I do too
many readings like that I go blind
anyway you guys know my story and then I
can't pick out what I need to pick out I
try to go to the store when if I ever go
to a store I try to go early the less
people the less readings I get instantly
from Spirit the less chances I go snow
blind and so I can pick out my mangoes
and my tomatoes and get my frozen Wild
blueberries and get all the things that
I need and get my lettu uses and get my
kale and get everything else I need and
I could get it in time before I start
losing my eyesight from all the people
coming in in the readings and then if
somebody asked me for reading forget it
then I leave there practically blind I
have to sit in the car and wait it
out the bottom line
is the liver gets filled up sorry about
that you guys the liver gets filled with
so many poisons and so many toxins and
the
bile breaks down and weakens and then
there's one other thing I have to tell
you the adrenaline Factor we're going to
get into the rest of it don't worry the
adrenaline Factor adrenaline pumping
into the liver pumping into the liver
and pumping into the liver from fight
our flight yes fight or flight that's
right that's right and that's happening
in in our lives all the time and
especially with like relationships and
heartaches and and all kinds of things
that happen emotional attacks mental
abuse you know continual arguments with
a spouse or partner dissatisfaction at
work high pressure deadlines um you can
keep on going on and on and on and
on all that breakups heartbreak whatever
just keep on going on and on and on
backstabbing betrayal trust issues trust
breakage all the adrenaline that floods
because that and then also things that
we do you know addictions and stuff all
the different addictions I'm not talking
about drug addictions there's so many
different addictions it's ridiculous
where the adrenaline runs
chocolate eat chocolate adrenaline is
pumping killing your liver eating
chocolate you can have a little bit if
you're into it but people eat it every
day they're eating it every day and they
think the healthy chocolate the
healthier chocolate healthy chocolate
blah blah blah meanwhile oh my God
adrenaline adrenaline every day coffee
chocolate coffee chocolate right to the
liver adrenaline pumping into the liver
weakening your bile more and more
weakening it weakening it weakening it
you know what happens when you weaken
that bile and you keep on weakening it
and the years go by and maybe you didn't
bloat maybe you do bloat but yet but
maybe you didn't but you're going to
you're going to bloat and you're going
to eventually bloat no matter what it's
coming no matter how old you're going to
be it's coming it's on your way you're
going to get bloated absolutely I hate
to be the bear of bad news the bringer
of bad news but I'm just telling you
this so you can do something about it
and turn it around I'm not going to p p
p patter around the truth and cookie cut
crap I can't do that I've never been
known to cookie you know to cookie cut
anything I've never been known to cookie
cut anything
never been known to do that I
can't I can't you
know life is precious and we we have no
time to waste
so the deal is is the liver yeah the
bile breaks down and then guess what
happens guess what happens next your
hydrochloric acid has to
overproduce it has to overproduce
overproduce the seven blend that science
and research does even know about that I
wrote about in book one medical medium
that I talk about in this Liver Rescue
book I talk about it in detail the seven
blend gastric acid okay the gastric acid
this the glands in the stomach to
produce all the gastric gastric
acid and and then that weakens and
breaks
down and hydrochloric acid breaks down
and you got low HCL it started with your
liver all low HCL starts with your liver
all acid reflux gastric problems gastric
distress everything starts with your
liver everything in the digestive track
starts in your with your
liver your liver someone said to me so
you wrote a book about the liver like
who who cares about
[Laughter]
that I couldn't believe I couldn't
believe what I
heard I couldn't believe what I heard
yeah yeah so anyway okay so bottom line
is hydrochloric acid can weaken and the
liver calls out for help and it's
bioproduction flags and waines and
waxes excess adrenaline from Life lowers
the hydrochloric acid on top of it the
emotional
everything adrenaline is like a monkey
wrench thrown into a delicate intricate
swish
grandfather wa clock what going to say
watch clock Swiss grand grandfather
clock it's like a neighbor dumping a
bottle of beer into your pot of soup
simmering on the stove that made that
you made using your grandmother's
perfect recipe check this out and this
funny you're making your grandma's like
perfect recipe or you found this recipe
that you really really like or you've
made it before and you really like like
it and you got this you got this pot of
soup simmering and it's really a good
soup it's a healing soup on top of it
and your neighbor believes that
everything that you you know that you
cook you know that you cook should
should have beer in it should have beer
in it beer on the grill on the chicken
in the sauce the barbecue sauce
marinating in beer whatever doing things
that beer you know that whole beer thing
and the neighbor just dumps a can of
beer in your soup in the kitchen just
but but you know honestly not thinking
they're doing anything harmful and they
know you even like beer maybe but you
you don't want it in your
soup yeah beer by the way lowers the
hydrochloric acid and doesn't help the
liver but you probably figured that one
out already that's not science and
research knows that one so you probably
know about you've heard a little bit
about that out
there so when you lower your bile
production bile salts lower hydrochloric
acid
lowers this is no
joke and mineral salts in the seven
blends of your stomach acid go down the
drain all of it falls apart and you
start to
bloat the small intestine isn't able to
absorb the nutrients it's meant to and
proteins start to rot and fats start to
go
rancid proteins start to R
and fats go rancid you want to heal a
digestive problem it's not more protein
more protein more protein like all the
experts
say no it's lowering protein lowering
protein for God's sake lowering
protein it's not increased fats increase
fats increase fats when everything's
going
wrong when your small intestinal tra
when your small intestinal tract is
struggling everything is struggling your
your your hydrochloric acid is is Rock
Bottom your bile weakening you don't
raise fats raise overt fats raise overt
fats you don't raise proteins proteins
prot you lower them if there's any
digestive problems whatsoever you have
to lower them and if it ain't fixed yet
that's because you got years of stuff
going on and everybody's got a different
story so it may take a little longer for
that celery juice to work and heal you
and fix you and you have to have
patience
because if you can be a fly on the
in some people's lives and see the
amount of stress or what's going on in
relationships or whatever that's
stressing them out causing adrenals to
run all the time causing their symptoms
to last longer you wouldn't believe it
you're not going to see it on Instagram
because Instagram is fantasy land for a
lot of people not for everybody of
course you know that's Fantasy Land I
mean there people don't even people are
on Instagram some people they don't even
really telling you what they're really
eating they tell you and they make it
look like I'm I'm eating this I'm eating
this I'm eating this and a lot of people
are but there's a lot of people that are
like oh I'm eating this and then they're
eating pizza on the weekend but they
don't show that part on
Instagram and know show that part on
social media I mean you know of course
it's they're right they don't have to I
mean of
course but you know it's it's it's if
you're staying diligent and you're doing
it long enough and you're doing the
right things and you saturate yourself
in the medical medium information in the
series the Timeless information you can
get rid of your digestive tract problems
thousands have you can it can be done
but a lot of people they're up against a
lot of things a lot more stress some
people are up against so much stress and
heartache that their adrenaline is
running all the time their livers have
been saturated with it some people are
more viral they got more bacteria issues
inside the liver more viruses inside the
liver some people have done more
Pharmaceuticals than others like tons of
Pharmaceuticals anti-depressants you
name it antibiotics periodically over
the years and they've done like they've
done the medications and that's all a
problem
too and some people have done all these
different things and they've they've got
everybody's different they got things
different things going on and some
people had a sluggish liver all the way
from babyhood and they had baby liver I
call it baby liver it's inside Liver
Rescue and you learn all about you know
children's liver conditions children and
baby liver and the thing is you have all
this going on some people are loaded
with heavy metals inside the liver it's
actually unbelievable and they got all
kinds of medications that have heavy
metals in them and and doctor treatments
and stuff like that conventional
doctor's office you name
it and a lot of people had braces where
they have the metal brace bra not like
the invisible line or something not the
not the whatever they have the metal
braces and all the metal just oxidized
you know for 2 years of having braces on
and it started when you're a child or a
teenager whatever and it saturated the
liver and then bloating comes later on
the metals are in there the steel and
everything else a stainless steel are
all feeding they're all feeding
pathogens and stuff I mean hey no big
deal you can clean it all up you can
work on these things but everybody has a
different story everybody has a
different thing going on one glass of
celery juice might fix one person one
day absolutely one glass of Cellar juice
is not going to fix another person yet
and they have to do a lot more besides
that they have to get all the things
down they have to saturate themselves in
in the information to learn how to bring
back their hydrochloric acid and learn
how to bring back their bile and learn
how to heal and learn how to move
forward and learn how to do
it it's that important it's that
important all of it
matters small intestine isn't able to
absorb the nutrients it's meant to
anymore rancid fats line the intestinal
tract and the colon fats line the gut
they line the gut and they Harbor
pathogens but we're told to keep on
eating protein and we're told to keep on
eating fat it's
unbelievable
unbelievable you don't think you're on a
high-fat diet you don't you don't think
you're on a high fat diet huh you're
wrong you're wrong you're on a high-fat
diet you are you eat chicken once every
single day you're on a high fat diet and
a handful of nuts and you're on a high
fat diet yeah you can have some chicken
but if you got problems and you're
struggling or anything else and there's
something going on with bloating or
whatever it's chicken every other day
you got to take a little break lower the
fats handful of almonds every other day
an avocado every other day and bring in
more leafy greens lots of celery juice
bring in some potatoes bring in sweet
potatoes winter squash bringing all
kinds of different things if you want to
go raw 100% raw do the 28 day cleanse
you do the liver cleanse to bring your
liver back and Li a rescue but you got
to work on it it's you can do it you can
heal you can heal
bloating and sometimes that bloating
sticks around for a lot of people for
quite a while cuz the deeper you detox
the more junk comes out the deeper you
detox when you start shaking and
rattling that liver and all that Gunk
and crap comes out oh my God and it
comes out it's surfacing and floating
around and it gets it's in the
bloodstream and it's floating around
everywhere that alone can get you to
bloat a little bit you better believe it
bloating healing bloating doesn't
necessarily mean the bloating goes away
the day you heal
it you can heal the bloating issue but
but because you're dumping so much out
of the liver on a daily basis you're
going to bloat for a while even after
your bloating has been
healed everybody's different with the
situation everybody's liver is different
so you got to approach it where okay
let's start here 16 ounces of celery
juice let's start right there hey if you
can handle celery juice and you like
celery juice do 32 ounces a day watch
how that really takes it to the next
level in an amazing way make sure you
have a fat-free morning no matter what
every morning is fat
free 100% fat free 100% what's called
protein free gotta be careful about that
because protein means fat in most cases
in almost all cases and if you're going
to put a bunch of plant protein like a
bunch of pea protein in your shake you
just made yourself a bloating shake my
God dried peas ground up is that's a
massive bloater if you don't feel
bloated after your shake you'll feel
bloated a week later you won't know what
it is it's the dried peas you're putting
in the shake whey protein is really bad
whey protein powder that's the bloater
of all bloaters how many people have
that collagen in shakes that's a bloater
oh my God the
bloaters that are in people's shakes too
all that almond butter all the oh my God
people put tablespoons of almond butter
in their shake and they're like well got
to keep the insulin balance got to keep
the blood sugar balanc meanwhile you
just you just totally destroyed your
blood sugar because you're making
insulin resistance by making putting all
that fat inside your shake now if this
is a foreign land for anybody that's
listening then you should learn learn
about the truth and learn about the
information if you're afraid of it and
you don't like what I'm saying I'm sorry
I'm sorry I mean I do
care I really do care it matters to me
what happens to you it does if I seem
insensitive I'm not insensitive to you
one bit I'm insensitive to the industry
I'm insensitive to the trends
Setters the trend setters that that put
out bogus information
I'm I'm insensitive to a lot of
situations out there that get people in
trouble so they waste another five years
another eight
years you know what I suggest with
people with bloating is to go plant-
base for a little while in their life if
they're afraid to they should but they
should try it they should try it if
they're big into animal protein go
plant-based for a little while
absolutely totally do
that if you're afraid to keep some
animal protein in do it at the end of
the day do your animal protein at the
end of the day and do it only once a day
if you can start with that then start
with that and during the day you got to
bring in mineral salts and leafy greens
mineral salts and leafy greens cucumber
juice celery juice celery juice by
itself of course you guys know that 16
ounces on an empty stomach if you can
salads spinach salads leafy green salads
lettuce mix butterleaf lettuce red leaf
lettuce green leaf lettuce Roma bringing
in the mineral salts spinach bring in
the mineral salts yeah you might be
bloated yeah you might be bloated for a
while absolutely but you know what
you're doing you're building you're not
trying to get a Curative power you're
not trying to get a Curative antidote to
cure your bloating in that one minute
because that's ridiculous what you're
doing is you're going you're doing this
so the bloating goes away for good
because your your liver can't Resto
restore its bio reserves and bio
production overnight and the people that
are even eating really good really
clean even low fat potatoes at night and
some shakes and you know like some fruit
fruit in the morning and a salad for
lunch or whatever they're doing and
they're still bloating that's cuz the
liver has that much more healing to do
there's that much more toxic nature ins
inside that liver there's that much more
viruses bacteria inside that liver
there's that much more trouble inside
that liver that has to come out and
toxins and all kinds of stuff and metals
that's why I like the heavy metal detox
smoothie
a medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie it's a
lifesaver because metals have to come
out of the liver pathogens have to come
out all of
that and then it gets and then it gets
pushed out and it takes time it takes
time for the bile reserves to rebuild
some people's bile is weak from the
beginning in childhood it can't be fixed
with a glass of celery juice but you got
to stay on it and work with it and get
it better you'll notice the bloating
getting better over time and it gets
better and better and better stronger
and then the liver wants to repair other
things sometimes it doesn't fix the bile
problem yet because you're actually
helping it to stop greater and bigger
problems that were occurring that you
didn't even know that could lead to
disease down the road when you're 60 70
50 40 whatever it is and your liver is
working on things by taking the
nutrients and taking the foods and
taking the advantage of having you do
low protein and low fats by taking the
advantage of doing that and then re
reestablishing itself healing itself
rebuilding areas of it that it produces
hormones areas that it produces enzymes
areas that it produces Miracle chemical
functions that keep you alive to protect
your heart to protect your brain all
these things it does that's also
weakening that bile is the last thing
it's got to worry about sometimes so let
it be rancid fats going down your gut
lining Let It Be rancid proteins going
down your gut lining because the liver
is more important fish to fry sometimes
so it's got to protect you if you're
really that bad with your liver over the
years and you don't need liver enzyme
tests that the doctor's office tell you
you got a problem believe me because
those things that's not even I got a
whole chapter on that in in Li rescue
right here and there's listen I can't
cover this book in these radio shows I
could only cover a little bit so if if
you're even a fraction interested in
what I have to say no matter what just
get the books and and really crack into
them just crack into them a chapter at a
time before bed just a chapter at a time
before bed you'll get nooks and crannies
and gems and jewels and you get things
that are really tasty and they'll help
you they'll help you there's some tasty
pieces in here you just got to look for
them you got to look for them they're
all in there here's the deal here's the
deal let's talk about a couple of things
people do nutritional yeast disastrous
disastrous there's glutamic acid in all
nutritional yeast absolutely
disastrous and that's hard on the liver
I'm just being straight up so you'll get
these people and they'll be like you
know they'll be on social media whatever
and they're doing all this stuff they're
like why isn't the medical medium
protocol helping me uh well first of all
there is no real medical medium protocol
per se there's just the information
that's Timeless in the books for every
single Walk of Life depending on where
they are meaning wherever they're at
meeting them at in their health and
their Health crisis on every level
there's something in EV in these books
for everyone to heal with and heal from
with and move forward with because not
one size fits all that's what the
medical medium protocol is
not one size fits all and then you'll
hear this person say oh well you know
meanwhile thousands of people I mean are
they're they're walking now they get
their anxiety gone they're healing their
guts their gut is better they got the
rid of their Lyme disease all these
amazing things and then you get somebody
they're eating nutritional yeast and lot
of nutritional yeast they gobbling it
down they have to have nutritional yeast
every single day with all that glutamic
acid totally saturating the liver and
they're wondering why their bloating is
not going
away and then you have and then you have
somebody who's doing the apple cider
vinegar the apple cider vinegar will
make you get bloated vinegar is it
pickles the liver it's the worst thing
ever yeah I know apple cider vinegar is
better than all the other vinegars I'm
not doubting that it's actually good for
your scalp too it's good for other it's
good for your skin to treat your skin
terrible for your liver internally when
you consume it but that'll that'll
weaken your liver weaken your bile
weaken your hydrochloric acid destroy
your hydrochloric
acid that acidic nature vinegar destroys
hydrochloric acid hydrochloric acid in
your stomach can only rebuild through
mineral salts that are
alkaline in nature both on the back and
on the front that means even if apple
cider vinegar has an alkalinizing kind
of effect in some way internally what it
is it's completely acidic in its worst
way and mineral salts are not they're
never acidic in any way back or front of
it on a on a on on an Alchemy level you
know the bottom line is you just hurt
your liver and you get you get
bloated so what's behind bloating like
I'm saying what's the other things when
the bloating occurs it starts to happen
part of bloating is the gut coping with
poorly digested food another part is
when the liver is unhappy and stagnant
to the point of lower bioproduction
right yeah it means that it's also
overburdened with toxic materials like I
was saying leeching out into the bile so
they end up back in your intestinal
tract how do you like them apples you
guys the bile gets filled with metals
and everything else from the inside of
the intestinal track drives right up
into the gut drops into your gut again
gets
reabsorbed really a difficult
situation it is there's so much
there and means that it's overburdened
with toxic materials and as they leech
on out into the bile they end up back in
the intestinal tract they're being
excreted from the bottom of the liver
off so floating down saturating
lymphatic vessels around the colon and
absorbing it into the
colon bacterian viruses waste matter old
viral casings from Epstein bar and
sticky jelly like sludge produced by
toxins combined with
pathogens that's among the materials
that can bleed into the intestinal
tract oxidative runoff everything all of
these things coat the lining of the
small intestinal tract and
colon causing more bloating and it
hampers everything it hampers good
bacteria that we need it feeds bad
bacteria it feeds unproductive
microorganisms ultimately I swear it can
get to the point where the overgrowth of
strep which causes sibo which is in the
subtitle of the book Liver Rescue to
develop strep flourishes and pockets of
the intestinal
tract it just creates gas more bloating
more intestinal problems almost
everybody has
sibo that's the irony they don't need to
get a diagnosis of it lower lower bio
and lower hydrochloric acid production
undigested food debris all of this fats
and proteins undigested and constantly
being thrown inside the B the bowels
every day with their
diet ultimately feeds the pathogens
whether you're vegan vegetarian or
animal-based
diets someone said hey you're just
you're just you're all about the vegans
you you're all what do you mean I am
since when and you're you're all about
the and someone said you're all about
the meat eaters the plant-based PE I
mean the the the Paleo people you're all
into that right you're you're against
veganism I am what do you mean I've seen
I've seen plant-based diets save people
from
Death I've offered plant-based diets
that have saved people from dying it's
one of the most powerful ways to heal I
don't care what anybody says you better
believe
it and I've seen paleo diets and high
protein diets PE keep people people from
eating too
stupid keeps them from eating like crazy
pizza every day keeps them from eating
whatever it keeps them from eating you
know gluten every day and whatnot and
and it it keeps them balanced in certain
ways they see to keep people balanced so
they actually have a rhythm because they
just love animal protein so you can't
take animal protein away you never be
able to take it away so you want to
support it of course and if they eat it
in a certain way if you guys like animal
protein there's a way of eating it and
still recover and there's also a way of
eating it and still get all those other
things you
need yeah I've seen it help keeps people
off of processed foods it keeps people
from eating worse things but yet sure
all the high protein diets are still bad
you just got to lower lower the fats and
lower the proteins and you could still
have some animal products all the vegans
you got to lower the nuts and seeds
lower the coconut oils lower all the
almond butter lower all the the avocado
and the other oils and and seeds and
everything you got to lower those down
too it's not that I'm against anything
or paleo or vegan it's it's just you
know what I'm against I'm against
killing your liver with fats no matter
what aisle you sit on how about
that you got to watch out for ammonia
permeability that's something that I
brought to the world ammonia
permeability doesn't exist that science
research does even know about it Le it's
not leaky gut it's ammonia permeability
rotting rotting food leaking out an
ammonia gas that actually doesn't cause
leaky gut but it travels everywhere
through the body it's
ghostlike don't confuse that with leaky
gut that's just old old
news old
misinformation so it's important to know
all these different
things so the bottom line is bloating
cramping discomfort distension all Rises
up from the gut into your stomach
contributing to further further
diminishment of hydrochloric acid and
reserves stomach GLS
weaken
everything bacteria like H pylori
proliferate in the environment strappy
coli ulcers can happen
staff all of it can prosper even candida
even though candida isn't a problem
there's other fungus that is a problem
though there's bad fungus that people
get so the bottom line is undigested
protein doesn't break down right
undigested fat doesn't break down
dangerous funguses viruses everything
can sit inside the gut and produce
poison
and sit inside the liver producing
poison so you keep on
bloating and if you haven't bloated yet
in your
life protect yourself now get your diet
good pick up the books get the
information saturate yourself in the
information can't afford books go to the
library get the information get it
because you're going to bloat down the
road because inevitably you're going to
eat wrong and you have been eating wrong
in some way some some some some way this
isn't about food
shaming you're talking to a guy that
gives you permission to eat fruit for
God's
sake okay what about all the elimination
diets oh take away this you can't have
cilantro you can't have oh you can't
have this you can't have cinnamon can't
have almonds can't have this can't have
that can't have um you Roma lettuce nope
that's out you can't have that you can't
have strawberries you can't have any
kind of fruit oh you can have blueberry
you can't have this you can't have that
and you got this elimination diets that
are absolutely utter insane oh you can
have eggs they they leave eggs in there
in a lot of them oh but you can have
eggs Mrs Jones you can have eggs the
very thing that feeds every pathogen in
the world that gets people sick and gets
their liver sick in the worst way that's
that's that's food shaming that's that's
meaning that's food crazy all that's
food crazy all the elimination stuff and
all that stuff you go to functional
medicine doctors drive you nuts they
give you a read out of food like a list
is Big it gets you in trouble meanwhile
I'm like more I mean and I've never told
anybody to be just on a fruit diet and
fruit only in my life you need the leafy
greens you can have all the fruit you
want of course but you need the leafy
greens you need the mineral salts you
need the spinach you need the mosh you
need the red leaf lettuce butter leaf
lettuce you need the green leaf lettuce
you need some kale you need all of that
you need sprouts sprouts sprouts there's
nothing wrong with Sprouts most
beautiful thing in the world you do the
Sprouts fenig Greek Sprouts broccoli
Sprouts radish Sprouts do a little
Sprouts on things all of that's
important cucumbers Tomatoes zucchinis
all of it broccoli caulif you can do
steamed vegetables you can do raw
asparagus you can do cooked asparagus
you can all these different things it's
endless it's endless all the fruits and
vegetables you want okay and if you're
into fats and proteins yeah you can do a
few nuts and seeds okay sure you can do
some hem seeds and do different seeds
and if you're in animal protein do some
do some salmon do a little bit of free
range you know free range something if
you really want but make sure all these
other things are coming in all these
other things can it's not food it's not
food fear it's bringing in foods that
people are afraid of these days too how
about that bringing in bananas bringing
in potatoes I'm one of the biggest
Advocate biggest Advocate supporters of
potatoes because potatoes heal you know
what they do they actually feed your
liver glucose and feed your brain
glucose they keep your brain from
shrinking potatoes keep your liver from
dying potatoes have amino acids in it to
kill Epstein bar
virus potatoes are that powerful that
antiviral that antibacterial and science
and research doesn't have a
clue and all the different communities
including the new letin community and
everything else has no clue you know I
opened up a lecture years ago I opened
it up saying we've been tricked we've
been fooled we've been tricked we've
been fooled we've been duped we've been
taken
for that's right the wool has been
pulled over our eyes that's right you
name it and it happens over and over and
over again and we live our life and
generations with misinformation and
lectin is a new one and we live our life
with
misinformation and all that does is feed
Empires you guys don't even know
about it feeds
Empires it feeds Empires people making 5
million a month on on misinformation
that they're feeding the feeding every
the masses it's
unbelievable yeah and like I said I'll
remind you one thing about celery juice
spirit and I brought celery juice to the
world straight celery juice we didn't
create celery
but we brought celery juice to the world
okay and the only science that research
to back it is spirit and all the con
took a trend to such a degree all the
conventional world out there including
conventional doctors and concluding
experts and everything are heralding
they're trying to hop on the train you
know as if they started the celery juice
ride they're trying to hop on the train
and it doesn't even have anything behind
it besides spirit and these are all the
people that have to rely on studies and
rely on this rely on that and look at
that huh isn't it interesting everybody
wants a piece of the celery juice
because it is a miracle cure and it is a
miracle healer and it can bring your
bloating and heal it it can bring it
about and turn it around it could do
everything and it's that amazing and
spirit's that amazing bringing the
information to you and I love you guys I
might suck but everything else but
spirit is amazing I love you guys a
little s youer take care bye