[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now I've
always said who has 10 or 20 years to
wait for answers life is precious who
has 30 years to wait for answers and
truth about chronic illness about all
the different illnesses and autoimmune
diseases and symptoms and conditions and
mystery problems who has time to waste
we need the answers now now now I've
been
fortunate enough to have a gift come to
me when I was at the age of four so that
I could give it to everybody else and
give the gift to everybody else give the
information that they need to heal of
dedicated my life I've helped heal tens
of thousands of people moved them
forward now it's in the hundreds of
thousands and I want to do the same for
you and any way I can any possible way I
can and um have you picked up thyroid
healing it's really helpful check it out
if you haven't already same with the
other books life-changing Foods or
medical
medium look into them if you're looking
for answers or if you're confused or
what you're doing isn't working enough
or working all so check those out if you
can Today's Show endometriosis this is
an important one because this is a great
mystery like a really great mystery at
least you know what happens is with a
lot of autoimmune
diseases um different illnesses
different chronic illness the theories
they have are they're never the theories
are never right about any of the chronic
illnesses out there but at the same time
they at least can like hang their hat on
a theory that feels comfortable enough
for the medical community to be like
okay sure okay no that okay autoimmune
the body's attacking itself okay I'll
buy into that and that's not true by the
way that's not how it works the body
doesn't attack itself you guys know how
it works um who know me and know my
information and the truth that comes out
but the bottom line is is that when it
comes down to endometriosis it's not
even there's not even stuff there's not
even stuff to make people feel
comfortable as far as to clear up the
mystery there's not even information to
even help clear up the mystery to even a
point where everybody feels comfortable
in the medical communities even the
medical communities are like well they
just throw their hands up in the air
sure I mean we have procedures to
removing endometriosis when it gets
attached to the outside of the colon you
know we do surgical procedures and we go
in there and we we uh we we we lift off
the pods the tiny little cysts and we
try to we try to snip and clear out the
adhesions the best we can some really
good doctors know how to do this
procedure and um it's more successful I
think a little bit more successful now
for some people than it was in the past
and so it's it's you know that's helpful
it's that's been helpful for people and
then some people you know they've
they've not had a lot of luck with that
but still there's there's ways to deal
with it out there in the medical Realm
but that's just you know and then
there's not a lot though to offer about
why it even happens what even happens
why does
endometriosis occur why are these uh
endometrial cells attaching themselves
to the
bladder why are they attaching
themselves around the
ovaries why is this even occurring
that's the it's like a massive mystery
it's like meaning all chronic illness is
Mystery but at least in a lot of
different areas of chronic illness
everybody can get comfortable with
whatever lie or
scam or whatever it is in the medical
industry that they want to pass off
something you know some kind of thing
like first of all it was all in your
head years ago Oh no you're crazy it's
all in your head your symptoms aren't
even real so that that whole thing they
try to pass on everybody right and
everybody bought into that you know I
talk about that in thyroid healing and
then you know there's been one after
another one after another all the way up
to autoimmune now it's the gene Theory
everything's genes doesn't matter what
it is at this point it's like oh it's
your genes that's your that's just
you're going to have that disease cuz
it's genetic uh we might have a somewhat
of a treatment that can almost work but
it's it's or not but it's genetic you're
stuck with it it's just who you are
you're born this way you're faulty
that's that's the new way that one is
even kind of rising going to rise above
the autoimmune way they're both going to
be hand inand it's like it's genetic and
your body's attacking itself your body's
attacking itself because it's genetic
because you have a genetic disease and
your body's attacking it's going to go
back and forth like that or or both both
together like that that's how it's
always going to be and so and with
endometriosis they're trying to head
there they're trying to head there
they're going to have to they're going
to be like oh it's just genetic and
they're going to or NE immune cells are
confused or something like that we'll
cover some of their theories the medical
community's theories right now but it's
but the theories of endometriosis just
you can't even swallow it it's down it's
like it's hard to choke down because at
least some of the other theories for
chronic illness are they're ridiculous
and they're wrong but people can buy
into it easier with endometriosis it has
to be eventually pushed off to those
those theories too the ones that okay
it's genetic or the body's confused it's
going to have to go there because
they're just they just don't know how it
occurs it's it but it's like that with
chronic illness all over them you know
what I mean they don't know how really
anything occurs to this point and um
just how it's always
been so you know this show has nothing
to do with repackage or recycled Theory
made to sound like a new understanding
of any kind of illness just for the
record the information here doesn't come
from medical interest groups medical
funding with strings attached Bots
research thumb on the scale you know
investors investing in a project so the
outcome has to has to be bias and and
fall into the Investor's liking because
they'll never invest again in that
person or that that that technician um
internal medical internal Kickbacks none
of that going on here no medical
lobbyists involved with any information
that's ever been on this show ever ever
ever ever that have been given out to
people to help them heal no persuaded
belief systems which is really dark
persuaded belief systems ends up make
making money go underneath the table so
that so that citations of studies and
per viws and all this other garbage and
junk science gets out there and then
that's why everybody's still sick and
chronically still sick and chronically
still sick because of all those
repackaged theories private panels of
influencers you wouldn't believe how
many of those are in alternative
medicine conventional medicine you guys
have no idea Health fueld payoffs and
trendy traps trendy traps really stink
because trendy traps just get people
confused they make them do dangerous
liver flushes they make their
gallbladders you know need need
surgeries CU St Stones get caught in the
gallbladder from you know liver flushes
they uh all kinds of different cleanses
hurting the liver hurting the body and
different things because they're all not
done right because that's just a way it
works trendy traps from high fat diets
to you know diets that just don't make
sense when someone has a certain disease
or a certain problem and they eat a
certain way for but it's all for the
wrong it's all wrong because it's not
right for the disease or condition or
symptom they have all that trendy stuff
that gets M swirls around over and over
again from doing bacon soda from filling
your intestinal tract with bacon soda
from doing every I'm doing coffee enas
enas are fine but coffee enas like all
the the swirling bull that goes around
around what no one under no one
understands doesn't make you get better
or make you feel better only gets you
worse while you're chronically sick with
no answers because no one understands
how Epstein bar really truly works how
viruses really truly work how sibo is
really just the strep bacterium how all
these different things all how Lyme
disease is is oh my God just you got to
get the lime chapter you got to read the
lime chapter out of medical medium book
one I talk about lime a little bit in
thyroid healing but medical medium book
one I really lay it out and it's
Timeless it's classic even though that
was a couple years ago it's classic and
Timeless because it's it's it's what it
is it's the truth the truth is the truth
and the truth just stands there like
that and um it doesn't matter how many
genetic theories and autoimmune theories
of the body attacking itself and that
are wrong and and and and backward out
there so here's the
deal the information on the show comes
from a pure untampered with
uncontaminated place a clean clean
source of information I was given a gift
at age four I've dedicated my life in in
giving the information that comes and um
and yeah so it's been for you this whole
time so we can get you better I've
helped people get better who have lived
great lives all these years after being
debilitated debilitatingly sick with
chronic illness
with no hope and so um but anyway we're
talking about endometriosis say so let's
do that let's get into it right away
thanks for uh having your patience
having
patience at the beginning here I'm a
little bit more light-hearted in this
show I've been pretty heavy heavy heavy
duty in the other shows pretty intense I
mean pretty intense a little too
sarcastic little too intense because you
know what happens is when when you know
people are suffering out there and you
know information is is backwards it just
it just gets to you I'm sorry but it
gets to you after year after year after
year after year it gets to you because
it's like aren't we aren't we there yet
aren't we there yet what year is it
aren't we there I mean look at the
technology we have aren't we there don't
we have answers don't we have something
better than what's going on did you know
people are getting sicker and sicker and
sicker faster and younger unbelievable
able unbelievable Spirit was right when
Spirit told me that's what was coming
our way and spirit was 100% right of
course as always um so yeah yeah so that
so here's you know the endometrium in
the uterus the tissue lining there um
grows inside the grows it what happens
is those endometrial cells they they get
out somehow get outside of the uterus
and they start to grow that's that's all
we know is somehow they get out side
they get outside the uterus so that's
that's what we know right there that's
basically it and it's it's not a lot
it's not a lot the cells meaning what we
know it's not a lot what we do for it
well you can you have some options the
doctors offer you could go on the
pill so that's one option they they they
try it's a try to to try to confuse
hormones because they believe the
hormones play a role with endometriosis
and um and they kind of do they kind of
do they do in some way they do and we'll
talk about that a little bit but all we
know really is that these endometrial
cells these endometrial cells somehow
get on the outside of the
uterus and then they
grow they grow they can grow in places
on the colon they can grow in places in
the pelvic walls they can get into the
pelvic Cav they can get into the the
ovar they can get onto the ovaries they
can get onto the
bladder what happens is with symptoms
that people have is that women have is
you know colon even though
that's actually not understood by
medical communities they don't really
understand that part but but
colon so lots of colon spasms can occur
so when these end endometrial cells are
actually on the outside of the colon and
they create
and little little um little pods and
little cysts and adhesions and micro
adhesions to larger adhesions to macro
adhesions are growing on the outside of
the
colon it's triggering off
nerves so then when uh you have your
menstrual
cycle then all of a sudden that happens
and all this pressure builds up and puts
pressure up against the colon and it
pushes those pods into the colon a
little bit it presses up against the
colon and then it touches nerves and
then colon spasms happen it's with a lot
of women when they're cramping they're
not just cramping from having a cycle a
lot of women with endometriosis they're
not just cramping from having a cycle so
you guys you probably many of you with
endometriosis probably experienced so
much like this and what happens is it's
also cramping from the colon
spasms and that's what makes it really
difficult
really difficult
because once these once these cells are
growing and these little tiny macro
adhesions and micro adhesions are are
developing and the cells are are kind of
prospering and and developing and and
and growing and that's happening on the
outside of the colon so the minute you
have your menstrual cycle and everything
swells everything swells and same with
ovulating every in during ovulation time
too everything swells ovaries swell they
expand so what happens is there pressure
there's not a lot of space in here
everybody thinks everybody thinks that
internally we have all the space they
all everybody does I honestly I've
noticed this even practitioners there's
the practitioners out there and
different healers and even some doctors
they they think there's a lot of space
in there not not everybody thinks this
but most everybody in your own body you
think there's a lot of
space there's no space in there
everything's squeezed everything's
already squeezed tight everything is
tightly squeezed everything the ovaries
are packed in there uterus everything is
packed in there everything's tight your
liver your gallbladder everything's
tight your intestinal tract your colon
it's all it's all tight connective
tissue all happening it's just all
packed tight and then what happens is
that all you need all you need is a few
things occurring so say you're a woman
and you have some lymphodema
and you're you have a little bit EMA
that means fluid retention so you're
dealing with some fluid and I'm not just
talking about weight or or extra weight
gain I'm talking about fluid retention
just a little bit of that happening
periodically and you have
endometriosis the fluid retention puts
pressure this isn't even a cycle or a
period a menstrual cycle I'm talking
about now fluid
retention it puts
pressure on everything in there there's
no place to go with that flu F retention
especially lymphatic system there's no
place to go so that pressure alone can
be uncomfortable when you're dealing
with endometriosis periodically make it
really
uncomfortable um the experiences could
be really uncomfortable if your bladder
gets too full so if your bladder gets if
you're holding in a a
pee if you're holding in a
pee and you know your kidneys got as
much PE as they can hold in and your
bladder you're holding that in with
everything you have and you got
endometriosis and the extra urine in the
bladder pushes you know kind of blows
the bladder up a little bit like a
balloon and it's got a little bit of
those pods or it has a little bit of the
intermetal cell sitting on outside the
bladder and they're all touching nerves
so the minute you have a little bit more
urine in your bladder oh my God it's
going to hurt it could burn it could
hurt it could be it could be painful you
can get bladder something
actually Medical communities are really
not too familiar with the
bladder so and you can get these bladder
spasms lots of these nerve related
bladder spasm so it's nerves triggering
off the bladder because the nerves are
sensitive because they got they got the
endometrial cells in the little pods
little micro adhesions macro adhesions
attach to the outside of the bladder so
then all of a sudden you're getting
these
spasms and that occurs and you know
every every woman is different because
they'll you know you could have a little
bit on the bladder you can have a little
bit on the colon you could have a little
bit around the ovaries you can have just
one spot a little bit around the
colon and nowhere else and you're
getting some colon spasms so when you
have your menstrual cycle and there's
all this pressure building up and
pressure building up from the menstrual
cycle it could put pressure up against
the colon morph because everything's so
packed tightly and then all of a sudden
it's pushing those little tiny cells
into nerves and when those get pushed
into nerves you're like oh my God you're
like this is a such an uncomfortable
menstrual cycle this is
brutal whether you're bleeding heavy or
not some women they're not bleeding
heavy and they're just they're just an
Agony and pain some women are bleeding
heavy and there're an Agony and pain too
so it's either or and then and then um
when those little nerves are being
touched by the pressure of a menstrual
cycle pushing up against the colon and
pushing against those pods and micro
adhesions and pushing them into the
colon then you got you got colon
occurring I mean I've seen it's some
women I mean that have called and
they're just like over the years and
they're just like they're like oh my God
I'm on the floor or their husband would
call call me and just be like look I
need to they're on the floor they're
having you know this is what she goes
through all the time we have to do
something about and and you know and
that's that's what women go through when
they're dealing with
endometriosis and so we're going to talk
about what to do actually to help stop
endometriosis to stop it from growing
because that's what you wanted to do you
want it to stop it from growing you want
to shut it down and there are some great
things you can do to shut it down so
we're going to cover that and so when
people go into as colon you got
to put heat on their belly hot water
bottle up against their belly a moist
hot um towel anything like that that
does help get women through spasms when
they're going through that but it's no
it's no fun it's brutal I mean you guys
know you guys know how brutal it is and
same thing with urinary issues
with the bladder
too um and and that's also a real you
know that's a real hot spot real trigger
spot right there and then ovary pain
that's a whole another story so when you
have the the micro adhesions the macro
adhesions and you have the little pods
and you have the little cysts and you
have the little growths from endometrial
endometrial cells you have that going on
around the
ovaries and that's also really diff ult
too because you can get some serious
ovarian pain especially during ulation
and so forth so and everything's so
packed tight things are hitting
nerves why do you think the pain and the
spasms come because nerves actually are
the reason for pain and spasms because
the nerves are being touched or or
pushed upon or jabbed in one way or
another in order for that to happen and
that's how we get into that
place so endometriosis is such a mystery
to the medical world absolute mystery I
mean they use the pill to try to address
it to give people get get women some
results and relief but how does the pill
do that is it really blocking hormones
or altering hormones is it doing that in
order to give somebody relief what it is
doing is it's a steroid so all all
contraceptive that's that are like that
like the pill hormonal based
contraceptives they're all they're um
they're actually
steroids and what happens is with any
condition of the body doesn't mean
matter what it is whatever disease
illness symptom condition mystery
symptom whatever it is steroids are one
of these goto moments one of these go-to
situations for medical research and
science they have really not too many
options they got immunosuppressives for
people they got painkillers they got
steroids they got
antibiotics that's pretty much what's
going on in the medical industry there's
not much outside of that besides a few
blood blood thinners and if you you want
to go into anti-depressant land and and
um and antis psychotic drugs that's
another story but the point is there's
not many there's not there's a lot of
medications but not a lot
of options and small groups of
medication what I'm saying is you think
there's a lot more options you got
steroids you got antibiotics you got
immune suppressives immunosuppressives
I mean it's a small group and you got
painkillers so research and science
doesn't have a magic magic pill and a
lot of women they don't they don't
respond to a steroid they don't respond
to the pill they don't respond to the
pill for their for for
endometriosis um some do where it eases
things and and many don't so it's hit or
miss
too when they do respond it's because
the steroid aspect of the pill is
suppressing the the inflammation part of
the issue so you get inflammation so
what happens is endometrial
cells um when they're clinging when
they're on the outside of the uterus and
they're in the pelvic cavity and they're
in areas and they're they're they're on
or they're on the outside of the colon
or they're up against the bladder they
create in they're they're kind of
creating
inflammation but they're not really
creating inflammation themselves these
little endometrial cells something else
is and we're about to talk about that in
a little bit so inflammation is is being
is created around the situation I'm
going to talk about that and clear that
up a little bit so you know what's going
on there and so what's happening is when
you take the pill which is a variety of
steroid it's a type of
steroid what happens is that you get
some suppression of it that's that's
what goes on um women with uh severe
severe severe endometriosis they
actually sometimes put them on not just
the pill but they put them mon
additional
steroids periodically to try to get to
try to get everything to calm
down so but there's there's not a lot of
options so there's not a lot of things
going on there in the medical world and
it's still a complete mystery to
research in science but there's ways to
actually stop it there's ways to
diminish it there's ways to to push it
back and we can do that naturally
through Foods we can do that naturally
through certain supplements so we're
going to go into
those
so we've covered a lot with what's
happening here and then the symptoms are
really you you get the painful periods
the you get also when you're going to
the bathroom the bowel movements can be
really really
difficult so when elimination is
occurring that's difficult because when
you have peristaltic action on the
colon and the col's twisting it's it's
it's squeezing and the peristaltic
actions happening and it's got got the
little pods and the little microions on
the outside of the
colon um tickling the nerves and it's
it's
twisting or squeezing I'm sorry
peristaltic action occurring where the
the Colon's actually getting messages
from nerves to actually move so that
your elimination can come out of you
okay and end up in the toilet when
that's happening you could be really in
a lot of pain a lot of
pain from that and that's one of the
things so many women go through and it
gets confused it get gets confusing um
and there's a lot of times you can go to
10 doctors and one doctor be like I
don't know what this is uh I think you
just got IBS another doctor be like I I
don't know what's going on and then you
get some women that have a little bit of
IBS and they have endometriosis or they
have endometriosis but it's not causing
the problem and what they really have is
something happening in the intestinal
tract it's there's so the it's really
difficult out there it's so not
clear-cut and it's not easy and it
should be that's the hard part about
chronic illness and everything that I
deal with you wonder why I get annarchy
and you wonder why I get sarcastic and
you wonder why I talk about how the
information here is different than the
the Recycled Theory that's out there
there's a reason why I talk about all
that because it should be
easier we shouldn't have to go through
this I've seen a lot of women and young
women have to go to doctor and doctor to
doctor I've heard their stories out
there there and they've had to they the
different answers everywhere one
doctor's like oh no it's really this one
doctor's like oh it's that we think you
have endometriosis we're going to have
to do this and this to do this and
meanwhile no that's not even what's
causing the pain or the problem or the
discomfort and no and you got this and
then it's it's
endless and maybe it's just candida and
you got chronic yeast infections we
can't tell yet we're going to figure
this out and it's just a lots of tests a
lot of different confusion and then you
get blood work and you're you know
you're going to another specialist and
yet then you you know you leave with
some kind of pres prescription or you
leave with a pill if you're not already
on it and then regardless of all that
you're still not doing good A year later
then you end up getting fatigued nobody
talks about that you get the fatigue and
now you're tired and now you don't feel
good and you're getting migraines and
it's it's all that going on you know
with young women having to deal with
that and and and older women having to
deal with
that it's really really difficult it
shouldn't have to be that way in this
day and age we shouldn't have to be
there we just shouldn't have to be there
when you really think about
it so there's a lot of theories out
there let's talk about the theories for
a couple of
minutes so science and research they
don't know how they they don't know how
endometriosis occurs they don't know
what happens they they got some guesses
so they've done a lot of round T guesses
and had a lot of people talking and to
figure out what you know a lot of the
time Top Doctors in the world and and um
and big Pharma and everything they've
gotten together and they've they've come
along with you know science and research
come along with a few
theories um so one is called something
like the uh um the um let's see there's
different the perianal theory so what
this means is the inner abdomen the
inner side of the abdomen cells line the
inner side of the abdomen because the
immune system creates this problem it's
really or its hormones the immune system
create the problem so you got you got
endometrial cells that are lining the
inside of the
abdomen so it's like the perianal theory
so that's one um it really doesn't make
a lot of sense so then there's the
retrograde Theory so it's called
retrograde that's another theory out
there and you know and and look I'm not
an expert on the
theories that are out there I'm not an
expert on the bogus theories so don't
you know don't quote me on the exact
bogus Theory
thing um I'm an expert at the truth and
the information that you need and the
truth of what causes whatever you know
whatever disease illness and and
everything that's where I'm an expert at
of course and I say that because luckily
I got spirit and that's why I'm an
expert I wouldn't be without spirit so
it's not me being smart I'm not a smart
guy okay I never went to school it's
because of spirit so the bottom line is
these theories that are out there um
they there're they're to swallow so the
retrograde Theory that's when you're
having a menstrual cycle so menstruation
is occurring and blood throws back up
through the Fallopian tubes into the
pelvic cavity spreading cells I I like
that theory you know I I I like it a
little bit because you know it's
it's it's reasonable it's a reasonable
Theory so that's one there it is
reasonable um anyway another theory
science and research has it's embryonic
cell transformation I think that's what
they call it uh if my memory serves me
right I mean you can look up these
theories out there and look this up
you'll you you know you could probably
read as much information as you want on
it and this has to do with uh ental cell
implants so it's it's all about estrogen
and and ental cell implants and you can
read into that one um so that you know
these are still all theories another
theory is C-section or surgery so when a
woman gets C-section or gets a
surgery that endometrial cells they tend
to find their way into the incisions
into the scar into the incisions or
where the surgery where the injury was
and the endometrial cells tend to get in
there and they spread and grow it's a
believable Theory it's kind of
believable that's one
too and then there's um there's another
theory it's uh cell
transport I like this one probably the
best out of all the theories out there
in the medical communities or the
medical science and research World
endometrial cell transport this is when
lymph your lymphatic system transports
cells to other areas of the body
intermetal cells to the other area of
the
body so look the bottom line is an alien
isn't coming out from outer
space and taking endometrial cells and
taking those endometrial cells and
placing them around the body so there
has to be a way they have to get around
the body there has to be a way you know
an alien's not coming out of the sky and
doing it
so all right we won't be talking that
silly um so so that's another theory too
and then there's another theory the
immune system disorder which it's always
going to go here and Lead here like
meaning in the sense that this this is
the theory it's always going to land on
which is your immune system is attacking
itself your body is distorted you you
know what I mean your body's Twisted
it's it's it's attacking itself it
doesn't know what's right or what's
wrong it doesn't know what's up and down
this is the autoimmune Theory so it
always goes in there the body can't
recognize and destroy the endometrial
cells so what's happening is these
endometrial cells are getting on the
outside of the uterus and they're
finding their way into the pelvic cavity
and your body isn't recognizing them to
destroy
them so they're just growing it's kind
of a little bit of the backwards a
backwards rendition of autoimmune
disease
disease but it's still in the same
category where they're putting it where
your body's creating this it's an immune
system
disorder and your body can't recognize
and Destroy these endometrial
cells so that's where that one is that's
a theory too all on its own so I'm just
running some of the
theories of modern medicine but no
matter how you slice the pie no matter
how you slice the cake or whatever you
want to do um the the the bottom line is
my medical science researchers saying we
don't know how these cells get on the
outside of the uterus we don't know how
they get there they just do they just
do that's the bottom line so there's a
couple things that happen with there's a
couple things so let's go into um let's
go into the nitty-gritty let's go into
the deep stuff let's go into The Real
McCoy let's go into the the real deal
okay of what's really going on and
what's happening with endometriosis with
a couple things one thing you have to
understand here is endometrial cells
have a life to them like no other they
have a life to them like no
other so we're dealing with the uterus
here we're dealing with the maker of
Life someone might argue and say well
the egg is the maker of life before it
even gets into the uterus so you're
wrong Anthony someone else might say
well the ovaries are the maker of life
so you're definitely wrong there
well no no no no no no the uterus you
can have all the eggs you
want and you can have the you know your
your ovaries can be perfect but the
uterus has to keep life sustained for
those nine months the uterus has to keep
life
sustained so precious
life a living being has to be sustained
and
protected and in good
standing more than good standing
protected a little Angelic being inside
the
uterus and a little baby and so the
uterus is a a really fierce fierce
fierce protector of life that's what the
uterus is and the metrial cells are
programmed with information tremendous
amounts of
information I mean honestly the
information in one endometrial
cell would probably explode a computer a
computer's database would just overwhelm
it override it I'm not I'm not computer
savvy or anything I'm not a big I'm not
a big tech savvy person but you get the
drift of what I'm trying to
say the information literally if it was
somehow DEC coded or somehow downloaded
from one endometrial cell it would have
centuries and centuries and centuries
and thousands of
years of information within it from the
human species alone and how life
sustains itself and how life is
protected within the uterus and
everything around
it so the will for an endometrial cell
to survive
is
great is great it's
great and so that's something just to to
realize and just consider of what you're
dealing with like if you don't know what
you're dealing with then you're going to
underestimate it you don't know what
call the wrong shots if you don't know
what you're dealing with then you're not
going to know what causes what and what
disease what
illness if you don't know what you're
dealing with like they don't know what
they're still dealing with with Lyme
disease out there I'm sorry to say that
if that confuses you get my lime chap
from book one just read it if you don't
know what you're dealing
with that's not good that's where we go
wrong right at the beginning if we don't
even know what we're dealing with if we
don't understand the uterus and we don't
know what we're dealing with to a degree
with the uterus or any kind of cells
uterus based or any kind of endometrial
cells if we don't know what we're
dealing with here and I'm saying that
over and over again because it's that
intense then we don't know where we
really
stand we don't know where we really
stand we don't we
don't what happens is the uterus a
uterus has to be clean it has to be
clean what does that mean what does that
mean you have your menstrual cycle it's
cleaning itself out preparing itself to
sustain life but it has to be clean
clean from what clean from poisons and
Clean from toxins clean from poisons
clean from toxins clean from pathogens
clean from viruses clean from bacteria
clean from heavy metals clean from to
from poisons and toxins clean from
troublemakers clean from all of those
troublemakers
clean what does that mean why am I
saying that over and over again I'm
saying it over and over
again because what happens is that the
endometrial cells are used used to leave
the uterus with a poison or a toxin in
it to keep the uterus
clean that's what's going on how do they
get out of the uterus we'll talk about
that in a couple
seconds but the point is is that they're
carrying something the uterus does not
want those cells inside the
uterus that's how this is
done so those endometrial those
endometrial cells if they were studied
with the right kind of science we're
just not there yet we don't have science
that could study much of anything we're
playing around with genes and that's all
fun and dandy and it's all because
they're they're interested in cloning so
they want they wanted all this money
going into genes and genes and then
they'll tell you that genes are the
reason why we're sick so more money
against dumped into it more money more
investing gets dumped into it but
meanwhile they're not working on any of
that what they're working on is just
more cloning more cloning more cloning
they want to clone monkeys they want to
clone humans they want to clone it's
just cloning it's a sick sick sick
cloning game that's being that's being
built without anybody's permission or
anybody knowing about it just so you
know that's why they throw the gene
Theory at us all the time it's so we we
we have everybody everybody becomes a
pawn meaning meaning experts become a
pawn um wealthy people become a pawn and
they dump more and more money into the
factory of genes so so they can say
they're working on our mysteries of
healing Us in chronic illness but what
they're really doing it's you're just
sitting there privately working on
trying to clone and clone and clone and
clone and do other Sinister things and
devious things but science and research
really doesn't do anything about
anything else so when you have these
endometrial
cells and these endometrial cells
they're literally packed with not only
information and a will to survive and a
will to live but they're harboring a
poison and a toxin they've been kicked
out of the
uterus they've been kicked
out and they've been kicked out they
they're not just kicked out during
menstrual cycles that's not enough they
get kicked out in between it
all they get pushed out endometrial
cells get pushed out through the lining
of the uterus a process that that no one
knows now what I liked about was one of
the theories that they have which I I
actually I actually thought it was a
cool
Theory um it was when the floian tubes
it went backwards it was the retrograde
menstrual cycle where your cycle the the
you know blood actually pushed up with
cells in it backwards up through the
fallopian tube and out into the pelvic
cavity I did like that theory a
lot it's not quite accurate a another
miraculous Theory
but it's not quite accurate I I I like
it and I say I like it because it's it's
really cool and it's is it
possible you know what it it it's
possible that blood can go through there
I've asked spirit and spirit says yeah
blood could go up it up the fallopian
tube but what's really happening and
that's rare situations by the way what's
really happening and because
endometriosis is not rare it's
common cells are actually being pushed
through the lining of the
uterus that's what's
happening and you can't you can't see it
or record it or or understand it because
unless you live inside of a human
being's body unless you live inside of a
woman's body and live in there which you
can't you'll never see the process the
process is just impossible to understand
but cells are pushed through the walls
of the of the uterus these are cells
that have poison in them that have to
leave the
uterus a lot of women have tremendous
amounts of heavy metals in them lots of
mercury lead aluminum arsenic cadmium
nickel
barium I I don't know more more than
that copper and and even more than that
and these toxic heavy metals are just
one thing but that's not why these
that's not why these cells are being
pushed through the uterus and out the
other
way these cells are being pushed through
because they're loaded with pesticides
herbicides fungicides redenti sites
larvicides they're loaded with all the
neuro antagonists and all the dangerous
chemicals that are actually Within These
they're loaded with um um dangerous
chemicals that are in colognes and
perfumes and
hairspray they're loaded with these
cells get loaded with everything thing
that we not only inherit through a
family line like
DDT so we inherit DDT we get that from
our family line not only Mercury from
our family line not only those poisons
we get a lot more poisons than that
every single day we're
here nanotechnology Finds Its way inside
the uterus all the time so
nanotechnology actually Finds Its way in
the uterus and that's on everything we
have today and then there's poisons in
foods and then there's Pharmaceuticals
too and all the pharmaceutical poison
that we inherit that we inherit it that
we have in our system from our
forefathers for mothers and then we
already have them and then we bring in
more pharmaceutical poison and more
pharmaceutical poison and then on top of
that I mean it's endless all the way to
air
fresheners all the way to air
fresheners it's everything it's poison
from Every Avenue
solvents I mean that are on everything
that you that we don't even know about
carpet cleaning chemicals it's that's
just some these are just some of the
exposure we get pesticides herbicides
fungicides especially fungicides are on
everything they're on clothing
fungicides are all over New clothing con
just all over New clo clothing and they
find their way these these these poisons
get in deep into the uterus and the
uterus is the life protector it has to
do everything it can to get rid of these
poisons so so it literally launches a
campaign a direction it launches it La
launches an
operation to excrete poisons using
endometrial cells the reason why science
and research has never going to tap into
this ever touch upon it or ever do
anything about it is because it will
then
showcase all the poisons they'll have to
do profiles on these poisons they'll
have to take an endometrial cell and
they'll have to do a Prof profile on the
poison and they're they're going to find
everything in there they're going to
find every every chemical from Every
chemical Factory that should be shut
down that literally should be shut down
trillions and trillions and trillions
and trillions of dollars in lawsuits
hundreds of trillions of dollars in
lawsuits because I mean because these
these chemicals that are in women's
bodies I mean just imagine what would be
where that would go if that was all
discovered and all profiled and science
of research decided to make a database
of what's in every cell they don't they
won't they don't want to know any of no
one wants to know anything no one not
wants to know anything in the
industries so the uterus sends these
cells
out pushes these cells out these cells
have a life
force and they're really really tiny
these cells start out so tiny but they
harbor not only tremendous amounts of
information of life life force and
needing to grow and needing to live
because they get that information
automatically from years and years of I
mean from being for years and years of
being in human history of a woman's
human being in history and in life force
to create life but from the uterus and
then to Harbor that information and have
that information to to to grow and to
become is is yeah is part of it but they
do need to be triggered in order to do
that too so not only they they filled
with poison but the endometrial cells
are not supposed to be triggered into
growing into pods and adhesions micro
adhesions macro adhesions insists all
through the pelvic cavity pelvic wall on
top of the bladder on top of the colon
they're not supposed to do
that they're not but they're filled with
a poison that pathogens love to feed off
of they're filled with a poison that
pathogens love to feed off of and there
are plenty pathogens to be had in the
pelvic wall in the pelvic region in the
pelvic cavity there's pathogens to be
had with a lot of women have a lot of
pathogens in certain areas and they are
in the lymphatic vessels they are on the
outside of the colon these pathogens
they are on the inside of the colon
these pathogens they are on the inside
of the bladder they are on the outside
of the bladder these pathogens are
available they're there they're
around and when any kind of pathogen
feeds off of an intermetal cell it's
it's like it's like a a
bonafied package it's like a Christmas
present of poisons and toxins because
the uterus needs to eliminate that
poison and toxin with everything it has
so that a being can be free from it
inside the uterus even though sometimes
the beings in the uterus may not be free
from it because there's so much poison
and toxin inherited or there in general
or be or are are coming in on every
level and so you have these intermal
cells that are not supposed to be
growing and they're not they're supposed
to be pushed out and
discarded
but they end up becoming also food for
pathogens so that's one thing that
occurs because a pod can only grow and a
micro adhesion a ma macro adhesion and a
cyst can only grow from a pathogen
feeding off of a cell a certain human
cell well the endometrial cell is a food
for a pathogen which will then grow a
cyst a pod a macro adhesion a micro
adhesion so with women with
endometriosis we have to keep pathogen
levels down we have to keep bacterial
and viral pathogens down any of these
pathogens any of the viral and bacterial
pathogens can can feed off of poisons in
these endometrial cells that could
kicked out of the uterus pushed out of
the
uterus and um and and so this is really
important to understand and so what do
we need to do about it and that's the
whole next thing we have to talk about
right now is what do we need to do about
it so what do we do
first of all we got to deal with Foods
foods are critical you got to think
about foods and what I recommend with
anybody with severe
endometriosis is to go 100% plant-based
for a little while in their life it
doesn't mean they have to be like that
forever if they don't want to but it
would go plant-based for a little bit
little bit it's just it's just it's like
if someone says well hey you know it's
like when your doctor says hey take this
medication for a little bit and then
we'll see we'll take you off of it it
doesn't mean that doctor is so Pro
medication or whatever it doesn't and
whatever it's just what's right for the
moment the doctor
believes and in the case of
endometriosis What Spirit believes is
you really really need to be plant-based
and that's something to consider stay
away from the most of the grains is what
is what's important when you're dealing
with endometriosis stay away from most
of the grains be grainfree and and even
consider the 28 day cleanse in medical
medium book one and take a look at that
and consider the 28 day cleanse even if
you do that for a little while and see
where your menstrual cycles are see
what's going on and then see what your
doctor's reports are as every every few
months when you're getting ultrasounds
or getting a CAT scan or however your
doctor deals with taking a look and
seeing what's what's going on with your
endometriosis um so Foods no dairy
products it feeds it feeds the very
pathogens any pathogen can take
advantage of an endometrial endometrial
cell that's filled with loaded loaded
with toxins so you have to take Foods
because Foods literally um will feed any
pathogen to begin with and you want to
get rid of all pathogens and any
possibility of pathogens you want to get
away Dairy you want to get away from
dairy that's milk cheese butter you want
to get away from eggs 100% away from
eggs you want to even keep the meats out
like I said before no Meats no chicken
no turkey you want to go back to that
down the road you can probably go back
to that down the road but you want to
really really go plant-based and see how
you feel and see where you are in the
moment but foods are critical no corn no
you know no pork no corn no canola
canola tends to aggravate the heck out
of endometriosis is meaning like it
makes it prosper and grow so be really
cautious with that that's important no
soy with endometriosis that's another
thing too so canola soy got to be
careful there okay and and making sure
there's you know you you want to stay
away from processed foods for sure but
you got to be careful overall with
whatever you're doing with Foods no
gluten and just try to be great rain
free for a while I would be working on a
lot of sweet potatoes sweet potatoes for
dinner every single night I would be
doing the heavy metal detox smoothie in
the morning I'd be doing the celery
juice in the morning heavy metal detox
smoothie in the morning I'd be doing um
lots of snacks like apples and celery
dates Apple celery all through the day
lunchtime I'd have an avocado and a
salad of spinach um that's what I would
do there salad of spinach tomatoes
cucumbers avocados at night you know at
night for dinner I would be doing um
sweet potato Poes and a salad a whole
bunch of sweet potatoes and a salad and
not a lot of dressing on a salad you
could probably get away with maybe um
you squeeze lemon squeeze limes on the
salad maybe a teaspoon of olive oil on
the salad you can throw a few hemp seeds
in the salad that can work too maybe a
little of avocado you don't want your
fats too high but this would be a
perfect diet you could also do winter
squash at the end of the day too but
sweet potatoes really important I would
I would lean on the sweet potatoes and
try to live off of those practice so
instead of doing chicken or turkey at
night for dinner I would lean on those
sweet potatoes it would be so the
morning celery juice then it would be
heavy metal detox smoothie okay look
into that to figure it out you to know
which one how that works from there I
would go to more snacks from lunchtime
avocado and a salad that would be
perfectly fine spinach different lettuce
tomatoes and cucumbers in the afternoon
dates celery sticks apples at night time
dinner time lots of sweet potatoes and a
salad again I would stay plant-based
while you have endometriosis that's one
D diet that I would do with
endometriosis and you're going to start
seeing results the other thing is lots
and lots of lemon balm High dosages I
would do like two three cups of lemon
balm tea a day I would do two I would
mix equal parts you know like like I
would do Cups of Tea where i' have two
lemon balm bags of tea two bags in one
cup two bags of of nettle Leaf you know
with that one would be like literally
four bags of tea basically here's what
you need to do make a big jug big jug of
tea and put a lot of leaf and a lot of
lemon balm in it and drink that
periodically through the day you can
even switch that off with raspberry leaf
like on another day and just do Straight
raspberry leaf on that day this is this
is what really gets the endometrial
cells to also clean house see here's the
thing when you have these endometrial
cells and they're filled with poisons
and toxins and they've been kicked out
of the uterus for a very good reason and
they're sitting on the outside anywhere
in the pelvic cavity and all around the
bladder or anywhere it is that they're
finding their way you want to clean
those up too you want to clean the
poisons out of those intermetal cells
when you clean the poisons out of there
pathogens won't even care they won't
even feed off of those poisons to create
a cyst or create a tumor or create
anything going on inside the pelvic wall
or or anywhere on the bladder or the
colon okay so other supplements getting
your zinc reserves is good you know get
find the right zinc on the directory if
you need to that's important if you look
at the heavy metal detox smoothly you'll
see it's got the spear lean The Barley
crass look at the right ones to get on
my directory uh on medical medium black
kohos can be an herb you can you can
play with you can talk to your
practitioner and doctor about black
black cohos it could be helpful
sometimes depending on if you're on
medications or not you can talk to your
doctor practitioner and vitamin C I
would consider vitamin C2 and b12 so
those are the supplements I would bring
in and those are the teas I would bring
in and I would do lots of parsley lots
of cilantro in your salads if you can um
consider that you can juice parsley with
celery if you really had to or juice it
with cucumber and celery throw an apple
in there in between it all these are the
things I would do focus on the foods I'd
focus on that kind of diet I would focus
on these kinds of supplements and then
what's going to happen is the heavy
metal detox movie is going to start
removing heavy metals from the outside
of the uterus too and from the inside of
the uterus and from everywhere else it's
also going to removing other poisons and
toxins that are in these entr
endometrial cells so that they don't
become food and fodder for pathogen that
are in everyone pathogens that are in
everyone in everybody's liver and going
into the repr reproductive system and
I'm talking about all the HH uh vs to
epine bar to all the streps in different
groups of strep to all the other groups
of bacteria that would that could be
harboring and that are naturally in
people and you have to understand that
these pathogens love to feed off of food
that's poison and toxin when you start
clearing this up and cleaning this up
your your uterus won't be kicking out as
many endometrial cells to begin with
they won't even grow when they're on the
outside they won't be triggered by
viruses and your immune system will get
stronger and things will be in the right
place I love you guys that's the
direction we got to go take one day at a
time this is a start we're going to do
another endometrio uh Osa show we're
going to do another one coming up too
eventually and we're going to cover some
other things bless your heart byebye