[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information it's
often decades ahead of what's out there
now decades ahead of time who has 10
years 20 years to wait for answers and
today we're talking about viigo so who
wants to wait for answers for Vitiligo I
mean you would be surprised you really
would um with chronic illness in the
industry right now the there's very few
answers it's unbelievable even where we
are today you know I remember you know
back 30 years ago and I remember 30
years ago helping out people and I
remember Spirit telling me we're way off
as far as the timeline as far as getting
getting the right information with
research Arch and science getting that
sorted out getting straight so we have
to do it for everybody we have to get
the advanced information out there for
everybody early and when it comes down
to
Vitiligo and some people call it Vio
some people viigo um some people call it
something different but you know what
happens is that even with
vidigo um I'm going all the way back I I
I remember helping people out giving
them the same
information as I'm going to give you in
the show about viigo the same
information what that means is it's
always been Advanced when Spirit hands
that information over to me um since a
young child that's how it's always been
and for anybody who is not familiar with
with how it works with medical medium
and the show and everything what you're
going to find on on these shows is
information that is not polluted and
it's not polluted by um certain groups
interest groups medical funding with
strings attached or botched research uh
thumb thumb on the scale kind of thing
where it's like internal Kickbacks and
persuaded belief systems and private
panel of influencers health field
payoffs and trendy traps those things
all exist in conventional and
alternative I repeat alternative
medicine in fact alternative medicine is
polluted with that there's a lot of
Empires built right now you guys don't
even know you don't even know how many
empires are built in the conventional
but but most I mean most importantly
alternative movement which is really sad
back in the old day it wasn't like that
I remember back in the old days it
wasn't about Empires building on
alternative medicine so that means you
know uh lots of money and lots of
studies being Twisted to for outcomes to
come out the way you know they want it
to be and stuff like that that didn't
really exist in alternative medicine in
the old days well it exists now and it's
really really horrific and this show
doesn't have any of that so if you're
you're first logged on to the show and
you're like what is this the medical
medium blah blah blah what is this show
what what is is he saying where's his
research and science where's his studies
let me tell you something you want to
stand by research in science with
chronic illness then you're just going
to be standing there for decades I'm
sorry decades and decades and decades
whether you like it or not whether you
don't like me whether you don't like
what I'm saying I don't care it's the
truth the truth is the truth the one
thing when people are sick with chronic
illness or with vialago or anything like
that is it has to be the truth when
people are suffering and they're
struggling with anything there's no
playing around there's no playing around
and I don't play around that's I don't
do it when it's when when it's about
this right here you know there's no way
because you're talking about people
suffering you're talking about people
going through so much in their lives
with all the different diseases
conditions and illnesses and symptoms
neurological symptoms everything from
aches and pains to chronic fatigue to
neuro fatigue to to I mean whatever
people deal with eye problems ear
problems you know throat problems
thyroid problems hashimotos thyroiditis
and hyperthyroidism and diabetes and all
these other things that we all deal with
out there and that's just this tip of
the iceberg but when chronic illness
when people are suffering and struggling
we can't play around it has to be
straight out it can't be protecting the
interest groups of research and science
it can't be about that because that's
what that does in chronic illness it's
all only about an outcome that they want
to hand you to protect them it's never
to protect the people in chronic illness
it's never to Pro protect the people
ever this is the only show you'll ever
find that is not contaminated it doesn't
have any of that talk nature to it okay
it's pure it's untampered with it's
Advanced Clean source of information so
you know I said something on one of my
Facebook lives I I said um you know I
don't know if it was an Instagram live
or Facebook live but I said I can hand
you the go I can hand over the golden
ticket okay I can hand it over to you or
I can smack it out of my hand you can
take it or smack it out of my hand you
can smack it out of my hand I could take
a good beating and give me a slap
totally fine but you know but but take
the golden ticket and that's what I tell
everybody now because it really because
I'm trying to give you the information
when I was a young child and this
information was just Advanced even
though I didn't know what the hell it
meant I had no clue what it meant 8 n 10
years old excuse me 89 10 years old
getting handed
information about
vidigo then information about multiple
sclerosis then information about every
single ache and pain and every single
neurological twitching and all kinds of
different symptoms including emotional
psychological everything and getting the
information it was Advanced and it was
the same it was the same it was the same
information it was you know and that's
the and and and it's just Advanced right
now that's the whole point it wasn't
like oh okay Each decade went by and I
took information from some book gleaned
information from some Source never all
the medical medium
information it all starts from the
original Source right here it starts
from original Source from the books from
me all the way going back to Childhood
and it always has and it's been passed
around a lot of it's been passed around
and it's it's it's over the years and
it's come back full circle to me where I
where where it was started to begin with
I'm saying all this because with chronic
illness it has to be something above it
has to be something bigger and above
what's out there now because it's not
working what's out there now I'm telling
you right now it's not there are so many
people sick so many people struggling
I'm talking about every digestive order
disorder there is every bloating
constipation um Burning uh you know
people's hands feel like they're on fire
I mean I've seen it all aches and pains
all over the body um skin rashes eczema
stasis everything and people walk around
suffering migraines headaches sinus
infections chronic all the time lung
problems breathing problems nowhere do
they can get any help besides steroids
and immunosuppressive drugs you know new
inventions of immunosuppressive drugs so
you tell me is science and research on
the ball with chronic illness or they
got it all squared up they got it all
squared up huh just because you just
because you're convinced at how good
your car works right just because you're
convinced on how good GPS works just
because you're convinced on how good all
the technology works you think
everything else is sewed up just because
they could remove an appendix for
somebody and say their life which is
amazing but you they got it all sewed up
no they don't they don't and that's
what's that a Vitiligo we're talking
about I'm just covering a little bit one
of the greatest mistakes with vidigo is
and I'm just going to be straight up
about this is that it's said out there
in the industry and the alternative
industry believes this too see the
alternative industry Now isn't really
the alternative industry it's just a
conventional industry that's been kind
of kind of uh shook up a little bit kind
of a mixed bag of nuts it's not the
alternative industry of the old days I'm
just going to tell you right now and um
so and believe me I love the
conventional industry and I love the
alternative industry I love the people
that work in there it's not I'm not
talking about the people I'm not talking
about the people I'm talking about the
hierarchy of these these these um these
these industries yes there's a hierarchy
to these industries sorry to say it but
it's the truth so okay so here's the
deal so um one of the greatest greatest
mistakes with Vitiligo is the immune
system attacking itself and the
alternative industry adopted that so if
you're walking around if you just got a
diagnosis with
viigo if you just got a diagnosis with
viigo and you you know you walked into
the doctor's office you came out of the
doctor's office and it's just like well
yeah and I just got a diagnosis that my
body's attacking itself it's destroying
something it's destroying something so
Vitiligo is the whole thing with it is
okay it's autoimmune that's what you get
told it's
autoimmune it's the belief that your own
immune system is attacking its cells
destroying
melanocytes destroying melanin so the
producer of melanin so this the pigment
the pigment that makes the skin color so
the cells are dying and they're dying
because your immune system is destroying
it so when you start getting the white
patches or the white blotches or you
start getting you can get all kinds of
it can hit you in all kinds of different
places with viig go but the thing is is
with this understand that um that when
we get told their body's attacking
itself when we get told their immune
system is destroying our pigment
producing
cells that's one great mistake we just
started off with one unbelievable great
mistake we just started off with and
what happens is that mistake is concrete
meaning it stays cemented it's
grandfather law in it's grandfather in
and I know I've talked about autoimmune
with you guys so many times I'm not
trying to bore you I'm not trying to
throw you I promise I'm not trying to do
anything like that I just have to tell
you because when it comes down to viigo
you walk out of the doctor's office just
like you do when you have Hashimoto
thyroiditis you walk out of the doctor's
office and you're told you have you
you're told you have a a problem with
your thyroid you're imune your own
immune system is destroying your thyroid
tissue causing hashimi thyroiditis you
know meaning causing thyroiditis
swelling of the thyroid it's the same
thing you walk out of the doctor's
office with anything now it's your body
attacking itself you walk out of the B
the doctor's office now with
fibromyalgia diagnosis oh that's
overactive nerves because your immune
system is is inflaming your nerves it's
just it's
unbelievable and oh it's genes by the
way everything's genetic genetic genetic
now throw everybody off the path throw
everybody off the course it's
unbelievable what's going on out there
and you know spirit and I were the first
were the first to bring to the world
decades ago bring to the world a long
time ago that Epstein bar is
responsible for Ms it's responsible for
fibromyalgia it's responsible for
Hashimoto thyroiditis it's responsible
and you know what happened the movement
got so big you guys have spread the word
the books got out there the information
got out there and it shook up the
industry you know what the industry did
they put out a bogus study saying hey we
now know that Epstein bar is linked is
linked to so check this out linked to
multiple sorosis fibromyalgia tashimo th
we know it's linked it's a trick what
that is is they're getting you to
they're baiting you and then they tell
you that it's not the cause though it's
not the cause epine bar is the cause of
all these different elses and they tell
you it's not the cause they just tell
you no it's your genes that are the
cause and it's autoimmune still it just
so happens Epstein bar might be a
trigger it might be linked no Epstein
bar is a cause this is this is done
purposely so you get tricked so when you
see these new articles out now those are
actually traps set because of what we've
done so far I know everybody's been
excited in the groups saw on the
Facebook groups and everything else that
you know that the that there were some
articles out there and it was like whoa
hey science just discovered that epsteen
bar is responsible for this and this and
that everybody was cheering and I don't
blame them but no it's it's not respond
they they were saying it's link to or
it's it's it's there's an affiliation no
no that's not good enough because you'll
you'll read through there and you'll see
where they set the Trap they're trying
to say don't don't believe the truth the
truth got out there so stop believing
the truth and then believe us cuz we're
taking you down now the path of its
genes and autoimmune still this is how
it's done it's done and so it's really
really demented actually demented it's
it's it's sick because it's not about
healing people it's not about healing
anyone and even in the industrial I mean
the the alternative medicine now it's
all about infomercials and selling and
selling and selling and selling things
to make hundred million companies and
Empires and me meanwhile no one wants to
put out the truth no one wants to put
out the free information and the truth
we do that at Medical meeting for a
reason we put that out there so Vitiligo
so so I'm talking about all this because
because it's not that I'm trying to
throw you off course yet I'm going to go
right into it we got a whole 45 minutes
left here it it's just that the
autoimmune diagnosis of Vigo is is is
disgusting because it's it's so it's
it's negligence it's negligence in its
highest highest fashion and its highest
order it's
negligence by by E that even being there
it's an instant instant cancellation of
a person's ability to heal sure they
might get get to a doctor that's throws
a few fancy supplements in them and gets
them on a better diet and sometimes some
people improve and sometimes people get
worse but the point is it's an
instant stop you from healing just that
diagnosis alone it's your body's own
immune system attacking and destroying
melanocytes attacking and destroying
this the cells that produce melon in
your pigment the T Ing and destroying
that alone that alone and and they say
okay well you know maybe stress is
triggering it maybe something else is
that alone but your body is still
attacking itself is an instant we don't
want you to heal that's what it is it's
an instant industry rule that says we
don't want you to heal from Vitiligo and
we don't want you to know the truth and
never know the truth of viigo we never
want you to know the truth ever ever
ever ever ever ever ever ever I'm
serious I'm serious about that I'm
serious and that's what that is so we
have to break that I'm pretty intense
today I know I know pretty intense I I
don't sound like I have a lot of humor
in in this today for some reason meaning
like I'd like to keep lighthearted I
like to have a little bit of humor in in
there because we can heal and the humor
is basically based on the Ridiculousness
of the industries and and and how they
take advantage of people and I try to
keep lighthearted about this but today I
I can't do it you know because I've just
recently even talked to somebody a
friend of mine a friend of mine um you
know their their their child is vialo
and they and they just went to the
doctor they came back to the doctor and
the friend said my friend said look the
doctor said you know it's autoimmune
there's nothing we can do um and you
know and and what can we do and they
said Anthony what can we do what can we
do I said well I'm about to do a show on
it so you can you'll you'll find out
what we need to do during the show and
and we'll get some and you know you'll
have some clarity on the whole thing
it's unbelievable how it works so here's
the deal you know there there's
something there's something out there
that says okay well you you know
Vitiligo can be triggered by exposure to
Industrial chemicals that's the closest
they've ever been to something real
something real it's the closest they've
ever been to Something Real so what this
means is if the industries science and
research has a theory that the exposure
to Industrial
chemicals possibly could trigger
vidigo then I mean hats off hats off to
him hats off to him a little bit I mean
maybe a half hat maybe a half hat right
um so because because there there's
something I'm going to cover what that
means they're saying exposure to the
outside so they're saying exposure so
say you work in a factory say you work
somewhere and you're exposed to
chemicals industrial chemicals and they
noticed wait a minute someone gets F
light and they don't know what it could
be maybe it's the chemicals being
exposed on the skin maybe it's chemicals
being exposed in some way it's really
not
clear but what's happening is is there
re there is industrial chemicals in
everybody who has Vitiligo there is
industrial chemicals industrial toxins
deep within the body since birth or
after birth or during childhood and
these industrial chemicals you guys
these industrial
chemicals are they
are part of why we have Vigo so but but
the but but but the medical industry and
science research they don't know that
part they're thinking it's like an
exposure to maybe the outside of the
body they're thinking like it's an
exposure I mean hats off they're even
thinking that but we're talking about
the real we're talking about the truth
we're talking about the real stuff we
don't play around with the bull we don't
play around with people and their health
it's all about getting it right because
you has to be right it has to be right
we don't throw you guys a whole bunch of
crazy bogus cleanses out there in the
world and all the different books that
are out there now it's like they have
all these different programs and stuff
like that I mean we don't throw anything
like that out at you because you know a
a lot of those things are just not going
to be right they're not going to be
right they're not even going to have
celery juice in them in order to get you
better it's always got to be right when
we have to get somebody better when we
have to figure out what the truth is and
what we need to do so these industrial
chemicals they actually sit inside the
body of everybody deep down and then
that's just one part of it there's more
to it than that there's more to that so
it takes more than that it takes the
industrial chemicals whatever those
might be from the past toxic heavy metal
exposure passed on from generation to
generation to generation which may make
it look like it is genetic when it's not
genetic so toxic sotic heavy metals you
know um all the different metals that I
talk about all the time copper aluminum
Mercy you know lead just all the
different ones cadmium you know nickel
arsenic just lots of different metals
and then there's got to be something
else though there's got to be another
thing one other thing that has to happen
there has to be something called
oxidation the
metals need to be
oxidizing they need to be oxidizing
izing meaning to cause Vitiligo they
need to be oxidizing to cause
Vitiligo and when they
oxidize they they run you know what that
means is run it's not like somebody
jogging somebody
running what it means is the metals they
they corrode and when they corrode they
blow up the metals blow up that's what
they do that's what they do so the
metals actually blow up aluminum
is a big part of
Vitiligo aluminum that's a big one
that's a really big one for Vitiligo and
the aluminum has to sit inside the liver
it has to sit inside the liver and
that's what it does it sits in there and
then the aluminum interacts and reacts
with other metals well that's what the
aluminum does it interacts and reacts
with other
metals and then it blows up large
but it needs something to blow up large
with something to cause it and that's
fats high fat diets so high fat diets
are an instigator for
Vitiligo a lot of times when somebody
cleans up their diet they're still
eating high fat but they got rid of
other fats too they got rid of so many
fats in their diet that they didn't know
it but they threw away processed foods
that were filled with fat they threw
away other fatty foods and they changed
over their diet cleaned up their diet
whether an animal protein diet a you
know paleo diet a vegan diet a
plant-based diet a whatever kind of diet
there is out there you throw away the
process foods you end up blowing your
fat a little bit because you're probably
throwing away lots of different other
fatty sources along with the normal fats
that you eat every day like meat and
everything else and then so you start
and a lot of people with Vitiligo you
start seeing a little bit of a
difference not everybody but some people
start getting a little bit of a
difference going on that's because the
fats have reduced in their diet diet and
the fats get inside the liver and they
actually cause the reason why you want
to reduce these fats in your diet is
they get inside the liver and what they
do is they oxidize the metals quickly
they oxidize the aluminum quickly so
aluminum with the fat on it will then
oxidize it'll blow up it'll blow up what
does that mean blow up well cons you
know just like if you take a balloon
little rubber balloon you start blowing
into it and it starts to blow up with
air starts to fill up with air well the
the the luminum yeah little bits of
micro aluminum that's right little bits
of aluminum just like Nano
aluminum and when this aluminum gets
starts to oxidize it starts to expand
starts to expand and that's why the high
fat diets are so bad for Alzheimer's and
so bad for because any kind of metals
like mer Mercury inside the brain and
aluminum Mercury inside the brain and
you got and you got a high-fat diet
going on and that's why when people go
off their processed food diets and
they're saying hey I got somebody with
alzheimer's they're starting to come
around a little they're they weren't
that advanced to begin with but they
were they were you know they were they
were having problems they weren't you
know they weren't F they weren't
functioning right and they were and I
and and and I went to this doctor and he
put them on this special remove whatever
out of your diet and and whatever and
what he the doctor did was removed
without realizing it a lot of processed
foods with bad fats but then still kept
the diet a high fat diet because the
doctor could have done a lot better than
that if the doctor lowered the fats
altogether in the diet like we talk
about here and you know I mean then
forget it you can get somebody with
alzheimer's even backtrack even more to
to where they remember all a sudden a
relative's name or a sibling's name or
something and um or a loved one's name
and they remember and you can go even
further than that but nobody knows that
yet by the way you guys so so so the
deal is the deal is with Vitiligo is you
get this aluminum it's sitting inside
sitting inside the liver and aluminum is
is a
destructive destructive industrial Toxin
and how did you get aluminum inside your
liver what do you mean you just we pass
it on from generation to
generation how do you get how do you get
aluminum inside the uh liver I mean
medical practices there's there's
Medical Treatments that just are filled
with aluminum I mean everything
deodorant for you young adults using
lots of aluminum based deodorant I mean
aluminum in in toothpaste I mean just
loads of aluminum in everything aluminum
in the water
supply there's aluminum in everything I
mean it's just we're saturated in
aluminum just like where we got so much
mer pery going on but that aluminum
that's responsible for viigo so what do
would so you know where I'm going right
you you you guys know where I'm going
you know where I'm heading I hope hope
you know where I'm heading so that
that's what's going on with that
aluminum so that aluminum with along
with a really you know high-fat diet
which is basically standard American and
even and even healthy
American that that high fat those High
fats whether they're even healthy fats
too they
oxidize they oxidize that aluminum and
then something else has to happen I'm
telling you a story it's like a bedtime
story it's like a nice little bedtime
story I'm telling
you it's like a bedtime story I mean you
know or it's like a campfire a Scary
Campfire story you know so then there's
something else that has to be there
inside our liver it can't just be
aluminum and then the fats building up
inside the liver and then the oxidizing
of the aluminum the expansion of the
aluminum there has to be one other thing
you you know what it is it's a virus
it's a
virus and so the
virus has to be present really low grade
not even anything serious the
mildest low grade viral
condition yes Epstein bar is a big big
big one for this but other viruses can
do it too all the hh's all the HH v6s
and sevens and the hh10 and 11s you
epine bar is a common one that does it
and even the shingles inside the liver
can do this I mean it can there's a lot
of different herpetic viruses that can
sit inside the liver I mean there's so
many there's multitudes of them and so
when that virus and that Epstein bar
sitting inside the liver it
feeds it feeds off of the aluminum now
in the case of eimos soris it has to
feed off of
copper it has to feed off of copper to
give you the
eczema but in in when it comes down to
Vitiligo it has to feed off of the
aluminum runoff the aluminum expansion
the aluminum that's blowing up the
aluminum that's
oxidizing it has to feed off the
aluminum and it does it feeds off this
industrial toxin yes this industrial
Toxin and you know I mean
seriously
seriously and and what happens is that
when the virus feeds off the industrial
toxin aluminum the the runoff the
oxidative Alum aluminum it then goes the
bathroom it eats it which is something
else research and science doesn't even
know the viruses eat they eat to stay
alive they eat to reproduce they eat to
stay stay functioning they they fuel
they fuel themselves right through the
membrane of the virus they fuel
themselves and research and science
doesn't know that yet and if they do
know it they don't want you to know it
how about that okay if you think they're
that smart then let's give them benefit
of Doubt and say they do know it but how
come they won't tell anybody how come
they tell everybody that viruses don't
eat anything well then you know then
they're lying to you okay whatever
however you want to look at it they're
lying if they know or they're they're
stupid they don't know whatever you want
to do whatever whichever direction you
want to go so and you know so viruses
they feed off and then they release it
when they release a poison the poison
has to go to the skin it has to travel
and go to the skin aluminum oxidative
methyl aluminum being eliminated from a
virus creates a type of dermatoxin a
different kind of
dermatoxin that that inevitably can
affect yes affect pigment creating cells
so it can affect the melanocytes it can
affect the melanin it can affect it and
what happens is when that toxin surfaces
to those pigment cells there's a
reaction that happens that science and
research will never touch upon I mean
honestly not in my lifetime and I don't
even know if our in our children's
lifetime or their lifetime I just don't
know if they can go there it's just too
advanced it's pain it's
painful and so you know what happens is
that that dermatoxin it becomes a
dermatoxin it surfaces the areas of the
body different skin
areas and it explodes the cells there's
a reaction that occurs with a pigment to
oxidative aluminum that's been
eliminated out of a
virus that's been eliminated out of a
virus
and it's in a different
state and so it it it's it's in a
corruptive state and that poison
industrial poison and viruses are
industrial too yeah they are got to say
it they're industrial too many of them
not all of them but many many of them
are industrial and so this industrial
this all of this it's an industry thing
so that's why I said hats off to medical
research and science when they're like
exposure to Industrial chemicals which
they meant you're just working in a
factory and you've been sprayed by brake
cleaner carburetor cleaner you know some
kind of cleaning agent that's you know
just toxic no I'm not talking about and
what happens with those is those can
those have aluminum in it yes all that
could have aluminum in it but they don't
know that meaning they don't know that's
what's happening and that aluminum can
go into the liver so if you're somebody
exposed to a lot more toxic chemicals
than somebody else then you're getting
more aluminum and then more aluminum
goes inside the liver then more than it
can do what it's doing and oxid oxidize
and expand and everything I just said it
can
do and there's different varieties of
Vitiligo because there's different
situations it it all depends on where
the toxins traveling in someone someone
may exercise a lot someone may be active
it it can travel further it can go into
different places it could go to all
kinds of different areas it can go to
the eyes it can go to the it can go to
the ears it can go to the the lymphatic
system of often times it goes to the
face on a lot of people because it heads
up to the lymphatic system goes to the
knees because the lymphatic system can
you know it all depends on what they're
doing do they sit on the couch a lot do
they sit on the couch a lot with their
feet up and they watch TV you know like
like like I do too much of yeah no I
wish I had the time to do
that that's my dream that's my dream
okay is to actually take one day off
writing the books and actually watch
watch a funny show or something or watch
a funny movie maybe I'll be able to do
it 10 years from
now maybe people maybe people are
sitting on the couch a lot maybe they're
standing all day or maybe they're
working and standing all day maybe
they're sitting all day maybe people are
exercising more maybe people aren't
maybe people you everything is different
with someone also how their liver is
working how their liers functioning are
there other poisons and toxins and
different things and bugs and other
stuff inside their livers everything is
different to how it can develop like
where the dermatoxin can lie where the
dermatoxin can go and travel to what
joint to what part of the body to what
area to what lymphatic area to through
the bloodstream to what direction
because you remember the liver releases
all this stuff right out of the
bloodstream right up through the you
know Paddock portal vein right up to the
heart right up to it pumps through the
body and then it you know it finds its
way in all kinds of areas and lymphatic
system and every else and it travels and
travels and so you know it can give you
different situations with this now why
does stress play a role as a
trigger stress is a trigger isn't it
interesting whoa it's a it's a you know
and that's the thing that's what's funny
about research in science I hate being
that hard on Research in science because
I love science I absolutely love it
because how can I not love it what
spirit gives me is nothing but science
science that's undiscovered but nothing
but science how can I not love
science so you know yeah okay there's
bogus science out there in the world
yeah and it's the thumbs on the scale
like I said so but the point is I still
love the fact that there's science and
there's good science too I mean there's
fantastic stuff out there too it's
amazing achievements going on out there
it's incredible but the bottom line is
the bottom line is is this is that you
know science comes up with oh well
stress can trigger
viigo okay yeah well why and how is that
50 years from now we learn or is that 80
years from now we learn no learn this
now learn it now okay I and I've been
talking about this for years going back
and back and back I love when someone
says says to me oh you've been you're
the medical meeting what when did you
start three years ago or something oh
three years ago oh how about when I was
three years old well it's four years old
but you know what I mean it's four years
old is when it started but I just you
know I'm just saying if someone says how
when did you start 5 years ago I'd be
like yeah how about 5 years
old you know how about when I was a
child is what I mean and so you know the
bottom line is with stress is stress is
a trigger for a couple of reasons
because what stress does is stress
weakens the immune system and then
allows a virus to actually Thrive a
little better remember I said you have
to have a virus inside the liver too so
people with Vitiligo have to have a
little bit of Epstein bar sitting inside
the liver also they have to have the
aluminum and it aluminum has to be also
oxidizing from a high fat diet
throughout the years years
before and so what happens is the stress
the stress lowers the immune system a
little bit which gives the Epstein B
virus a little bit more of a kick it
could it actually fuel itself eat a
little bit more now how does it fuel
itself because of adrenaline too you're
under a lot of stress you're under a lot
of adrenaline adrenaline feeds viruses I
talk about that in medical medium book
one you know adrenaline feeds
viruses and when adrenaline feeds
viruses then viruses fuel up they get
stronger um and so therefore you have
the stress trigger right there you see
how it
works so it's a really important to
understand and um because because we're
going to be under stress but we can do
something about it look I'm under stress
I'm under stress I'm always under stress
and um I'm sure I'm sure a lot of you
guys are too I'm sure a lot of you guys
are too I mean I mean it's easy to be
under that it's easy to be under that so
stress is a big trigger but but just
saying stress is a trigger is is an
insult what about the answers to why it
is you know and that's how you win you
win when you have the answers you win
when you have the truth you win when you
know what to do what can we do now what
can we do well we certainly can't lower
our stress really I mean we can try to
we can take care of ourselves the best
we can we can try to lower our stress we
can try to take care of ourselves in
different ways sure there's ways of
lowering stress I mean in medical medium
book one I did all the healing
meditations in there and you know
there's there's lots of ways to cope and
deal with our stress and really
help but even with that being said the
crap's still going to hit the fan
somewhere it always does I mean you know
there you always still have to die out
fires and I talk about that all the time
there's always fires to die
out and that's how life is so we can't
control that we can't have this full
control over that so what do we do one
of the things we do is we a we get the
aluminum out of our liver to get rid of
Vitiligo we do that by eating better we
do that by eating a little bit of a
lower fat diet whatever aisle you sit on
whatever that is and I you know and I'm
not into the propaganda thing just
everybody's throwing propaganda at
themselves at each other out there I'm
not into that I'm not into like in naleo
picking on the vegans like they do and
the plant-based people which I think is
totally unfair because the plant-based
people it's very small it's it's just a
very small crew in the country it's
really small when you think about it and
then you know and then the mediating
World um why are the hospitals filled
and filled filled with sick people and
oh my God dentist offices are filled
with rotting teeth I mean drilling root
canal root canals pulling teeth implants
dentures and they're not all vegans I
mean the vegans are really small so it's
unfair when the paleos do that and then
the vegans pick on the Paleo people and
they pick on the uh and they pick on the
meat eaters which is you know which is
unfair too which is unfair too because
then they throw at them you know all
kinds of stuff they throw out all kinds
of stuff at them and you know like I get
it but it's like they they're both
attacking each other and it's it's kind
of
unfair because no one's using no one has
the truth in their hand it's all like
they're throwing theories or bogus paid
science and studies to try to out
science themselves everybody's so upset
they're all out sciencing themselves
with bogus science with science it's
actually just crazy and it's just and
they're just you know no we got higher
protein no we got higher protein we got
better this no we got better that and
it's just this battle out there
meanwhile people are just staying
sick because they don't know what to do
and so what I'm saying is whether you're
vegan or plant-based or whether you're
paleo whether you're you're immediate or
it doesn't matter to me what matters to
me is you lower your
fats you lower them down you lower them
your down you lower them down with viigo
so what I'm trying to tell you is if
you're you're a happy meat eater and you
got
Vitiligo cut the meats down to once a
day not twice a day cut it down once a
day maybe even once every other day you
know throw an avocado in there whatever
you want to do throw some other things
throw an avocado in there throw throw a
little bit of plant fat to offset it the
plant Fat's a little easier in the
system I'm just saying when you're sick
with something and you have a liver
problem like Vitiligo which is really a
liver problem in the end yes you want to
do that you want to lower your fats and
if you're plant-based cut the nuts out
cut the nuts out kill the nuts
altogether I mean I love nuts and
they're they're healthy they believe me
they're healthy for people but if you
got
Vitiligo kill the nuts drop the nuts
back watch the cash used drop them back
a little bit you know Watch the watch
the walnuts drop them back a little bit
watch the sunflower seats drop them back
a little bit yeah maybe bring some more
hemp seeds instead they're a little bit
healthier you know and so so the point
is is that we just got to lower the fats
a little bit drop the oils both sides
both sides drop the oils bring them
down and then and then you because
everybody's now gluten-free for the most
Parts everybody's glut gluten- free
they're wheat free they're gluten free
most people are getting grainfree I mean
you could still have quenan get rid of
vtil you know Vio you can still do that
get rid of Vio you can you can get
quinoa you can get you know you can have
Millet you can have you can even have
some black beans in there and still get
get get rid of viigo you can still do
that you can still do that but just
lower the fats because that's another
thing too if you believe in oatmeal you
can still get rid of Vitiligo because
oatmeal essentially it's not it's not
going to cause that much harm at all I
mean it's it's actually I've seen it
help people I've seen it help a lot of
people doesn't hurt a lot of people I've
seen it help people I've seen people
heal from Vitiligo and still have
oatmeal so it's there's this big war out
there it's like no grains Everything is
grainfree Everything no grain and high
fat high protein high fat high protein
and you know who suffers in the end from
all that
misinformation the person with Vitiligo
the person with Hashimoto thyroid is the
person with you know all kinds of
different
things you know whatever whatever I mean
there's so many different illnesses I
mean I could bore you with the list it's
just the list can go on but the bottom
line is if you bring down those fats a
little bit guess what's going to happen
you're not going to oxidize the aluminum
you're not going to oxidize the
aluminum the aluminum inside your liver
if you have this condition if you have
this condition you're not going to
oxidize the aluminum
and therefore that Viral issue you have
inside the liver that's feeding off of
the oxidized aluminum and feeding off of
that crusted aluminum in there that's
expanding from oxidizing from the high
fats if the virus isn't able the feed
off of all the oxidation you just won
the battle right there by lowering your
fats in your diet and I don't care what
trend I don't care what expert goes on
some show where there's a TV show that's
common where a bunch of doctors I don't
care who's on what
they still don't know about these
chronic illnesses I know that for a fact
that they don't know about these chronic
illnesses and what's really behind them
instead it's just all about eating in a
trendy way that somebody believes in
that some guy believes in that doesn't
understand women's health is completely
different and some guy who goes to the
gym who never really had anything wrong
with them as nice and fit and exercises
every day doesn't know what it's like to
have an illness or a condition like
millions and millions of women out there
and men too but then all of a sudden
it's like a spokesperson for some trendy
diet so an Empire can be built that's
demented it's deranged actually I'm
talking about what about the answers to
getting people better what about that
what about the information to turn their
lives around so what's the first thing
we need to
do first thing we need to do I said is
we got to lower the fats no matter what
aisle you sit on you got to lower the
fats I'm not anti-animal protein I'm not
anti- plant-based I'm not
anti-vegetarian you just I well
you can't do eggs you can't do eggs in
dairy products and yes of course nobody
should be on gluten but you can't do
eggs and dairy products I don't care
what kind of dairy product you like if
you got a condition you can't be doing
it you're just going to feed viruses and
feed the Epstein bars to create these
conditions and everything else and you
can't do it you got to keep those out
you know I'm I'm tired of seeing
egg is the perfect food out there cuz I
know it's just going to create more PCOS
in women more cysts more tumors more
cancers more breast cancers from Epstein
bar more conditions more multiple
sclerosis more fibromyalgia more Lyme
disease more whatever it's going to keep
on creating conditions and you know
what's tricky you get tricked because
you get a semi-healthy person like say
somebody who's 29 years old or a woman
that's 29 years old and and they're
eating their eggs they're promoting it
all online and they're all like eggs
eggs eggs and they don't you know and
you just don't understand that you can't
equate that to what can happen 15 years
down the road when they're sitting there
getting like hysterectomies and when
they're sitting there getting all kinds
of problems because those eggs literally
caused the worst fibroids down the road
15 years down the road so it's a
misconception same with men you know
with the eggs and everything meanwhile
when they end up getting prostate cancer
when they're 58 years old and yeah it
was all cute when they were 28 and
saying they eat their two eggs a day
they're on this new protocol and whatnot
meanwhile the egg is feeding the epine
bar virus inside the prostate creating
prostate cancer they end up with
prostate cancer at at 58 it's all fun in
games and it's all deception and
deceiving and nobody really knows how it
works so keep away from the eggs so we
don't want to eat the eggs we don't want
to do that don't want to feed the
viruses that create Vitiligo the other
thing is we want to remove the toxic
heavy metals out of our liver that's the
other people that's so critical and
that's that's the key removing the
aluminum and the aluminum runoff the
aluminum oxidation so we lower the fats
we lower the fats we get rid of
instigators that feed viruses so there's
a few steps you have to do and you can
do one of these steps and get
improvements with Vitiligo you can you
can reverse that condition you can
literally reverse that condition there's
ways of doing it and being free so what
happens is you lower the fats in the
diet like I said that alone stops the
ability or slows down the ability to
oxidize the aluminum then you remove
foods like the eggs and the dairy
products and the gluten that feed
Epstein bar virus or other viruses so so
that they don't keep on proliferating
and growing stronger and then feeding
off of the aluminum so that's another
step that's another step third step now
you're now it's about removing the
alumin itself and if you can only do
that step hey I'm fine I'm totally fine
and you know the thing is with the
celery juice the celery juice movement
that Spirit started and that you guys
you know you guys took off on I mean
honestly because you guys are Champs and
did the celery juice and changing your
your life and other people's lives it's
unbelievable the celery juice the celery
juice alone is helping people with
Vitiligo I hear about it all the time
you do because the celery juice the the
the cluster salt sodium salts that I
talked about in Facebook Faceook live
and I talk about it go check out the
Facebook live someday too that I did on
on celery it it you know it the celery
sodium celery salts what what it does is
it dissolves the membrane on the viruses
like the like the surface membrane and
it starts to destroy the epine bar virus
that's why celery juice is so critical
for Vitiligo and critical for every
disease illness condition and symptom
celery juice everything across the board
it's good for so you got that going
going on okay but the heavy metal detox
smoothie the heavy metal detox smoothie
spirulina the barley grass juice powder
okay the spirulina the barley grass
juice powder don't get confused I saw
somebody get barley grass powder no no
no no barleygrass juice powder so you
know and then you get spiruline the
barley grass juice powder you got the
you got that and I like vimergy I like
vimergy for those and then you got like
and then you you know you got the the
cilantro in there you got the wild
blueberries you know the whole deal you
know the drill a little bit of dols
these in the combination can get into
the liver the heavy metal detox smoothie
into the liver bind onto aluminum runoff
bind on to aluminum and start bringing
it out so if you do these steps you do
the heavy metal detox smoothie you do
the celery juice you take eggs and dairy
and gluten out of the diet and that's
the thing there's people that get a
little better with Vitiligo and other
things because they took gluten out but
yet here's the here's the irony I mean
here's what's unbelievable yet the
practitioner or the program that it was
in or the cleanse it was in or the
doctor that that was talking about it or
whatever was on television or whatever
whoever was talking about the gluten
doesn't even know the gluten was feeding
the
virus that was behind any illness or
condition the person was suffering
from and so you take out the eggs the
gluten the you know the you take out the
milk the cheese the butter but you take
all of it I don't care if it's grass-fed
butter you get rid of it because it's
going to feed a viral condition keep the
Vitiligo around but you take those out
then you lower your fats a little bit so
if you like animal proteins bring them
down a notch if you got a really bad
case of Vitiligo bring them down more
every other day every other day you do
it and then you know you do other things
other
days and that's that's how you do it
that's the power of it that's the power
of the foods and the different that's
what's in your hand so I can hand you
the golden t like I said which are these
things which can totally turn around
Vitiligo or you know or you can smack it
out of my hand whatever whatever
whatever and um so here's the deal okay
if it's overwhelming if this is too much
and you just these things are too much
alone like you might be saying well what
do I eat how do I eat what do I do how
do I do it you know the medical medium
the 28 day um eating with the 28-day
eating cleanse and medical medium that's
a good way of actually really jumping
ahead so whether you're a meat eater or
you're plant-based you do this for a
month and you jump ahead another thing
too is a thyroid the 90-day thyroid you
know healing and and um and thyroid
healing the the 90 days where you just
work on your thyroid where you got three
months and you work in there you can
pick a month any month in there can help
with figgo it can help with the liver it
can help with all of it but keeping your
fats low bringing in more fruits and
vegetables don't be don't don't have
fruit fear if you have fruit fear then
you're going to have a difficult time
healing and and and reversing thego
you're going to have a more difficult
time so you want to make sure that
you're not afraid of fruits you're not
afraid of more apples you're not afraid
of a few grapes you're not afraid of
some banana you're not afraid of these
things these things are really important
to reversing this condition and salads
and leafy greens so you know all the
different leafy greens spinach mosh you
know even leafy herbs little parsley
little cilantro all these things matter
lots of butter lettuces red leaf lettuce
green leaf lettuce green leaf kale
Dinosaur Kale just a little bit in some
of your food wherever you can that's a
really an incredible weapon tomatoes are
amazing the the the man it's so I'm you
know the thing is with tomatoes is I get
really kind of emotional about it for a
second because they're under attack
right now once again the very thing it
took years to get people back on to
tomatoes to it took it took me years to
get them using Tomatoes they don't get
certain cancers so they actually don't
get problems with their eyes so they
don't get glaucoma so they don't get eye
eye degeneration so they don't get all
kinds of different conditions and
problems and and so tomatoes are really
helpful bring in tomatoes lots of
cucumbers bring in those you can bring
in some avocado bring in a few nuts and
seeds don't overdo them and you can
bring in all the different vegetables
broccoli cauliflower flour you can bring
in all the different things but the more
fruits and vegetables you bring in you
you actually help heal yourself from
vitil Lago you really do and potatoes
that's a secret weapon for Vitiligo too
sweet potatoes butternut squash bring
those in I like butternut squash sweet
potatoes and potatoes I like all three
and you can switch off you can have them
for dinner you can have them with salads
you can have them you can switch off but
those are really important for
viigo and supplement wise on hly I I
wouldn't even you know with the
supplements you can do a few different
supplements that that are that are
partially helpful you could do a little
bit of MSM so you can do a little bit of
MSM you can do a little bit of ala you
can do you know alphal opic acid you can
do a little bit you could do the B12 you
could do the
5mthf you can do the methyl folate you
can do a few different supplements but
I'm telling you with vido it's about
making sure your diet gets cleaner and
making sure you get the heavy metal
detox smoothie going and you make sure
you get rid of that
aluminum that's the key I don't want to
throw you on a whole you know truckload
of supplements here when really you want
the aluminum out of the liver that's
what you want and that's the key for
this and you want the viral load down
and you know one way to get the Epstein
bar viral down is the LI scene for sure
you know you know the drill you know if
you go to thyroid healing you'll see all
the different you see all the different
supplements like our weapons against
Epstein bar same thing with book one
medical medium and you know you do want
you know you do want to knock down the
viral load but by not feeding the virus
gluten dairy and eggs you're already
winning you're already winning you're
already getting yourself in a better
place to not feed the virus I mean these
things are that important that important
a little bit of licorice can help with
Figo so licorice little bit of olive
leaf lemon bomb I can't thank lemon bomb
enough for what it does I can't thank it
enough enough it's that powerful bring
in a little lemon bomb knock down your
viral load that can help but I want the
aluminum out I want the aluminum out of
the liver and you know by doing that is
getting your diet better bringing in
more fresh fruits and vegetables
lowering the fats no matter what side of
the aisle down you're you're on lowering
their fat blowing your fats so that's
the whole story with Vitiligo um I love
you guys it's an honor to be here with
you I can't even believe another day
another radio show I'm so happy I'm so
proud of everybody bless your hearts
bless all of you seriously and keep a
lie heart have compassion for yourself
pat yourself in the back I love you
dearly talk to you soon see you on the
next show
bye-bye