[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found any anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now as
I've always said who has 10 years or 20
years to wait for answers to their
chronic illnesses to why they have
rashes to why they have aches and pains
to why they have migraines to why
they're constipated to why to why
they're they got all kinds of problems
why their knees hurt why they have edema
why they have swelling why they have hot
flashes why they have hair loss eye
problems floaters in the eyes tingles
and numbness you know everything I said
aches and pains and then all kinds of
other stuff neuralgia tingles and
burning pain and prickly pain to oh my
God back pain neck pain it goes on
shoulder pain
btis everything under the sun and we
talk about on this radio show you name
it it's here because we don't have 10
years to wait for answers for any of
this stuff we could keep on going I mean
there's fibromyalgia there's chronic
fatigue syndrome there's Hashimoto
thyroiditis there's everything and you
name it and we got it here we got it
here hopefully everybody out there you
guys hopefully you're not dealing with
all of this and I know a lot of you do
suffer and I know a lot of you do have
all kinds of different conditions and
were diagnosed with different kinds of
diagnoses and then ended up at the lime
doctor then out of the lime doctor to
somewhere else I know you guys been
through it all and um the bottom line is
I stand behind you I believe in you and
I'm so sorry you had to deal with any of
this let's heal together let's move
forward let's get the right information
let's get what we need and so today
we're talking about the healing power of
vegetables the healing power of
vegetables we always hear about
vegetables we always hear about eating
our vegetables we always hear about how
important they are we always think about
them consciously whether or not we eat
enough of them or not so today we're
covering the in the ins and outs about
them the power of them you name it I'm
pulling some of the information straight
out of my lifechanging Foods book um the
one I'm so excited for you guys to to
get in your hands uh soon and open up
and just you'll you'll be in shock it's
really cool Spirit gave me tremendous
amounts of
information that I put in this massive
catalog this massive cat so this is this
is going to be really exciting so and
I'm pulling some of that out for today
today because I want to talk about the
power of these vegetables and what they
have to offer um think about the LA
event if you're going or not um tickets
are selling so think about it we're
doing the light blast ever since I was a
child Spirit offered that opportunity
for me to give to people because I saw
so much suffering all the time non-stop
no matter where I went no matter what I
did and um the gift that I received at
age 4 to diagnose my grandmother came
with uh a lot of hardship and I know
some of you guys know that about me if
you just logged on and this is brand new
the medical Medium show is brand new to
you and this is your first show this
this will kind of fill you in a little
bit about it I diagnosed my grandmother
at age 4 uh by hearing a voice perfectly
clear as if someone was talking to me in
my ear so it's on the
outside of the body I'm not channeling
and it's not intuition although I have
tremendous respect for intuitives
because they have to work so darn hard
on mastering their intuition I know that
that the audience that that's listening
to right now all you guys are intuitive
too and everything else but it wasn't
intuition it was actually hearing a
voice perfectly clear in real time just
like you're hearing me right now with
your own ear and it came with a lot of
pain a lot of suffering in its own right
and um and a lot of Agony and I was able
to get through my teenage years without
basically ending my life because of the
severity of how difficult it was to live
in the world today and hearing a voice
24 seven telling me what's going on with
every aspect of someone's health and um
and so but with that I saw a lot of
suffering non-stop like I always have
and um and and I do you know the
readings come through no matter what at
all times it makes me go partially blind
I know that many of you who have read
the book you've you've you've heard seen
that it's like a snow blindness I call
it and um and so what happened though is
I asked Spirit at the young age I said
what else can I do for people first of
all there weren't a lot of resources
back then I'm not trying to date myself
and and and everything but but if we go
all the way back down to that that place
in time uh you couldn't get anything I
mean you basically there are a few
fruits and vegetables at best in the
grocery store depending on where you
lived in the country not everybody lived
in California in the in in in Los
Angeles where there was the first health
food store in the United States you know
we you know not everybody had that
opportunity okay so you know and and
because of that resources were low there
weren't a lot of uh supplements that
were discovered or or uh or or what is
it created by Geniuses that we have
today in alternative medicine and um and
there there wasn't a lot of that going
in fact there was virtually none of that
going on and so I would ask Spirit what
else can I do to ignite the healing
process and spirit said we're going to
do the light blast on each person if you
want and at that time you know I asked
for that help and spirit sent the light
down on the person that I would ask for
the light to hit and run right through
the body unlock
blockages completely change their
chemistry on all levels and give them
that ignition we do that at the events
it drains the heck out of me but that's
okay doesn't matter if my my um my
assistants have to actually scrape me
off the floor after we're done it
doesn't matter because guess what it's
so miraculous and what has happened from
these light blasts has just been so
great um just in the last event alone
over 600 people reported experiencing a
benefit to their health in one way or
another so um anyway the bottom line is
that's how it all happened that's what's
happening go you know you can get to an
LA the LA event November 5th if you want
go to Medical medium.com check it out
I'd love to see you there before the
tickets get sold out um and you know see
it it's basically like this when it
comes down to Healing there's different
levels of of healing in the sense where
we need different things so we need
different things and the life-changing
Foods book you know I made it clear in
that book about what we're looking at as
far as what is hindering us all you know
I'm releasing the truth about what's in
our way because no one wants to hear it
not you guys you guys want to hear it
you guys want to know the truth you guys
want to know how to protect your
children you guys want to know how to
protect your family you want to know how
to protect you know yourself and your
loved ones and your friends you know but
there's a lot of people out there that
just they don't want to know they don't
want to know like what's really holding
them back because it could be a little
scary in the life-changing Foods I talk
about the unforgiving for the
unforgiving for are these things out
there that you need to be aware of and
look out for so you can protect yourself
because you want that insurance you want
that knowing that knowing that
information and that knowing and and so
that's that's what that's about so
there's a lot of things that's one thing
that we need that's one part of the
puzzle that we need to heal and then
there's other parts like what I call the
holy four holy four are the food groups
the food groups like The you know um the
vegetabl the fruits the vegetables herbs
and spices and wild foods and today
we're covering uh a part of that Holy
four we're covering uh the vegetables
part and you know and how I laid it out
in the book is if you if you look at
what's happening and look what the
vegetables can do and you line up your
illnesses there's there over 700
illnesses I have and conditions I have
in in this book and I and I link these
to what can help you get over these
things through these fruits and
vegetables it was a daunting
grueling task with Spirit but it had to
get done and so so we're going over
vegetables today today now you know the
when it comes down to vegetables and
stuff so you've heard it since you were
young right eat your vegetables and hey
not everybody heard that when they were
young and you know it's not anybody's
fault there's some mommy and daddies
that they get so busy and they have so
much on their plate and so much dress
that they can barely just get a happy
meal for McDonald's and their children
and some chicken fingers out of the
freezer to survive and I have complete
and total respect for that you have to
understand that like um you know that's
a that's a that's a big deal just you
know making sure there's food on on the
table for your family as it is and
everything around it and children have
minds of their owns my minds of their
own okay they're the little people so
they have their own palet they have
their own tastes they have their own
likings and you know and a lot of times
um children don't like vegetables and
don't want to eat a vegetable and a lot
of times parents are so busy that you
know working working with coaching um
our children's really difficult
sometimes when we're trying to survive
we're trying to work we're trying to
make sure there's everything else in
place so we can protect our children so
we kind of you know the the food thing
gets put on the back burner a lot with
families and as long as there's food on
the table though that's all that matters
you know when I was growing up and that
was the the only thing that counted was
was there something to eat you know for
us kids was there something to eat on
that table regardless of what it was it
just we had to be eating something and
you know and and it makes a lot of sense
but you know but there's a lot of people
that talked to that I've talked to and
they're like yeah when I was younger I
was always told to eat my vegetables I
was always told you know you got to eat
them you know you're not and then i'
I've had people tell me you can't leave
the table until you eat your vegetables
you know when they were a child child
and their parents would say you know
you're not leaving the table there'd be
punishment you know you wouldn't be able
to leave the table you'd have to be sent
to your room like all kinds of things
I've heard from people because you know
vegetables are
important and so um you know our parents
have tried to get some of some
vegetables innocent in many of us in our
lives and and like I said before others
other other times it's just survival and
whatever we can get to eat but so but
vegetables have always been a role in
humanity and the future of humankind in
our survival in what we need to survive
here because they hold keys they hold
keys to the door the door of Health the
door of well-being the door of
lifegiving the door of
fertility and um by the way there's a
fertility chapter in life-changing Foods
that's going to knock your socks off
um
and information about fertility and
infertility you can't find anywhere and
I'm not just trying to say that in a
boasting way I'm just meaning it knocked
my socks off when I got the information
from Spirit I was blown away um but you
know all this vegetables play a role in
all of this you guys folks it plays a
big role in opening up the door to to
lifegiving to our future to where we're
going to what we're doing everything our
Consciousness everything about it it's
involved with a vegetable it's a big
piece of that and so it's one of these
holy four I call them holy four it's one
of these that's crucial and critical to
our well-being to our life to where
we're going to what we're doing just
like I said before and it it matter
matters that much to get them into us
and what's really important in the
vegetable department is leafy greens
which I'm going to cover a little bit
about what leafy greens do but leafy
greens are they're practically almost a
category of the Holy four on their own
even though they're in the vegetables
but they hold a lot of power and we tend
to forget about leafy greens a lot even
if we're um eating a really healthy
paleo diet we tend to forget about
eating a lot lot of leafy greens if
we're eating um you know a vegetarian
diet we forget about eating a lot of
leafy greens if we're eating a
plant-based or vegan diet which is
pretty much the same if we're if we're
you know we we forget about eating a lot
of leafy greens it's easy to forget or
to not get enough leafy greens in our
system no matter what diet you subscribe
to and you know I I don't care what diet
it is really I mean in a sense that
you're that you're into too if you're
really into a paleo diet um which is
basically now almost a vegan diet with
just a little bit of lean meat because
you know that's T we're learning to get
people better it's more vegetables
that's where we're going everybody's
going that direction it's more
vegetables and more fruit to get people
better by the way so but whatever it is
if you're on a you know paleo diet if
you're on a ketogenic diet if you're on
an Ain diet if you're on some branding
diet like that if you're on you know a
diet that has a branding name whatever
it is you know um you have to bring in
more leafy greens if you're on a
Mediterranean diet you're just eating
all this fish and if you're on a wild
game diet you're just eating all this
Wild game um someone was talking to me
the other day and said you know I I I
hunt my own game you know I I I hunt and
kill my own rabbits I um you know hunt
deer and stuff and and you know and uh
first of all yeah it's the healthiest
food you could possibly eat in theend
Animal Kingdom as far as in the animal
world if you're if you're into meat or
you're into you know you're into the
paleo diet then Wild game is by far you
know the healthiest for you but I said
to the person are you eating enough
greens and maybe even Wild Greens and
maybe even greens that are cousins to
Wild Greens that you could buy in the
store and they were like well no I
wasn't thinking about that I was
thinking about just protein protein
protein and I was thinking about just
getting the leanest leanest good fresh
you know leanest freshest meat I can get
and so I was just you know doing the
hunting the game thing and everything I
said you know what first of all you know
that sure that's one aspect like people
do grass-fed meat because it's
closer to that area grass-fed it's out
you know it's the free range it's you
know pasture raised you know the cows
are out there eating grass so if you're
into meat that's the kind of get there's
no doubt you don't want Factory you
don't want that g garbage Factory meat
that's just filled with you know GMO
corn and GMO soy and the conditions are
unbearable you want the grass-fed beef
you know we know that if you're into
meat same thing with chickens same thing
with turkeys you want it all free range
you want it cage free you want all of
that and hopefully even grass you know
free pasture raised and so uh the
chickens and the turkeys can eat little
bits of seeds and stuff that are
naturally in the wild and grass seeds
and everything else that they pluck out
of the ground and bugs and insects
because you want that wild attachment to
it but what about the greens the greens
have to be there no matter what you like
talking to other person are like I only
like fish it's say everything from the
ocean is what I like well I said you
better not be doing the tuna you better
not be doing the tuna no tuna for you
they're like well I love tuna I do you
know I go out and get sushi and I do the
tuna that's what the person will say to
you know said to me and I said well okay
you're okay sure you know you like you
like the tuna okay fine well you better
then be eating a lot of greens and
preferably herbal greens like
cantro and parsley to bind on to all
that excess Mercury you're leaving in
your intestinal tract colon in liver
from that tuna and like I never never
thought about that I don't really eat
many greens I'm worried about my protein
you know so it's everybody's worried
about protein protein protein and
they're not eating any greens do you
guys get what I'm going there do you see
what I'm saying do you see what I'm
saying you know what I mean because
where's the most powerful protein there
is on the planet that actually does do a
lot for the human body where does that
lie it lies in Greens it's in spinach
it's in kale it's in parsley you know
it's in it's in barley
grass I like the barley grass cheese pow
it's in that it's in all of that that's
where those those
microproteins they're simulatable they
absorb they break down they do things
they got amino acids attached to them
actively
bioactiv so you want those proteins I
tell people look okay sure you're
getting a lot of protein from fish I I I
okay I'm with you I'm not I'm not you
know fighting you on that but where's
your where's your bioidentical protein
you know and they're like what are you
talking about I go you know from the
greens from the greens and so you know
so so if you want to do fish make sure
you do a salad with that fish you want
to do tuna you better have that Tuna on
top of a big salad so if you guys like
tuna regardless of the Mercury I I'll
stand behind you but put it in a big
salad you know if you guys like
grass-fed beef because you guys are into
that kind of diet I stand behind you
let's get a with let's make sure we have
a nice salad of leafy greens going on
there you guys are into Wild game like I
run into you know a few people here and
there it's just everything is wild wild
turkey whatever they can find then you
know wild pheasants they order them they
ship them you ship them they ship Frozen
or something now you can get wild
pheasants then then yeah then where's
your greens though where's your
greens because that's what the pheasants
were eating Where's your green you've
got you know that has to be in the mix
the
bioidentical proteins that will actually
help the animal proteins work better for
you so the protein in the fish is going
to work better for you when you actually
have your greens the protein in the wild
turkey it's going to work for you when
you have your greens the protein in the
wild game or whatever the grassed beef
you name it it's going to work better
for you and then if you're a vegan or a
vegetarian I tell vegans and vegetarians
all the time you better eating a lot of
greens they better be there you can't
you can't not have them in there you
know I mean fruits are critical in our
life I don't care who's eating what diet
you got to get some fruit in there if
you want longevity because of
antioxidants you want your you don't
want your brain to rot and oxidize you
better be eating fruit it's not about a
belief system it's not about sugar no
sugar fruit's bad fruit's not bad no
it's about longevity it's about making
sure your butt makes it all the way to
the end and that's going to happen
antioxidants and fruits but
greens have mineral salts in them
mineral salts in them critical ones and
critical
proteins they do critical proteins and
mineral salts so I tell vegans and
vegetarians you better be eating your
leafy greens I want a spinach salad
going on I want a spinach smoothie throw
some tomatoes in a blender with one to
two bunches of
spinach okay or a container of spinach
shove it in that you know Vitamix or
whatever you like using throw in three
or four good siiz tomatoes one celery
stick it's a little handful of cilantro
one clove of
garlic and if you if you like garlic
okay if you like garlic a squeeze of an
orange get some orange juice squeezed
fresh from an orange in there and blend
it up grind that baby up and you got
yourself a living fresh spinach soup if
you're into living Foods if you're a
vegan if you're plant-based then that's
the that's what you need right there
that has to be in between everything
else you're
eating and if you're into animal
products then get that spinach salad
going now don't don't grill that spinach
don't Grill it don't throw it in a pot
and steam it up no no but have a spinach
salad if you want some grassed beef make
sure you're you you're doing enough
spinach
salad get the
greens so it's about making sure you're
getting something no matter what that
you're supposed to get that's helping
you no matter what diet you choose for
your health or what diet you've been
pushed into you know from you know uh
something out there some kind of pseudo
science telling you why you need to eat
a certain way or some kind of you know
prehistoric science that really is just
isn't just accurate so whatever it is
that's going on just make sure the
greens are in there bottom line you know
whether you're vegan whe whether you're
a Paleo whether you're whatever whether
you're what whatever brand you're doing
Mediterranean whether you're doing
Atkins whatever you're doing so the deal
is is make sure the greens are in there
so okay I'm glad we covered that we're
going to cover a lot of things now
there's something there's a big
confusion a big confusion out there
about the brain and we're going to do a
brain show that that is coming up but
there's a big confusion about the brain
and I I want to make sure we clear it up
here here we clear it up now because
it's important now if I say what's your
brain made out of what are you guys
going to say what are you guys going to
think all right so what's your brain
made out of what are you thinking you
thinking are you thinking what it's made
out
of my first my first thing to say would
be it's made out of brain but I'm just
being silly that's just to me always
being silly but what do you guys think
it's made out of well there's a lot of
transends and fads right now that have
pretty much telling us oh your brain is
made out of
fat not n not okay the brain's not made
out of fat it's not the brain's made out
of glycogen
storage glycogen storage okay that's
what it's made out of it's made out of
stored
carbohydrates
that's what it's made out
of it melts in your mouth if someone
eats
it it's
sweet and it's like basically a brown
rice pasta if you guys ever eaten a
brown rice pasta now I haven't eaten
brain but I'm telling you right now a
lot of people eat brains out there they
eat sheep's brains and lamb brains and
and all kinds of different animal brains
out there cow brains there's cowb brains
and supplements don't take those don't
take those supplements by the way don't
take any supplements with any animal
parts in them because it's always
questionable about where those animal
parts came from cuz supplement companies
have to Chin every penny and every dime
in order to survive and I just never
trust where sources lie um but the point
is is that people eat brain out there
they do all across the world in
different places I've heard from many
accounts many accounts even had a friend
that tried brain when they were
traveling and it was
sweet sweet is what it
was okay it was like not candy sweet
carbohydrate
sweet and science already knew this is
what I love about science science can be
twisted in every way in every angle in
any direction for any reason for
anybody's purpose at any time and that's
why spirit and I kind of back away from
science and spir I always say Spirit
trumps
science and because it's about results
and about truth and it's about truth and
it's not about propaganda and it's not
about interest groups spirit is above
that but the point is is that the brain
once was that was discovered it's
glycogen that was a correct Discovery
and then it flipped later on like like
just recently with fads and Trends where
we're now convinced that it's made out
of fat now it's not made out of fat
there are traces of Omega-3s plus traces
of other rare oils in the
brain rare rare oils and fats traces
only and those traces come from hemp
seeds walnuts they come from butterleaf
lettuce they come from Black
berries they come from wild blueberries
traces of Mega 3s in them and other rare
omegas I'm I'm not just even talking
about three sixes and nines I'm talking
about rare not even identified yet
groups of omegas not
nonidentified that's what's cool about
the life-changing Foods book is I just
love going into the stuff by the way um
so so basically that's in the brain but
it only accounts for a tiny percentage
of the brain the rest of it is
salt
salt okay salt and sugar sugar the
brain's made out of sugar but it's made
out of a carbohydrate polysaccharide is
made out of glycogen
glycogen a polysaccharide a a starch a
carbohydrate a
starch I'm just trying to get this point
across
because we need to know what the brain's
made out of because when you're dealing
with vegetables one of the Holy four
when you're dealing with vegetables you
got to know what you're dealing with and
you're dealing with precious vital
mineral
salts mineral salts for neurotransmitter
chemicals actually to create
neurotransmitter chemicals to be a
neurotransmitter chemicals and amino
acids precious life-giving amino acids
are in vegetables the ones that go to
the brain and charge up the electro the
the um charge up electrolytes charge up
electrical impulses fire up GLE cells so
this is serious stuff this is vegetables
so you know I was telling you like well
you got to eat your vegetables when
you're told as a child it's important to
eat your vegetables but why this is why
this is why because if you don't eat
your vegetables you won't have the
conductor the conductor for the brain
which is part of the electricity which
is all the precious vital mineral salts
and if you don't eat fruits or starchy
vegetables or vegetables that have
carbohydrates in them if you don't eat
those you won't have a glycogen storage
a glucose storage in the brain a sugar
storage in the
brain that gives you a brain because
your brain's made out of that I don't
care care what book comes around the
corner tomorrow I don't care what
concept I don't care what person expert
says oh no no the brain's made out of
fat you got to keep away from your sugar
you know what's going to happen your
brain is going to shrink your brain
shrinks and shrivels up without glycogen
which is carbohydrates which is out
glucose and then without the conductor
the mineral
salts that's a fact Jack that's a fact
Jack so when you're getting pushed
around in the diet world and the food
worlds you better be you know thinking
about these things because it's all
about watching your back it's all about
being on your side you know and it's not
about anything else it's not about
selling a
product it's not about selling a product
I don't have 50,000 products to sell you
because you know I'm telling you that
the brain's mad out of fat it's not that
at all it's about what's going to help
you your family your children your
grandchildren your grandparents your
parents it's just about we got to do
this together so let's talk about some
vegetables let's talk about it
vegetables provide these mineral salts
they provide these critical things that
actually give us life it gives us a
brain a brain is made out of literally
these mineral salts and then
carbohydrate that's what our brain is
made out of how do you like that how do
you like them
apples so let's go into some of these
because it's really important to go into
some of these um talk about the leafy
greens what can leafy greens do for us
what can they help they can totally help
acidosis right when our body systems
become so acidic that disease State
happens and occurs that means that any
viruses bacteria pathogens in you they
want to take over they got a better
opportunity to take over if you're if
you're really acidic if you're eating
you know just no vegetables and no fruit
you get really acidic so any kind of
heartburn it prevents heartburn it may
not fix it on the spot right when you
eat your first Leaf of lettuce but it's
going to help it in a long time not
occur okay iron deficiencies especially
do do by viruses like Epstein bar
creates the iron deficiencies out there
so you got lettu uses to help that you
know like lettu uses and leafy greens
could butter leaf lettuce Romain leaf
lettuce red leaf lettuce someone told me
recently they said I like red leaf
lettuce I said you know what I'm with
you let's do it let's do it just red
leaf lettuce just every day have some
red leaf lettuce and you know and and if
that's the one you like that's the one
you like I'm not a big Iceberg fan I'm
not a big iceberg lettuce fan okay I
remember being a kid when Spirit was
telling me in a grocery store you know I
I don't know you you guys might know the
story but you know I used to work in a
grocery store when I was 14 years old
and I was stocking shelves and um I just
needed something to do to take my mind
off of spirit and but of course Spirit
would actually you know tell every every
single Shopper that was there in the
store pushing their cart by Spirit would
tell me what was going on with their
health what they needed for food and
that's where I built up my first
clientele at age
14 and and and so um so I go around the
store even the owner of the store was a
client of mine the owner of the store it
was a big grocery store and um so and he
he became the client of mine because it
was inconceivable of how I would know he
had
gout you well because of spirit of
course anyway the the whole thing is the
whole thing is is that iceberg lettuce
was like the only thing on the Shelf
back then practically I'm serious it was
I mean depending where you were like I
said if you were in California that
would be an exception everywhere where
else in the United States it was iceberg
lettuce and and I hated it I hated it
cuz it was iceberg lettuce because
Spirit would say well there's not a lot
in here and it was conventional iceberg
lettuce and spirit would tell me there's
not a lot in here but spirit said to me
you wait you wait and see what happens
down the road all right so you want to
get your different Roma lettuce you know
red leaf lettuce green leaf uh um get
the masculine mix with all the different
little mixes they even have the you know
the riko they have all these different
things MH you name it get what you can
spinach any leafy greens you can they
help with mineral deficiencies Trace
mineral deficiencies swelling fluid
retention edema inflamed liver
everybody's liver is getting inflamed in
this day and age you need the leafy
greens food allergies starts to knock
down food allergies spasms and cramps
because of the mineral salts have traces
of magnesium that are even better than
magnesium supplements how do you like
that how do you like them bananas or how
do you like them leafy greens huh
instead of them apples all right helps
with weight gain because helps clean up
the liver any kind of menopause symptoms
premenstrual symp symptoms um PMS
hormonal imbalances lettu uses help
because they help clean up the liver
which is causing a lot of the problem
they help knock down Epstein bar which
is causing a lot of these symptoms in
women and being completely overlooked we
talk about that um stops calcifications
in the breast
there's so many calcifications in
women's breast it's there all the time
you know no matter where I go spirit's
telling me okay calcification in the
breast nodu on the thyroid calcification
on the kidney calcification in the lower
back calcification in the joints I mean
the calcifications are just out of
control um so you know this is all the
power of leafy greens leafy greens hold
great
power and it it's actually an incredible
incredible experience to bring these
into your life so there's something
there's something that I really love
another thing another vegetable
radishes radishes who's eating radishes
are you guys eating any radishes did you
know when you have your salad and you
have a SL slice of radish on top that
that radish is probably one of the most
powerful things on top of that salad I
mean even with all those leafy greens
around the radish is a medicine it's a
different kind of medicine it's like
having a pill that you think is you know
really valuable in the pharmaceutical
world that's a medicine it's like having
that pill sitting on top of your salad
you know um so anyway uh the radish is
even more powerful than that of course
so radishes are like a little miracle
the greens on top are practically a wild
food so when you shop for radishes the
farmers market right now or wherever you
go and farmers markets are loaded with
radishes right now at least North
America whatever they just load it with
radishes and you know grab radishes
where you got the greens attached where
you can chop up the greens throw them
into your salad and then you got the
leafy greens again but another powerful
one but then you chop up the radishes
you put those in your salads put radish
in your
guacamole um you know if you it whatever
whatever you can do chop up radishes
have a salad with your grass-fed beef um
whatever you want but you have to have
the radishes in there at this time of
year just just one bring in one what I
like about radish is an amazing cancer
preventor amazing for for a lot of
cancers radishes help with asthma people
with lung problems that's what I love
too pneumonia people who chronically get
pneumonia radishes are amazing for
they're amazing for like simplexes
simplex one Simplex 2 so you know the
herpes family um you know if you're
worried about uh any kind of skin
cancers make sure you get you because
there's skin cancer in your family or
some you're someone you know has it
you're worried just make sure you're
bringing radishes in I like radishes for
ALS ALS radishes do amazing job they do
powerful job really profound um way of
healing occurs for people with ALS you
know I put this because the spirit's
orders I put this one one guy on with
ALS put them on with ALS symptoms and
the whole bit we know that's a diagnosis
doctors still don't understand but he
was given the diagnosis of ALS and he
really had a severe neurological
condition and that's unknown to medical
research and medical science but Spirit
knew um he had to eat eight radishes
every single day eight radishes daily
and he improved
50% when the only other way he was going
was opposite and fast and he improved
50% he got out of his wheelchair because
of radishes
so so you know you just That's The Power
of radishes we got to keep that in mind
um you know symptoms if you have all
kinds of different symptoms if you have
high blood pressure radishes help with
the liver food sensitivities
inflammation you know random
inflammation that you know that we talk
about of what causes it but just
inflammation in general radishes tend to
be an anti-inflammatory like a medicine
like a pill like an anti-inflammatory
pill they they are like a medicine and
congestion cough dark circles under the
eyes because you get toxicity blood
toxicity radishes are amazing what I
like about
radishes is that they help
emotionally nobody knows this this is
this is info being pulled out of
life-changing Foods right now for you
guys and you know and and it's this this
book's packed with this this is just a a
fraction this isn't even a
.1% and um what I like about radishes is
the emotional support Spirit told me
about when failing is a word in your
life when when fail is a key word of how
you're feeling you know when we feel
like we're failures you know we wake up
I mean even I wake up once in a while if
I feel like I can't save the world and
all at once I wake up in the morning and
I want to kick myself in the butt and
and feel like I'm failing because I'm
only reaching so many when you know
that's another reason why I love you
guys cuz you're helping people so I feel
like the reach is getting bigger and
better because you're taking the
information further and helping others
wherever you can you family ones loved
ones and every that and that makes me
feel less of a failure so thank you um
but when failures that like in your
system when you're feeling that way in
life and you think that you know you
failed something or whatever just don't
fall into that it's a bad place to fall
into first of all it's not true we're
not failures second of all bring
radishes in and it changes the mindset
emotionally changes the mindset I'm I'm
telling you right
now precious vegetables kale broccoli
cauliflower the whole gang you know all
of them broccoli Rob um you know Collard
collared greens of course you know like
I was saying kale collared you know all
of it um is you know brussel sprouts
that's another one these are amazing
Foods incredible Foods so keep these in
your life and the conditions they help
is also there's a whole bunch of
varieties of conditions that they help
they help with acne with knocking down
strep that we talk about help with
diabetes they help with with Hashimoto
thyroiditis cruciferous vegetables
actually stop Hashimoto so don't fall
into that whole mistake that that trend
of goitrogenic being a problem if you're
new to my information and you just
logged on to this first time learn about
it read about it or listen to what I've
talked about before and um because don't
fall into that goitrogenic mistake
that's out there terrible because it's
not true um there's phytochemicals
undiscovered in these vegetables that
stop those cogenic properties from being
a problem and stop thyroid issues
because first of all you need to know
what's wrong with the thyroid to even
know how to treat it or how to to
address it and apparently medical
research and medical science both
alternatively and conventionally doesn't
know yet up until I brought it to the
table that Epstein bar causes Hashimoto
and to kill off Epstein bar you need
certain things cruciferous vegetables
one of them so you keep the kale in
there keep the collards in there you
keep all of that going on um I like the
emotional support of these vegetables
that's what I like they're really
amazing like like for instance okay if
you know if you know anybody that's
baffled all the time or bewildered or
befuddled or just you know confused if
you know somebody that's struggling with
that and you know you want them to get
the support they need just get them
eating more broccoli getting them eating
more cul flour because the mineral salts
in here not only support the brain but
they help an emotional part of the brain
so this is an emotional support
vegetable group that helps helps people
get out of that always seem like they're
confused always seem like they're
baffled always seem like they're
bewildered even if they're brilliant
people of course and they have this
going on you want these vegetables keep
that in mind um these vegetables are
also amazing for weight gain issues
where you you want the weight off um
hyperthyroid they're amazing for that
inflammation all through the body you
name it fatigue tingles and numbness
ringing buzzing in the ears you want
these vegetables let's go on to another
one
celery celery the miracle like the
heavens have opened up like Jesus is
coming down from the heavens like celery
is that
powerful and and it's one of the Holy
four that that I really admire fire and
so it's one of the Holy four it's one of
that group of the groups that I talk
about in life-changing Foods you guys
have seen it go to the Instagram page go
to go to the Instagram go to Facebook
see how many lives are changing from
celery juice 16 ounces of celery juice
because of the nature of the mineral
salts the nature of the blend which is
undiscovered by research and science
totally undiscovered food hasn't even
been tapped into you guys by on any
level by research and science any level
compared to what what's in it as far as
phytochemicals mineral salts Spirit
jumps ahead of all that cuz by the time
they tap into some of that it's 40 years
from now where you going to be in 40
years or 50 years okay I know where I'm
going to be in 50 years you know so and
I'm not going to be here in 50 years so
the bottom line is I hope I'm going to
but I don't think so and uh for 60 years
or whatever so the deal is is that we
need the information now the celery is
that holds that okay it's got the keys
to the door remember at the beginning I
was telling you guys the keys to the
door are these vegetables let me tell
you something celer is one of the keys
builds up the hydrochloric acid um helps
with adrenal fatigue the mineral salts
help with the adrenal fatigue helps with
anxiety urinary tract infections with
with strep that I talk about kidney
stones dissolves kidney stones gall
stones dissolves Co you know gall
stones how with you know dry eyes
Addison's disease rosacea lipomas when
people get lipomas do you guys have any
lipomas on your body you know the fatty
tumors um helps with Cancers like
bladder
cancer Interstitial cystitis caused by
strep Crohn's disease colitis IBS
irritable bowel syndrome right you know
hypoglycemia hypoglycemia depression
sleep apnea yeast infections which is
Strep insomnia mold exposure did you
guys get any mold exposure in your life
better be drinking that celery juice
this is what we're talking
about an emotional support get this get
this okay hang on in there you know how
we hold a lot of fear in our gut you
know cuz the minute we get scared hits
our gut we hold that fear and then it
hangs on if we had an experience or
somebody's let us down or something went
wrong and or afraid of something or we
just have some type of weird fearful
anxiety I don't know if you guys have
ever experienced that you know but if
you have celery juice helps get rid of
that emotional issue meaning that
emotional trauma to that to whatever
started that it supports that function
helps rid
that so we tend to lose the fear in our
guts and we get more kind of iron
Ironclad in the guts instead of having
fear and all these butterflies nervous
the nervousness
the sensations when her tummy flips the
butterflies in the stomach celeries gets
rid of that over time that and nobody
knows that you're only going to hear it
here on medical medium and on
lifechanging Foods let's talk about one
that I really really love a lot too
artichokes did you guys have any
artichokes lately because if you have a
lot of them and you have them on a
regular basis which no one
does it can help help you with all kinds
of different things diabetes reversing
diabetes um kidney stones gall stones
all the calcifications IAL about earlier
with your nodules and our thyroids
calcifications in our breasts and
everything else Scar Tissue artichokes
help Reaper Scar Tissue viruses like
shingles carpal tunnel syndrome bone
fraction therosis of the liver make sure
you listen to this to this um show again
go back to the archives and take all
this down
Hepatitis B hepatitis A hepatitis C
which is caused by Epstein bar HIV the
retrovirus artichokes are amazing weapon
just destroys HIV destroys it okay um
liver cancer all the neurological issues
associated with lime and if you read my
lime chapter in my book medical medium
you'll see what lime really is in the
end but artichokes are amazing for that
stomach ulcers
lupus you name it I mean artichokes but
if you you have to eat the arch chokes
it can't be like oh yeah I had an
artichoke 6 months
ago oh yeah I had an artichoke like
eight months ago now we got to bring
them in okay all right and emotional
support from the
artichoke get this anyone dealing with a
heart related emotion like a heart issue
meaning coldhearted or was brokenhearted
or someone is coldhearted or someone
who's
downhearted bring the artichokes in for
that person or for yourself if you're
dealing with that and your heart will
lift you will feel it change it'll shift
the heart shocker it'll lift everything
it'll ignite sacred healing in that
channel of the heart so remember that
okay so that's
artichoke last but not least for today
CU we're running out of time cucumbers
cucumbers are a fruit though but I have
them listed in the vegetable section for
a reason because they're they're
disguised as a vegetable they're
disguised as a vegetable it's the green
skin loaded with minerals it's a secret
weapon you juice your cucumbers cucumber
juice stops kidney disease kidney
failure missing kidney problems meaning
like it supports the other kidney
adrenal fatigue on the kidneys adrenals
helps with the Epstein bar the
mononucleosis the migraines it goes on
ALS stroke you know you name it I'm
talking about it it's powerful cucumber
can do it and it it goes on and on I
mean I can tell you more and more about
cucumber you know we're talk you know
anything from itchy skin hot flashes if
someone has a stagnant liver you know
all the like I was saying one time in
the other show all the acupuncturists
they catch the liver problems they see
in all their patients I know cuz they're
telling me you know acupuncturist are
telling me they're saying hey Anthony
you wouldn't believe how many stagnant
livers and how many messed up livers we
got coming in and they're all heated up
and they're all burning up yeah cucumber
juice cucumber juice is a big deal for
that right there so we want to bring in
those cucumbers so think about that and
on an emotional level do you know
anybody that has a lot of anger do you
know anybody that has a lot of anger in
their life or they're too irrit or
they're they get infuriated easy or
disgruntled or crabby or cranky or
irritated or heated up too fast or
they're hostile or on the edge of that
if you know anybody like that if you're
feeling that way sometimes juice some
cucumber juice because Spirit has taught
me and I've used this all the time this
emotional lesson that Spirit has taught
me that that gets rid of the anger in
people it drops it down by Leaps and
Bounds over time when they have cucumber
juice in their diet or cucumbers lots of
cucumbers in their diet the anger drops
the frustration drops it heals this
emotional issue and nobody knows about
it until you guys know right now and
thank God you know cuz you can help
others and that's all I care about right
now is you guys healing and your friends
your family and your loved ones and the
people you care about and the people you
love heal and that's what I care about
out right there okay so really important
in the green Department remember Greens
Greens Greens bring in a rugula bring in
some Sprouts if you can't eat a lot of
greens blend them up in a smoothie a
little bit do a little bit of a green
smoothie through in there throw a little
handful of spinach little touch of
cilantro in your smoothie look take your
vegetables one vegetable at a time I'll
stand behind you if you don't eat
vegetables at all that that's that's
okay let's just start with one I'm I'm
with you I'm with you on the ride okay
I'm with you on that ride don't worry
get some barleygrass juice powder I like
vimergy get vimergy barrass juice powder
in there you know I put a little in
there when you don't if want vegetables
I put it in my smoothie when I can't
when I don't have time to eat a
vegetable cuz I don't I don't have time
that day and I'm just you know all I
could eat is an apple which is still
amazing because it's it's an incredible
anti-inflammatory food but I do is put
barley grass juice powder in that
smoothie so if you're somebody who um
doesn't like a lot of vegetables but you
love a lot of meat or you're on a some
kind of diet where it's a lot of animal
protein put in the barley grass I want
to get some vegetables in you guys
spirulina Hawaiian spirulina that's a
great replacement because of what it has
its composition of what it has is
nutrients wheat grass juice
powder which I like vimergy once again
so wheat grass juice powder that's
another really good one um so think
about these when you get a chance
remember to go to my website
medicalmedium.com okay you can sign up
for my free healing path 18 steps audios
of me giving you information from Spirit
to change your life for free just for
free just free that's it there's no
there's no snag there's no hook it's
free um La event you know make sure you
you know get get to get to the LA event
for the light last and you know think
about getting the the pre-order for
life-changing Foods we offer all the you
know the downloads for you know all
these kinds of things and all this
different stuff a part of me just wants
you to have it so the first day it comes
I could just I could experience that
with you because when you open the book
your eyeballs are going to pop out of
your head and you're going to be like oh
my God and uh so I'm just excited about
that um um plus the stockage I really
don't know what's going to happen so
maybe you won't might want to get your
name on one of them if you can um so
anyway look it's about you healing it's
about you getting better remember that
you're not a bad person you didn't make
your sickness occur you didn't make your
symptoms occur it's not your fault
remember that you got to keep a landmark
in your mind that you're a good person
you deserve to heal you have every right
to heal okay and nothing's going to stop
you from healing you keep that landmark
by your side you hold that to your heart
you hold that to to your side and you
don't don't let anybody break it and you
don't let anybody mess with it because
you're a good person and you didn't
create your illness I promise you that
people get sick for other reasons it
challenges us it moves us forward we
become powerful amazing people and and
we move forward with our illnesses and
our experiences and we heal from them
and this is how we're going to do it
we're going to do it together I believe
in you I care about you you know the
other day in the other show I was saying
I really do care because I do I hear it
in real time from Spirit you and what
you've gone through and I believe in you
and I love you I stand behind with you
okay hang in there blessings lots of
love