I'm at Cafe Gratitude in Venice right
now. This is a delicious tahini butter
cookie called I am comforting
collaboration between Cafe Gratitude and
Medical Medium. One thing really
important to know, no oils. Most cookies
have oil in them. They either have
butter or oil. These cookies do not have
oil. That alone is amazing. Doesn't have
any crazy sweeteners added to it either.
It's got pure maple syrup. These are
comfort food cookies. The name is I am
comforting and it's not like peanut
butter. It's better than that.
Especially if you have it with a cup of
this healing time tea. Now, this is a
medical medium healing tool where it's
straight sprigs of thyme put right into
a cup of tea. Thyme tea has all kinds of
benefits. It helps with all kinds of
different health issues. It's
antimicrobial, antiviral, antibacterial.
Having that with this cookies. Amazing.
Truly.
Cookies and tea. Are you excited? Yes.
Yes. Yes. The cookies were good. The
tahini cookie was amazing. I think the
cookies stood out most for me because I
never get to eat cookies. So, I really
enjoyed those a lot. The cookies was
very yummy. Yes. I have to say I love
the tea. Also, I dreamed about the
cookies to put the cookies in the thyme
tea to put a little bit in and then a to
get like this flavor in your mouth. It
is delicious.
[Music]
The menu items, come on. Like pizza,
it's the noodle salads, it's the
cookies, it's the tea. Like, I'm
incredibly grateful for Cafe Gratitude,
the creativity that they put into it.
It's so refreshing to go to a restaurant
and not have to worry about like waking
up feeling like you don't have any
energy the next day or your healing's
been compromised knowing there's no seed
oils and all that. So yeah, we're ready
to feast. I'm ready for a four course
meal. I cannot wait.
Everybody loves a good cookie. This is
an epic cookie here. A collaboration
between Cafe Gratitude, Chef Drew,
Medical Medium. I hope you come down and
experience this here at Catholic
Gratitude.
[Music]