hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week we bring Advanced
Health
Information that's years ahead of where
science and medical research is now and
um hey who has 10 or 20 years to wait
for information too I hear it all the
time I hear it all the time what people
go through and how many years they have
to wait and you to get to get results
and everything else you know you have to
know I want everybody to know the
information here doesn't come from
interest groups medical funding with
strings attached botched research
lobbyists internal Kickbacks persuaded
belief systems private panels of
influencers and health field payoffs or
trendy traps the information health
information that spirit and I are
bringing to you that I share comes from
a pure untampered with Advanced Clean
Source a higher source the spirit Spirit
of compassion there's nothing more
healing than
compassion and you know when you think
about it well hey wait a minute you must
be just talking about conventional
medicine no I'm talking about
alternative too all the things I just
mentioned Kickbacks persuaded belief
systems private panel of influencers to
make the thumb on the scale go a certain
direction because investors and money
invested into something you guys have to
know something about both alternative
and people think it's all conventional
meaning conventional is where all the
sour the sour stuff happens that's what
everybody says actually that's not true
I'm sorry to say it's painstaking it's
painstaking that say this but it's
alternative too because when someone's
invested and a group is invested to get
an outcome through science and research
the thumb is put on the scale in most of
the cases because the money is going to
be lost people are going to be really
really angry funding's not going to
occur again and so things have to kind
of get persuaded one way or another I'm
telling you this because guess what the
information that's here doesn't hold
that contamination attached to it
because that's what happens and you know
there I I see it out there I see
information in the health realm both
conventional and alternative and it it's
got contamination to it because there's
something going on with it that's you
know going a certain Direction because
of these reasons that's not going to
happen here I've refused to let it
happen here the information you're
getting here comes from Spirit and So
for anybody who's new in this show you
know listening to this show and you're
brand new to this and you're like okay
let's check out this show um Anthony
William that's how it works here and I
want you to know that hey by the way I
love seeing everyone on Instagram going
to the medical medium Instagram and
telling their stories they're drinking
their cell juice you know all their
different things problems are going away
they're healing they're telling their
inspirational stories it's so powerful I
I look at that all the time and I want
to tell you guys just thank you for just
doing what you're doing because it's
inspiring it's so inspiring and it it's
inspirational to me you need to know
that when I see it I'm like you know
what I'm I'm
reinspach day like you know what
inspiration is something that doesn't
it's it inspiration
has to be you know always
reignited all the time because we get we
get so busy with everything like you
know I just finally finishing up the the
thyroid book the thyroid healing book
where you guys are going to be blown
away by that I promise I'm not going to
let you down with that one you're going
to be blown away and you know you know
and I get just I get lost in there I'm
just like sweating it out getting the
information from Spirit making sure that
that book has the most advanced
information it's never before ever been
in anybody's hands and I'm in there and
you know so when I when I get to the
Instagram and I'm seeing the feed and
I'm looking at what people have what
they're doing with their lives with this
information I'm
reinpuck that means it's changing
everybody else's lives and that's what
really hits me that's what really hits
me it's changing other people's lives
and getting them inspired it's inspiring
me it's inspiring everybody and you know
and it's incredible it really is someone
said to me the other day someone said
you know why do I even need any of your
books why do I even need it I could just
listen to your radio show and that's
what somebody said to me the other day
they said well I said what do you mean
you don't you don't have the book One
medical media
you don't have that with all that
information in there so no I I felt like
I didn't have to get it I you don't have
life-changing Foods well why you talk
about fruits and vegetables on the show
I said there's so many things I don't
talk about on this show that are in
those books and that that and and then
and then the person said to me well you
know normally when people put books
together they're usually just kind of
like the ideas there it's in the book
The Concept is there the idea is there
and that's great but usually when they
go talking on their podcast or radio
shows or whatever it is they're they're
they're talking way more I go that's not
the case this is this is information
from Spirit that I placed into these
books for spirit and for everybody that
I don't talk about there's so many
different facets and pieces of fabric
all in those books and and and this
person said you know what I'll go I'll
go get one and they went and got one
they went into into the store and they
got one and and they said you're right I
never even heard you talk about this I
go yeah
yeah anyway anyway listen you guys I
hope everybody's doing good I hope
you're working hard on everything today
we're talking about
sibo talking about sibo today okay small
intestinal bacterial overgrowth have you
have you heard about that before I I
mention it every now and then in a gut
health show or I mention a little bit
about it um in different ways you know
when we talk about the different shows
I've mentioned and have gone in and out
but I think it deserves more time all on
its own and we have a lot of different
gut health issues and there's you know
there's a lot of rampant sibo diagnosis
going out there
constantly and we need we need it kind
of aired out and we need the information
in your hands because you know there's
there's something to be said you go to
the doctor's office you know whatever
doctor that could be you know and and
and all doctors I have tremendous
respect for because the minute you want
to be a doctor you know and and that's
like it with anything the minute you
want to just help anybody even if you're
not a doctor and you want to say hey
look drink the celery juice and you're
not even a doctor I respect all of this
because what it means is there's
something inherently deep inside of us
that makes us want to help people and so
you know that but there's something when
you go to the doctor and you get you
know get told you get you know you get a
test or you know different kinds of
tests doctors do different things they
have different
do you know a breath a breath test
they'll do um you know some doctors
actually just start scooping out you
know they take a Q-tip and they start
doing cultures in the mouth and they're
doing that now they just start you know
what basically putting you know doing
cultures on on different areas of your
mouth looking for things and you know
stool samples right you know doctors
want to do that too and you know and you
get told you have
sibo and you're like okay well okay I
got sibo now what
and a lot of good doctors be like well
you got to do the antibiotics you have
to do the antibiotics for sibo I don't
like doing the antibiotics for sibo I
don't like that because you know and and
I understand with respect with respect
you know that that's that's a tool
that's used out there but the problem is
with that is when it comes down to sibo
nobody knows what it is nobody knows
what it is it's just bacteria
nobody knows what kind really what kind
like what's causing that overgrowth
what's causing what kind of bacteria is
that overgrowth I mean you some of you
probably already know the answer and
you're like oh yeah I know what he's
going to say and you're right I'm going
to say strep strep bacteria strep a
coaco stacus however people different
people call it different things for
different reason but the point is it's
Str rep that's the bacteria that's
behind sio that's the front runner
that's the big front runner now how is
it possible we can't get a solid
diagnosis whether you do stool sample or
breath test or whatever it is how can we
get a solid
diagnosis of it being strep because it
can't because when streps been in the
system too long and it starts at
childhood for a whole bunch of reasons
it starts right from childhood
right at the very beginning could be
passed on from Mommy Daddy okay could be
passed on and it also could easily be
picked up so simply and you know in in
daycare center okay and you know and
kindergarten in school or whatever and
strep is easily passed along and there's
so many different varieties of strep
that when you start with it in the
system young it changes how it can ever
be tested for or discovered or
seen by medical research and medical
science in fact it's so elusive it's
virtually impossible to know how to
identify it or test for it for instance
you know I talked about this before you
know this that UTI are mostly strep
yeast is
present but they can't tests for the
strep now they look for strep for you
know when you're in the pregnancy MO
mode and and they want to you know they
want to do the strep test vaginally and
they look for it there and and sometimes
they'll they'll find it because they're
looking really hard for it uh but most
of the time it's impossible to find but
it's the only time they even kind of
research and science even care to kind
of look for it but you know it but it's
not tested or looked for with bacterial
vaginosis it's not which which is caused
by strep is the front runner it's not
it's not looked at with anything else
with UTI forget it it's never looked at
with e it's just UTI it's just a
bacterial infection it's just a yeast
infection and because strep is so
elusive it's really hard to test for
it's really hard to look at when it's
been there a long time it's been there a
long time and with sibo sibo is the
ultimate situation where strep is in the
body it's in the system it's in the
intestinal tract it's
there and
it's it's it can't be discovered so
easily in fact it's never discovered you
know and of course you can theoretically
say well you know doctor say well it
could be a bunch of different bacteria
it could be um a whole bunch of
different things but people have a lot
in them and I want to talk about
something I want to talk about something
a question that I'm always asked
question that I'm always asked by
professionals is how can there be
bacteria
in the
gut in general when we have hydrochloric
acid in the stomach that actually you
know kills off any bacteria that's
possible so how can there be bacteria
and then some professionals will say
well you know um in the intestinal tract
there's there's you know there's no
hydrochloric acid some professionals
will say so you know I could see
bacteria being in there but what about
the
stomach you know how is it possible to
bacteria in the
stomach and it's very possible very
possible so it's not just CBO is not
small intestinal track is what I'm
trying to say
sibo is
stomach dadum small intestinal track
large intestinal
track that's where you know sibo is it's
all the way at the beginning to all the
way to the
end sibo is even ESOP
esophagus sibo is even
mouth all the way down to
rectum so here's another thing that's
happening is is you know right now the
trend is um look you got it's small
intestinal tract overgrowth you got you
know you got some bacteria and that's
you know that's what we call
sio but it's it it's literally mouth all
all the way down and out to the
rectum that's where the bacteria H you
know can
lie and we have to keep that in mind
that's a big that's a big piece that's
kind of missing in the trendy atmosphere
of
sibo but how can it be there with
hydrochloric acid and the ability to
kind of use that hydrochloric acid to
break down and kill bacteria in the
stomach so some professionals be like
it's possible to have bacteria in the
stomach it's impossible it's not even
possible and that's not true that's not
true at all because you know spirit and
I brought to the table that hydrochloric
acid is
complicated it's not one
acid it's a blend so even if someone
seems to have elevated enough elevated
hydrochloric acid you guys someone that
seems like you know if the doctor's like
no your HC seems to be strong doing a
saliva test we're doing different
testing and and now your htl seems to be
strong you don't have real low
HCL you could have
low um different parts of the
hydrochloric acid combination that only
spirit and I have brought to the table I
say that in case you're you're brand new
to listening to the show and you're like
well what can he bring that's new and
different why is the show you know doing
so good what's what can he bring well
for one and and the whole hydrochloric
acid thing is it's a complex blend of
acids it's a seven blend it's a seven
blend and I love that number seven look
out for seven that's that's the number
you want to look out for keep your mind
and eye on that number you'll see it
popping up more and more so the
hydrochloric hasd blend took you off
track really sorry about that it took
you off track all right hey did I tell
you to fasten this your seat belts too
okay let's fasten your seat bels for
this this one it's going to get pretty
good so that seven
blend three of that seven blend could be
out gone low really low no one's going
to know no one's going to know because
four of that seven blend one of the four
of that seven blend is what everybody's
more familiar with it's what science and
research is familiar with look I've
always said this it's so important to
know I don't care how much technology we
have and I don't care how great science
is getting well I do care because I want
heart transplants I want everybody
getting liver transplants if they need
one I want kidneys replaced meaning I
want kidneys you know um I want I want
people to be able to donate a kidney I
want all these things and then some I
want it all but the problem is you know
when it comes down to just even the most
simplest thing of what happens to food
when it enters your mouth and goes when
it enters your stomach when it enters
your stomach what happens to food is a
mystery that will not be solved for
hundreds and hundreds of years I'm not
talking about decades I'm talking about
hundreds of
years that mystery will not be so solved
because I'm going to tell you right now
one of the reasons why it won't be
solved is because that's a Godly thing
that's a God thing that's where God
that's where it's it's a it's about God
okay it's about the higher power the
higher source it's whatever whatever you
believe is up there some people they say
well I just believe it's a light I'm I
go okay okay you know people say you
know I just believe there's a light up
there I go okay totally and you know I I
support that absolutely I'm I'm I'm so
thankful that you believe something is
out or up there and some people be like
I call it the Creator some people are
like you know and some people like you
know I call it the universe some people
are like yeah call and I'm like I of
course I mean I call it I call God
that's what I say it's God and that's
what I do and so whatever your belief is
of what's up there just know that that
has a hand on a handle on what happens
to food when it enters your
stomach what happens with food when it
enters your
stomach so as far as we are with
technology even in medical research and
science in different aspects in
different ways you know and we with all
the amazing things that we're
developing is that's the mystery all on
its own so can you imagine the mystery
of
sibo or bacteria and how it works in the
stomach or in the intestinal
track and that's why I'm kind of be
bringing that up so you can have some of
the some of those pieces of that seven
blend of the hydrochloric acid you can
have two or three low two or three
components elements to that seven
blend of hydrochloric acid they could be
low and even though you seem like you
have high
HCL
right and what happens then is bacteria
doesn't die it doesn't die when it
enters the stomach or when it goes up
into the stomach from the intestinal
tract so when and I was telling a
professional this I was telling somebody
this was a practitioner I was saying
look you have to understand that
bacteria moves and grooves it does a
dance okay and it and it it can travel
like yeah yeah yeah I know that I know
it could bacteria can travel I know that
go but it can travel up into your
stomach even if you think you got the
best strongest hydrochloric acid there
is to kill it it could travel up there
and get there so you want to keep your
hydrochloric acid strong so a big part
of what we're talking about today with
sios is keeping that hydrochloric acid
strong that's going to be a big part of
it really really big part because that
bacteria can crawl right up there and
get up into the
tummy and it can start doing things you
know there's people with ulcers they got
ulcers in the stomach these ulcers are
created by what by what back bacteria
they're created by bacteria these ulcers
Scar Tissue occurs ulcers they mend they
heel they open again mend in heel open
sores and ulcers in the stomach why
because there's bacteria there's people
with what seemingly seems like enough
hydrochloric acid and enough powerful
hydrochloric acid but why do they have
the ulcers because they're missing
pieces of the hydrochloric acid out of
the seven blend they're missing some of
them and maybe some of the most
important ones out of that seven
blend the most important ones so it's
about getting that hydrochloric acid
really strong it's about getting that
hydrochloric acid in a much better way
so bacteria can be in the stomach but it
can be in all kinds of different places
which bacteria we talking about we're
talking about talking about the
strep and that's the one and what I like
about strep it's once you got a hand
handle on what's going on once you know
what's going on you can take control you
can do stuff you can heal nothing can
stop you from healing once you have the
information the body the body wants to
heal but it has to connect to something
it has to connect to also information
that you've that you've
gathered you got to cut on your hand you
got to cut on your
hand and if you don't have information
your body wants to heal that cut if you
don't have information to keep that
wound
clean and
dry and care for it just say you don't
want to do any of that say you want to
bang your hand around stick it you know
stick stick it someplace grab something
all the time constantly injuring the
wound not ever cleaning it not ever
washing it out not ever putting a little
bandage on it for now not doing anything
there's a chance your body is going to
be like look we're doing everything we
can we got your immune system we got
your killer cells we got your blood
count we got everything on top of that
wound going going going and we're
knocking down that bacteria we're
knocking down anything else we're
knocking down staff that could get on
that
wound but it's too much because you
don't have the information to take care
of that wound you don't have the
information to take care of that
wound you you're not doing anything for
it you're not putting salt on that wound
salt on a wound is actually really
healing even though it can hurt like
hell you're not you know you're not
cleaning it you're not washing it you're
not looking at it you're not care for
caring for it you're not putting an
herbal pus on
it P you know so whatever it is the
information has to be there too to help
the body to help the body you know some
people I my god I've heard this o over
the years people have gone to a lot of
different practitioners a lot of
different doctors they've been all over
the globe they've traveled everywhere
they've you know they've taken planes
across the I mean across the
world and for answers oh they're still
sick because their body wants to heal
it's keeping them going but they just
need the answers
too and that's the other half it's the
other
half knowing you know what's wrong is is
half the battle knowing how to heal it
is the other half of the battle spirit
taught me that Spirit taught me that a
long time ago when I was
young when I was really young when I was
in my single
digits and spirit tell me that half the
battle is knowing what's wrong the other
half is what to do about
it and you know and your body's fighting
for you no matter what in and out of all
of it
so with sibo
yeah with strep it's conquerable really
conquerable when you know what you're
dealing with here's here's something
that's important if you think your your
overgrowth of bacteria is a whole bunch
of different random bacteria and you
don't really know which ones it doesn't
help you it doesn't help
you enough it doesn't help you
enough but knowing this is the strep
that was your strep throat 20 years ago
this is the this is the STP that was you
know that whole
strep um hand and mouth strep that you
had when you were 8 years
old this is that strep that was you know
the swollen tons
soles when you had swollen tonsils this
is the strep that was that worst sinus
infection you had ever years
ago this is a strep that was that UTI
that was a pain in your butt that one
time in your life
when you know how to identify it this is
that strep that gave me sty in the eye
when you know how to identify it and
what it is it changes everything it
changes
everything everything I'm serious if you
know this is the strep that did the
sinus infection this is the strep that
gives you yeah that belly ache this is
the strep that gives you that
inflammation in different areas it
matters this is the strep that causes
all that severe cystic
acne and now all of a sudden I'm
diagnosed years later with with
sibo a people
say they're diagnosed you know years
later with sibo and they're like okay
what's this now when you know what it is
and what's been in your system it's
lifechanging it's lifechanging maybe
some of you are like oh I don't want to
know what it is I kind of like going to
the doctor and just been like okay what
is it okay I'll just take this
antibiotic and I respect that I honor
that because you know it's not it's not
it's not like everything's so easy it's
it's not so I'm with you but hang in
there if you're one of those you know
kind of people you know just know I love
you and you're one of those kind of
people that're like look I don't know
what's going on but but hang in there
because it's still we're still going to
do some things that that are helpful
because if you're dealing with something
you're suffering or you're really going
through something it's important to know
these
things so knowing what it is is
important and that's the key knowing
that it's just a melt pot a bacteria
that's possibly in your stomach no Rhyme
or Reason Tak an antibiotic hope for the
best is really not not the best and L
even in when it's alternative
medicine and you know you get a really
good practitioner and they give you some
herbs and they change your diet you need
to know more because it's time to
conquer the bacteria that's wreaking
havoc or causing problems or interfering
with your life on any level
level interfering with your life on any
level and we want to do that we want to
be able to do
that so we have to look back at our
lives and see well what happened earlier
on in my life where could I what you
know I did have a strep throat earlier
on in my life whoa I see and that's
that's how it works so strep is kind of
elusive it stays in her body it lives in
US it lives in us now the reason why I
don't like the antibiotics with strep is
because it it empow strep Don't Panic if
you taking antibiotics it's fine meaning
don't don't worry don't be like oh my
God I took an antibiotic forward it must
have been strep no it's it it listen
it's okay the point is it's about
forging ahead moving
forward so strep tends to change it
tends to get smart wise it gets immune
to antibiotics and you got to do it use
a different antibiotic I know people
that have suffered from severe UTI
because of strep and they've had to
change different antibiotics they have
to do a cocktail of antibiotics I've
seen that over the years same thing with
stomach problems same thing with Leebo
same thing with other things and it the
problem is is that strep tends to not
get affected by the antibiotic anymore
and it gets immune and it grows past it
and it could get stronger and it can
mutate and there's a lot of different
varieties of strep now I think medical
science research have something like
groups through a through H so strep a
the strep B those are the two main
groups that science and research have
been working with all these years and
then it went you know then finally you
know some some some funding and research
went to a right the right place for at
least the
recognizing recognizing the fact that
there's more groups sounds like a
through H but there's not enough letters
in the alphabet to match the groups and
that's where it falls short that's where
I was saying where the thumb is on the
scale because I'm sure some amazing
scientist or researcher that was
researching the different groups of
trying to classify the different groups
of stre strep looking at them under the
microscope wherever it can be gathered
out of people I'm sure these amazing
practitioners are like in the lab saying
oh my God I think there's I think
there's way more past a strep group a to
Group H I think there's a lot more here
and they can't do anything about it
because someone else is in the way of
everything I said originally when I was
opening the show something else is in
the way some some interest group is in
the way for the scientists to be like
wait a minute here we got a
problem so so if there was you know
there's not enough letters in the
alphabet to match the amount of
mutations and the group of strep that's
creating the sibo the whole sibo effect
that we're we're seeing out there
and so taking control understanding what
it is is actually starts to break down
the bug itself so right now you and me
just you right now together okay you and
me know we
know that that little bug is weak and
I'll tell you why it's
weak because your immune system is going
after it as we're talking right now see
knowing what's wrong knowing what to do
okay that's that's the two pieces that
Spirit taught me going all the way back
knowing what's wrong knowing what to do
what happens is when you know what's
wrong your immune system connects to
your thoughts you know that part you
know your thoughts help govern your
immune system you know that and but when
you really know what you're after
something really takes off really takes
off and really takes place this is this
is even more advanced than a whole thing
kind of the thought power thing where
you know you're you're thinking you're
thinking you're healing and that's
powerful where you're thinking your body
can heal and that's powerful but you can
take it to another level when you take
it to the level of wait a minute I know
it's giving me that small intestinal
tract overgrowth now I know what bug it
is what happens is your killer cells can
connect to that very thing it can create
what's an identification process that's
beyond beyond our vision it's an
identification process to the bacteria
that means the immune system starts to
redesign itself so your immune system
right now right in this moment is
redesigning
itself seriously it's redesigning it
itself I'm going to tell you how through
chemical compounds chemical
compounds our immune system has the
ability to shape shift it has the
ability to redirect itself it has the
ability to take on new information just
through frequencies of thought but it
has more than that even more than all of
that it has the ability to restructure
chemical compounds not found in any
science of research and maybe that'll be
decades ahead of the time maybe two two
three decades from now maybe 30 40
years from now they'll figure out that
chemical compounds are created by your
different immune system you know your
lymphocytes for example how they can
change they can change by creating a new
chemical that matches the understanding
and information that you know about
what's inside your body a chemical
compound can develop from that alone and
change to look for a bug that's been
immune it's been immune to your immune
system you know how we we're always like
well you know let's we want we want to
be immune to
something we want to be immune to
something if you're dealing with
something emotional you know if you're
dealing with problems emotionally if you
have somebody that's that if you or you
have somebody that's just causing
trouble bullying or you got somebody in
the workplace or whatever you want to be
immune to them so you want you want to
create
something a foundation or you want to
create something that could make you
immune to them what I like to do is I
like to use the word
light in those
situations if there's nothing more
powerful somebody's bullying you at work
someone's giving you a hard time or
whatever it is I say the word
light that's what I like to
do and you here's here's the deal and
I'm going to talk more about that in in
another show we're going to talk more
about that but the deal is the bug can
have immunity too to our immune system
and when you know what's going on and
you know what's causing it it changes
that your immune system changes and
Alters in order to kill the bug and rid
the U and R rid the sibo and and and rid
the the um bacterial
infections and you know rid the pelvic
inflammatory um problems that that that
a lot of women have too which is caused
by different groups of strep and rids
everything the sty that keep on coming
the sore throats that keep on coming the
sinus infections that keep on
coming and of course the sibo the
intestinal tract issue too so not only
are we going to rebuild hydrochloric
acid which what we're going to talk
about next but it's about changing
changing the structure of the immune
system having it create new chemical
compounds that strep is not immune to so
so we can destroy it so we can start
kicking it out of her body and that's
why it's important to know what's going
on so when you know and I've heard it
before someone said you know said to me
a while back I forget how long ago now
this is but and I've heard it over the
years here and there where somebody like
I really don't want to know I don't want
to know I just want to go to the doctor
and I just want to know everything's
okay and I didn't walk out and I don't
want to know really what's what's
happening in there and I'm I'm too young
for to think about these things and I
want to go out and I want to you know I
want to have fun I want to have fun and
I I of course we should have fun we need
to have fun but it comes the time we
need to know what's going on too inside
of us to heal so let's get our
hydrochloric acid built up when you get
your hydrochloric acid built up you're
killing bacteria that's trying to even
get into the stomach and more than that
hydrochloric acid runs deeper than the
stomach it runs
lower than the stomach how hydrochloric
acid Works in the
dadum and here's another thing unknown
to research and science hydrochloric
acid Works in the small intestinal tract
but it goes down deeper in the small
intestinal tract one of the reasons why
that research and science isn't keen on
that is because they're looking at one
element one part one fraction of the
seven blend hydrochloric acid that I'm
talking about that not looking at the
other
six and some of the other six have a
responsibility they have a
responsibility to go deep into the small
intestinal tract and start killing off
bacteria and working with your immune
system working with your lymphocytes
monocytes nutrifil basophils basil B all
of that working with that and so that's
why it's important to really enhance and
rebuild this you know that hydrochloric
acid
why on
Instagram are people saying you know on
on the medical medium Instagram their
lives have changed and they've been
everywhere they've done
everything but their lives have changed
because of this green celery juice and
only celery juice that's sitting in
their hand why is that happening and and
how come nobody else knew that straight
celery juice has the power to do this
besides spirit because of spirit that's
why that's why nobody knew Spirit knows
I wouldn't even know I wouldn't know any
of this I wouldn't know any of the
information I've ever written about or
put out there I wouldn't know a single
piece of it if it wasn't for Spirit we
know that you know it's Spirit people
say you're the greatest someone said to
me you're the greatest well I was out
the other day cuz I I was forced to have
to leave the leave the office and
someone said you're hey you're you're
you're Anthony I said yeah how you doing
he said you're the greatest and I'm like
no I'm not spirit is the greatest
because really I don't know anything
it's Spirit anyway the bottom line is
that celery juice that celery juice is
that powerful and it's life-changing
because it builds up that structure okay
I want to tell you something about the
celery ju I never talked about when you
buy celery you're you're buying
different celery from different farms at
different times of the year so when you
go to the store and you're buying celery
it's a different Farm it's not always
the same farm and sometimes it's the
same Farm growing celery in a new
field or in a different
field and it changes that mineral
composition so what I'm saying is you're
getting celery from a juice Place
chances are the celery came from a
different place this is a good thing
this isn't a bad thing you're getting
celery from your Co-op it's a good thing
it's a different batch of celery you're
getting you know from a different farm
that was out in California shipped
across the United States possibly a
different one all this all this
matters because celery juice has
different compositions of mineral salts
but all the same but different
levels and that's the key to rebuilding
the hydrochloric acid too if you could
only have one celery and it's all you
can get and it's one Farm only for the
rest of your life then that's fine too
believe me that'll also help move you
forward and you'll heal
so why is celery so important because
that mineral blend was meant to actually
restore those missing components out of
your hydrochloric acid blend the seven
blend remember I told you look out for
seven look out for that number look out
for
seven seven is so profoundly powerful
for so many reasons when it comes down
to the human body and it comes down to
the way things are structured in in the
human body the way things are designed
in the human body the way things are
created and seven actually matters in so
many different ways with the immune
system with everything hydrochloric acid
I can go on and on with the liver you
you it's seven has a lot to do with
what's happening in our bodies for that
seven Hydrochloric blend to build back
up and kill off and this is what happens
the mineral salts are poisonous the
mineral salts in celery are poisonous to
bacteria they're poisonous not poisonous
to you I promise you they rebuild that
missing seven blend so the mineral salts
in the celery rebuild the missing seven
blend Hydrochloric acids that are
combined in there that alone helps kill
off any kind of SEO bacteria any kind of
strep bacteria but it also enhances the
immune system the immune system rides
off of creating chemical compounds like
I was just saying so your lymphocytes
can create chemical compounds how do
they create them what are they made out
of what chemical compounds are we
talking about I know I'm I know I'm
going into some deep
space but the chemical compounds are
made out of salts made out of salts this
doesn't mean you go run and start ding
yourself with salt doesn't mean you
start filling you start eating a ton of
salt don't don't even do that that's not
what I'm talking about talking about the
celery and it's even some of it's even
in the spinach stems so spin
itself and and you know so those have
you know sodium salts too that are
special and designed in a special
way so this type of these mineral salts
that are in the
celery they're used they're gathered by
your white count that destroys sibo for
good and moves it out of your body for
good they utilize that because it what
what your immune system cells what your
immune cells can do is create chemical
compounds devised devised out of those
mineral salts from the celery science
and research we're talking light years
away from knowing that piece of it light
years and but it's important to know
that because you start looking for that
you're not going to find that you start
hopping on the internet you start
looking for that you're not going to
find
that so the bottom line is we want to
rebuild that up and you're doing that
with celery that's one thing you can do
but I'm giving you the information you
guys I'm giving you this stuff so you
know why you're getting better so you
know why when you're on when you're
doing the Instagram when you're seeing
the Instagram you see somebody getting
better so you know why things are
happening this is one of the reasons
because your immune system wants to kill
every virus and every bacteria that we
have in our body it just needs the right
sodium salts or the right chemical salts
meaning that are in chemical compounds
that they can create new chemical
compounds that are in vegetables and
fruits I want to talk about fruit fear
for a minute when it comes down to any
type of problem someone thinks they have
whether it's candida whether it's yeast
whether it's mold whatever it is whether
it's bacteria sibo they're told not to
eat any fruit ever and it creates a
fruit fear like no other you know I did
a show on fruit fear you you guys know
that I did a show and there's a chapter
on fruit fear in medical medium book
one and you know so I take you know you
know I've taken it seriously but it's
getting worse out there it's getting
worse and worse and worse someone might
say and argue hey look yeah but I got
off of all my bad foods I even kept
fruit out and got off of all my you know
pizza and cheese and other stuff and I
just eat a really clean clean clean diet
some protein and some vegetables because
a book out there says that that's going
to be you know beneficial in some that's
going to be beneficial and it's going to
help you fight this and that and I felt
better of course you're going to feel
better because if you eat cleaner food
you're going to feel better if you eat
cleaner foods but if you're somebody
that's really been struggling and
suffering and been to every doctor tried
everything and they're past that point
not past that point of not healing I'm
talking about past the point where
they're not just like hey I finally got
off of my fast food I finally got off of
you know of of ice cream and I'm eating
clean proteins and vegetables and I'm
getting better if you're someone that's
way P you know you're past that whole
thing the fruit's critical because the
fruit does matter the fruit really does
matter cuz you take somebody who really
needs the fruit and the right kind of
foods and you take them and you put them
on the kind of you know just clean diet
that's out there that's minus fruit and
Clean Diet that's out there and they're
going to they're going to hit a wall
they're going to hit a wall I've seen it
happen for years and years and years
what I'm saying is don't be afraid of
fruit even if you're on a Clean Diet
regardless of what that is is protein
and vegetables whatever whether you're
vegan you do doing vegan protein or
you're a meat eater and you're doing
meat protein whatever it is don't keep
fruit out I've seen I've seen
plant-based people vegan people say look
I don't want to touch fruit I don't want
to touch fruit ever I just don't like it
bananas are bad everything's
bad um and but I'm doing tons and tons
of protein powders and tons of
vegetables as a vegan they'll say same
thing with you somebody who's a meat
eater like no just you know lean cut
animal protein and lots of vegetables
don't keep the fruit out one of the
reasons is the fruit kills
the bacteria that causes
sibo it kills
it there's assets that are naturally in
fruit fruit
acids that dissolve bacteria sometimes
it's why people some people be like well
I kind of feel like I'm detoxing and I
eat a lot of fruit because you are
detoxing you are detoxing detoxing for
the first time in your life
actually and that's how critical fruit
is like bananas
yeah bananas bananas are now becoming
the
Antichrist literally the Antichrist
because of
practitioners that are writing books
that are influenced by information that
came out about 8 nine years ago that was
never even lab created
information it was a poisonous Theory
came out for a reason to stop you from
ever eating a banana again to stop you
from ever eating certain fruits again
this is contaminated
information that certain famous people
well-known people have made sure they
got it into the alternative system about
9 10 years ago I remember when it
happened and don't get poisoned by that
information don't be afraid of eating a
banana something very important what
does the banana do it grabs on to
sibo and look if you're somebody that
says oh I don't know if it's streping me
but I got sibo and the doctor said that
I got lots of bacteria then a banana is
that powerful it can grab onto that
bacteria and pull it out it doesn't feed
the bacteria it kills the bacteria
suffocates it pulls it out something to
know so all fruit is good all vegetables
are good I'm just saying so don't be
afraid of different fruits the fruit
fear is so out of control now that it's
I I honestly can't even battle it
anymore out there I need I need you guys
to actually stick up for some fruit and
you do that you do that I see it happens
out there um leafy greens vegetables we
need all of that let's talk about some
herbs and things I want to talk about
how to kill the strep inside of you
that's creating the
sio so rosemary thyme Sage oregano
parsley cilantro you know the Rosemary
th Sage I'm going to say it again
oregano parsley cilantro the simple
herbs that we have in food all the time
make sure you're using them that kills
kills off sibo that kills off small
intestinal tract bacteria such as strep
it destroys it make sure that you're
using that when you can a little time
fresh time is fine time tea you know
about that right talk about it all the
time I talk about it all the time Sage
have sage in your food sprinkle it in
chop a little sage leaf fresh sage leaf
in there whether it's cooked food
whether it's raw food whether you're
somebody that eats meat whether you're
somebody that doesn't whatever it is
bring in more Sage kills off that
bacteria it can free you so you don't
have to end up using an antibiotic 5
years from now 8 years from now or
whenever it is to try to get something
under control that you're confused about
make sure you get this in you oregano
you can do the oregano oil capsules that
can work oregano fresh going into the
Garden or your pot that you have fresh
oregano Brewing or growing you can you
can pluck you know pluck it off chop it
up throw it in your salad and you have
one of the most powerful antibo weapons
there is fresh
oregano parsley big time Big Time
mineral salts are in parsley that do
help juice a little parsley in your
juices get a juice going do the celery
as the base put a little parsley in
there if you want great sibo killer
cilantro cilantro we know pulls out the
heavy metals you guys know that we talk
about it all the time and and you know
the heavy metal detox with all the
different things but cilantro is a great
sio killer great sibo killer so these
things have to be in here the Rosemary
time the sage the oregano The Parsley
the cilantro seems basic seems simple
yeah we'll bring it in get a rosemary
plant going get buy fresh
Rosemary and chop it up throw it in the
food make a guacamole make a guacamole
put a little Rosemary in there put a
little time Sage all of it in a
guacamole do that so um Pao Aro great
herb hup get some hup tea going on so
hup tea is fantastic for for sio so you
know that's a great one so go get some
his up herb and make a cup of tea strong
cup of tea with it that's a secret
weapon a great weapon habiscus tea do
you like habiscus tea I I'm hoping you
do because you got a you got a weapon
for sibo right there you got a great
weapon some of these things hold those
you know chemical compounds within the
foods phytochemical compounds within the
foods that your immune system can then
take and recreate a chemical compound to
kill off sio just like the celery juice
I said what can happen with some of
these as well olive leaf taking it every
day is great olive leaf
capsules very helpful you know pod Arco
is another one you can get it in in a
tincture form that I talked about before
vitamin C to support your lymphocytes
support your immune system so that the
strep doesn't take over especially when
it comes to other things that strep
creates besides siba which is UTI pelvic
inflammatory problems siy sinus problems
cystic acne you name it vitamin C is Inc
incredibly important very very important
so all of these things are that
important also zinc because you're
battling strep so you do want zinc in
your system so that's another thing too
the liquid sink I always talk
about and um and the B12 and the B 12 is
important too Elderberry so elderberry
tea you can get the Elderberry
elderberry tea is a great one for sibo
if anybody's into chocolate terrible for
sibo one of the worst things in the
world for sibo so I'm just saying if you
don't have sibo and you love chocolate
hey don't let anything stand in your way
I'm just saying if you got small
intestinal over overgrowth you know
diagnosis that you the bacterial
overgrowth diagnosis that has been given
to you stay away from chocolate if you
have have that
diagnosis stay away from chocolate you
can have a little bit if you're really
into it you can have a little bit here
and there but C cut it back some people
eat a ton of it they have it every
single day so I'm worried about that if
someone has an issue that that's too
much there's many more supplements and
and foods you can do and incorporate to
address sibo running out of time so go
to my blog check out the strepa caucus
revealed blog post I did before where I
have a radio show too and an article
that gives you many tips that can also
help you heal from sibo but I'm going to
be putting out a new blog post on sibo
specifically with more supplements More
Foods as well coming soon so keep on
looking out for that too that's going to
be really helpful and uh look I stand
behind you guys 100% with everything and
I care about you guys and I'm proud of
you seriously with all that you're doing
everything you're doing take one day at
a time your body can heal nothing can
stop it from healing we're just making
sure you get the information you need so
you can turn the tide completely around
so the struggle's not there anymore and
that it can change if you're struggling
in your healing for a long term you will
heal because things are healing inside
of you every day always know that bless
you God bless you and take
care