[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found in anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now B
paly happens to be an example of this
and I say this because years and years
and years
ago the thought that
shingles the virus had anything to do
with Bill paly did not exist it didn't
exist anywhere in medicine but yet
Spirit offered me the information and
going all the way back decades I was
helping people out telling them that
they Bel B's py was a shingles virus now
not every type of bell paly sometimes a
bell paly could be a stroke but that's a
different story that's different than
Bell's paly and there's different
symptoms so much many more different
symptoms that come along with it I'm
already jumping into the show this is
unbelievable So today we're talking
about Belle's paly now you know with my
shows um this is the only Health show
anywhere only El show anywhere that the
information is not from group like
interest groups in medical funding with
strings attached and BOS botch
research um internal Kickbacks persuaded
belief systems private panel of
influencers yeah does that stuff matter
to say does it matter to talk about yes
it does because there's always something
behind information that's even passed
down passed around in alternative
medicine and conventional medicine both
but even alternative to alternative
medicine and because just Bell's poliy
alone is going to get cast off it's like
genetic down the road as some kind of
genetic thing meanwhile we know what it
is and we're going to talk all about
what it is and how you get it and
everything else this the only show where
the health information comes from Pure
untampered with clean a clean Source a
higher source a source that was given to
me at the age of four a gift that was
given to me I was blessed with and or
cursed with or cursed with that's how I
felt anyway when I first received the
gift and along the way I had my Tantrums
of course while dealing with the gift
but the gift is for you guys it's for
you it's always been for the people
spirit said said that to me a long time
ago spirit said that you know this gift
isn't for you for you and I remember I
was crying I was complaining I remember
there was this one time when I was think
about 12 between 12 and 13 years of age
I think it was in the fall because I
remember the leaves on the trees I was
outside of Nature and the leaves on the
trees were turning the red you know the
maples were turning turning red and
orange
and those beautiful colors and the oak
trees were turning those beautiful
colors and I remember and I had this
little it was a beautiful day the sun
was out the temperature was perfect it
wasn't crazy hot and it wasn't cold and
I remember having a tantrum I was 12 and
1/2 years of age and it was having a
tantrum to spear and I said you know why
me why do I have this gift why do I have
to deal with this always knowing what's
wrong with every single person no matter
what the case is no matter where I am no
matter who's in front of me why do I
have have to hear this and see this you
know why was I given this gift and
spirit said to me this gift wasn't for
you I was like what I wasn't shock I was
in shock I was in shock and I know
Spirit mentioned that to me over the
years you know even a little bit before
that once in a while but didn't quite
get it cuz I I wasn't at that age where
I could understand certain things and
and and spirit said this gift this this
wasn't for you this isn't for you and I
was like what I this my mind mind was
blown spirit said this is for everybody
else this is for them this is for them
the people that you you're upset about
the people that you're upset about
because you see what's going inside with
them every day this is for them I was
like oh my God okay okay I get it I get
it and that just made it worse that made
it worse when you're younger but you
know but the whole point is the source
of information is is pure and tampered
with information in the medical field in
the medical world and we got to worry
about that isn't that sad isn't that sad
that we have to worry about that in
alternative medicine it's so sad I can't
even tell you it's so sad because
funding goes in certain places there's
there's belief systems so tied into so
many different the fabric and pieces of
the alternative medicine world it's it's
it's different it's not like it was not
like it was a long time ago not like it
was when alternative medicine was in its
it's in its its place and in the late
1800s early 1900s then mid 1900s and
then conventional medicine try to squash
it out like a bug and and and just
locked up conventional medicine locked
up every single chiropractor every I
mean that that was trying to break break
above and beyond every single home
homeopath and then the word quack was
designed for all the alternative doctors
in the 40s and 50s there were ostracized
they were
tortured they were they were and and it
was unbel believable what happened they
had to go run off to Germany and hide
and even that wasn't even a safe place
for alternative
practitioners it was unbelievable time
an unbelievable time an alternative then
alternative medicine had to fight and
had a fight for its right to to to you
know to hang in there and stay in there
conventional medicine wanted it squashed
like a bug put a lot of people in prison
a lot of PE can you believe that you go
to your naturopath you don't even know
how many naturopaths went to prison
before that naturopath because it's so
swept under the carpet it's unbelievable
how many chiropractors went to prison
for for nothing for doing nothing back
in the in the 20s and 30s back in the
40s you couldn't believe the
trail the trail of
Darkness that that occurred for
alternative medicine to fight its way
through and then when it finally did it
finally birthed and it finally
grew the world found a way to find
contamination to slip it in in
everywhere it could so the information
you don't know it's there studies and
financial stuff behind it that's
unbelievable like no other inconen of
course but in alternative now so it's a
fight what's out there on the internet
what's in books is it legit is it not
what's going on where's the studies are
the studies real is the thumb on the
scale and that's what's going on out
there and we're not going to let any of
that kind of get in the way of getting
the source that that I was born with to
give you the information and when it
comes down to Bell's policy it has to be
right it has to be
right and that's that's what it's about
that's what it's about isn't this stuff
isn't this stuff annoyingly fun it's
annoying and fun maybe it's not fun at
all maybe it's interesting maybe you
don't even care you want to just talk
about pels paly but either way I I you
know history I really love the real
history history that just is completely
buried and hidden and just you know
burned up and just turned to ashes I
just I love bringing the old history out
because if you don't know where you came
from you can't appreciate what you got
and right now we got unbelievable and
amazing freedom in Altered medicine but
we got some problems with a lot of the
information that's tossed about in it
and there's a lot of gems and jewes
incredible information in alternative
medicine and in conventional medicine
there's incredible stuff and good
scientists and great doctors incredible
doctors everybody it's never the
doctor's fault when it comes down to
information being passed around really
it's not the doctor's fault they care
they love they want to help you they get
into this to help you they get into it
to help you that's the whole point I I I
I know doctors that selfishly work and
they just they're they're in the
trenches day in day out I know
pediatricians that are in the trenches
day in and day out I know you MDS that
are in the trenches day in and day out I
got unbelievable respect and when I hear
doc doctor what I'm I'm you know someone
said to me H you don't even you don't
like doctors you don't have respect for
doctors you should see what happens when
someone's like when they're a doctor
they come up and they come up and they
say hi to me or something or it or I
bump into a doctor somewhere I'm like
I'm like saluting I'm like doctor oh my
God and and you know whatever kind of
doctor it is doesn't matter including
some some healers healers that aren't
even doctors of course because they care
they want to help people different
practitioners different walks of life in
the pr in The Healing Arts you should
see me snap too you should see me hop
too talking about you know if you talk
about a g has no respect for doctors or
practitioners you should see me up too
like you can't believe like oh my God I
just whoa I I I I just you know I just
met
God okay and that's I because because
when we go into The Healing Arts you
know no matter what direction where it
is s surgeons non-surgeons it's serious
stuff it's serious stuff because it's a
different line of work it's it's not
like oh I'm going to choose to go this
this way in life which is still
purposeful which is all the different
ways people have purpose is amazing the
way they go into life with purpose the
way everybody has purpose whatever job
they do it's
incredible it's
incredible but when it comes down to
people that are ailing there's there's
an emotional connection there's an
emotional connection when people are
suffering you guys know when you when
you're not feeling well there's there's
it it it tugs on the heart so the doctor
or the practitioner they have to they
have to be there for that even if they
don't have good bedside man or doesn't
mean they're not feeling it or it
doesn't mean they don't know because
they know they know they know you're in
pain they know you're suffering it's the
business they went into they see it they
feel it and there's something about that
it's something about
that and so yeah you see me H too you
wouldn't believe it it's like Anthony
William okay just up to like oh my God
what do you do
whoa okay and uh and that's the kind of
respect I have but I know the history
and I also know how contamination has
occurred within in and out of certain
information and there's great doctors
have to pick and choose and they have to
pull those gems and jewels out they even
know they even know there's stuff going
on with information out there so that's
my little monologue to start with before
we before we get going um thyroid
healing what do you think are are you
going to are you going to get thyroid
healing because when you get it you are
going to be so psyched you're going to
be so psyched I mean seriously um I I I
I
painstakingly took down every note the
word from word from Spirit and I put it
in there I didn't want to miss anything
and um even when Spirit was going on
tangents I said okay I I'll have to fit
that in somewhere I'll have to that's
not what my question was to Spirit but
I'll have to fit I'll have to fit that
in somewhere in the book and and I just
I just did everything I could to get
this book to where it needs to be so you
become an expert an expert not just in
thyroid but an expert in medicine in so
many different ways in so many different
ways in chronic illness so don't miss
out I talk about the thyroid the
different things about the thyroid I
talk about the Undiscovered hormones of
the thyroid talk about what the thyroid
really does what it really does for the
body like what its job really is
throughout the entire body and how even
if you had it surgically removed there's
tissue left over even the best surgeon
can't get all the tissue out of a
thyroid and the tissue still
communicates within the body nobody
knows this but Spirit nobody knows this
but Spirit you know I got some people
that you know they just don't they just
don't like hearing what I do because you
know it's not it's not um it's not the
way they would like it so like well okay
he's got all this information where did
he get it oh who knows where he got it
no I know where I got the information
from my source and then you got some
people that say this had to come from
his Source because it's impossible for
this to come anywhere else you couldn't
get this in this just there's no way
anyone could even you know create this
information on chronic illness it has to
come from a source I've had people say
that to me that's said it has to come
from a source there's no way this
information can come from anywhere else
but the source you talk to I mean it's
there it's there you cannot miss
it I talk about what happens when when
you get sun on the thyroid I talk about
what happens when you don't get sun on
the thyroid I talk about all these
different things that you wouldn't
believe that nobody talks about you're
going to love it you won't get
disappointed um you know before when
life-changing Foods came out I was like
was last year I think it was last summer
and I was I was on the radio show and I
said you know what I don't think I let
you down I don't think I let you down in
this wait till you see this book I know
that was a risky thing to say because
what if I let yall down what if I let y
all down you guys you guys be you guys
be pissed at me and I heard from a lot
of people don't no and I saw it on
social media when I go on Facebook and I
look at Facebook and everything else and
I saw it social media and I saw some
people say he didn't let us down he
didn't it's like a it's like a food
Bible he didn't let us down it's
unbelievable you wouldn't believe what
this is
and and so I don't think I let you down
again with thyroid healing meaning I
don't think I let you down as
well if that sounds right okay so let's
go into Bell's paly here we are here we
are the droop the droop in the eye the
droop in the face the droop on one lip
droop in the mouth a droop on one side
of the nose the muscles that can't be
use so you can't like raise raise your
face up if you want anymore some people
have a droop in one eye droop just in in
one part of the mouth some people have a
droop in an eye on one side of their
face a
droop in their around their mouth at
their mouth at the other side of the
face I mean it can go it can go in all
kinds of different
ways you can get a droop on the side of
the head but not quite really feel it
cuz it's not hitting the face so much
but yet it's it's there it's kind of
putting a little bit of a
tug but bills paly and general can even
you know affect more than that see they
tend to if if if Bell's ply
occurs and it does more than the face
then you know a doctor be like well I
don't know if it's B poliy maybe it
looks like now multiple sclerosis maybe
it looks like something else in the
guessing game
happens and then it's like you know
where do we go I mean what is it isab
Belle's py we're going by a set of
symptoms person feels it in their arm
they feel it in their shoulder and the
side of their face is this multiple
scris what is this whole thing still
could be Bells
paly yeah sure you could put a name on
it you can put multiple Ms on things
whatever you want but what causes that
mess well it's viral what causes Bell
paly it's
viral it's
viral say with bell paly with B paly
it's the shingles virus I brought this
to the table through spirit I was the
first I I I'm going to I'm bold enough
to say that cuz I can say it I can say
it because it's it's it's a fact I
brought the shingles virus and the bell
Paul Bells paly connection to light
years and years and years
ago to such a
degree that it actually worked its way
around a little
bit it's worked its way around and then
of course it's in medical medium book
one which really got it to just take off
like lightning
all through the medical communities both
conventional and alternative where
shingles can be Bell's paly the very
mystery thing the very mystery
thing now but what shingles where what
how well I was the first to bring up the
fact there's over 31 varieties of
shingles unknown to medical research and
medical science medical research and
medical scientists think there's one
type of shingles herpes
zer that's just one type of
shingles you know you get the rash the
rash has to be textbook there you go bam
there you are that's
shingles but that's changing a little
thanks to the medical medium book one in
spirit that's changing now it's amazing
and and that's starting to change a
little bit and that's helped from you
guys you guys telling doctors telling
people just it's all getting around and
and that's helpful because we're helping
to change the world we're helping to we
we're contributing
contributing into medicine that's what
we're
doing and the deal is with Belle's
ballsy is it is a shingles variety but
it's it's one of the varieties you can
have two different shingles varieties in
the body one that gives you that that
plain old shingles like bam you got
shingles you got the rash it's brutal
you got it on on your butt top of your
butt your hip you got it on your back
you got it across your
stomach ug ug ug ug it
hurts but that's a different variety
than the one that causes Bel that causes
Bell paly you can never show you can you
cannot even have a rash
ever ever not one push will pop out of
the skin and
hurt okay and still get Bell's paly from
shingles and still get Bell's paly from
shingles because Bell's paly from
shingles is one of the 31 varieties it's
a specific variety that causes Bells
paly which still won't be identified by
research and science for another 30 40
years if even
mhm and
um just took a sip of some herbal tea so
looks like I think it's chamomile and uh
today so
anyway the bottom line is is it's just
this one specific variety that t tends
to go after the trigeminal nerve but man
you don't have to have Bell's paly from
this variety this variety is really
annoying because it can hurt the gums it
can hurt the teeth it can burn the mouth
a little
bit it can cause pain in the
ear which I really hate I hate when
someone comes to me meaning I love when
people I love all people but I hate when
they have to go through that I hate when
someone has to come to me and they're
like you know I got this pain that's so
bad it's completely I can't get a
diagnosis from it it's this mystery pain
in my ear and in my jaw that's killing
me I got to go on opioids I got to go on
drugs I got to go on medications I got
to go t on tons of medications to try to
numb this thing up I can't function I
feel so bad for people that go through
that that's a variety of shingles that's
the one that causes Bell's py but it
doesn't have to cause Bell's pausy too
it can miss the nerve to the face it
could miss certain nerves to the face it
can just instead slam the trigal nerve
down lower it can hit different parts of
nerves it's not a perfect virus where
it's going to hit its Mark every
time that's not how it's going to go
that's not how it's going to go and it
can go on one side or the other it's
really annoying and you can have another
shingles virus to boot that can give you
shingles on the back of your neck puls
it can give you shingles on your face
and it still not be that variety
and that variety can still cause nerve
pain on the face and head and all this
other stuff and all kinds of problems
sure but the Bells Palsy one you know it
it can hit the trigeminal liver can hurt
the teeth back of the jaw hit up there
in the ear ouch ouch ouch and go to the
dentist he's drilling all your teeth
he's pulling teeth he doesn't know
what's happening now they're getting a
little bit more wiser the information I
put out there is getting out there and
dentists are being very cautious they're
like I'm not going to touch those teeth
I'm not going to touch those teeth they
don't look bad I'm not going to go near
them I drilled out a bunch of teeth 10
years ago during a few patients who had
this I learned from the past I'm hearing
different information through other
patients I'm not going to mess with
those teeth we got something going on
that's causing nerve pain and that's
what's happening now so dentists are
getting wise it's it's an amazing time
it's an amazing
time it
is but
when that Bell's paly happens though and
it hits the nerve just
right yeah just right and the eye troops
are the face troops
and it's really
annoying sets people back sometimes it
hurts sometimes it doesn't hurt at all
sometimes it's just straight numb
sometimes they don't feel anything it's
just a droop depends there's so many
nerves there's thousands of nerves in
they little tiny once and if the virus
kind of worked its way into a batch of
nerves versus another batch of nerves
and that's what it could do it can alter
the symptom it could change the
symptom and that's what it could
do so this Bell's paly that's the
shingles
variety and even the shingles variety
these nerves they also run to the brain
a little bit they connect to the Vegas
they connect to the frenic nerves they
find their ways until all these nerves
kind of come together into the brain
there's little little places where these
nerves join together connect or get
close to if one nerve gets inflamed and
it's near another nerve it can affect
that other nerve to some degree even if
they're not even directly
connected so you can get you can get a
host of different symptoms when it comes
down to Bell's paly Bell's paly usually
hits people when they're in their late
30s early 40s how come how come how come
then because like most viruses they tend
to hit a little later it's like the
original Epstein bar virus like the
original Epstein bar virus in the 19 50s
when all the women were upset because
they had hot flashes for the first time
in history they had night sweats for the
first time in his history they had um
fatigue for the first time in history
that was different than just staying up
late or something or taking a cruise or
a trip or working hard at the office or
working hard on their job in the factory
they had fatigue for the first
time it was all in the late 1940s early
1950s this is when the medical world was
developing hormones and decided to
overlook what was really the cause of
this was this the first outbreaks of
real Epstein bar the first big outbreaks
the the whole swing of outbreaks and it
hit women all in their 40s so what what
did they do they put two and two
together one and one together said uh
this is okay a lady and she's um she's
45 years old she was born in 1900 she's
45 years old now and now she has these
symptoms it has to be the change it has
to be per menopause it has to be
menopause one of the greatest mistakes
in history that's still made now and it
was Epstein bar so women right now
because women didn't go through the
change in the old days the only thing
that stopped was their their period it
stopped and they got more energy they
felt better they had more libido they
had all these things that came to them
after this that was known but all that
changed when Epstein bar came into town
when the change the change came epine
bar snuck up on everybody created all
the symptoms weight gain fatigue all
these different problems well when that
happened in
1950 when that happened it's like well
why is it at this time is at this time
because most of these viruses they have
a timeline to them I see it happen all
the time with men in their late 30s men
get whacked and all of a sudden they
think they have Lyme disease they're
getting diagnosed with Lyme Disease by
by 10 Lyme doctors that have no idea
what's wrong with them and it they're 39
years old men that are 39 years old and
they got neurological problems they're
getting diagnosed with Lyme disease
carelessly
and the same thing with women all the
time now it's either late 30s now cuz
the world's the world is different M the
viruses have mutated stress is up the
world is a whole different place to live
in now and women have a lot more
pressure on them so they get they get
whacked around 39 now
42 sometimes 30 now there's different
varieties that all of a sudden they're
being 30 years old and they got all the
symptoms Epstein bar or they have their
first baby EP Ste bar afterwards all
this different
stuff the viruses have these times lines
and this certain variety of shingles
tends to wait a little bit later before
it comes out and it comes out later on
you don't see too many um you don't see
young women with to you know with B paly
too often it does happen but it's very
rare I me it's not as rare as it used to
be it used to be extremely rare before
20 years ago it was almost
impossible that to see that out there
now it's a little bit more out there but
but mostly it's women you know 45 48 50
39 it starts it could happen um and they
get their first bat of Bell's py 42 43
years old and that's when it
happens that's the timeline and that's
what these viruses do just like the
epine bars there's so many varieties of
Epstein bars
now that you know they can affect women
when they're just coming out of college
where they're fatigued aches and pains
they get you know diagnosed with
rheumatoid arthritis and then they get
diagnosed with uh with the chronic
fatigue syndrome then they get diagnosed
with Lyme disease then they get
diagnosed with whatever and they're just
fatigued and they can't they can't work
they come back home from college it hits
them really young you get those
varieties of Epstein bar and then you
get the varieties of Epstein bar that
people have with people who are 60 years
old now and they get their first wave of
epine bar at age 60 where everything was
smooth sailing all the way to age 60 and
now they're getting the fatigue the
aches and pains and now they get all
these symptoms and some tingles and
numbness and they get the ringing in the
ears that's the epscene bar there's
different varieties different varieties
that actually come later different
varieties that come earlier I'll tell
you in thyroid healing I talk about
Epstein bar some information I've never
talked about anywhere like it it it it
it is unbelievable What Spirit gave
me so so when it comes down in Bell's
paly that's just one variety of shingles
that one variety of shingles could
mutate and get a little different and
change and all through the years go on
and it could hit people a little younger
but for the most part it hits people a
little bit later that's at one variety
of Bell's paly
I mean you know that one variety of
shingles which causes Bells paly sorry
about that
um so what do you do for
it
antivirals you could do antivirals
before that I mean say you're in your
30s and you haven't gotten Bells posy or
anything and you're under tons of stress
let's do some good foods let's do some
antivirals so we don't get it so we
don't get hit with it how about that how
about them apples right we can do that
that but if we have had it we want to
nip it so it doesn't come again cuz it
could come
again it of course it can and it could
do uh it could come again it could do
other things it could hurt the jaw it
could hurt
anything so we want to protect ourselves
antiviral let's talk about Foods never
to
eat someone said to me how come you're
so against
eggs what how come you're so against
eggs and I know that many of you know
the story where when I was a kid when I
was a kid I can make eggs like nobody
can make
eggs I mean I could scramble them I
could fry them Sunny Side Up I could
poach them I could throw cheese in
them I could throw I could throw ham in
there right okay big deal right who who
can't do that who can't do that but no I
was really good they were never burnt
unless someone requested a burnt egg
okay
and you know I got that pan hot just
right just right you know knew when to
throw those eggs in the pan okay could
make a wicked omelette could throw every
vegetable in there right well yeah of
course everybody I guess everybody can
make an omelet now right everybody can
make some eggs but I'll tell you I was
good I was good I was good and it kind
of you know and it bothered spirit I did
it because it bothered spirit I love the
fact that it irritated the heck out of
spirit because spirits spirit's most
disliked food is
eggs not spirit's most disliked food
would you believe it eggs spirit is
nothing against eggs chicken eggs
nothing against eggs what it was was
what happened to eggs eggs became a food
along the way cuz research and science
used eggs to actually grow bugs it's a
grave mistake because they ruined our
eggs they ruined them ruined our
eggs they took eggs and they used it all
in the labs all in the
1920s all in the 1930s all the 1940s
1950s all in the 1960s all in the
1970s propagated tons and tons of
different kinds of bugs viruses played
around with viruses played around with
bacteria they put egg and
antibiotics eggs and
antibiotics they messed with eggs
they've ruined them it became a food for
bugs it became a food for Epstein bar it
became a food for shingles it became a
food for
viruses and it's not the perfect food we
wanted it to be or wanted to be but
anyway you know I knew it pissed off
spirit so I I really just you know I
fell in love with eggs cook them up
became an egg expert you know 7 years
old 8 years old could cook eggs like
nobody else and I said to Spirit you
know what I got a dream cuz I'm not
going to do this stuff stuff I'm not
going to do what you want me to do I
know so I'm going to have an egg Shack
I'm going to cook eggs for people people
are going to come they're going to buy
my eggs that's how I'm going to make a
living you can't tell me different you
can't stop me that's what I'm going to
do spirit says you'll see you'll see you
won't be able to do that you're just
going to hear me and that's all you're
going to do and you're going to help
people I said no no no no so you know I
had a thing for
eggs but you so it's not like hey it's
not like I'm anti-g in some way I just I
gotta I gotta you know play by the real
rules the truth
rules truth rules that's pretty cool you
know real truth rules and what it is is
eggs feed bugs of every single kind
every single way so if you're a meat
eater keep the eggs
out keep the eggs out if you're a vegan
well you're not going to eat eggs duh if
you're vegetarian you're going to eat
eggs though that's another thing
vegetarians eat eggs that's one of the
not every vegetarian you'll find a
vegetarian like no I don't eat eggs I
don't eat this but you'll find a
vegetarian they be like no I eat eggs
every day where am I where else am I
going to get my protein you know a
confusion on
protein because protein you know protein
is not what fuels people it's calories
that fuel people that's how you can get
up in the morning function that's how
you can get through your day that's how
you can work that's how you can think
it's
calories it's not protein that does that
protein doesn't do that that's not what
protein
does you take protein and separated and
just feed that to a person they will
starve to death in no time become
emaciated and
die cuz there's no calories in protein
if you you can give somebody cartons and
cartons and cartons of protein carton's
a protein and if you separate the
calorie from it which is the sugar the
carbohydrate or even the fat and you
separate that and you just give them
protein they will die I mean fast it's
horrific it's
horrible it was actually done before in
an experiment back in the
1950s it's just terrifying
terrifying bunch of people signed on to
it and stupidly did
it you know so the point is the point
back to where I was saying the egg I'm
ripping it apart today I can't help it
and sadly I'd want to but I can't help
it the deal is is it feeds bugs it l
loves feeding the shingles well shingles
loves the egg is what I'm saying it's
one of its big Foods it's one of its
favorite foods you get Belle's paly quit
the eggs you stop them whatever you do
because it's a virus feeding food and
it's not the egg's fault it's not the
chicken's fault it's not your fault it's
not my fault it's it's actually the
people in the labs that was a food they
they actually gave bugs to keep them
alive even though they tell us bugs
don't eat anything it's amazing
amazing I mean there's some smarty pants
people out there in the industry that
have have you know thrown on social
media or something else and they say
they say look he doesn't realize that
viruses can't eat anything they can't
feed on anything oh look how dumb he is
the medical
medium unbelievable
unbelievable of course viruses feed on
something it has to it's just a science
and research a doesn't know how a virus
e and B it does know it eats something
because they raised bugs on food to keep
them alive in Labs All Through The
Years okay that's just the bottom line
I'm telling you so you want to stay away
from
eggs well that's the
deal stay away from dairy products that
doesn't help with shingles there's no
question about it stay away from pork it
doesn't help the shingles it's so high
in fat that it's not good and believe me
those high fat diets out there aren't a
great thing they're not a great thing
even though they made them healthier by
saying well let's do a little bit more
avocado let's not just have it all
animal fat let's do a little bit more
avocado let's do a little bit more
coconut oil and how come they're doing
that they're doing that because they're
learning from mistakes because when you
go all animal fat that's not good
either that was tried and done heart
attack city man heart attack city so
they going to coconut oil and other and
some you know other fats and some high
quality oil and going with avocado fat
so that's coming into the play I mean
it's like it's it's it's ridiculous it's
like it's like come on of course coconut
oil is okay for we could have some of it
of course avocados are good but you got
to keep your fats low especially if
you're viral especially if you go Bell's
paly vgo Bells py you got to keep your
fats low you you can't have high
fats you don't want to eat table sugar
you don't want to eat cotton candy at
the
fair but you but you want to have fruit
which is really good for Bell's
paly you want to have sweet potato
really good for Bell's paly incredible
actually regular potatoes are even
better for excuse me for Belle's
paly talking so fast here excuse
me so regular potatoes are really good
for Bell's paly amazing for Bell's paly
because they're so loaded with a a
bioactive lysine one that's so strong
and so powerful that a weapon it's a
weapon against Bells paly lene take a
lot of lene too take capsules of line
Plus have a few
potatoes you know that's the kind of
thing you do you don't have eggs and
potatoes because the eggs will feed the
virus while you're trying to kill off
the virus and yes you want to kill off
the virus you want to get the right zinc
if you have any concerns you go to about
what supplements are best what lysine's
the best you go to my supplement
directory on medicalmedium.com and
that's not a ploy to sell you vitamins
cuz I don't sell sell vitamins I don't
have a vitamin line I don't sell you
vitamins I don't I don't suck you into a
radio show to try to sell you a vitamin
it's a directory to take you to a place
that actually tells you hey this not
tells you but it's it's we telling you
this is what I would use if I had Bell's
paly this is what I would use it's this
lysine it's you know it's this vitamin C
it's this so um medical medium.com and
look for that and if you're comfortable
with what you got already and you're
comfortable with something you have like
who might have changeed that just then
if you think it works or feel good it
feels like it's working use it um but
yeah yeah you want to have foods that
actually are weapons against viruses so
you don't get the Bell paly back or you
can shorten its duration licorice Root's
incredible for knocking down Bell's py
licorice fruit lemon balm those two are
great for knocking down knocking down
Bell's paly I like kumin that's a great
one for knocking down Bell's paly that's
a great one right right there okay
Elderberry is actually helpful too for
knocking down Bell's
paly all right so you got the zinc
lysine Elderberry you got the licorice
root you got the lemon
balm okay you can you can do these to
really help with bells py monol Lauren
monolaurin Now coconut oil you can eat
all the coconut oil you want you're not
going to get the monolaurin that you
need so you have to you have to get um
you have to get a
supplement so monol laurin's really good
I like golden seal for helping to knock
down Belle's py too the shingles virus I
like golden seal little little stin of
golden seal go on it for two weeks then
take a break for two weeks go on it
again for two weeks take a break for two
weeks talk to your practitioner on some
dosages maybe your practitioner is
really liberal with dosages and can fill
you out and know what you need and what
you don't need and that's really helpful
too and that's what's amazing that's
what's amazing out
there so these are some of the things
you can use I like B12 because B12 the
right kind of B12 the B12 that I've been
fortunate enough to introduce to
everybody to get the to get that going
finally a trend that's that's in the
favor of someone so a trend where Dino
Sil kabalan and methyl kabalan both
joined is the actually way to use is
what you really need to use for B12 for
neurological problems Spirit taught me
that many many years ago and I had to
wait for that to be developed by
Geniuses out there in the
world and so you know so many good
things an alternative medicine I know I
rip apart the bad things but there's so
many good things it's not even funny
it's incredible so the B12 you use the
right kind of B12 every day that's
important right there because it helps
restore the nerves because the nerves
get so they're so stressed out it's
unbelievable because they're so stressed
out from the shingles
virus so that's another great thing to
use I like Spina because it gets rid of
heavy metals that the shingles virus
likes to feed off of so I like the heavy
metal detox smoothie always always offer
you know because it helps get the metals
out and it's a gentle one it's so gentle
but effective God that's what we
want so that's really helpful too hup is
a good herb hup that's a good antiviral
time time tea time water that's good
oregano capsules that's good for uh
Belle's
paly oregano capsules it's another one
there so we got we got different options
we can use as antiviral
to um really help with Bell's
paly and sometimes it doesn't even take
too much catclaw is a great one too for
Bell's paly I love cats claw for
shingles first of all shingles the
shingles virus is responsible for Lyme
disease all the herpetic viruses are
responsible for limes disease Lyme
disease I talk about that in book one
you could read the
chapter and um that's the real respon
that's the real responsible group for
lime that's why cats claw actually helps
lime
patients that's why it helps lime
patients something I've been
recommending cats claw going back 30
plus years for people with lime and then
some that didn't have to to live in the
lime trap of misinformation forever and
they've been freed long long ago I feel
so bad for people that don't know about
the real lime information the truth and
they just don't know because the the the
airwaves are saturated with
misinformation on
lime and yeah sure but you know people
get mad they get the pitchforks out and
they get their torches and they throw
stones because they're mad because
because they you know they there's so
much information on Lime that's so
that's so crazy that they don't know who
to believe what to believe but I I wrote
a chapter in medical medium book one and
it's the viruses that cause the symptoms
the lime is neurological because viruses
cause the neurological problems I don't
care who what what lab what is saying
what that's what causes the neurological
problems in Lime cat's claw works
because cats is in is is
antiviral I love it for Belle's
paly so that's a great one
there so I mean there's a lot of things
you can do foodwise you got a lot of
secret weapons in food it's unbelievable
what you can do with
food any fruit any fruit's a weapon
against a virus I'm going to tell you
that right now phytochemicals and fruit
are antiviral many different fruits are
antiviral Al something to think about
leafy greens very good any kind of leafy
green is antiviral to some extent fruit
is probably more so antiviral but leafy
greens are to some extent there's
there's a lot of great stuff in
food I mean look if you're an animal
protein lover you just need to know fine
it won't
feed it won't feed a shingles virus
causing Bell's paly but if you eat too
much animal protein while you have
Bell's paly you get too much anim animal
fat which thickens up the blood and it
doesn't allow oxygen to get to the
nerves to help and it doesn't allow your
immune system to get to the nerves to
help get rid of the Bel py fast if
you're eating too much chicken too much
lean chicken and too much lean meat and
whatever there's still so much fat in it
got to be cautious you got to lower your
portions if you're an animal protein
lover there's nothing in animal protein
that's antiviral that's not me against
animal protein I'm just telling you you
can still eat it and you can keep it in
your diets but there's nothing antiviral
in animal protein against a virus
there's just nothing there that there
there's nothing there now look if you're
saying oh he's bias against meat eaters
no if you're a vegan or a
vegetarian if you're a vegetarian
there's nothing antiviral in Dairy and
nothing antiviral in eggs it's even
worse because eggs and dairy feed
viruses a piece of grass-fed lean meat
might not feed viruses so much it could
feed a little if the fat content gets
too high in the body then the viruses
could they could just they could they
can proliferate so that's true but but
eggs and dairy are
worse and then what if you're a vegan
and you're eating nothing but just white
bread all the time you're eating that
star bought white bread and you're
eating you know whatever that kind of
thing all the time but you're staying
vegan but you're eating tons of white
bread that white
bread there's nothing in there to to
kill a virus there's nothing in there to
kill a virus see I'm not picking on one
diet but in fruits and vegetables and
leafy greens and herbs and spices
everything I list in lifechanging Foods
the book life-changing foods and many of
the things I list in book one and many
of the things I list in thyroid healing
are antiviral that's the whole
point that's the whole point right
there just seeing you know 40 years ago
Spirit telling me when I was a little
kid over 40 years ago Spirit telling me
about antiviral and me trying to express
that to somebody just see it's like they
thought they they thought they thought I
had four
heads but here I am S 8 n years old and
I'm trying to tell
somebody about
antiviral and I'm trying to tell them
about antiviral I'm trying to tell them
about foods that will stop viruses I'm
trying to tell them that their condition
is viral you should see you should have
seen what happened it was like their
eyeballs popped out of their head they
like went someplace they like went out
of body they went out of
body I mean people they don't know what
I've done and what I've been through
they can't even imagine it's so funny
because there's a lot of different
people psychics and different mediums
and stuff like that you know out there
now it's great I'm glad we need as many
healers as we can but I'm going to tell
you right now you should have seen you
should have seen me as a child telling
somebody this is the virus you have you
have hhv6 this is what it's causing you
have hhv6 this is what it's causing and
you need an antiviral food and this is
what you need it was like it was like a
flying saucer came out of the sky landed
right there made a burn mark right in a
right right on the ground in front of
them and they like went out of body cuz
there was just it wasn't even
computable and even
seriously
so right all right so look the bottom
line is I guess the point I'm trying to
make as I'm telling you telling you
these things the point I'm trying to
make is that yes we want to do
antivirals both in herbs both in spices
and everything else and you can do
garlic is anti viral I love garlic and
onions for Belle's paly it's incredible
what does it do it go it it it it
defends you against the jingles virus it
knocks its Army down it drops its Army
down it lowers its neurotox
the neurotoxin that saturates the trial
nerves and the different nerves the the
fascial nerves and it saturates those
nerves that neurotoxin and it causes it
to get defunct and it causes it so boom
you got the droop like wow we got the
droop darn it's it's
there I know people that have come to me
over the years and they're like oh thank
God I got got got to talk with you and
this is before I I I put the books out
and all that stuff a years ago and they
me say thank God I found you because
I've had this Spell's policy for a long
time I said how long how long you had
it and and and they would say and they
would say you know I've had it for 10
years I've had this trp for 10 years and
I was like oh my God 10 years yeah you
can have Bell's py for 10 years you can
have it for 15 years you can have the
droop and can stay there your droop can
go
away but but if you've been through for
10 years 12 years 15 years let's make it
go away let's get the antivirals let's
get the right Foods I like the celery
juice because it gets special mineral
salts mineral salts that are
undiscovered to the nerve endings to the
nerve
endings that's a great one right there
do the heavy metals you know heavy metal
smoothie get all the heavy metals out of
the nerves and out of the brain and out
of all that area but out of the jaw
people get all the fillings be cautious
more Bells paly events happen for people
who get the Mercury fillings taken out I
can't say this
enough okay I can't say this enough if
you got the Mercury fillings and you
really want them out do not get them out
all at once do not get I repeat do not
get them out all at once do not put a
load like that on your nervous on your
immune system get one one out at a time
one out at a time space them out if you
really want them out if I I don't have
any Mercury
feelings and um and you know I've been
lucky I've been blessed I've never had a
cavity in my life so I've never had a
filling or my teeth have never been
drilled in my life and I've never had a
cavity and you know and I and honestly
that's not genetics that's not genetics
I promise you that that's not genes that
Spirit when I was a young age telling me
to bring in some foods at a young age to
get rid of mercury and heavy metals that
were inherently our already in me so you
know so that wouldn't happen number one
and also to to to to make sure you you
mineralizing the teeth so I was lucky
because Spirit was like you know what
you're not going to be eating eggs
you're going to be eating this and i' be
like eating some weed out in the lawn I
don't mean dandelion I'm talking like
some you know just bizarre weed like red
clover I'd be chewing and spitting out
red clover
tops you know that's what I would be
doing you know chewing up red Clover
tops and spitting them out and spirit
told me look that's going to actually
help your gums do red clover tea for any
kind of viruses it's antiviral for for
viruses when you do the te's do the red
clover the red clover the flower the
flower do
that you know or the
plantain or the sea plantain I mean I
was I was down on the beach pulling sea
plantain which looks nothing like
plantain you got to be careful eating
that stuff that stuff is just wired up I
mean you can only eat so much of that
and I was and I would eat some of that
that had so many minerals in it but
it'll it'll get you if you eat too much
it's like fiddlehead greens oh my god
I've never been so sick in my life from
overeating fiddlehead greens I was on I
was laying on the floor
crying after you know going through the
woods with spirit and eating T you know
was spirit said look these are
fiddlehead greens you eat these and I
was in the woods I said okay so I ate a
couple and I was like that is delicious
in incredible and spirit said ho ho ho
ho don't eat too many gobbling them
down eating them eating them eating them
eating them eating them fiddle had
greens filled my belly fiddle had greens
I was so sick so sick some of those wild
foods are so potent so intense you just
got to be real easy with them real easy
with
them all right so you know we're coming
to the end of our show
coming to the end of the show um
remember you know that's what it's about
it's antiviral you know go into book one
look at the shingles chapter look at
some of the antiviral supplements even
go to EP Epstein bar supplements some of
those really helpful really helpful um
they are and thyroid healing thyroid
healing is is just a great book overall
because it it'll give you so much
information on on viruses in general
they really arm you arm you not just to
protect your thyroid but to protect
other things other things you can heal
you will heal you can get rid of old
Bell's paly meaning if you've had it for
a long time and you can get rid of new
Bell's poliy and you can prevent Bell's
poliy you can do it you can do
it you can do it there's no question no
doubt about it okay so I want you to
know that
um so listen take one step at a time
incorporate the foods when you can bring
in cucumbers bring in tomatoes cucumbers
and tomatoes make a cucumber and tomato
salad throw in some cilantro put in some
parsley parsley's
antiviral get some Rosemary get some
fresh Rosemary dice it up put it on top
of a salad Rosemary is great for Belle's
paly fantastic for Belle's paly Rosemary
that's an amazing one all on its own do
some Sage put some Sage on your food get
as many antivirals as you can remember
you can do the hup tea you can do that
it's a great anti we talked about the
golden seal it's incredible for it the
lemon balm do a little elderberry you
can do these Mullen Leaf get the Mullen
Leaf tincture get the Mullen Leaf
tincture get the right one go to go to
my directory or you're going to get one
with alcohol or some kind of bogus one
you get the right Mullen Leaf Mullen
Leaf is just
incredible for Bell's paly could you
talk to your doctor talk to your
practitioner whoever it is and you you
can do three four ask ask your your
practitioner if you can do three four
dropper FS twice a day of Mullen Leaf to
get rid of your Bell's paly or help some
with Bell's paly very helpful Mullen
Leaf is a great
one and El
glutamine is actually really helpful for
Bell's py too Al glutamine turmeric is
helpful curcumin is helpful like the
monel Lauren I mentioned earlier too
that's helpful too so you know these are
these are simple they're easy breezy you
don't have to go into a jungle you know
well you got cats claw that's available
but you don't have to go into a jungle
searching out some magical you know you
know some magical herb some magical
jungle weed to try to get rid of R your
Bell's py it's a simple crew of
antivirals plus antiviral
Foods okay just know that I stand behind
you one day at a time I'm with you check
out thyroid healing check it
out I promise you you won't be let down
when you start reading that one and um
and then know that I stand behind you
100% And I got your back well spirit's
got your back and spirit wants me to
have your back too and you take one day
at a time you know there's nothing worse
than getting hit with symptoms and not
knowing what's going on and it and I
promise I'm going to do everything I can
to bring that to the surface the truth
and the and the information so you're
lost and you're not searching so you're
not suffering because one of the things
is you have to know what's wrong and you
have to know what to do with it there's
half the battle know what's wrong know
how to fix it and that's what we got to
do this gift that was given to me is for
you and I'm going to continue to keep on
putting out information helping in every
way I can I love you I want you to take
care of
yourself be gentle on yourself have
compassion to yourself bless you God
bless you take care bye-bye