[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now
and I'm serious about that I am folks
listen everybody's got a symptom these
days I'm going to tell you right now I
mean you know it right are you seeing it
out there I mean it's not just their
loved ones and friends it's everyone Ian
if someone doesn't have in attention
deficit problem if someone doesn't have
an ache and a pain if someone doesn't
have a headache if someone doesn't have
you know blurry blurry eyes if someone
doesn't have a migraine if someone
doesn't have tingles and numbness or
something or anxiety or depression or a
funny tummy what about a funny tummy you
know this why call it a funny tummy
someone's got some kind of gut health
issue you know intestinal tract problem
IBS you know something like that or just
a funny tummy but the bottom line is
everybody's dealing with symptoms out
there folks I'm seeing it you guys must
be seeing it huh I mean seriously right
are you seeing it because it's going on
you know I remember I mean decades ago I
remember it was it wasn't like this it
just wasn't there were people that were
not well there were sick people out
there we've always had that I know that
we've always had that for quite a while
but I'm serious about this something's
changed something's changed like
drastically just in the last 15 years
just in the last 15 years changed
unbelievably literally from from night
and day where all of a sudden now
chronic illness just jumped Leaps and
Bounds we're talking about Leaps and
Bounds over and over I mean really
really it's gotten bad and I got to be
honest about it I have to be truthful
about it cuz you know I got your back
and and it's all about making sure you
have answers it's all about making sure
you have advanced information and
ironically enough I want I want more
advanced information out there you guys
I want more of it out there it's just
not there I just got to be open about it
it's just not there I saw somebody come
out with the latest information on gut
health recently and and it was it it was
bad and I'm not just saying that I want
it to be good I want it to be good I was
talking to somebody the other day and
they said to me they said to me look you
seem to be negative about other
information out there it's not about
being negative I said it's the
information just isn't there it's
recycled it's from 20 years ago it's
from 30 years ago it's from ma from 1987
in gut health it's
recycled and and it and then you know
and thrown into that recycled bit they
talk about some you know fermentation
and some different probiotics and gut
biome but that's not answers I'm sorry
but that's not answers and you know when
someone's struggling and they got Celiac
and they got you know IBS and they got
you know intestinal tract problems and
crones and they got colitis or they got
all kinds of other different symptoms
that information is just not answers the
same thing with Hashimoto thyroiditis
all these experts out there now you guys
believe it you guys are the experts now
because you're tuned into the show
you're tuned into the show you're tuned
into Spirits books you know I'm going to
tell you and then when someone's an
expert about a thyroid problem and all
the different things and triggers and
all the stuff but they don't even know
what causes the thyroid problem to begin
with they don't even know what causes
Hashimoto's thyroiditis to begin with
and they put literature out there and no
one even knows the the cause and you're
going to hear the cause here on this
show you better believe it anybody
tuning in just now and this is your
first time here at the show that's
what's going to happen you're going to
hear the causes the real truth behind
all these different illnesses and
everything we talk about because the
information out there is literally
antique shopping I know I said that
before I'm probably driving you guys
crazy you know you really everybody out
there you guys really have a good
tolerance actually to hear me say you
know a couple of things over again so
thank you for just hanging in there with
me all right I can't help it but you
know that's what's happening now is the
information that's coming out on the
internet and in books and stuff it's
like antique shopping may as well just
go and buy yourself an old lamp I know I
said that before okay go let's change it
around let's go out and buy yourself an
old trunk or an old you know table
because you know in an antique shop
somewhere some Barn store somewhere you
know listen uh the bottom line is when
it comes down to Healing we have to have
the information we have to know what
causes that thyroid problem we have to
know what causes our gut problem we have
to know what's causing our depression
and our anxiety and what's causing our
fatigue it has to be known it can't be
like oh it must be adrenals or cortisols
off no we need to know that it's a viral
fatigue we need to know things are
happening out there we need to know
what's behind fibromyalgia we need to
know behind you know rheumatoid
arthritis you know Cushings we need to
know what's behind Addison we need to
know all all these things have to be
figured out exent psoriasis list goes on
and on and on Lupus lime yep lime the
ultimate confusion of all time okay so
listen life is precious we don't have 10
years for the answers 20 years for the
answers we need to know now and I stand
behind you and that's the whole point
and we're going to get down to the
bottom of all this stuff let's talk
about today a little bit Today's Show is
about the healing powers of fruits ooh I
said a swear word right there there hey
I said a swear word was it bleeped out
you guys I said fruit was fruit bleeped
out because if this was anywhere else if
this was anywhere else on some kind of
alternative medicine Forum or even
conventional medicine Forum now it's
even getting to that point um fruit's a
a bad word that's a swear word that's a
naughty word so did you hear the bleep
okay listen the point is is that we're
talking about fruit today and the heing
powers of it because fruit is literally
crucified and that's what's going on
right now and it has to change it has to
change because fruit is healing it has
power it holds the magic it holds
medicine what I'm trying to tell you is
you just have to eat some fruit because
no one's eating fruit and we're going to
talk about the power of fruit and what
it's doing so I don't care what what
belief system you adopt it you know what
diet strategy you adopted from new
fangle diets out there from whatever it
might be okay you know what I'm talking
about you know about all the different
diets and Trends okay whatever you adopt
it cool fine I'm just telling you now
you better bring some fruit in there I
don't care what it is you better bring
some fruit in there and there's a reason
there's a reason you guys I'm serious
about this so I mean look everybody
who's listened to this know knows about
my life a little bit it started at age
four and I Heard a Voice just like
you're hearing a voice now me talking
just like a friend talks to you it's
from an outside source and I've been
given the gift to hear it from an
outside Source that's different than
what's out there what it means is the
information comes through whether I like
it or not since age four that diagnosed
my grandmother and also is given
information throughout the decades to
help tens of thousands of people heal
and that's a little bit about my
background but listen you guys we're
going to go into Fruit you know fruit is
a scary word right now and I me that I
know I K I was kidding around saying hey
look did you hear the bleep cuz I said a
swear and fruit really is a bad word
today it really is I'm serious the what
what comes to your mind when you hear
fruit is it sugar is sugar that comes to
your mind where did you hear that you
heard that from somewhere and if you're
into Health on any level and you're into
alternative medicine and you're into any
kind of medicine You're Going to Hear
Too Much Sugar's bad that's what you're
going to hear well I got news for you
okay because this is about your health
this is about your life this is about
your organs inside your body functioning
giving you Vitality to get take you all
the way to the end of this lifetime this
is about recovering from illnesses and
diseases that people don't even have a
clue to what causes these things to
begin with so why do we have such big
experts out there claiming you shouldn't
eat fruit because it has too much sugar
when they don't even know what causes
the most basic things like sibo you know
small intestinal overgrowth BAC
bacterial overgrowth they don't even
know what causes the basic things of thy
hypothyroidism they don't even know what
causes colitis we know but everybody's
an expert saying fruit's bad when nobody
knows that causes any of the chronic
illnesses the hundreds and hundreds of
chronic illnesses that we're going to
cover over the next year on this show
and you're going to become the expert
you're going to know more than anybody
out there that deems thems some kind of
expert and is on the circuit or talking
or writing books or literature you're
going to be the expert way better than
any of them it's you you're the one
because you're getting the information
right here you're actually getting the
real information and nothing stands in
the way of that so you can help people
and help yourself and and and and apply
assistance and be there and be really
entrenched in the real truth and that
makes you the expert
okay so it's not about and I got to tell
you something it's not about saying oh
you know all these people they're not do
these experts whatever they're not doing
good it's not it they good people and
they're working hard it's just that this
is coming from a different Source this
is so the fog is lifted so we can see
the light this is so you can heal this
is so you can become that Authority
because that's really what's going on
you guys you're you're becoming the
authorities in healing you know just
heard a um I Heard a little story on
Instagram of somebody in the line not in
line but they were they were at Whole
Foods or they were at one of the health
food stores and they were they're
picking out celery they were getting
celery okay off the shelf all right and
someone else was had a whole bunch of
celery too and they were taking celery
off the shelf and they looked at each
other and one of them one of them said
hey wait a minute is that for juicing
the other said yeah are you on the
medical medium celery juicing
protocol and and the other person was
yes I am we're both doing the medical
medium celery juice because it is that
lifechanging celery juice is incredible
so you're becoming the expert is what
I'm trying to say look at that and then
you know more than anyone else I even
hear the health food stores are starting
to boot up and just do celery juice
because of you guys because you guys are
spreading the information out there and
they're literally just offering celery
juice Now by itself never before done so
now when you go to a health food store
and you say I want straight celery juice
they don't look at you like you have 10
heads or you're an alien from outter
space it's changing as we speak because
you guys and I love you for it I have to
tell you this and when it comes down to
fruit that's got to change too that is
has to change too really important okay
look the average American okay you guys
the average American consumes 100 lb of
straight can sugar a year okay you think
you think that everybody you know would
say hey that's not possible this is the
average American that is health
conscious this isn't the average
American that's not health conscious the
average American that's not healthc
conscious consumes 400
lbs of over close to 400 lb of table
sugar a year 4 100 lb okay people that
are health conscious people that are
like eating salads and having chicken
and and you know being cautious and
they're having that one muffin when they
do or they're at a friend house and they
have that one canoli whatever is they're
eating 100 lb of straight sugar a year
and they're having that one slice of
pizza where the tomato sauce has cane
sugar all laced in there and they don't
even know it and they're having this one
slice of just just what seems to be like
a healthy slice of pizza whatever it is
it's 100 lb a year okay of straight
sugar just just just know that all right
now check this out right now in this
time okay Americans eat an average of 80
lounds of fruit a year 80 lounds of
fruit a year okay that's that's that's
average Americans now that's
not this is what's crazy those average
Americans that are eating 80 lbs of
fruit a year I'm not talking about
people in the Alternative Health you
know like movement they're eating 20 lb
10 lb of fruit a year 5 lb of fruit a
year two pounds of fruit a year the
people that are actually now all hooked
into the alternative Vibe right now and
they're hearing no fruit no fruit no
fruit no carbohydrate bad for you bad
for you just protein protein only
protein and a few vegetables that crowd
is eating 2 lbs of fruit a year to 10 at
best I mean that's said best that's
being generous but the average
American is eating 80 lb of fruit a year
let me tell you what 80 lbs of fruit a
year is it's a case of apples it's a
case of apples okay in a whole year a
case of apples it's 50
apples it's 50 apples I'm going to say
it again I can't help it it's like I
can't open right okay listen hang in
there listen let's let's get the seat
bels on cuz this is going to be this is
going to be a ride this is going to be a
real ride listen um 50 apples okay how
many days of the year is there what this
365 or something right 365 days a year
okay all right 50 apples and that's the
most it gets in the average
American so 80 lbs of fruit at best a
year think about that right now and
guess how much sugar that is is
virtually nothing because apples are
water pulp fiber pectin minerals
vitamins
nutrients and course of course I said
fiber I'll say it again fiber again
because different forms of fiber in the
apple and when it's all said and done
including the seeds and the core in the
center and the seeds when it's all said
and done there's very little sugar in an
apple very very little sugar and an
apple that we have to understand see
what's happening is we're on a trend
right now to take down fruit I'm telling
you right now I'm serious about this
there's a trend to destroy fruit okay
and to take it down it's literally
novelty as it's sitting in the store now
not a lot of people are buying it they
throw it out by the hordes in all the
health food stores and conventional
stores it's thrown out by the hordes I'm
going to tell you guys right now okay so
we have to start eating it so they're
not throwing it out that's a whole
another game that's that's swept in the
carpet that's a dirty secret I'm telling
you a dirty secret right now that the
stuff is just thrown out in hordes
because no one's buying it
anymore being straight up okay so let's
talk about that a little bit let's talk
about what's going on with it first of
all University professors are teaching
students not to eat fruit anymore
University professors are teaching
students not to eat fruit anymore I'm
not talking about every University
Professor okay I got I got a family
friend who's a university professor and
and he said to me I'm not teaching that
which is going I said yeah I know but
have you heard of it he goes yeah I have
kind of heard of that I had I have but
I'm not doing it Anthony but I have
heard of it yes but that's not where I
got the information I'm getting that
information from students I'm getting
that information from students just so
you know that that University professors
are teaching students not to eat fruit
anymore I just want you to know that
right now and and then and and I know i'
I've told you this before recently I
told you this before but in in one one
of the biggest alternative um um
conferences medicine alternative uh
medicine conferences they start off
throwing a banana against the wall
they've done that I don't know if they
do at every conference I I have to be
honest about that too I don't know if
it's everyone but I know it was a bunch
of them and and that was a big thing
going on and that was happening on and
off in just the last six seven years
that was part of where this whole thing
start at the downslide on the fruit so
is this information important at all I
mean yeah it's really important there
big reasons for this because without
fruit we're going to be in big trouble
really big trouble without fruit we're
going to go back into the the vitamin C
deficiencies the Deep vitamin C
deficiencies the Deep ones the Deep ones
that cause all that kind of stuff that
used to happen when we l we we had a
lifespan that was like age
40 um lifespan of age 45 cuz we died of
scurvy and and and squalor and and and
and rickets and infections and you know
disease and leprosy because there 's no
vitamin
C and so you know and it gets us in
trouble cuz vitamin C runs everything it
runs your
adrenals it cleanses the body it
detoxifies you it it detoxifies you
there's people out there that can't
detox because they have no vitamin C
Reserves at all there's no Reserve
there's no vitamin C Reserve you guys
where does vitamin C come from it comes
from fruit whether anybody likes it or
not out there I don't care I don't care
who it is who they they are if they
don't understand that those deep
reserves of vitamin C are critical For
Your vitality for your thriving for you
being able to handle the quickening
coming up which means things are
happening faster faster and faster
people are getting sicker faster than
ever before in history so all of this
going on it's the vitamin C reserves
that stops cancers prevents cancers
halts cancers you know protects us on
all kinds of levels with chronic illness
it's the Deep levels of vitamin C and
there's one other thing and that's this
is related to vitamin C and it's
antioxidants antioxidants stop you from
dying we oxidize that's what aging is
oxidizing you know I hear even in
longevity in the longevity world out
there they're like anti fruit in the
longevity world they're anti fruit in
the longevity World seriously you guys
got to know this not not the entire
longevity world that's out there you
know in The Healing Arts not the not the
entire group of them I know a longevity
guy that's like no I'm totally into
Fruit I'm believe me I get it I get it
Anthony I get the antioxidants you don't
have to tell me I got it and so not
everybody in longevity but but the
majority and the stars of longevity are
anti fruit that means anti- longevity
did you know that that means
anti-longevity
I'm serious about that I'm not fooling
around I mean that because guess what
guess where the antioxidants come from
the antioxidants come from fruit and
we're only eating a little bit of it now
we're being told to stop it yeah I'm
pretty passionate about this one there's
a reason this is going to hurt us this
is going to hurt us this is going to
knock the fertility rates right down INF
fertility is going to be just just you
know thriving
infertility and this is going to hurt us
in all kinds of different levels you
know our children's brains are not going
to be able to develop the way they need
to because they need certain pieces
certain you know pieces of the puzzle
that are in fruits we're going to talk
about all these things that are going to
go wrong because of this and like I said
the longevity fronts anti fruit they
really are because someone someone
messed up and no one wants to admit a
mess up because you know why we got all
kinds of what is it the ego thing or
whatever that is that's out there you
know someone said to me the other day
they said well sounds like you got an
ego I go I don't know if I do or don't
all I know is I care about people in
their health and their life and I care
about their well-being and I care if
they're really sick or not cuz I get it
I've seen it I know what it's like to
suffer I've watched it I feel it and I
get it so you can call it what it is but
I'm going to call it what you think it
is but I'm going to tell you what I
think it is and I care and that's that's
what I can't what I really you know I
really feel what someone has gone
through and seen what they've gone
through and I know you guys have too
someone was telling me that when you
know when they're around people that are
suffering they they can they can really
feel it in a way that it gets it brings
them to tears when they're around people
that are suffering with symptoms or
around a loved one that has symptoms and
they're struggling and it brings them to
tears they feel it you know they feel
that that feeling inside I know what
that is I I understand understand it and
it's about it's about look reclaiming
our health moving forward rising out of
the ashes and and getting healthier and
that's that's what I stand behind and
the thing is like the longevity thing as
I was talking about so it means
basically the longevity stars of today
are saying don't eat fruit they're
saying we don't believe in longevity but
we're going to use the word and the term
yeah I know it's harsh I'm saying this
but I don't care I don't care it's
either what hold it back and not tell
you guys what's going on out there so
just what I'm worried some longevity
starts going to come out and start you
know saying stuff I mean the bottom line
is it's about you it's not about them
it's not about you know it's not about
what's going it's about you and here's
the deal we oxidize every day that's how
the aging process works we're
oxidizing bottom line oxidizing means
we're dying okay and you can turn that
around you can turn that around with
antioxidants that's the one word
that became pop became pop culture in
alternative medicine that is real it
really is real so I
congratulate
congratulate the scientists that was
like oh wait a minute there's wait a
minute there's something in here that's
stopping oxidation inside this lemon
wait a minute um I could see it in the
lab in in the lab report there's an
antioxidant here you know I I
congratulate that guy okay that did that
because it's that important that
critical so what do antioxidants do they
stop your brain from
rotting that's what they do and they're
in fruits they're in all the fruits
we're going to talk about some fruits
too just just hang in there for this
ride but the antioxidants stop your
brain from dying it stops your brain
from
rotting okay it stops you from getting
Alzheimer's it stops you from getting
dementia it stops you from losing your
mind it stops you from suffering on all
levels of life it is the thing that
keeps our hips from rotting it keeps you
so we don't get hip replacements all the
time antioxidant stop us from losing our
hips it stops us from getting to have to
get our knees
replaced you know and I understand that
I support that if someone's hip is going
and we have to replace it and and it's
gone too far I'm I'm I stand behind
technology today and surgical procedures
and surgeons and the work we've done in
medicine I stand behind that
100% I know surgeons that are doing
great and mean everybody's working hard
but the antioxidants stop more of that
from happening stop more of the
breakdown of the body on all levels and
where does that come from where does it
come from it comes from fruit you guys
comes from fruit you believe it I keep
on saying that bad word again over and
over again I hope I'm not going to get
in trouble all right so here's something
that's really funny right now okay in
the uh the Forefront of alternative
medicine one of the things they're
saying now is that fruit causes a fatty
liver fruit causes liver problems or a
fatty liver I can't even begin I I don't
won't even waste your time how about
that I won't even waste your time cuz
your time matters to me and I'm not even
going to waste it on that one okay so
it's not pork that makes makes a fatty
liver no it's not it's
fruit all right you know I'm being
sarcastic of course but no fruit doesn't
cause a fatty liver it stops a fatty
liver it reverses a fatty liver it re it
brings back your liver it stops
hepatitis C it stops scarring of the
liver scar tissue of the liver fruit
literally changes your liver health and
right now liver cleanses are abound and
oh it's all about your liver well you
better be bringing in a lot of fruit
than it is if if that's what it is you
better be bringing in a lot of fruit all
the different liver cleanses and
everything else it's all for the liver
fruit cleanses the liver more than
anything else does on the planet Earth
right
now and it's being shunned do you see
like what's happening here all right
maybe it's just me maybe hey maybe it's
I'm in the Twilight Zone and it's just
me and I'm caught in the Twilight Zone
right now and everybody's right and
fruit's bad no they're wrong fruit is
amazing that's going to change your life
it's going to help you live and it's
going to help you thrive and everything
I'm going tell you one more thing right
now everybody's into the brain right you
guys are into the brain you know there's
brain books abound and there's brain
health this and brain health that right
totally I'm going to tell you right now
without fruit the brain shrinks it
shrinks because the brain is not made up
of fat it's a very micro small
percentage of Omega oils that are in the
brain the majority of the brain is made
of glycogen storage that's a thick gluey
carbohydrate and that's what conducts
electricity it's a carbohydrate in the
brain the brain is made out of
carbohydrates glycogen and fruit keeps
that glycogen stored in the brain so
your brain does not
shrink you take away fruit out of your
life completely your brain slowly
shrinks nobody knows that that out there
yet okay you know and you're now an
expert okay you know more than the best
brain book out there right now in
alternative medicine you know more I
mean that's amazing okay that's amazing
you guys are incredible because you know
that now and you can that's the football
right there you know that's that's right
there you can pass that football along
to someone else and change somebody's
life and stop their brain from shrinking
and then you know what you think how it
change somebody's life I'll tell you why
cuz if you get somebody eating fruit and
they get into the habit and they bring
it in every day and it's in there every
day and twice a day three times a day
they're eating some fruit here's what
happens you stop Alzheimer's in their
life when they probably would have
gotten it there's a chance that that
person may have been an Alzheimer's
victim and that could have been their
demise way way down the road and you
just stopped it 30 years before it could
happen cuz you gave them a habit that
brought fruit into their life like the
wild blueberries like you know those
wild blueberries they are the ultimate
brain food of all time in history right
now on planet Earth is the wild
blueberry and it reverses not only
reverses brain diseases but it stops you
from losing you know your brain and
having it get corrosive and having heavy
metals wreak havoc and
oxidize oxidize the brain and cause of
memory loss and Alzheimer's and dementia
and and Parkinson's and everything else
that we that goes wrong in our brain and
wild blueberries stop that so when you
get somebody on fruit you get them on a
habit of it like yourself like yourself
and then you bump into somebody you're
like hey you really need to be doing
this fruit you don't know it but you
might have stopped them from getting
dementia 20 years down the road what
what a great thing is tell me that's not
a miracle it's a powerful Miracle want
to talk to you about eating fruit out of
season there's this big thing like you
eat in season and I I'm I'm all about
eating in season so if you're you know
if you got the farmers market and you
got the Farmers Market has some type of
fruit that's in that season like apples
or something it'll have that elevated
biotic I talk about all the time like in
my book medical medium right you guys
know the elevated biotic that's the
biotic no one else knows about that's
really Advanced and ahead of everything
else in the gut health books and I say
this so if you just tuned in and this is
your first show you know where to get
the information so you can heal and help
others because that's what it's about so
anyway you pick that apple right at the
farmer's
market and it's in season it's
incredible without a doubt but when
fruit goes out of season I don't want
you to stop eating fruit because it goes
out of season cuz I'm telling you right
now it's in season somewhere else
somewhere else on the planet it's in
season doesn't matter if it's shipped
it's in season somewhere
else okay and if you took a trip to to
France or you tri took a trip down to
you know Brazil or whatever it is and
there was a fruit in season there that
wasn't in season here are you not going
to eat it cuz it's not in season you're
going to eat it you're going to eat that
melon you're going to eat that mango
you're going to eat that papaya whatever
it is if it's in season over there
you're going to eat it well it's still
in season over there regardless of where
you are in the planet so don't fall
don't fall victim to that myth that's
been thrown out there where don't eat
anything that's out of season now so
just walk by the entire produce section
because it's all out of season just
don't don't don't do that okay that's
not good either it's a whole another
thing that's gone wrong out there so I
mean look the bottom line the bottom
line is we have to get more fruit into
our bodies and I'm going to tell you why
let's start cutting through this a
little bit all right this is fun this is
fun you guys relaxed you guys you guys
relaxed are you guys hanging in there
cuz we're going to go over some fruits
we're going to start with melons melons
let me tell you right now melons are the
mother's milk of the planet the mother's
milk okay they take no digestion at all
at all they're literally pre-digested
they have so many enzymes in there that
they don't need digestion at all on any
level your body does not have to even
digest it on any level your body
instantly digest it because it's already
digested it's pre-digested it's it's
that power ful and you know did you ever
hear about you know like intravenous
vitamins you guys have you ever have you
ever done that you did that have you
ever done that where you had like you
know intravenous vitamin C in
intravenous glutathione intravenous
Myers cocktail which is a
multivitamin well if you've ever done
that and you know that hey there's
there's you know there's something to be
said about that but let me tell you this
melons are equal to an
intravenous vitamin to getting IV
vitamins melons have a highly Active
water content binding on the poisons of
all kinds mold MotoX ands neurotoxins
from viruses like Epstein bar undigested
proteins ammonia you know ammonia
permeability the real problem behind you
know leaky gut the real problem behind
gut problems that nobody knows out there
the experts don't know ammonia
permeability
that whole thing Spirit brought to you
guys all of that gets absorbed by the
the the minerals the active water in
melon it's the ultimate detoxifier pulls
all the poison out of the body can even
pull radiation along with it because the
the content the water content in melon
is so grounded it's so grounding and so
bioactive and so
alive and it's filled with so many
electrolytes that it literally grabs
onto everything that shouldn't be in the
body and pulls it out of the body some
people say well I don't feel good when I
go on melon I got you know something
yeah I just don't feel that great when I
go on melon that's because it's pulling
so much garbage and so many toxins and
so much poison out of the body and
rushing it out of the kidneys you're not
going to feel that great it just tell
it's going to tell you you're that toxic
and then when you start feeling a little
bit better on melon you've gotten rid of
that much poison and you're that much
more vital and you're moving forward
that much
more melons have so much silica in it
you guys silica you know silica right so
much silica they restore joints
ligaments teeth bones that's the kind of
silica we're talking about and as far as
people that worried about kidney
problems and kidney function melons help
restore kidneys they give the kidneys an
ability to heal and you're talking about
diabetes and blood sugar issues melons
are amazing let's cut let's cut into
some of the conditions that melons do so
that melons offer okay Crohn's disease
colitis peptic ulcers melons are
incredible for these conditions okay
mystery infertility and I say mystery
because it's a mystery because all the
stuff is Mystery that's the whole point
in chronic illness it's mystery and and
this is about answers here this is this
is what it's about so we're all keeping
fruit away from people and we don't even
know what's causing these mystery
illnesses it's
unbelievable IBS okay irritable bowel
syndromes Barett
esophagus okay that's that's what melons
help embolisms stroke heart attack heart
disease liver disease of all kinds
therosis of the liver liver cancer
kidney disease breast cancer melons help
with breast cancer it helped with breast
cancer pancreatic cancer melons are
amazing for okay epilepsy septus I don't
know if you guys had known anybody with
any of this maybe maybe you maybe you've
experienced that hpylori you know the
hpylori infection you go to the doctor
and like oh you got hpylori we're
testing you for h pylori melons help get
rid of hpylori and these are just some
things and in the symptom World
alleviating constipation it helps lift
up low hydrochloric acid you know how
you know how I have you do in the celery
juice to lift up that hydrochloric acid
melons help lift it up too so don't be
afraid of melons they help with blood
sugar problems connective tissue
inflammation
Tremors chronic
dehydration bone density issues back
pain spasms
twitching blurry eyes inflammation food
sensitivities everything blood tox
toxicity that's what melons help and
then they even help on an emotional
level check this out you know and just
by the way you guys I have all this in
my life-changing Foods book and a ton
more so the lifechanging foods book you
got to get a copy of this thing and you
got to get it before those before those
babies are sold out cuz I'm really
getting nervous I just don't think
they're going to be that available now
and I keep on hearing that people are
really you know looking to try to get
this book right now so so check this out
emotional support if you're someone
that's easily frightened like you go
into that shaking thing where you're
like frightened or someone gives you bad
news and you're like shaking and you're
you know you're like you're gotting it's
not really anxiety it's it's like you
just got hit emotionally and you're you
kind of got the shakes and you don't
feel good about the bad news and you
feel like you're being under attack or
something that kind of vibe you know you
can't bear bad news good or you know
you're dealing with a heavy load and
you're emotionally sensitive or you got
like some PTSD where if someone gives
you some bad news every time you start
shaking a little bit all of this melons
can Aid they can Aid in this nervousness
they can help in this nervousness and
they can help heal this this reaction we
get over time but here's the deal you
got to eat a
melon you know and some people they say
I'll say to them like when's the last
time you had a melon and they were like
well I don't know I I had one and be
like when be like I don't know and they
start thinking about it was last year
was last year they had a melon let's hit
another one we got to get through this
lemons and limes are you guys doing the
like the lemon water squeeze it in a
glass of water I talk about it in my
book and everything and and that's been
around for a long time I've been pushing
the lemon water thing around for decades
I remember I was 6 years old and spirit
told me to have someone do lemon water I
was 6 years old if you go all the way
back then no one was talking about lemon
water in fact when you told somebody to
to actually do lemon water they looked
at you like you had 10
heads all right so you know that's the
same thing if you told somebody to be
weak gluten-free 35 years ago you know
40 years ago you tell somebody 40 years
ago to be weak gluten-free and yeah they
thought you just got off of a spaceship
so you know it's important to understand
that that you know I'm glad that we're
doing different things now but we got to
know where we were it's really amazing
um lemons and limes look you guys these
are the ultimate
hydrators ultimate hydrators I don't
know if hydrator is a word I'm just
telling you that it creates tremendous
amounts of hydration on a deep level
deep hydration from you know when we're
dealing with we walk around with chronic
dehydration all the time just so you
know like you could be dehydrated and so
you got to get the lemon lime water
going squeeze it in the glass get it
going every day do 16 ounces of lemon
lime water every day okay lemon and lime
trees send the roots deep into the Earth
extracting dozens of precious trace
minerals minerals that have everything
to do with neurotransmitters in our
brain neurotransmitters those are the
neurotransmitters that keep us thinking
talking walking
speaking it comes from these lemon and
lime these trees the the roots go deep
into the Earth and we we receive these
trace minerals when eating the lemon or
lime so we receive these trace minerals
when eating the lemon or lime or you
know or juicing it or putting it on food
or putting it in your guacamole or in
water okay and literally they're a
driving force for electrolyte production
you know there's electrolyte drinks out
there they're really not good okay I've
looked at them I'm like this is just
dead
this is just dead you know what your
electrolyte drink is you squeeze lime in
in a glass of water you squeeze squeeze
lemon in a glass of water okay and you
know don't be afraid of doing this don't
be afraid of doing this don't be scared
thinking you're putting sugar in your
water we can't think that cuz it's just
so off the game and it's not your fault
it's just in misinformation flying
around everywhere let's talk about the
power of lemons and limes let's do that
right now urinary tract infections UTI
incredible lemons and limes are
incredible for that staff infections you
guys worried about staff we're going to
talk about staff someday kidney disease
kidney stones gall stones pancreatitis
rosacea okay
conjunctivitis pneumonia you guys
dealing with any of this you should be
doing lemon water every day multiple
sclerosis which we know is Epstein bar I
talk about it in medical medium if you
don't have the medical medium book by
now I don't know what to say I don't I
don't have words okay so you know bottom
line I hope you have it and and get that
book so you can learn what causes
multiple scos and rheumatoid arthritis
and so much more okay so mystery
infertility lemons limes help with that
diabetes you know influenza um
everything that we deal with in today's
world all the way from you know herpes
simplex one and two acne from strep that
we tal we talked about in the strep show
cancers strep throat um
apib lemon lemon and lime I mean come on
and symptoms like you know I mean muscle
pain post-nasal drip earaches you know
digestive tummy discomfort lemon and
lime it's amazing for all of this
unquenchable thirst if you guys just
feel real thirsty you you're dehy
chronically dehydrated lemons and limes
help on all kinds of level they they
lift hydrochloric acid they help with
headaches they help with neurological
problems inflammation you name it and on
an emotional level check this out on an
emotional level okay you know lemons and
limes help with feelings of sadness
feeling of sadness so are you know
someone told me the other day they said
you know what Anthony I feel sad like at
4:00 4:00 at the end of the day it hits
me this deep sadness I said what you
have to do you have to squeeze lemon and
lime put do both of them right in a
glass 16 o and you drink that at 3:00 an
hour
before and they did it first day and
already reported that it's changing that
sadness because it lifts the spe Spirits
it lightens the heart it helps get that
Melancholy out of us in troubled times
that's the power of lemon and lime and
that's from Spirit that information you
guys that's from Spirit you can't find
that anywhere else it's from Spirit you
know so we have to give Spirit a little
credit here because it's not me
delivering this information I'm just a a
voice and a messenger from you know for
Spirit let's go into some more grapes
are you afraid of grapes that's that's
what I want to know are you afraid of
them because I hear about it all the
time oh grapes whoa grapes sugar too
much sugar and that's what I hear about
grapes is that there's just too much
sugar
involved and but that's not accurate
actually not accurate at all grapes
don't have a lot of sugar I'm being
straight about this they don't grape you
know what grapes have they have a
sourness to them
they have a sour nature to them okay
they have a tart nature if they had that
much sugar they wouldn't be tart they
wouldn't be slightly sour you wouldn't
detect any sour nature you wouldn't
detect any tartness to any Grape at all
if there was that much sugar in grape
there really isn't I mean of course if
you juice tons and tons and tons of
grape and then concentrate it then juice
it then reconcentrate and concentrate it
again you're going to then build up the
fructose and that's what you're going to
do but I'm talking about eating grapes
is what I'm talking about okay they're
misunderstood completely let's talk
about the power that grapes have the
antioxidant power that keeps our brain
healthy that
detoxes and revitalizes every organ you
know grapes kill off viruses help
eliminate radiation help even take out
heavy metals out of the gut and
liver they do they still have some power
to even remove some of the metals even
though I talk about the heavy metal
detox of choice that I like best bring
in some grapes too and don't be afraid
of them they are the anti-ager they are
the longevity anti-aging fruit as grapes
pick the one you want the darker the
grape the more medicine and the more
medicine quality the darker the grape
but pick the one you want anyway any
grape is powerful it eliminates mold
right out of the bloodstream right out
of the body mold exposure okay helps
reverse macular degeneration
hypertension okay kidney disease kidney
stones ADHD autism grapes are critical
for autism breast cancer diabetes
androme
endometriosis
PCOS okay you know what they tell
women to do with
PCOS ovarian cyst you know what they
tell them they tell them to eat eggs
they tell them to eat eggs the
authorities the best experts there are
tell our women you know in the world and
and young women and older women of any
kind of wom that has ovarian cysts and
any kind of PCOS to eat lots and lots of
eggs lots of eggs four to five eggs a
day all that does is grow more cysts and
more cysts and and actually grows them
out of control causes an absolute
disaster and that's the best information
out there you guys and when it comes
down to grapes grapes are lifechanging
for
PCOS and even PMS symptoms everything
that we deal with in that realm of
reproductive system fibroids grapes help
I see we're running at a time we got to
get through this a little bit um if
you're dealing with any kind of liver
issues grapes or Miracle work or
sluggish liver stagnant liver fatty
liver they're the ultimate cleansing
food okay so remember that um and you
know grapes pull out metals and
pesticides in a whole bit let's move on
to something else if we can let's move
on to um figs let's go let's hit the
figs we're going to have to all right so
figs get rid of parasites out of the
intestinal tract bacteria staff eoli a
cacus sio related bacteria like strep
anti antibiotic resistant bacteria like
strep figs get rid of it parasites any
kind of bug that's in the intestinal
tract that shouldn't be there figs get
rid of but here's the other thing here's
what you don't know nobody knows is that
the skin of the Fig feeds good bacteria
but also has a phytochemical in there to
kill bad bacteria so this information
that's in a fig tree that's thousands
thousands of years old in a fig tree
information that's designed to repel bad
bacteria but feed good bacteria when you
eat a fig remember that the power of
that's incredible fig stop IBS celiac
disease you know if you're not eating
some figs once in a while I mean you
don't have to eat a ton of them just eat
a handful of figs when they're out and
maybe some dried fig high quality dried
fix eat a couple of those once in a
while that's what you need to do um and
spirit says that you should eat your
figs in nine in numbers of nine that's
what Spirit tells me I have that in life
changing Foods book so you really have
to check this book out it's loaded with
this information plus so much more I
couldn't even cover it on these shows
it's not possible to cover it on these
shows there's no time to cover it
there's too much information but eat
your fig in number of nines that's nine
figs a day okay that because every fig F
tree every fig tree and I'm going to
give you a piece of information that
does that's not out there anywhere that
comes from Spirit every fig tree ends on
a nine meaning all the figs that grow on
that tree that fall off the tree that it
has in that season equal to number nine
in the
end never does it equal any other number
it never lands on a two it never lands
on a four it never lands on a five it
ends on a nine and that's the power of
the Fig tree and the universe and God to
know that that's what happens with fig
tree and then when you eat your figs in
nine in a number of nine it's
lifechanging and it helps reduce
literally so many of these illnesses we
deal with from everything from like
stomach pain nausea um cartilage issues
blurred vision enlarged spleen clogged
veins and arteries constipation itching
trigeminal neuralgia scar tissue in the
liver nerve inflammation app penic
issues
everything sinus issues that's the power
of the figs and an emotional level okay
emotional wounds formed from feeling
excluded did you guys ever feel like
you're excluded at all like did you ever
get that feeling well I felt like that
when I was a child for a little while
because having this gift and everything
I just couldn't do the reindeer games
couldn't play all the reindeer games
with everybody else because this gift
wasn't letting me I felt kind of
excluded for a little while when I was a
child
and then Spirit told me bring in figs
and it helps Aid that exclusion it helps
get you feeling better about that so
that's something to think about too is
that's the power we have coming to the
end of the show I thank you for just
being you know here with me right now I
love you for it thank you for spreading
the information blessings seriously from
my heart and soul to you you are
becoming an expert with health and I'm
realizing that and I see it I love you
dearly I believe in you I know what
you've been through check out medical
medium.com look for life-changing foods
and I'll see you next time take care
bye-bye