[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now as
I've always said who has 10 or 20 30
years to wait for answers to their
illnesses we don't have that time to
wait we need these answers because as
the time goes on as each year goes on
and we're not well and we're not feeling
good and we're struggling and battling
different symptoms we need the answers
we need to know we need to know now it's
going on and we can't wait for
literature that's 10 20 years behind 10
20 years behind to keep on circulating
over and over again even if it's got new
Frills and chills going on it's got a
little bit of flash going on so it looks
like it's changed up it's still the same
theories behind it and that's what's
amazing about the medical Medium show
because spirit's going to bring you
what's real what's now what you need to
heal how you can heal what we can do to
move forward together how we can not
just backtrack over and over again how
we can move forward instead and that's
what this show is about it's really
important to know that anybody knew that
just you know got on to the show just
now and listening and you know you
clicked on your device and you're
listening that's what this show is about
it's about getting you information
that's Advanced because if you're still
talking about leaky gut you don't even
know what leaky gut is because that's
the whole thing there's new new
literature coming out new books new
information new stuff on the internet um
coming out about leaky gut and it's
actually not accurate it's
misinformation it's old information
keeps on coming back at us but it gets
repackaged over and over again and even
when an idea is slightly new in the
health field it has an old baggage
attached to it like all the baggage like
your body's still attacking itself kind
of baggage where it's all your genes and
that's your problem and that's why
you're sick so you can't doing anything
about it it's that kind of stuff it's
just the old stuff or it's all in your
head still
and that you're you're you're fine and
it's all in your head and you look good
and you you look fine so what's wrong
with you because you look fine from the
outside so what can be wrong with you on
the inside and so all this old baggage
is attached to even new stuff coming out
every day and I'm waiting I'm waiting
for that to change and you it didn't so
spirit said it's time for you to start
doing something about it you have to
help people now on a wider basis on a WI
wider audience thank you for tuning in
thank you for listening um it's it's an
answer to my prayer knowing that you're
there so we can all work together
because technically what we're doing or
what's really happening you guys is
you're becoming the health expert you
are you're becoming the health expert
you're going to get better than me
you're going to get way better than me
because I'm just getting the information
from Spirit and I'm giving it to you I'm
messaging it over to you but what's
happening is you're getting good you're
taking your intuition that's right those
intuitive skills that you have that have
been there the whole time and then
you're taking this
information that's Advanced ahead of
time of research and science ahead of
time of what's out there now and In
Articles and books and internet and
feeds and everything else you're getting
information you're plugging it into your
intuitive nature and that's
strengthening it it's taking it there
and then you're assisting other people
without even realizing it sometimes
you're in the health food store and
you're like hey did you try the celery
juice did you know that the wild
blueberry is what really heals the
neurological system so if you got all
these problems the wild blueberry helps
it does everything fixes the digestive
tract cleans up the liver helps the
brain feeds the brain takes care of the
heart the vascular system did you know
that and so when all this information
you're learning here at the medical
Medium show you're taking it and you're
using it for loved ones friends then you
bump into people and you're creating
this movement that's the assistance
movement I call it and it's powerful and
when you have real information and it's
not misguided or it's misinformation or
it's the same old stuff
repackaged over and over again when
you're dealing with the right stuff
people heal people are going to listen
you're doing it I appreciate you being
here and being involved just know that
know that I am honored truly honored and
blessed and thankful that you're here
taking this information getting
yourselves better turning your health
around listen even if it's just one
piece of information just one piece
that's it one tiny piece that you can
take that you can do so even if your
diet's not perfect so what even if
you're not doing this or that so what if
you're taking one little piece you're
going to start moving forward one way or
another and it's going to be the
foundation we're building the foundation
of your health of your life so we can
move forward together so that's the
medical Medium show that's what it's
about we don't have 10 years to wait for
answers you know and and it's about
knowing what's causing our problems now
and that's what we're doing every week
and it's a blessing to be here with you
thank you for listening so today's show
is about Allergies have you heard about
allergies did ever anybody ever say hey
I have I have an allergic reaction to
that or I have an allergy to that or you
know I'm I'm there's something
allergenic or this this thing is
hypoallergenic or this thing is
non-allergenic or this thing is
allergenic have you heard about all
these different things have you been to
the doctor and have you been to the
allergist have you been to the
alternative doctor that's also now an
allergist have you been to all these
different allergists have you been to
different places I'm just wondering
maybe you have maybe you haven't maybe
you know someone who has but today we're
talking about our allergies and we're
going to air it all out and we're going
to get down to the bottom of everything
around it so just stay on here stay
tuned hang in there we're going to talk
about food allergies we're going to talk
about reactions we're going to talk
about what's behind it all we're going
to talk about some symptoms we're going
to have a blast we're going to have some
fun so hey look if you don't know about
me and this is the first time coming on
check me out medicalmedium.com you could
always go there and look at things um
you know with me it started age four and
I woke up one morning heard Spirit
speaking to me perfectly clear and this
is from an outside source so I hear it
just like you're talking to me right now
fluently nonstop it doesn't stop and
this is why the information's accurate
all the time when I'm working with
people and how I've helped them all
these decades and all these years since
I was a child because I'm not in the way
of it and and this way this gift has
been given to me to help people in a way
so I could never get get in the way so
it doesn't matter if I get tired doesn't
matter if I'm exhausted doesn't matter
if I'm just totally totally frustrated
about something you know or going
through a hard time or you know totally
just tired where you know you just you
you've worked all day and all of a
sudden spirit's still going to come into
the information's going to come Non-Stop
and it can't shut off um you know it's
it's basically been like this my whole
life so anybody first tuning in and they
haven't you looked into me or you
haven't seen anything about me yet
understand that I hear a voice it tells
me what's wrong with someone at all
times no matter what I'm doing whatever
what mood I'm in or whatever I've been
through whatever I'm going through and
it's it's endless and it's non-stop
that's what I've had to deal with I
almost didn't make it here literally
here at all there were times in my life
when I was 10 11 12 years old where I
said you know what this is not I'm not
going to make it because you can't
function as a normal human being knowing
everything about someone all the time in
every crowd you're in in every place you
are and I fought for it I fought for it
to be here I fought for it to help you I
fought for it to make sure that you guys
take this information and help others
and I stand behind you 100% And I back
you up and I'm with you and we're going
to do this have you checked out the
life-changing Foods book it's coming out
soon check it out go go to the bookstore
after ask about it go to Amazon go go to
Barnes & Nobles whatever check it out
and it's coming out and you're not going
to be disappointed I promise if you're
disappointed then I'm really in trouble
because I gave it
everything and you're going to be really
excited because in there are over 50
fruits and vegetables and what they do
for us what diseases they heal what
conditions what symptoms they heal in
and here's the thing I'm talking about
this right now because we're going into
allergies and we're going we're going to
be talking about food and we're going to
be cutting into this a little bit and
just so you know there are foods that we
we were told we have a sensitivity to
that are actually lifechanging and we
and really healing us and we're doing
other things we're having a little bit
of a detox or we're having a healing
effect and we're told that that isn't
what it is we're told we're allergic to
self cery we're told we're allergic to
an Apple we're told we're allergic to an
orange we're told we're allergic to a
lettuce we're told we're allergic to
asparagus and we're confused about foods
and life-changing Foods I spell it out
Advanced information from Spirit that's
decades and decades ahead of its time in
there about what phytochemicals are
really doing what for us what's changing
our lives when we eat and how to protect
ourselves and it we need this resource
today and how to protect our children
how to protect our family you know all
of it is in there what we're what we
need to avoid and what we need to
actually be afraid of out there so we
can rise above it and push it away
that's right it's about what we need to
really know about and look out for to
protect our family and our friends and
our loved ones so you know look into to
that when you can as soon as you can
check it out so hey look look you know I
I'm sure you've heard it before you know
you're allergic to something or maybe
maybe you know you think you you're
allergic to something but I want to
start out talking to you about a couple
of things with this to begin with
science and research doesn't know what
happens to food when it enters the
stomach you heard me say that before
you've heard it from me to cor okay and
I have to say it again because it
applies it applies once
again so here we go Medical Science
medical research and Science in general
doesn't know what happens to food when
it enters the stomach okay we are in the
baby stages when I mean baby stages I
mean we're in the actually we're in the
dinosaur prehistoric stage of
understanding that yeah the assimilation
enzymes
digestion
absorption but what does all that mean
enzymes breaking down food okay the
pancreas does a little bit of this and
the hydrochloric acid does a little bit
of that but did you know that science
and research doesn't know that there's a
blend of seven different acids in
hydrochloric acid that's in the stomach
and they've only singled out one of them
why maybe funding maybe nobody cares
maybe they just haven't stepped on it
yet maybe they haven't just come across
it yet but that's just one example of
how we don't know what's going on in the
gut okay so the latest information about
leaky gut sure but that's out there but
the information about the fact that your
hydrochloric acid is a blend of seven
different acids seven okay and those
seven acids actually do a whole bunch of
things that nobody knows and there's
foods like celery
that build up the seven different
acids because celery has mineral salts
undiscovered by medical research and
medical science this is a big one today
this is about medical research medical
science blah blah blah blah blah but
that's a big this is a big one today
about that because it's really another
place where we're
lost and so so think about that there's
these mineral salts and celery that have
not been identified measured or weighed
we know there're sodium in celery but
that's it and we think all sodium's the
same just like we think all Sugar's the
same okay just like we think now the
sugar and an apple is the same as as
corn syrup I mean come on come
on just all right and that's what's
going on out there okay and so you have
to understand that celery is comprised
of these different mineral salts that
are not that are not discovered and they
change the chemistry inside the
intestinal tract and inside the gut and
the dadum and in the stomach itself so
that we Thrive so that our liver heals
so that our liver doesn't overproduce
bile and burn out and burn itself out so
we get fatty liver pre fatty liver the
whole bit and so that we can kill off
hpylori so celery juice actually has
phytochemicals in it to kill off H
pylori to kill it to burn it right out
of there literally
okay but science and research doesn't
know that either you see where we are we
we're really in a place that we're just
walking around bumping heads until we
see something on TV on one of the shows
on one of the health shows they're
saying oh you can do this and do that
and all that information is outdated
I've I've tuned in once in a while I I
can't help myself and tune in once in a
while and look at those and say oh my
God that stuff is that stuff's back
again from 30 years ago that steps back
again and you know and everybody's just
like doesn't know and so you need to
know cuz we're going to arm you we're
going to arm you with health we're going
to arm you with with health and
spiritual information we're going to arm
you with truth okay and we're going to
arm you with truth about all of this see
science doesn't know what happens to
food when it enters the stomach and
that's a huge foundation and it's going
to take a long time before they get
there okay so how does science know what
we're allergic to or not how does that
happen okay first of all science of
research doesn't know what healing
powers are in food yet thousands of
phytochemicals I talked about raw honey
right I talked about that the other day
over 200,000 working alive
phytochemicals that have every function
ability meaning that are involved with
every part of your hormones to every
part of the organs to your immune system
to every aspect of your immune system
your rbc's your white counts your
lymphocytes your basophils your
monocytes your neutrophils it goes on
and on and on and that's in Honey and
nobody knows and these phytochemicals
that are all in these fruits and
vegetables and honey also like I was
saying destroy bacteria mold viruses
they stop and prevent diseases they
reverse and prevent
cancer and how these Foods care for us
is another thing that is completely
unknown and I talk about a lot of this
in the in the life-changing Foods book
that's why I brought it up earlier
because it's in there and we're going to
you know we're going to always talk
about it but it's in there and we don't
know about what these foods do to care
for us we don't know science and
research doesn't know how they fuel us
what organs and glands they care for and
nurture and
fuel okay and none of this is known by
science just like mystery illnesses is
hundreds of mystery illnesses that have
labels and names of symptoms that
science doesn't know the cause of do you
see where we are right now at
2016 I mean come on you see we where we
are right now this is
unbelievable so autoimmune like I talked
about before is not the body attacking
itself okay we we talked about that and
that's not how it works you know I won't
you down that Lane right now but that's
you know the body does not attack itself
okay in fact it's the opposite there's
something attacking us and our body is
involved in trying to heal that so
that's how autoimmune works and then it
goes on down the line to other great
mistakes so if we don't know what's
causing lupus and ra and you know
Hashimoto and we know we know here at
the show you know cuz you're learning
every day from What Spirit has to say
because that's where the information's
coming from you know the truth and and
I'm delivering that to you guys you know
and and I'm learning from Spirit just
like you are I'm learning from Spirit
okay so you know the truth so we're
becoming those experts we're becoming
those Health experts right you're with
me on that
100% and that's what Spirit tells me
that we're we're becoming those experts
with all the information spirit's giving
us we know what what's causing the ra we
know what's causing the hashimotos we
know what's causing fibromyalgia tentis
vertigo brain fog like really what's
causing brain fog not not not
misinformation about brain fog that's
riddled all over there out there I mean
we know the real things behind all of
this now and we're still
learning look look you can actually
research and look up the tallest
mountain and you're going to get an
answer because they've been able to
research and science has been able to
measure the tallest mountain okay cuz
you can weigh it and you can measure
it you can systematically on a physics
level weigh it and measure it okay you
can look for the deepest ocean the
deepest ocean and look to see how deep
the deepest ocean is and you're going to
get a pretty darn good answer because
they're able to weigh it and measure it
that's science that's
science but you can't weigh and measure
lupus you can't it's a name for a
confusion of elevated inflammation
there's no weighing there's no measuring
nobody knows what causes the symptoms we
do here you can't weigh and measure
mystery illness that everybody's
suffering from decade after decade and
then their children get that mystery
illness over and then their children get
it you can't weigh and measure it yet
science is just not there so we have to
do we what we have to do listen I
recently was talking to a mother whose
son is in college okay and his Professor
went on a tangent to the whole classroom
to the whole you know to everybody there
went on a tangent about how fruit is bad
for us fruit is bad for us and is filled
with sugar okay a professor college
professor is sitting there
okay talking about how fruit is bad for
us telling kids okay young
adults that fruit is bad for us and how
how this is a type of fruit fear that
I've seen many times lately over the
last couple of years develop and a fruit
fear and a food fear I should say a food
fear has seeped into our own
universities and I've heard this before
some of our professors have adopted a
belief system from misinformation
they've adopted a belief system so they
went to like a belief system that
doesn't have any real medical research
or science so we're in the University
okay all right professors are supposed
to be doing stuff that's only measured
and made only measured and weighed so
professors are only supposed to be doing
something that's only measured or
weighed because it's about it's about
University it's about science it's about
research this was a science class that's
why I'm saying this this was a science
class but then adopts a belief system
from some other place that says that
sugar is all the same now and it's bad
and that's not correct science at all on
any level tells an entire group of
students a large Class A large Gathering
to not eat fruit at
all I mean and this isn't the first time
I heard heard this I've heard this a lot
I mean I've heard this multiple times in
the last couple of
years and so her son challenges the
professor and says since since when has
an apple been bad for
anyone especially since college students
don't eat fruit anyway they eat caffeine
coffee bad sugar Donuts
Bagels
Pizza um I don't know the list goes on
and on and on and on alcohol the list
goes on and on and on okay so and but
everybody's being told not to eat an
apple or a piece of fruit so the so this
this um this student challenged the
professor and the professor was actually
upset and the student you know is paying
the price so this is this is an example
of what we're up to so you pay all this
money send your children to school
you're entrusting that they're at least
going to get research in
science and you know we're we're feeling
that we're being taught the truth the
what science is best to offer I'm not
saying this is how it is in school all
around at all I'm just saying this is
where the health movement is getting
twisted up into everything it's where
it's being pulled into everything at
every angle and getting us in trouble
because that Apple can help save lives
keep you here longer and help you heal
so why am I talking about all this why
am I getting into research and science
to such a degree because I I know we're
talking about allergies and everything
because in order to understand the
allergy the world you have to know the
flaws you have to know where everything
is unstable because if you don't you're
going to buy into the system that has
been created for allergies and you're
going to mess yourself up and mess your
head up and you're not going to be able
to feed yourself the right Foods because
you're going to let science and research
that isn't correct dictate what you're
supposed to eat you guys so that you
don't help your own family so that
you're afraid to give your child an
orange because you think that something
came up on some test that you might have
been allergic to it or your son or
daughter or your
husband and and then that's just going
to cheat you it's going to cheat you out
of something that's going to keep you
here healthier keep you here
longer and it matters it matters when
you get to the age of 60 which is
Young and you want to go the Long Haul
to 100 it matters when you're 70 and
it's those
oranges that you had 10 years ago that
are keeping you here longer because of
the phytochemicals in it it matters that
that cilantro you had in your
guacamole 5 years ago believe it or not
has power in it that's keeping you here
till you're
75 without realizing it cuz we don't
know because science and research hasn't
measured and weighed any of this
whatsoever and so when we get told in
the allergy testing world that you're
allergic to this you're allergic to that
it's in your way get rid of this and
it's all the foods that are good for you
that are actually lifechanging that can
save your life give you a longer life
bring you on down to that that final
place of succeeding in a length of life
that we want to and need to succeed in
it matters big time you see why I'm like
extra what is it extra sarcastic extra
annoying today extra extra passionate
okay okay extra passionate about this
you guys see okay so let's go into this
a little bit let's let's let's have some
fun okay so you got your seat bels on
let's do it all right now I'm not
talking about anaphylactic shock I'm not
talking about that we're going to do a
whole show on that down the road
anaphylactic shock that's a whole
different occurrence and a whole
different thing when someone is
dangerously allergic to
something and that means it's not just
peanut butter somebody can have
anaphylactic shock to
latex somebody can have anal
paint someone can have it to
gasoline you know Gasol gasoline hits
somebody's hand when they're at the pump
pumping their own gasoline and they need
an EpiPen because they're going into
anaphylactic shock to a
beasting this is different than what
we're talking about today this is a
different reaction whole different thing
so we're going to separate that but
today talking about allergies seasonal
allergies talking about food
allergies on a different level we're
talking about those you guys hear about
this before have you been through it all
have you been through the whole thing
okay well we're going to talk about IG
IGG
testing that's what we're going to talk
about immunoglobulin testing okay
antibodies in the blood so we're going
into that a little bit right now what's
happening is we have this testing that's
happening right now that can showcase if
you are allergic to certain foods or
some
foods but it's not
accurate it's not correct is what it's
not and I'm going to talk about why for
example since we don't know what food
does we don't understand what's
happening inside the
body so when IG tests come back
and they say Hey you are allergic to
celery and I hear that once in a while
you're allergic to celery what's really
happening is that the celery is killing
off a
pathogen the
pathogen is releasing a
toxin that toxin creates a
histamine and this is for some people
that you know it shows up on the test
hey you're allergic to celery they're
saying that because you're celery juice
and your celer is destroying hpylori
it's killing off strepa cacus that
causes sibo it's lowering and reducing
sibo it's it's knocking out it's
literally knocking mold and disarming it
completely so if anybody who's worried
about getting mold in their system or
has mold in their system and that's what
it's doing so when we do the IGG test we
come home and we're like okay I got this
big list we did not you know 90 Foods
plus plus plus Foods okay I'm allergic
to Cinnamon I'm allergic to celery I'm
allergic to Orange I'm allergic to um
Blackberry I'm allergic to hazelnuts I'm
allergic to uh cucumber allergic to
Tomato um we're doing the you know the
what is it the uh process of elimination
diet now through all this process it's
totally chaotic and not correct and look
I could be hurting somebody's feelings
right now I mean I got a lot of good
practitioners that that take the
information that I have and they do
different testings and stuff so I'm
saying that if you are a practitioner
and you do the IGG be open-minded in
different ways you can still do this
test and still be open-minded to what's
going on meaning I know you're
open-minded but you can still pick up
more data from what we're talking about
today and incorporate it into there so
you can still be aware of why it's
showcasing that test not you as a
practitioner or a doctor or as a
physician that's um not the one that's
not understanding it's the test itself
on what it's built upon it's the tool so
this is going to broaden that tool and
that spectrum and the information
involved around there so let's go into
it here um what happens is when someone
has a dairy allergy that they feel
lactose
intolerant that they feel that they they
have something go wrong the minute they
eat dairy products that's
because the dairy itself is feeding
something rampantly it's feeding
something so there's something inside
someone's gut or intestinal tract that's
feeding off of the dairy itself and then
eliminating eliminating a poison a much
more poisonous substance than the dairy
itself this is what lactose intolerance
is lactose intolerance isn't because
someone is intolerant to
lactose see how behind we are with
science and
research you got to have yeah get your
notepad out get a cup of tea too get
listen to this show over again in the
archives as well and you get a cup of
tea and you get your notepad and just go
over it again and again and so when you
eat the dairy and it's someone like
yourself okay and you've been told your
lactose intolerance because you have to
run to the bathroom you're running to
the bathroom because that dairy product
is hyper feeding it's called hyper
feeding that's it Spirit tells me Hyper
feeding it's feeding a set of bugs in
the colon and intestinal track that's
having a Feeding Frenzy just like a
whole bunch of piranha a whole bunch of
piranha in a fish tank and you throw
some food in there like little fish and
they just have a Feeding Frenzy and they
just bite all these fish fish in half
they just they just eat all these fish
gobble them up and it's like crazy and
that's what happens and when this occurs
the body reacts acts it reacts because
when bugs feed rapidly they go to
bathroom the bugs go to bathroom they
have to eliminate and when they
eliminate they eliminate the dairy
product the
lactose and other things in the dairy
product not even the lactose that's
another thing too it's not about lactose
intolerance it's about more than lactose
intolerance it's all kinds of aspects of
dairy that feed problems and then the
bugs eliminate a poison that's much more
toxic it's like a methyl poison a methyl
poison meaning it is synergistically
designed
differently it can travel it can do
things it's much more
poisonous and then the body reacts and
you have diarrhea you have cramps you
have stomach cramps you have bloating
all of this okay that's how it works
that's how it works now you can
still be allergic to dairy products but
it not show up on the IGG test not show
up on the IGG test that's how confusing
the testing is or any kind of allergy
testing you can be allergic to Dairy and
other foods will show up I'll tell you
why other Foods okay are killing off
pathogens they're killing off pathogens
and it triggers off the allergy testing
so here's how it works here's how it
works if you eat a fig and it's killing
off eoli in your intestinal tract ecoli
which causes diverticulitis
diverticulosis or strep which causes
diverticulosis diverticulitis whatever
when you kill that off it
explodes so when you eat a
food like garlic that kills off H pylori
CI staff strepa cacus
eoli mold is mold mold actually mold can
be alive so when you kill off
anything it
explodes and it's poisonous when it
explodes when it
explodes and it's Affiliated to the food
that killed it off it's going to show up
on the IGG test that you're actually
that you're actually allergic to figs
that you're actually allergic to a food
that you're actually allergic to
something that was doing this you're
allergic to banana because banana kills
viruses in the intestinal tract it kills
shingles which cause causes colitis so
it kills off shingles which causes
colitis that's what bananas does bananas
do and and so bananas do more than that
they kill off lots of things in the
intestinal tract that shouldn't be there
but they leave good bacteria they feed
good
bacteria but when a banana kills off
HIV you said it I said it you hear it hi
IV when it kills off
retroviruses when it kills off stealth
viruses when it kills off you know
colitis viruses such as such as
shingles when it kills off epine bar
cyto megler virus when it kills off
bacteria that bacteria that virus
explodes it explodes it dies because
there's a phytochemical in this food
that kills off that pathogen okay so
then it's a crap storm on the IGG test
or that thing's flying everything you're
allergic to this you're allergic to
Santo you're allergic to Strawberry
you're allergic to Banana you're
allergic to Apple now you're allergic to
artichokes out of nowhere you're
allergic to asparagus you're allergic to
zucchini you're allergic to Winter
squash butternut squash and it's insane
it's lunacy I'm just going to be
straight up it's lunacy so you have to
understand how it works and the
difference is alternative medicine
doesn't know and I don't care if it's
the best book The Best Literature I
don't care if the best article I don't
care if it's the best thing on the
internet the most advanced guy girl you
got out there doing what they're
doing if they don't know that we're
allergic to wheat because wheat feeds a
pathogen and then that pathogen's
eliminating causing the allergy or
causing the body to have a reaction
causing a body to have Celiac if they
don't know that yet which they don't
then we're way
behind so we're hoping that gets fixed
and you you guys are actually part of
that you're part of the knowing the
information cuz you know the right
information and it changes everything
and it breaks all the rules and it moves
forward it moves people forward so we
stopped you know we're stopped you know
being in the in the old ages or the back
you
know back in the that day we're back out
of that day here's the deal so when
you're eating wheat when you're eating
wheat and that wheat is feeding
something in the intestinal tract you're
going to get Celiac it's not your body
attacking itself self it's not the fact
that your body is trying to destroy
itself it's not the fact that these
antibodies are out to destroy you so
when IGG testing does all these
different foods and they say well
there's you know there's there's there's
proof here in the testing that says
there's antibodies that tell us that you
know your body is attacking it's
allergic to an Apple it's allergic to
asparagus it's allergic to Basil it's
allergic to parsley it's allergic to
nettle and when we get told that it's
not accurate it's not how it works
partially nettle and asparagus and
artichoke they get rid of pathogens
they're phytochemicals are clean and
detox and when you clean and detox it
ruins the IGG test it completely ruins
all of the allergy testing in general
that
occurs and when somebody's eating wheat
and they're having a reaction that can
last days or weeks later or they're not
even sure it's the wheat doing it it's
just the wheat feeding bugs and bugs are
feasting releasing
toxins that's what's really
happening same thing with eggs eggs can
feed bugs it can grow cysts and
tumors even if I I've seen people I've
seen people they got tumors they got
cysts they got breast cancer they get
the IGG test they get the the allerg
allergy testing and the allergy tests
come back they're allergic to a food
that's going to help stop their cancer
like wild blueberries they're allergic
to blueberries is what I'm saying or
they're allergic to raspberries even
though they're not having a r reaction
when they eat the raspberry blueberry
but then the test says they're not
allergic to eggs they're not allergic to
eggs the very thing that grows Cy in
tumors and feeds viruses to grow cyant
tumors and creates breast cancer and
thyroid cancer and all these other
Cancers and liver cancer eggs and the
tests come back where you can eat eggs
so you walk out of the office office
whoa I can't eat blueberries raspberries
and blackberries I can't eat melon I
can't eat watermelon I can't eat this
but I can eat eggs do do you see what
I'm saying or you see where I'm going
here so that's what I'm talking about
right there so here's how it works
there's Foods we
eat that kill off bugs like apples
there's Foods we eat like raspberries
that kill off bugs inside our body
pathogens that responsible for most of
all disease there's Foods we eat that
are eliminating toxic heavy metals you
guys pulling them out of our body
eliminating F Malahide that's in her
body eliminating ammonia
eliminating um uh
byproduct eliminating jelly that's
produced by viruses and
bacteria eliminating all kinds of these
poisons and toxins and toxic heavy
metals and chem chemicals and pesticides
and DDT that's been in her system from
our
forefathers everything these foods are
eliminating and when they eliminate
these toxins they trigger off a reaction
sometimes histamine reactions sometimes
other reactions because they're detoxing
they're pulling this stuff out of the
body so when you get your allergy tests
they're chaotic they're all over the
place they're not even in control
they're picking up the fact that you're
detoxing that you're killing off bugs
you're eliminating toxic heavy metals
and it's it's picking up all of
that and then in the end you get a list
of data that tells you not to eat
certain
foods and that's where it's all
wrong and if you are having reactions to
pollen to Ragweed hay fever get rid of
wheat get rid of dairy get rid of eggs
get rid of canola oil get rid of soy get
rid of corn get rid of MSG I talk about
it all the time look for it it's in
everything in natural
flavors get rid of all of that and if
you want to go further get rid of
Rye okay and you know get rid of some
other grains if you really want to and
move those out bring in more fruits and
vegetables you'll be less apt to getting
anything from hay fever your hay fever
symptoms will drop your Ragweed
symptomss will drop your you know your
symptoms from pollen will drop and you
won't be so light sensitive and you
won't have so many problems because
those foods are feeding strap in the
sinuses strap in the system strep in the
lungs strep of cockus all over the body
all kinds of bacteria all kinds of bugs
different viruses and because all these
foods that I mentioned are feeding all
of that all the
time what including pork well that feeds
all these bugs and when that happens
you're going to be more sensitive to the
overload so when you start getting in
front of mold you're going to react more
when you start getting in front of
pollen you're going to react more when
you start getting in front of you know
hay you know when you start getting in
front of hay when you start getting in
front of ragweed you're going to react
more so remember that keep these Foods
out if you want and listen if it's too
much or it's too scary start with one
food just get weed out one food that's
it you know I remember 30 years ago I
told somebody to get off wheat spirit
said get off wheat it was like an alien
landed from another planet or something
it was like spaceship just you know
everybody was looking up in the sky as
if there was like spaceships coming down
be they could because no one could
figure that could fathom what do you
mean wheat what's wheat oh is that the
bread I'm eating it's 30 30 years ago
like what do you mean wheat you mean the
bread that gives us life is it I need to
get rid of that that's what it was like
30 years ago okay I'm just telling you
I'm sure many of you you know that and
um so the bottom line is if you need to
but if you need to wait on that you need
to just get rid of one thing get rid of
one thing get rid of two things whatever
you think you can do and bring in more
more things okay why would somebody
react with burning sensation around
their mouth if they had an apple there
are a few people out there they have an
apple and they react they get they get
um they get a f funny feeling in their
around their lips because that means
that one time they had an apple when
they were younger that was loaded with
pesticides or DDT with a different name
on it DDT switch names over and over
again it's always been around so DDT or
other pesticides with an with you know
on top of that Apple waxed into that
apple and so when they bit into that
apple and it had a line of pesticides
from a conventional apple and it got on
their lips and in their mouth their body
reacted from that chemical agent so then
when they eat any Apple after that any
Apple their body actually is going to
react that can go away by eliminating
all of the foods I talked about
and um bringing in more fresh fruits of
other fresh fruits and other vegetables
and things like that over time that will
go away and someone be less reactive
when they have something like that and
then there's other reactions when
someone feels funny in different ways
those are detox reactions from the foods
healing the person in different ways now
a lot of things happen when you eat
wheat or you eat dairy or you eat eggs
you won't know what it's doing to you
keeping you back holding you back with
your chronic illness for weeks or even
forever because you just you'll stay
chronically ill eating these things and
not know what's doing it and then when
you eat something like a celery stick or
a cucumber slice you feel funny or a
tomato because those things are pulling
out toxins pulling out Lots and lots of
toxic
debris and all kinds of bugs and then
you start reacting so you don't know so
you go back to just eating you know
bread and cheese grilled cheese
sandwiches with butter I get it but you
know you take one day at a time you work
with it the point of this is not to be
afraid of that list you're getting
handed to you at the allergy's office
meaning I'm not talking about
anaphylactic shock list that's a
different story you know be afraid of
that that list that's different there's
a whole different reason we're going to
cover that in the next show and not in
the next show coming up but coming up
we're going to do that in the future but
don't be afraid of the other list but be
afraid meaning be be
concerned about the wheat the dairy the
eggs okay the milk cheese the butter the
ghee be afraid of all that stuff be
concerned of all that stuff too that
stuff will keep your hay fever keep your
Ragweed problems keep you on allergy
medicine keep on all those different
allergy medicines the nasal sprays all
that that stuff will keep feeding MGS
keeping you on all of that like I said
take one day at a time just incorporate
celery juice into your life maybe some
some wild blueberries just incorporate
something like that into your life you
take one day at a time is what you know
is all you have to
do
so the bottom line is because medical
research and medical science isn't there
yet with what foods do for us and what
foods don't do for us it's going to
going to be you know it's basically
going to be just a guessing game or a
guessing match out
there okay a guessing match I'll say
that instead of the other thing so so
just realize that we can't be guessing
with your life with your health with
your children's health with your
grandchildren's health we can't be
guessing anymore aren't you tired of it
I just I I want to know are you guys
tired of it okay cuz may maybe hey maybe
I'm pushing it too far because I'm tired
of it and I know other people tired of
it I'm just wondering if you guys are
tired of it because it's real out there
that's just a guessing game and we got
to blow by that we need more that's what
it's about today that's what it's about
with allergies so what I suggest in the
allergy world is don't fall victim to
the misinformation from the IGG test or
other allergy tests you keep the doctor
because the doctor cares and the
doctor's an amazing doctor in probably
every every way it's just that the tool
is what I'm saying don't fall victim for
the testing tool you know talk to your
doctor and practitioner if you really
like your doctor and your practitioner
and and they're telling you to stay away
from all these foods that you're not
sure if you even react or not to fruits
and vegetables meaning stay away from
all these fruits and vegetables that you
don't even know if you're really
allergic or not to or you're reacting to
you know talk to your practitioner talk
to your doctor and say can I have these
asparagus cuz it never seemed to really
bug me that much I I had them in my diet
before you know can I bring them back in
and talk to your doctor and say look is
it possible the asparagus is offering
something else for my health that could
keep me here
longer and I need that back in
here is that
possible I want to talk about sweet
potatoes who eats sweet potatoes do you
guys eat any sweet potatoes out there
who's eating sweet potatoes out there do
you like them because they're
good okay if you're told you're allergic
to them don't listen make sure you eat
those sweet potatoes unless you're
having an anaphylactic shock with it
that's a different story but I've never
seen that with sweet potato yet so but
definitely bring in sweet potatoes and
I'll tell you why okay because sweet
potatoes help heal colitis Crohn's
disease skin cancers breast cancer
ovarian cancer cervical cancer stomach
cancer intestinal cancers esophageal
cancer colon cancer they help with Sleep
Disorders chronic fatigue syndrome which
is Epstein bar because you guys know
that Epstein bar I brought that brought
that to us sweet potato helps with heart
diseases heart helps with
insomnia alopecia which is really an
adrenal hormone issue alopecia not an
autoimmune attack on the body sweet
potatoes have these Powers I talk about
this in the lifechanging foods book okay
sweet potatoes help lift depression help
with anxiety but listen it's not going
to happen if you have just one sweet
potato once a month just have sweet
potatoes every day for 90 days start
getting rid of your anxiety and your
depression and so many other things
sweet potatoes are incredible for PCOS
if you're someone that was diagnosed
with PCOS you know cystic ovaries and um
and hormone imbalances bring in sweet
potatoes whatever you do it's important
and the symptoms sweet potatoes help
with are unbelievable from scar tissue
to spasms to cramps to diarrhea to
anxiousness they're incredible and the
emotional support from sweet potatoes is
really powerful too so you just know
there's even an emotional and spiritual
lesson from sweet potatoes that help us
in every way so check out check out
life-changing Foods you know when you
can get a hold get a hold of it get a
copy before they're all gone and um and
lock that down and know that I care
about you I stand behind you 100% you
know it's about the journey we're on all
together it's about making the best out
of everything and that's what we're
doing right now we're making the best
out of everything out of our time out of
our energy and that's a spirit wants to
do making sure that you get what you
need so you can
heal you know when when I was 10 years
old when I was 10 years old somebody
came to me with an eye problem they came
to me with an eye problem because they
heard through my family that I had the
answers from
Spirit and they had they were blind in
one eye the eye was damaged it was too
damaged to heal it was too damaged to be
fixed and they were blind in one eye and
they came to me and they said fix my eye
said I don't care about that eye I don't
care about that eye that's what I said
and spirit said yeah don't care about
that eye and the guy said what what do
you mean don't care about that eye I
said I care about the other eye and
keeping that other eye here and keeping
it alive and keeping it healthy so
you're not blind to both eyes and that's
what we're going to do and we're going
to get the right Foods in you that keep
that other eye healthy so that you stay
here and you can see and that's what
it's about and we want these Foods we
want everything I love you guys I stand
behind you
blessings just know that I
care