cardiovascular health heart health
it's so funny to me
the whole heart health thing
you know
eggs are a heart healthy food
butter's a heart healthy food
are you kidding me the one thing about
heart health is people don't really know
what's going on about that right blood
pressure is rising rising rising blood
pressure is rising rising rising
high cholesterol high cholesterol out of
control everybody's on statins
everybody's on blood pressure
medications everybody's on satin hi
courtney hi everybody see courtney
amazon everybody's coming on right now
you guys we're live right now tick tock
we're live on rumble we're live on
youtube we're live on facebook we're
live on telegram
telegram where i leave those exclusive
messages there right
you guys
it's good that we're talking about this
this is a
a heart health talk right here this is a
top the prevention realm thanks for
coming on hey right awesome uh paula
bennett thanks for coming on good to see
you guys emily misty dawn all you guys
are coming on brad's coming on whoa
yvonne's coming on eliza
everybody renata everybody's coming on
here chan you guys incredible good to
see you guys so we're talking about
heart health and it's it's important to
know because so many people they're
confused about heart health right and
think about it right we're told to eat
butter
and butter is the heart stopper
it's the heart
stopper like do you really want butter
in your coffee do you really want butter
in something do you really want it's
literally the heart
killer right i mean it is it's one of
those
pork fats another one there so it's like
you know it's it's
it's really a bad thing i mean in so
many ways for people because they don't
realize it it's not that it's not that
it's a bad thing because there's there's
a lot worse things in the world and i
get it
but it's one of those things where
people don't know how to navigate out of
it where they don't know how to navigate
out of things like butter they they
can't find their way they can't leave it
they can't get away from it it's really
hard and then you know you end up eating
them there's butter on everything you
end up eating all kinds of stuff good to
see you guys i just want to tell you
just a quick announcement before we talk
about heart health because that's where
we are right now we're talking about
heart health we're talking about
cardiovascular health a little bit
and we're going to hit the liver on that
too i just want to tell you i made some
drinks
non-alcohol drinks you guys on telegram
non-alcohol drinks
you guys in rumble you guys on youtube
right here they are
and here are the drinks right here
okay we got a spice creamy chaga which
is incredible
and that's what the uh the vimerji chaga
right there which the quality of this is
is incredible i actually showed
everybody at amazon live i made these on
amazon live with the new medical medium
cooking show that's where i took the
cooking show and here i'm talking about
symptoms conditions and everything else
right the amazon live link is in the
description and on tick tock it's in the
the link is in the bio
okay just so you know in the profile so
just just so you know where that link is
and what happens is when you go to that
link that amazon live link
it takes you there make sure you follow
me so you know when i'm doing the amazon
lives and making all the stuff cat
barrard says that was a fun cooking show
thanks again anthony with a bunch of
explanation points thank you kat for
being there
that was really great that you're there
kat thank you that was awesome and
so i'm just telling you guys and i'll
show you the other drinks too i made the
spicy hot chaga drink which i'm gonna
have a little bit of it now
so good so i also made the mold wine
the mold wine it's not mold wine it's
not moldy wine it's mulled wine right
non-alcohol i made it on the show right
there i'm gonna show you the other
drinks too
okay i mean
i made the apple cider i also made the
apple cider which i'm gonna have a sip
of
[Music]
you got to check out the drinks on the
cookie show emily thank you for coming
over here to this live
incredible i'm having a little bit of
this
lorraine i'm getting a little tipsy
and then we got the hibiscus
hibiscus apple tea
this is knock your socks off
um
that's really good
that's got like it's a that's like
there's that's a zing in there
right
i got that one too
and then
there's these it's like
oh i'm just uh
oh
i'm doctor show and show from the i'm dr
so and so here i am on my youtube
channel and we're gonna give you five
best tips and by the way come to my come
to my mansion and you can i can serve
you this delic delicious champagne here
as a guest i'm gonna have all the people
from the medical board there
oh i'm dr um i'm going to have all the
people from the medical board
i'm having the people from the clinic
from the famous clinics all that that
we're going to be giving them champagne
and we're going to be fancy smancy
glasses i'm doctor
[Music]
oh i forgot to tell you what these
drinks were so this is the mimosa which
is incredible by the way
so this is incredible this is the
cranberry orange mimosa i made this
wait mimosa
that's why we're live
i always say that's why we're live man
you can't it doesn't matter you can't
beat bloopers you can't beat bloopers
man they're the best okay so i got that
right
and what else do i have the mocktail the
champagne mocktail would you like some
champagne are you a guest at my mansion
i'm doctors i made a billion dollars on
youtube last year
with my millions and millions of
followers
and i'm gonna have oh no i don't
practice medicine really anymore i'm
just a youtube doctor now
would you like to come to my mansion and
have a champagne be open-hearted good to
see you don't they look good
i got a champagne right here okay
and um and it's alcohol free it's elk
free
it's alk free man so where do you see
the medical medium cooking show i just
want to tell you guys you see it on
amazon live
right i can't talk about certain things
but i can do the health tips and all the
foods in a different way that i haven't
done use the link in the description you
guys and i tic tac the links in the bio
okay scroll down to the bottom of the
amazon live page my page right when you
go and you hit that lit hit the link go
to the page scroll down and you'll see
my past live streams you can watch all
the past live streams when you go to the
amazon page you have to scroll down for
some reason they got it down there you
got to scroll down and find all those
those past lives make sure you follow
medical medium on that platform so you
can see the fun cooking shows and i i
talk about all these health tips i mean
like sorry cooking tips
so it's really cool
anyway these are incredible drinks right
here
i am going to sip more
apple cider right um
in my house you can come in there and
i'm going to i'm not going to go i'm
drinking
i'm from is everybody from the medical
board here
oh the board no i'm not going to do that
i'm going to say hey you want an apple
cider
yo
you want an apple cider
yeah you could sit down just go ahead
it's fine sit down relax
kick your feet up you couldn't put your
feet on my coffee table
okay you guys you're talking about
cardiovascular health health let me kind
of move these drinks out of the way
all right
let's get the drinks out of the way
but i might keep this one around because
i think i'm gonna have some cider
okay you guys so we're talking about
heart health you know everybody seems to
be a heart health genius right
people are freaking dying of heart
attacks left and right
there's people dying of heart attacks
they're just got just dropping off like
this like heart attack central
strokes heart attacks blood clots people
are literally dropping like flies
out there right now
you don't believe me it's true
literally they're just like
like that okay
and and then we got high blood pressure
sure out there we got high cholesterol
but we're talking about
like
people are going down with their hearts
like you cannot even believe it so it's
pretty crazy you guys we're on tick tock
live right now
we're on
live on youtube we're live on facebook
let's get rolling on the show let me
love good to see you danielle
martha good to see you
so you guys the thing is is that where
did butter come in as being healthy
that's one thing right there like where
did butter come in right
so you know where did
where did these things kind of come in
like eggs like heart healthy stamps on
eggs
that's a tricky one right there it's
like heart-healthy stamps that are on
the egg cartons it's like
heart healthy heart healthy good for you
right and you know so what happens is
we're totally in the realm of eating
foods to
possibly
cuddle our condition to get our heart
attack down the road well that's what's
really you know that's what's really
crazy out there how it works so let's go
into it of how what happens with the
heart how does that work so here's the
deal
your heart
okay
right
is a muscle machine
its job though is to pump your blood
we know that
but there's something we don't know
it's not supposed to pump
blood
really high in fat
yes
it's not supposed to pump blood
really high in fat
that's what it's not supposed to do
because what happens is your liver
starts to become a fatty liver because
of butter
eggs
pork
all of that and
your liver starts to become a fatty
liver so here's what happens your
heart's job is to pump blood
out of your liver
your liver is a filter
okay
i don't know what kind of system you got
do you have an air filter system and
your
hot water heater system your oil burner
maybe maybe your apartment building has
a big old oil burner down the basement
nobody knows about and there's a filter
on there and the filter gets dirty
your air conditioning has a filter on it
there's filters on everything
so when the fan is pumping it's sucking
air through the filter and as the filter
gets clogged you can go and change the
filter you can be like you know what
i can go change the filter
you can't change your liver you can't go
you can't change your liver your liver
is the filter your liver is the filter
you can't go and just say i'm just gonna
go change the filter out of my liver i'm
just gonna go change the filter out of
it of course you're doing medical medium
stuff and you're cleaning your liver and
you're cleansing all that you can do
that
but
what happens is that filter starts
getting clogged up with fat
too much dairy
milk cheese butter
eggs
more cheese
vegan cheese
regular cheese
nuts seeds right and it's okay if you
want to have a little bit of nuts you
want to have a little bit of seeds and
nut butters you might have some coconut
oil you want some olive oil
but it starts to get tired the liver
gets tired all the fat starts to bog
down the liver and the liver then
starts to get tired starts to get
clogged
and then
the heart
has to now
work harder
a hard job
is to pump the blood
from the liver
if your liver is clean and there's not a
lot of fat in the liver
your blood can pump easy
you know easier
to the to the heart so the heart's job
is to pull the blood from the liver
up to it
right
but then we
make our blood so thick
like a thick milkshake
we turn our blood into a thick milkshake
our blood is dehydrated
it's thick
it becomes congested
our blood becomes dirty and i talk about
that in the medical medium books right
the blood becomes congested or blood
becomes dirty blood becomes thick
right i talk about that liver rescue
cleanse the heel
okay
and then the heart gets tired
years go by
and the heart is due it's hearts i don't
care if you're exercising that's great
you can be working out how many guys are
working out they're like i've been
working out for 10 years i'm now 45
years old and i know my routine and i
got my workouts and i could do this
but
they're just sitting in there on their
couch
they're sitting on their couch with
their family and they're like hey honey
can you go can you go answer them can
you get my phone
oh my god my arm
they go down
every day
people in their 45 people they're 47
people they're 50 people who are working
out people are riding bikes people are
doing
cardiovascular work and what happens is
that the heart
it gets tired as the years go by and the
years go by
so the heart
it has this limitation on it it's not
just clogged arteries and clogged veins
and clogged valves
it's not just clogged ventricles
it's not just clogged ventricles it's
not just clogged arteries it's not just
clogged valves right
it's more than that it's dirty blood
michelle l says check out the dirty
blood podcast medical lean podcast at
apple podcast you can listen to that
episode
and this is original medical medium
information
you can go to
you can go to a big conference
all the medical doctors in the world
there that know about heart health they
won't talk about this they don't know it
this is the way life is right r rose
says i got the sickest when i was doing
high fat high protein
yeah it bogs the heart down
i'm not saying you can't if you're an
animal protein person i'm not saying you
can't have a piece of chicken you can't
have a piece of grass-fed beef i'm not
saying you can't have
you know
a piece of fish
but we overdo it if you're a vegan and
plant-based i'm not saying you can't
have walnuts
i got some walnuts in the cupboard over
here
i'm not saying you can't have some
walnuts
you can't have some nut butter right
but we overdo it and we over do it and
sometimes when we need to do clean up
and clean that filter and clean that
liver filter up we can't clean it up
because we're running so much fat
through there
we're running so much fat through there
okay
and then
we get too many poisons built up inside
our liver and too many poisons built up
inside
our organs and then we get the viral
issues and then all of a sudden we got
the viral issues right
the viral issues
and then we're sick we get the
fibromyalgia the chronic fatigue
syndrome the aches and pains the
dizziness the vertigo we get the tingles
and numbness we get the we get the um
brain fog
we get all these different things right
we get the eye floaters we get the you
know we get the the vertigo like i said
we get all of that
trigeminal neuralgia neck pain back pain
ear pain jaw pain right knee pain our
knees start blowing out everything
starts blowing out we start going
downhill
because we get all that viral
inflammation in there too
but one thing's for certain
right now
we're accelerating into
heart attacks
blood clots
strokes
clogged arteries
heart problems
we're in a place where heart failure
we're in a place where that's
more so than ever before in our history
and it's only getting worse and worse
and worse so let's talk about this for a
little bit
so when you eat a stick of butter
it goes into your bloodstream
a hunk of that butter goes into your
bloodstream
now
if you like grass-fed butter don't get
mad
i i i'm gonna say that you know what
if you eat
a block of vegan cheese
i'm gonna say the same thing
the difference is with butter it feeds
bugs and that's another story we're on
cardiovascular
but you know feeding bugs is another
story butter does feed all the pathogens
right when you eat a stick of butter
okay you guys see this
tik tok you can't surprise see it tell
her eat a stick of butter and that
butter goes down into the stomach
right now that butter's in the stomach
right here
okay
then that butter
goes into the to the duodenum
and then
that butter starts to get dispersed by
your bile from your liver
and as your bile is breaking down
the butter
fat
okay dissolving it
it's now getting dispersed and going up
your veins
now it's going up to veins that are
attached to your duodenum and your small
intestinal tract
those veins
are sucking the butter up
and who's doing all the work
your heart
your heart you guys on tick tock
that's who's doing all the work on
telegram your heart
okay
so now your heart's
trying to suck the butter
up through your hepatic portal highway
which is your veins
attached to your small intestinal tract
and your heart's trying to pull that
butter
up through that intestinal tract
and up the veins
into your liver
so now the stick of butter
is in your liver
okay
as the years go by
butter gets trapped in that liver
now you don't know it even if you didn't
get a diagnosis you got a fatty liver
and then
okay
your heart
is getting tired
and now you're getting high blood
pressure
now you're getting
high blood pressure
you don't have to get high blood
pressure for this to happen
this can happen and then you get high
blood pressure later later later
it's like people who say my
great-grandmother ate butter
her whole life and she's 90 years old
right
and then you get on the phone with that
great grandmother i hope she calls
i say my great-grandmother
ate butter until she's 87 and she's fine
there's nothing wrong with her my my
grandfather my great-grandmother ate
whatever my aunt
hello
great grandma
yeah we we asked to get your number we
saw somebody leave a comment yesterday
and they said that their their
great-grandmother who's 94 years old has
eaten butter her whole life
is that you
it is
well that's amazing you're 94.
so he said you are perfectly fine like
you had the best
the best run and you're 90. yeah you're
you're 91. okay
so
what does what does your what does your
great-grandson not know
so you're great rega you had two
miscarriages
really
so you had wow oh my god
that's terrible you had two miscarriages
and then you had a hysterectomy
because the fibroids were really bad
okay
you had cervical cancer
you survived it though you're here
okay
you had a gallbladder taken out
really when you were 50
okay why doesn't your great-grandson
know this well he doesn't pay attention
to all that you've been through he just
visits you once a month
and just starts shouting at you
okay
well did you oh my god really you've had
high blood pressure you're on statins
what other drugs are you on lots of
medications
and
you had a you you had a leg infection
so you had infection in your leg
you were in the hospital for three
months
does he know about that infection in
your leg
you had you have a stint
oh my god you have two stints in your va
your you have two stints in your
arteries to keep your arteries open
why
they said your arteries closed off and
you had a you had a heart attack
how many heart attacks
how come you're
wha what
you don't have your you don't have your
dentures in
all right
she's putting her dentures in hold on
you guys
when did you lose your teeth when you
were 60
you lost your teeth when you were 60
how come your great-grandson doesn't
know you you lost your teeth when you're
60.
you you had the worst tmj ever
what do you mean anti-anxiety
medications you're on those too
it sounds like he
he doesn't know anything about your
health history he left a comment saying
that you're 90 and you've been eating
butter your whole life and you're fine
all right i gotta go like i know there's
more i'm gonna call you back after the
show
okay i'll call you back after the show
michelle l says they don't care to ask
so the point is is where i'm going with
all of this right
so what people don't realize is that
their heart is doing double time
and heart health is really being
cautious to how much
grease
whatever we're greasing our wheels with
goes in our body if that's butter if
that's anything else april tap says my
parents keep saying their high blood
pressure is hereditary they won't listen
to me to the true cause
anyone can get rid of their mystery high
blood pressure anyone can get rid of
their mystery hot blood blood that is
one thing you can get rid of you do the
right things you can get rid of mystery
of high blood pressure i can't tell you
how many people i've talked to were able
to just get rid of their high blood
pressure and it's gone boom it's gone
like gone that's it
and my grandmother fed me sticks of
butter as a baby oh avis
right and that's what causes the
fluctuating high blood pressure right
it's a liver
that's getting too much fat stored up in
it
and a heart
that's trying to regulate
so it's a heart that's trying to
regulate so fluctuating fluctuating
mysterious high blood pressure
even if it's like for one month and then
one month it's off one month it's on
three months it's on three months it's
off it's on it's off right it's
fluctuating right sunrood says love your
live shows i'm so honored you're here
truly okay
that fluctuating blood pressure
is the heart trying to regulate
it's the heart trying to regulate so
it's the vagus nerves
it's messages coming from your brain
sending them down your brain stem
sending them down the vagus nerves
sending them to the heart
and and trying to help the heart
regulate why the heart is trying to
struggle if the heart is actually trying
to to regulate with your vagus nerves
there's so much fat in the bloodstream
and fat inside the liver every single
day that the gas has to be put on so you
get these messages from the brain so
what happens is
you get messages from the brain
going down the vagus nerves heading to
your heart
telling your heart put on the brakes
step on the gas put on the brakes step
on the gas put on the brakes step on the
gas put on the brakes that's what's
happening
because the liver is clogged and getting
clogged every day with a fatty liver
because of so much of that butter and so
much of that grease and so much of those
nut butters too
nut butters
yeah too much nut butters this is
medical medium information just letting
everybody know
can't go to a hard conference and hear
this stuff
right we can't i can't go anywhere and
hear this stuff but this is so important
michelle says it makes so much sense i'm
honored to hear it
really happy you're here
so yeah in in
so what we're dealing with is mysterious
high blood pressure it's one thing
let's talk about strokes
okay
strokes happen for a couple of reasons
one is
the veins in the arteries the tiny
arteries
tiny arteries see that see the arteries
right there
blood vessels and small arteries see all
the small arteries right
they start getting
clogged up
they start narrowing everything starts
to narrow okay
but that doesn't mean you're gonna get a
stroke ever you can
live your life without a stroke
and you can have narrowing in all the
arteries and all the little tiny
arteries right in blood vessels you can
have those you could have those but
here's what does the stroke
invaders
invaders right here
clusters of viruses clusters of
pathogens
clusters of pathogens viruses and toxins
clusters of these
they have to find their way through
all the narrowed arteries
viruses tend to
become cluster clumps
cluster
beep
bleep that's what they become cluster
bleeps
what happened is
your white blood cells
okay
want to kill the viruses
so they jump on the viruses
to try to stop the viruses
but if you got too many narrowings
in all the different blood vessels
too many narrowings
what happens is when the your immune
system tries to do its job and jump on
the virus
it clumps up and then you got like a big
clump
of bugs and viruses and everything right
and immune cells everything's just
battling each other and that clump
just starts to get bigger and bigger and
that clump is now traveling through
narrowed passageways and then it gets to
the brain
when it gets to the brain
when that cluster of pathogens and
immune cells get to the brain
everything starts to get smaller and
smaller but the clump is bigger and
bigger
finally it blocks
a blood vessel completely
but it wouldn't have happened
if
your whole life you didn't have your
bloodstream filled with a ton of fat
your liver filled the fat
and the arteries filled with fat this is
advanced medical medium information if
you heard it here you heard it here
first
just so you know smokey mountain smoking
mountain paradise good to see you guys
so
what happens is that we can do something
about it right we can protect ourselves
okay
so
right now people are overloaded with
toxins
and
also when they're really foreign toxins
demand
your immune cells to jump on those too
right now people are getting foreign
toxins
lots of them
and the foreign toxins from everywhere
all places air fresheners scented
candles
just everywhere to pharmaceuticals like
everywhere just people are getting
foreign toxins through everything the
antibiotics there's foreign toxins in
that there's 40 foreign toxins in
everything right so all this stuff
right centicams clones perfumes
laundry detergents fabric softeners
cleaning supplies like all this stuff
foreign foreign toxins and and your
immune cells have to eat up those
foreign toxins so when you have a
foreign toxin so let's get some toxins
see if we can find some of that right
when you get some foreign toxins okay
let's say you're doing some fish oil
so there's mercury in fish oil
so
that's a foreign toxin so say you're
taking your fish oil every day and you
think you're helping yourself
here's your fish oil right
the mercury in there
gets eaten up by your immune system so
your white blood cells are trying to eat
up that mercury to protect you
okay and when it when it's eating up all
these forward toxins constantly
constantly
it can clump it can cluster around all
the toxins
and that cluster can find a narrowing
somewhere in the brain or brain stem
anywhere it could find a narrowing
anywhere and that's where we get in
trouble right there
and then boom we've got a stroke
there's no evidence whatsoever to back
up
in any medical literature
or studies
yeah i mean there's no evidence to back
up what there's no evidence to back up
this information
because you heard it from here first
and then science takes it later i mean
like they always do with medical mean
information look if you're if you're
here to really learn something i'll just
fill you in right now okay medical
medium information is the first
to bring epstein-barr causing
hashimoto's thyroiditis ra and
fibromyalgia right advanced information
science took it after the fact it was
published by medical medium medical
medium also
brought reactivated epstein-barr being
long plagued so the long plant the long
plague the long-haul plague right
so the long-haul plague now doctors are
saying it's reactivated epstein-barr
that was medical medium information
public for published first
the long-haul pandemic
so you might be sitting here saying
there's no substantiation behind your
stuff then tell science research to stop
taking all my stuff
dude call up science and research and
tell them to stop poaching all of
medical medium stuff
okay why don't you do that for me once
you go somewhere else
i'd like you here though once you go
somewhere else and tell them to stop
taking medical medium information please
or cite it
back to where it originates
right so that's just a couple of things
i've been going on all day about that
right
okay this is funny
medical medium
right talks about celery juice does for
everybody and now
all of a sudden
it's being picked up
by some of the biggest like industries
in the world now and they're all gonna
be putting out celery juice
right
i guess uh
[Music]
what does that tell you right there and
they're gonna be spouting out all its
benefits
much of what medical medium put out
first
anyway
but that's another show let's not talk
about all that stuff right now let's
talk about how to heal and how to
protect ourselves
this isn't complicated
none of this is complicated
just gotta lower down your fats
if you're a pork eater stop eating pork
that's all
keep with chicken stay with chicken and
turkey
but lower your chicken and turkey just
lower it
okay
if you're if you're a bambi eater if
you're a deer eater if you like deer
lower your amount of deer
if you like venison
lower your amount of venison
don't eat a lot of venison
right
if you like
i don't know how many of you guys are
eating reindeer right now
if you like cow
if you like cow lower your amount of cow
right a friend of mine said one mean
grass-fed beef i'm like
you're eating cow right you're eating
cow i said how's it go cow what do you
mean i'm eating cow
what are you talking about that's crazy
i'm not eating cow
i said
don't you have a grasp of beef he's like
yeah
i said you're eating cow
how's it going because i'm not eating
cow
i said you're eating cow
anyway the point is if you're eating cow
lower the amount of cow you're eating
right
lower the amount
if you're eating nut butters lower the
amount of nut butters if you're eating
avocado bring them down a little bit
don't do three avocados every single day
somebody could be doing two avocados and
they have chicken and they have coconut
oil and they have you know what i mean
give the body a break that's what i'm
talking about so the whole point is is
give your body a break learn how to
bring it down a little bit
cold white spring says some people don't
even know that meat is muscle
some people
how about almost everybody
but that's a really good point how about
almost everybody so when it comes down
to cardiovascular cardiovascular health
okay keep in mind
and i love it when somebody says there's
no substantiated evidence to back this
up
three years later where'd the person go
where'd the guy go who was doing his
keto diet and exercising he's 41 years
old oh he died
what heart attack
i can't tell you how many guys are dying
right now women too how many dudes are
going down
how many dudes you guys
it's crazy actually how many dudes are
getting the the myocarditis how many
dudes are getting the endocarditis how
many how many days are getting the heart
attacks how many dudes are getting like
angina until they get a heart attack how
many guys are getting the cloned
arteries it's crazy
how much
should dogs so okay it's a question nika
yeah should dogs eat meat every day
dogs should not be vegan
a dog's intestinal tract is this long
let me show you okay
so
so dogs should not be eat dogs should
not be vegan they should get some fruits
and vegetables dogs should get wild
foods fruits and vegetables they should
but that's a dog's intestinal tract
right there
okay
that's a human's intestinal tract right
there
that's a dog's intestinal tract
basically right there i mean not not
totally it's more than this but
basically that's what it is
and so yeah dogs are dogs are carnivore
but i'm not anti-animal protein medical
medium information supports animal
protein eaters because you can still
heal on medical medium information while
eating animal protein and you can still
eat you can still be vegan and
plant-based and you know some people
think of anti-plant-based anti-vegan
because they're confused because they
don't understand i never took a side of
an aisle they're wondering why how come
i never took a side of the aisle in the
health realm you're either one or the
other
any speakers in health anybody they're
either vegan or they're animal protein
if you want to if you want to know about
oxalates
fear of faith says what are we supposed
to eat already don't eat vegetables
because histamine carbs oxalates
salicylic acid acid so watch the
oxalates episode on rumble
so i would watch that in rumble you guys
what i love to do is just produce free
content non-stop to get you guys the
most information i can and i don't put a
firewall a paywall
in front of everything
okay so just letting you know it's free
free free free the books you can get at
the library the books have the true
causes make sure you pick up a book it's
a medical textbook
okay
where's the substantiated evidence what
about all the medical doctors that have
these that have these books
about all the medical doctors that use
these books every single day
what about that are they looking for
substantiated evidence
no they see their patients getting
better every day from these books and
that's all they care about because they
got compassion they want to see you
better you got it guys i'm going i'm
going on instagram i'm going to turn
tick tock back on i'm going to turn
telegram back on check out my newsletter
by the way
medicalmedium.com sign up to my
newsletter because i'm doing so much
with that i'm gonna be doing a lot of
stuff with that newsletter all kinds of
cool stuff all kinds of free information
because that's what i do i'm not gonna
be hitting you with subscribe subscribe
you know subscribe and pay this here's
subscription fees you guys my newsletter
isn't about pay a subscription fee pay a
scripture no it's not my newsletter is
about information so we can heal that's
free free free
the link is in the bio the link is in
the description for my newsletter check
it out
and the amazon live link is there too
okay but check out the newsletter so you
can know where i'm at know what i'm
doing know what i'm offering all of that
it's it's really it's important to go to
medicalmedium.com and make sure you sign
up to the newsletter
so many people are like i can't sign up
i can't sign up well you can sign up now
it's all fixed it's all good
and because i want people to get what
they need
i'm going to ig
turning telegram back on i'm turning
tick tock back on
and i love you guys and thank you for
being here truly this is really fun