get ready it's real medical medium heavy
metal detox launch party at aan in La at
Culver City I'm going to be there
signing books bring your book your
favorite book medical medium book and
I'm going to sign it going to say hi to
everybody all of that there going to be
like meet and greet people are going to
be coming from all over the world to
come there it's going to be insane it's
going to be incredible it's going to be
June
15th June 15th that's right this year
register go to medicalmedium.com
and guess what it's free yep my favorite
words are coming out of my mouth right
now free free free for free free free
for free free free for free free totally
free you don't have to buy a 200$ 300
$400 ticket to enter it's going to be
the medical medium heavy metal detox
launch party collaboration with Ean and
irwan is putting the heavy metal detox
smoothie on the menu right there in
their stores made fresh and I can't
[Music]
wait