detox smoothie so i got everything out
here right now you guys
i got the frozen wild blueberries look
at that nice bowl of frozen wild
blueberries
look at that which is great got the
bananas of course gotta have that
gotta have the cilantro that's something
that you have to have
and atlantic dulce right there
got some oranges here too um got the
spirulina
got the barley grass juice powder
investor is out there hands down
got some wild blueberry powder too so
the metal medium heavy metal detox
smoothie
has saved a lot of lives it's been out
there a long time
i've been teaching people about it for
many decades
hello loon hello everybody coming on
natural beauty came on
everybody's coming on now and so the
heavy metal detox smoothie has been a
big part of
getting people's lives back getting
people off of mattress island
getting people off of couch island
getting people back to work again
getting people to function again and we
have to
think about that the power of what the
heavy metal detox movie has done for
people
we're talking reversing serious
debilitating diseases
conditions symptoms anxiety depression
bipolar ocd people with crippling ocd
got their lives back i'm not talking
about mild ocd
where your thoughts are just compulsive
and i'm talking about where you feel
like you have to act on those
compulsions to such an extreme
it completely invades your life takes
over your life
and then you're trapped i'm talking
about that kind of ocd the ocd that
helped thousands over the years overcome
the heavy metal detox smoothie is a big
part of this right here including
helping people with tourettes the
medical medium heavy metal detox movie
has reversed
people's tourette's conditions autism
um adhd esophagus
spasms ticks spasms twitches
sleeping disorders insomnia okay
and schizophrenia i mean it's helped
people
on all levels ptsd not just anxiety
depression but also ptsd
depersonalization
focus and concentration memory issues
alzheimer's
the medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie has reversed
people's conditions such as alzheimer's
bringing
people back where people can actually
know their name again
that's the power this has and that's
what this has a track record of doing
and then the heavy metal detox smoothie
has
never been better it's at the point now
where the ingredients are perfected what
i mean by that
is i haven't had a chance until pretty
recently
for the best spirulina and for the best
barley grass juice powder that you can
ever
use in a heavy metal detox smoothie and
that played a big role because
over the years i've had to use inferior
spirulinas
i've had to use inferior barley grass
juice powders
and i even had to use barley grass
before we can get a barley grass juice
powder out
there so the heavy so what happens is
when i was younger
spirit of compassion told me when i was
seven
eight years old nine years old about the
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie
and what the ingredients were and how to
use them
but it was hard to get the ingredients
it was hard to get the wild blueberry at
that time
it was hard to get a spirulina that was
worthy it was hard to get
a barley grass that was worthy it was
hard to get anything really
and so as the years gone by and i can
get the best
ingredients to actually make it work up
to the standard of spirit and compassion
where it originated and it started
medical medium book one as far as
published here
even though i was using it years before
this and this is the medical media book
new edition revise and expand you guys
got to check this book out your mind
will be blown
it's a whole new book in this um
so i'm giving you a little bit of
history of the heavy metal detox movie
showing you the ropes about that how it
works you're going to get the whole
thing today about
the power it has i'm going to make it
for us right here i'm going to talk
about things i don't normally talk
about within the heavy metal detox
smoothie too so that's exciting
so right now the medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie
is at its most powerful because
i got the wild blueberries i use the
weinman's wild blueberries
but i got that right there and i got the
vimergy spirulina barley grass juice
powder
so it's never been so powerful with the
best ingredients
there are to date and what that means is
even speedier more speedier recoveries
of anxiety
speedier recoveries of depression
bipolar
depersonalization ocd okay
ptsd alzheimer's dementia
parkinson's disease speeder recoveries
parkinson's and there's never been
anything
out there to reverse somebody's
parkinson's to reverse somebody's
alzheimer's
to reverse somebody's memory loss to
reverse somebody's
ocd condition tourette's condition okay
to reverse any of this there's never
been anything out there okay you take a
drug and you hope that it kind of
minimizes it
that's the best it does okay that's all
you can do
and even gastroparesis can be toxic
heavy metals at times
so and that has been reversed in a lot
of different people
over the years when doing the medical
medium heavy metal detox smoothie
because you're dealing with the nervous
system versus a nervous system
gastroparesis with toxic heavy metals
affecting those nerves
so we've never been in a place now
where it's been so perfect and the
opportunity to heal
a condition and this is just
the these are just some of the
conditions i'm talking about
this heavy metal detox smoothie is
instrumental
with chronic viral conditions you guys
epstein-barr related and caused
conditions
hashimoto's thyroiditis heavy metal
detox smoothie it's critical
all right fibromyalgia critical pots
critical renault syndrome
critical okay and these are just some
things
eczema and psoriasis the reason people
in the medical medium community all
right are reversing their excellent
psoriasis
for decades now getting rid of just
thousands and thousands of cases of
excellent psoriasis
and dermatitis and vitiligo and other
conditions like that and rosacea
is because they've used the medical
medium heavy metal detox smoothie and
they've gotten the metals out which
took metals away from viruses and
pathogens
toxic heavy metals are in everybody they
are the food that feeds the bugs
see guys metals feed
bugs that's how it works right and so
to get the metals out and get large
quantities of
metals out of the body you need a
powerful tool
a powerful weapon and something that
works
now be different if i was sitting here
saying well you know i don't know what
science says
and i don't know what works or doesn't
maybe collagen could work maybe it
doesn't
maybe charcoal works and it doesn't
maybe something else but
here's the deal and here's the
difference there's already a track
record
there's already a proven factual track
street cred that this heavy metal detox
smoothie
has reverse conditions even save lives
got people's lives better and that right
there is indisputable
indisputable right there
so i'm gonna make this for you i'm gonna
talk about where we get our toxic heavy
metals where do they come from
how do we get them how do they enter the
body what
forms okay and i'm going to talk about
the best way to make it using the best
stuff that's the stuff i use
now it matters if i'm using something
because that means it's the best and
that matters to the people who know me
my friends
my family anybody who knows of me and
wants to try something
knowing that i'm using something they're
like okay well that's the best one
why would he put something in him
that's not the best and so
and this medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie is
at its epic height of perfection at this
point in time in history
because i've been blessed to discover
and find
products that actually take it to the
next level
because i've had to suffer with inferior
products
in spirit of compassion's heavy metal
detox smoothie
and that's been a problem so over the
years
i've had to use a pacific pacific
spirulina
and it was okay it was as good as you
can get at the time many years ago right
and then when something came along
better i was able to dump that
and move on to something that was so
much better
the same thing with dolls and the same
thing with other things i was able to
move
on and get the best stuff out there
that there is to make this that epic
level of healing the taking it to its
full capacity
to get somebody better to get somebody
out of bed
to get them recovered to get them
healing to get their life back
to get rid of that crippling anxiety
that severe depression
and get their memory back get rid of
that depersonalization and that's just
some of the
things the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie has done
and so it's come to a point now
where unless something comes out there
that's better
than like what i'm holding in my hand as
far as the ingredients you see
as far as the beemergy spirulina and
barley grass until
something comes someday that would be a
different story right now that's the
best and this is at this epic place
i see something right there from cheryl
what would cause high level of arsenic
other than rice
apple was recently tested for heavy
metals and arsenic was
only one only one that was high please
advise
arsenic's in water so where's your water
supply
what's going on with that what's your
water supply in your body
keep that in mind arsenic can be in
pipes
so it's another thing too they have made
uh solder in all the pipes that had
arsenic in it so in all your plumbing
pipes
if you got a well your well pump can
have arsenic in it
there's arsenic in soil too and i'll
talk about that in a little bit too
so are you gardening in your garden are
the farms you're eating
local food that you're eating local
because a lot of farms use water
supplies that have arsenic in it and i'm
not talking about conventional talk
about organic
so arsenic's high in all organic food
out there
so keep that in mind too so organic food
has arsenic because
organic all kinds of organic food grown
they use water they have to pump in and
they don't test that water
and they pump that in and so and
non-organic foods really high
in arsenic so those are things there too
we also breathe it in
it drops out of the sky it comes from
different areas
and if you have farms conventional farms
nearby
arsenic is in pesticides herbicides
fungicides
so keep that in mind too it's in
herbicides pesticides
fungicides it's on new clothing so if
you buy a new clothing
it's fresh on the clothing arsenic's in
grass-fed beef
very high in grass-fed beef it's high in
lamb
it's high in and so it's out there and
that
that question is really important
because it leads me to the part i want
to talk about
is we have toxic heavy metals everywhere
and they have completely invaded our
lives
at this point in time so it's important
to know
like where they come from and how to
defend ourselves
and one way to defend ourselves is using
a tool
that has already worked for years
tool that doctors have been using for
their patients for
decades when i've been teaching about
the heavy metal detox smoothie
and it's critical it's not just about
hey have a little garlic that removes
some metals or
make something up like some people have
out there that
you know they'll say oh this helps
remove metals apple cider vinegar
can help move metals no it can't acv
doesn't
but it takes a combination
that i've been given from my source
starting
as a child and then watching it
bring lives back get people
out of mattress island get people out of
hell
to get rise out of the ashes and it's
not just
one person it's not just my
neighbor back 30 years ago who couldn't
walk
because of toxic heavy metal poisoning
and nobody knew
and then spirit of compassion knew and
then had
her do the heavy metal detox movie and
she was walking fine and got her life
back
it goes back it's historic it's not like
hey uh what's what what's this guy
selling over here what's this apple
cider vinegar chewie's now
what is this a collagen powder now it's
not
bs that's just bs out there that clogs
up
the airways for everybody to get just in
and out of and
suck into and all that and get suckered
into and
this has historic history
of working for doctors of
getting alzheimer's patients walking and
talking again
getting people out of crippling
depression where they were literally
seized up
in their bed rolling around and dying
from depression and having them sip
this and move out of it getting rid of
debilitating migraines that were toxic
heavy metal caused
eyesight problems people that were
half-blind
for no reason three-quarters blind for
no reason
got their sight back because of this
right here
so it's not like oh what's anthony doing
what's anthony william doing he's doing
his heavy metal detox smoothie that's
cool is that like the acv gummy bites
out there
or is that like you know something
stupid like mushroom coffee where you're
just you know that the drug dealers are
selling every day now that just get
people high in coffee and then throw
something in there
you know it's it's that's not it this is
before
people's time like people that got into
health four years ago
three years ago people that got into
health
10 years ago this is way before that
time this has more integrity
more merit more historic
truth of people crawling back from
sickness
than anything else out there that you
can buy or find or do or what
this is reverse epilepsy in children
this has stopped many forms of seizures
caused by toxic heavy metals now one
thing i'm going to tell you
is science research didn't know and
still doesn't
that all these conditions i mentioned to
you guys just now are caused by toxic
heavy metals
but they're starting to figure out and
they're starting to take it the
information's starting to get out there
because of the medical medium books
one is the medical medium new edition
but not the new addition but the
original and this is the new edition you
guys should check this out when you can
um that's a question i love right there
michaela says
how come you need glasses just curious
okay if you learn the history of medical
medium
you might want to get this right here
okay
the origins of a medical medium read
this chapter out of the new edition
so you can learn okay what happened
since i was age four
because of having to do readings on
people having to
see what's wrong inside their body i
spent 30 years
working with people one-on-one over 250
000 people
over the last 30 years before publishing
the medical medium books
and with that comes a price the price is
i get
what's called snow blindness i've talked
about in the books i've lectured about
it for years
it's what spirit of compassion does
sends down a light
makes it difficult for me to see in the
moment because all i see is your organs
i'll see your liver i'll see your
pancreas i'll see your intestinal tract
i'll see your brain
i'll see your bloodstream i'll see
viruses inside your body
wherever spirit of compassion tea has
has given me the gift and the sight to
see
but that white light is very blinding
and what it does is it makes me squint
now when i'm at home when i'm around
some friends
when i'm actually you know around uh you
know maybe
my family i don't use the glasses
glasses just go away
the reason why is because they know that
if white light comes
because i'm doing a read when i don't
want to because information is coming
down from spirit of compassion
they know i'll squint one eye i'll start
to squint one eye
is what i'll do and when i do that
they'll know what it is
but you guys may not because when you're
all here spirit of compassion is talking
to me because i'm getting information
about you guys
all while we're doing this so anyway
that's
that's what it is right there um
so you know so i can take off the
glasses and see perfectly fine like i've
done here on lives and so forth so
but it's there so that you guys can't
tell that i'm squinting
after a while from the white light but
either way i mean i don't know what else
to say
but other than that if you're not happy
i wear glasses i don't know what to tell
you guys
i really don't know um so we'll go back
to
go back to what the heavy metal detox
smoothie has done
it has saved lives that's the key and it
matters
fern says i stopped coffee and have
never felt
better because of you i'm honored you
did
i'm proud of you it matters that's
today's heroine
so it's good that you stopped it because
that's that's today's crack
cocaine really the industry has
everybody on it
every single person uses it everything
from trainers to nutritionists to
healers to doctors whoever it is they're
all high on
high in caffeine everybody's jacked up
on it and everybody's telling everybody
it's okay to drink it and okay to eat it
and okay to have it in your life and eat
lots of chocolate i'll talk about that a
little bit
so i want to talk about where we get our
battles before we start so you guys if
you just got on here
talking about how this heavy metal detox
movie
has been around for what quite a while
now it's reversed
tens of thousands hundreds of thousands
of people's conditions
got their lives back and that matters
because nothing else did that out there
butter in your coffee didn't and nothing
else does out there so
it's really the difference between when
you're really sick versus
you're not so sick and you're trying
cute little things out there and you're
hanging in there and you're trying a
little stuff and your acne almost goes
away it doesn't and things come back and
you're feeling okay you're working out
that's different than sick in bed you're
shaking and tremoring
okay you're you've got dizziness vertigo
tinnitus
you got fatigue with the point you can't
take your kids to school
and you're getting an autoimmune
diagnosis left and right everywhere
and no one even believes you're sick
anymore
because you've been sick so long and
you're laying in bed they start thinking
you're crazy
i'm taking what people have been through
hell and back that's what this
has done is got people's lives back not
the regular bs stuff or oh i went on a
keto diet and it got me a little better
and i lost a little weight
now try being sick try being sick
and going through something raging
eczema taking over your body well guess
what
you're gonna need this ain't no keto
diet out there gonna get rid of all that
eczema
and get rid of all that psoriasis and
get you off all those steroids
and it takes knowledge it takes
tools and it takes a history of knowing
it has worked already all of it together
is good so um
you guys keep in mind there's a lot of
people out there with fake accounts that
are pretending to be anthony williams
pretending to be me
so keep in mind they'll take a photo of
me they'll take a screenshot or
something like that and they'll
they'll try to extort money out of you
they'll try and they'll try to get why
you know they'll do wire fraud um
there's a lot of imposters
out there i don't sell classes i don't
sell courses i don't do consultations
i don't do any of this stuff okay i
write books for you guys i get free
information i teach you what tools you
use and i want you to get better and
heal
so look out for the imposters
all right so and blueberry pancakes were
so good
educating myself that's awesome okay
guys
where do we get metals so before i make
this heavy metal detox smoothie i just
want to give you the rundown those are
the frozen wild blueberries
um these are just incredible that's the
blue gold right there
really really beautiful got the cilantro
do you guys keep cilantro in your house
that's important right there okay got
the bananas
got some extra wild blueberry powder got
the
vimergy barley grass juice powder the
only one i trust and use
quality is is there's nothing like it
and i got the one
the spirulina not the hawaiian one i
want to say that because people say well
that must be the hawaiian one he talked
about in his first book
and like i said you know you can use
that one
you can use somebody else's spirulina
you could use any spirulina you can find
out there
but this is the one i use and this is
the best one
out there to date very important and so
when it comes down to removing toxic
heavy metals
you want to have the best stuff reason
why i don't like pacific coast
spirulina is because the ocean is
polluted
the highest heavy metals come from
the west coast bottom line
so the oceans in the west coast are
polluted
so if you're into surfing you're getting
doused with toxic heavy metals
on a high degree keep that in mind so
you're getting doused with mercury
getting dust with lead getting dust with
aluminum can
douse with arsenic so that's on the west
coast in the west coast oceans
so i don't like west coast derived
products coming out of the ocean on any
level
it's why i don't like the pacific
anymore like pacific spirulina
i don't like any of that so that's
number one right there you know
at the time years and years ago the
ocean
on the west coast wasn't so bad it
wasn't at
this epic terrible pollution that
it is today five years ago the west
coast the ocean
was less polluted than it is now right
now it's
historically dirty on a
level no one can imagine the west coast
so i'm letting you guys know five years
ago
seven years ago ten years ago it wasn't
as
bad and 15 years ago it wasn't that bad
so as far as like
a spirulina it's derived from the west
coast
it was the only thing out there at the
time and it just
did the job okay enough and then i had
to wait for better ones to come along
better ones so i would move to another
one that was better than that one
from you know a less polluted source and
then another one and then finally
i got the best one there ever was which
is the vimergi spirulina so i'm giving
you some history
if you look back in my first book you'll
see pacific
spirulina but like i said the ocean
was half as dirty as it is now now the
west coast
water is so bad people come out of there
with infections
they come out of there after swimming or
surfing with infections
whole another world it's changed in the
last two three years letting you guys
know
uh let's see dr fonnemd good to see you
here
yep uh hawaii's in the pacific um
so the spirulina is not as clean listen
to what he's explaining
so that's that's important to know right
there all on its own
and every little bit counts because it's
death
by a thousand cuts out there that's how
it is
so the goal for how how it works as far
as the goal for darkness the goal for
the industries the goal for chemical
companies
the goal for all of that is stab you
a thousand times until finally
everything goes wrong
and medical medium information is about
healing up every one of those stabs
wherever we can
it's about countering every little hit
kick ding slash
you know punch it's about countering
every one of those so you have the tool
to move forward you have the tool to
heal and so
let's talk about heavy metal exposure
right now let's go in there a little bit
and then we'll go into a couple other
things too so you guys if you just got
on here
i'm talking about the vimergy which is
the best products out to date right now
talking about the frozen wild
blueberries which is the best
blueberries out there that's the wymans
not sponsored and that's sponsored by
vin
got the cilantro right here got the
bananas i actually want to eat a banana
right now because i haven't eaten yet
this afternoon i had some had some
breakfast this morning i had the celery
juice
already had one of these but i haven't
eaten anything for lunch today it's
getting late
so i'm hungry for this i can't wait um
so let's talk about where we're gonna
get toxic heavy metals
all kinds of sources soda cans if you
guys ever touched a soda can
you don't have to drink soda all you
need is
a family member or a friend to be like
hey can you grab me that soda
and you just grab it and you bring it
over you just got aluminum in your body
the oil in your skin draws
metals in that's all just
touch metal with your hands
and you now own it you own that metal
bottom line that's okay we don't have to
be afraid
we just need to actually be able to get
it out of us
faster than it's coming in get the
metals out
faster than they come in that's the key
alexandra sofia is here
please have a banana she said so um we
breathe in metals
too every day every minute
and every hour they come off of your
couches
they come out of the formaldehyde that's
on your furniture
they come out of your bed toxic heavy
and metals
come out of our mattresses
okay they come out of everything we use
i use metal utensils i also use wood one
too woods
wood ones too but i use metal ones but i
know
that i'm getting that out of me easily
with the heavy metal detox smoothie
i know i'm getting rid of more than
what's coming in
porn to know pots and pans i use
stainless steel uh cookware
i do sometimes i do i've got this really
killer stainless steel soup pot it's
really big
i like to use it it fills up really high
could feed my whole family
can make a big suit but we can get metal
out of us
more and faster than any coming in
see how it works and that matters
okay fluoride treatments did you guys
ever have a fluoride treatment
because guess what that aluminum never
left
it's in you if you're not doing the
heavy metal detox smoothie
you're not getting it out there's toxic
heavy metals
in the soil every carrot you eat
every organic carrot every organic
broccoli
every organic cauliflower every organic
green bean
every organic fruit every organic herb
all your grass-fed meat all has
toxic heavy metals in it you hear that
organic organic everybody
has toxic heavy metals in it it's got
arsenic lead aluminum
mercury cadmium nickel copper
because it comes from the water supply
that feeds the organic crops that you
buy
at the food stores so when you go into
the food stores
and you're buying your organic
vegetables i got to load up on my
organic vegetables
i got to get this i got to get that
there's toxic heavy metals
all in the compens composition of all
those fruits and vegetables
yeah if you do conventional produce
right not organic
there's more there's more
and so you have to know that every
single thing you literally consume
i don't care what food you eat
has a degree of toxic heavy metals in it
because
it's coming from the water supply pumped
in
or coming out of wells to take care of
all the farmlands
and those have metals in it okay
it's also dropping out of the sky toxic
heavy metals
drop out of the sky from chemtrails
they drop out of the sky you guys should
listen to the
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
the chem show episode
they drop out with the chemtrails they
drop out from plain fuel
too all that plain fuel that you see
that's just coming out
metal that's in that petroleum they blow
around
but not just that pesticides ddt
herbicides blow around all around the
world
in the air in the air streams fill the
toxic heavy metals
perfume has toxic heavy metal in it
perfume
there's copper in it okay sometimes
mercury in it
okay cologne that also has
nickel in it cologne has nickel in it it
has copper in it got a little bit of
mercury some colognes
they have metals in them scented candles
air fresheners
loaded with toxic heavy metals you
breathe them in wherever you are
you walk into a doctor's office and they
got it going on you breathe in that
scented candle you bring it breathe in
some guys cologne next to you in the
doctor's office you breathe in somebody
else's aftershave
you're getting toxic heavy metals and
then you're sitting on somebody's
furniture whether it's in a doctor's
office or an appointment or maybe you're
getting your nails done
there's toxic heavy metals all in the
nail salons toxic heavy metals all in
the hair salons
it's everywhere and we breathe them in
and then
there's toxic heavy metals in the
pharmaceuticals
all in big pharma titanium in
almost every single drug antibiotics
are petroleum-based loaded with metals
if you had an antibiotic you've had
toxic heavy metals enter into you
so the bottom line is toxic heavy metals
are everywhere we get them there we get
them at the gas station when we're
pumping gas
we get them when we spray some kind of
spray or cleaner that's conventional
we get them when we spray some oil spray
on the door
to stop it from creaking we breathe it
right in we get it on our fingers we
just got contaminated with toxic heavy
metals
and we get toxic heavy metals from car
exhaust
you just got to breathe in one fume one
car exhaust fume
one truck fume all you gotta drip
breathe in is maybe the delivery truck
that came by breathe that in and you got
toxic heavy metals
all right dr fonz says titanium ox
dioxide in pills yes lots of it too
and then you're trying to take care of
yourself and do better
and someone tries to sell you an
alkaline ionizer water machine
which has metal plates that corrode in
every last one of them i don't care what
brand you throw up on the screen
i don't care what brand you think you
have that doesn't every last
alkaline ionizer water machine leeches
out
toxic heavy metals because the plates
corrode
whether you see it or you don't and then
you think you're doing something good
for you
and you're taking more toxic heavy
metals than you ever did before
that's just life well that's just a bad
product but also everything else i'm
telling you is life
so what are we going to do okay
toxic heavy metals are everywhere i'm
reading the comments you guys were doing
this
and so it's about countering that
the heavy metal detox smoothie has done
that
and you can't test for toxic heavy
metals you guys you know why
you can't test for toxic heavy metals
because they sit
deep within your organs toxic heavy
metals
sit deep within your brain your liver
your pancreas your spleen
your bones metals go in your bones
and the only thing i've ever trusted
to get the metals out of my body that
enter in
okay is the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie
and that's what i've always entrusted in
the five ingredients
that are critical for getting metals out
of
my bones your bones you know what
osteopenia is called caused by
osteopenia
toxic heavy metals osteopenia
toxic heavy metals degenerative spine
scoliosis toxic heavy
metals degenerative disc disease toxic
heavy metals
how about that bones getting brittle
bones getting weakened as you age
toxic heavy metals so
do we just kind of leave them in us or
do we work on
getting them out what do you want to do
you know because i'd rather get them i
would rather get
them out is what i would rather do and
that's what i've done
so toxic heavy metals are in our way
christian marie you're here and that's
been a problem
for everybody so taking control
empowering ourselves learning to do what
works matters you know
um aaron iv collation
mercury goes into tissue and lead in
bones
can't test for those can't test for
those unless you do a biopsy of a bone
you can't unless you're doing a biopsy
of your brain
unless someone drills a hole in your
skull and does a brain biopsy
you're not going to know you're not
going to know because blood testing
only tests new exposure
so if you're breathing in some air
fresheners that's only new exposure
you're gonna pick up
you're drinking your water from your
ionizer it's gonna be new exposure
okay from the toxic ionizer that's
leaching metals it's gonna be new
exposure
whatever that is it's all new exposure
that's what you're to find in the blood
test
but it's in our organs and it's in there
deep
and it's going to wreak havoc it gets
you a fatty liver down the road
and here's what really really really is
hard about toxic heavy metals you guys
what's really hard is they oxidize
wreak havoc and leech they rust
do you guys ever see anything rust
before have you ever seen anything
corrode
and rust i'm just wondering you know
because
anything that corrodes and rusts leaves
a stain
right have you ever seen that
something's rusting somewhere
you pick it up maybe you got an old
screwdriver that's sitting outside in
the rain
it's been there for a month and you grab
it and you see a little rust mark
starting to develop
whatever it is that rust you see whether
it's rust on a car
rust on some kind of door rust on metal
whatever it is that rust occurs because
that metal is oxidizing
and when your metals sit inside your
brain
and they sit inside your liver and they
sit inside your bones
they start to rust and they start to
oxidize
and then we do the high fat diets and
we're doing more high fat and we're
doing more high fat and we're oxidizing
them more
because fat and oil makes metals
bleed just hear me on a second you guys
hear me out
fats and oils make
metals bleed and corrode
so the more fat you dump in your body
and i get it everybody's on high fat
diets
they can't help it they're told it's
perfect to do they're never taught how
not to do it they're never taught how to
minimize them
and the more fats we bring into our body
the more and more we
oxidize that metal and that metal rusts
and rusts and rusts
and that's what happens and when it
rusts inside your brain
it leaches and moves over to glial cells
it moves over to
more neurons and then all of a sudden
you're getting some bad anxiety it's
getting worse
you're getting some bad ocd the ocd is
now level
three it's level four ocd now you're
getting depression
like oh my god now you're getting
depersonalization now you're bipolar
okay which is ridiculous because that
diagnosis is so
it's so backwards because really it's
just no diagnosis it's like hey you're
either up or down so let's just diagnose
you a bipolar let's create a word that
means up or down how stupid is that
right
terrible that's what medical research
and science does trillions of dollars
later medical research and science
doesn't know what causes
that symptom of feeling up and down so
they just name it bipolar
it's actually disturbing so metals are a
neuroantagonist
they disrupt your neurons they explode
neurotransmitters as if they were light
bulbs
so all your neurotransmitters all those
neurotransmitters are making you
communicate
they're making you talk they're making
you walk they're making you think you
can have a conversation with somebody
because all those neurotransmitters are
like
right well they explode they explode
like light bulbs like
that's what neurotransmitters do and
toxic heavy metals in our brain do that
and everybody has them and we're losing
neurotransmitters all the time
and then when you're 50 years old you're
like what huh
what's my name i don't i can't remember
my date of birth
i can't remember my name that starts
happening or
or i don't know i'm just forgetting
things who did i have to call i had to
make what appointment today oh
i forgot i have to write that down you
just forget everything
forget everything um courtney says hey
courtney glad you're here how do i get
my kids to drink the smoothie
popsicles i'm working on a popsicle
meaning like a recipe now because
um people have
people have electricity in their brain
because that's what we do we all have
electricity in our brain you got it
electricity's running around in your
brain it's running around on neurons
electrical impulses are swimming around
they're riding through all your brain
tissue
you've got thoughts emotions whoa i've
been betrayed boom
your electricity is unbelievable
somebody just broke my trust electricity
is unbelievable
all this electricity going on right i'm
happy i'm happy
i'm happy for a minute i'm happy for 10
seconds that's electricity going on
right
and that electricity the sad thing is
caffeine caffeine
burns out that electricity it robs it
from you it's like you take caffeine
chocolate whatever it is you're happy
for a moment but that's a
that's a drug induced happy so your your
neurotransmitters are getting eaten up
by caffeine it's destroying your brain
and all this happening there's metals in
our brain and that electricity is
running into that metal
and it's having spark attacks sparks are
flying
it's like putting a screwdriver in a
socket which i don't want you to do god
for a bit
but it's like literally short circuits
and that's the short circuit so
you're getting sick you're starting to
get depression you're starting to get
some ocd
you're starting to get some
depersonalization starting to get
anxiety
you're starting to get all of that and
what's happening is
with all that um
with all that's happening all these
conditions are starting
and that spark is dying out
because those metals they actually
collide with that electricity so
electrical impulses hit the metal inside
your brain and boom you got ocd cooking
and that ocd can get carried on and
become something else and become
something else
so okay you guys
your brain lights up like a christmas
tree when i look at it
you know when i was younger spirit of
compassion taught me to look inside
people's brains
he would give me the vision he would
show me with the light
and then he would show me that if
someone was high in toxic heavy metals
in their brain it would light up like a
christmas tree
in the vision the vision field he would
give me
and i remember as a kid
walking around in crowds of people and i
would see so many christmas trees
so many people's brains lit up left and
right just
lit up and i'm like whoa that person's
got a lot of mercury
that person's got a lot of aluminum that
person's got a lot of everything
you know question is where do brain
lesions come from
combination of toxic heavy metals and
viruses such as epstein-barr
neurotoxins too can do it so
epstein-barr neurotoxins are really
really responsible for a lot of brain
lesions that's one thing
toxic heavy metals are responsible for a
lot of them too
i've helped a lot of doctors with that
very thing with brain lesions taught a
lot of doctors about how toxic head
metals work with brain
lesions brain lesions or toxic heavy
metals that start to corrode
and they crystallize the corrosion
crystallizes did you ever see
like a battery that gets too old you
guys a battery gets too old
and it starts to corrode well that's
what happens in the brain with these
metals
when these metals are hitting
electricity
mark says my memory was was in a bad way
after
two years of the heavy metal detox
smoothie i have my memory back
thank you so much anthony it matters to
me that you got your memory back
see do i go to bed at night and that's
what i think about right there
that's what i'm thinking about i go to
back but i go to bed
and i'm thinking about mark like you got
your memory back
right and that matters to me
it does i don't clock out i'm not in a
doctor's office at five o'clock comes
and i kind of clock out and i better
just
all of a sudden go better play tennis
now i'm doing my tennis match
with my best friend and now i'm doing
that and that wait i'm on a boat now
you know i'm on a boat and i got a
martini now i'm doing that or
you know five o'clock happens and boom
i'm off family time family time he cares
about my patients i get
it everybody has the right to have a
life
and i get that but i don't clock out at
five
it goes all day all night and then right
before i go to bed
i think about you mark i think about you
getting your memory back
and i think about every one of you
getting something
back that's the bottom line so let's
make the smoothie
um so
let's do this
put this over here okay
so i'm gonna put some wild blueberries
in here but first i'm gonna drop some
bananas in let me do that
you guys don't be afraid of bananas
whatever you do
you know putting two bananas in you
could put more
if you want to put more you can put more
you can some days i will put more
what is in the heavy metal detox
smoothie sharon asks
i'm gonna put the help of these
bananas i'm gonna put that in there
and i'm gonna put um
with the help of some wild blueberries
we're gonna make this thing
i'm excited so we're gonna put bananas
in there we're gonna put some frozen
wild blueberries in here about two cups
i'm just showing you guys right here
these little guys are miracles is what
they are
so now i'm going to talk about the power
of the wild blueberry did you know
that you can't kill the wild blueberry
plant
do you know that do you know it's
impossible to kill them
do you know it's the only food on the
planet you can't
kill isn't it interesting put a little
bit more in here you guys
it's the only food on the planet
you can't destroy and stomp out
you can kill all our food
you can kill every cow on the planet and
they'll be gone forever
you can kill every strawberry patch on
the planet
and they'll be gone forever you can kill
every single chicken
on the planet and they'll be gone
forever
there was this one chicken though you
guys remember the story a long time ago
had his head chopped off and was still
alive
and then he would eat through his neck
so
i've asked spirit of compassion how that
happened and how it was even possible
because it was an absolute mystery
mystery to science and i got the answer
but i'm just not going to tell you right
now
i'll tell you maybe on a podcast um
so anyway the bottom line is
you can't kill the wild blueberry plant
you can
burn it to the ground in the fields
and they'll come back up but you burn an
oak tree
and it's not coming back up an oak tree
you can kill every oak tree on this
planet and it'll be gone for good
you can't kill the wild blueberry and
guess what it's
that power it has
that makes this that makes this heavy
metal detox movie what it is
it's it's the basis it's the core
but you got to have everything else but
it's the core
and that matters so noelle shepard says
tell hey noelle
phillip k says i thought i just said i
missed the comment but
glad you're here phillip k appreciate it
um
so yeah the bottom line is it's michelle
l i just saw that alien chicken it's
funny
this is the core fundamental basis
the epicenter the powers in that wild
blueberry
but you gotta have the rest and let's go
into it let's talk about it first of all
i just put the wild blueberries in here
you guys all right
just saying you see it right and the
wild blueberry
has reaching powers into your brain
into your brain stem it's got reaching
powers it can overreach and that's what
you want
in the wild blueberry can do that
anthocyanins undiscovered by research
and science sit in wild blueberries
because guess what science won't take
their time out to study it because like
i told
you before to actually fix things on
this planet chronic illness
you would need true science that's
actually
working for the people and not for
somebody's pocket and so what's
in this right here is undiscovered by
research and science anthocyanins that
are undiscovered
that's one of the key tickets another
key ticket is it's
it literally stops the metals from
rusting
in the brain so those frozen wild
blueberries
stop metals from rusting so that's the
thing right there i'm giving you some
powerful tidbits
on each one of these if i can let's keep
on going
let's put um let's just put some some
oranges in here let's get some oranges
in here
let's do that you guys i'm going to cut
some orange these are small oranges so
i'm going to pop in two
but they're small oranges
i like small oranges
i got a little straightener right here
and you'll see here
it's a metal strainer what do we have
here
okay it's a metal strainer but i don't
care
because whatever little leeches out of
the strainer over the years
this smoothie is going to remove it
times a thousand
and that's why so you know there's
something about
insurance right you know you're happy
when you got car insurance because
if you didn't have car insurance right
that would be a problem okay
um but the heavy metal
detox smoothie is insurance
it's an important insurance policy in
your life
and it's one that gives something back
to you no matter what
and that's what i love about it that's
how i see it too it's an important
insurance policy
it's like
so i'm popping in some orange here
alexandra said aw
is it okay to put the juice of three
oranges in your heavy metal detox
smoothie yes
it is just saw a question on millet yeah
no it's great but don't put in your
heavy metal detox smoothie montana
i know you're not talking about that
all right i got a little juice let me
put a little more because these are
really small
put a little bit more in here i squeeze
them with my hand that's what i do
can we use the whole orange cindy says
can we use the whole orange yes
all right so i get a little bit in there
there we go i got the orange in there
happy i'm gonna put a little bit of
dolls
put a tablespoon a few strips in it you
could put a teaspoon if you really want
to
it's fine but i'm putting that in here
a little bit
and then let's go into the rest of this
stuff
i got some cilantro to put in but i'm
gonna the barley grass juice powder so
that's the vimergy one right there
now here's an important critical thing
to know all right
you don't want to use barley grass that
you don't want to do
don't use barley grass that's important
okay
um it has to be barley grass juice
powder the vimergy one
is the best there is hands down it's the
purest
it is the best and
what i love about it is it has
a heavy metal detoxifying structure to
it
it's built it's created
the way it's created it can absorb
metals
hold on to them pull them out of the
body so it has a magnetic
effect to grab onto metal
in the body and that's what i love about
it
because it's not just about removing
metals
it grabs on to them as it runs into them
floating around
and the reason why you got to have the
barley grass juice powder you got to
have the spirulina you got to have the
wild blueberries you gotta have the
dulce and the cilantro
they work off each other they're a team
that's how you get something done
you need a team of people to get
something done sometimes right you guys
will you need a team
of heavy metal grabbers detoxifiers
pullers um you know and dislodgers
that's what you need so we'll go on
we'll keep on moving on i just put the
dolls in here now what i love about the
dolls is
it's incredible for grabbing toxic heavy
metals out of your intestinal tract
we have toxic heavy metals in our
stomachs everybody's stomach
has got metals in the linings stuck
in the linings what i love about the
dolls
okay the atlantic dolls is
it removes metals out of the lining
of the stomach it removes easy to find
metals not deep seated metals
the barley grass juice powder the
spirulina the blueberries
get the deep seeded metals
the dulce it gets perimeter metals
that are important to get your small
intestinal tract your colon
metals that are feeding bacteria metals
that are feeding viruses
it's getting it out so that's important
there so i just did
a little bit of dolson there let's put
some spirulina
so
that one's a favorite of mine right
there this is the best stuff
on the market today hands down
could bet my life on it i know
what it's comprised of i've seen
every single one out there i've picked
through them
tooth and nail all the stuff i've talked
to all the companies
all through the years by far best one
and it matters because if you put a
crappier one in which you can
you get maybe some metal out but
not as much as you could have or if it's
a really bad spirulina you get
no metal out and these foods
have the power of absorbing metals
lots of metal wherever it can find it
and that's what i love about it so the
spirulina
so here's the thing here's something
that's very important i'm still making
this smoothie
when you remove toxic heavy metals you
got an empty space
you got an empty space think about that
toxic heavy metals make a divot and a
pit inside your brain
and the more they oxidize the bigger the
divot
when you have alzheimer's that pit is
getting big
when you gotta focus on concentration
issues when you got
ocd really bad the pits and the nooks
and crannies get
big so what happens is in your brain
tissue
metals start to actually
burn a hole in your brain
electrical impulses are slamming into
those metals
and those metals are getting hot and
they're burning
into your brain tissue
as that happens over time you got now a
pocket
you got tiny microscopic pockets
inside your brain tissue
and that's there when you remove metals
you still got those pockets you still
got those microscopic
issues and that's why this is a miracle
from what i've seen in the last 35 plus
years even longer
the reason why it's a miracle is because
it doesn't just take the metals out
it fixes and repairs the hole
and that's the key right there it's not
just taking
something out it's putting something
back
in and that's what it's doing
i'm gonna put some cilantro here um
i love cilantro as a leafy green there's
a question right there from donna is
carella okay no it's not
no i've seen a lot of people bent over
the sides of their bed
barfing for days and days because of
corella i've seen lots of people
holding onto the toilet so tight where
they lived in the bath on the bathroom
floor for days
puking their guts out because of corella
cruella has microorganisms
and microorganisms in it that are not
supposed to be there
okay and bacteria bad bacteria
i wouldn't trust corella someone handed
to me i'd smack it out of their hand
because i wouldn't even want it near me
and
corella doesn't remove metals i don't
know where that farce came from and if
it ever did remove a little bit of metal
it would drop it immediately
so to this day i still can't believe
it's just out there
i can't tell you how many people have
barfed their guts out because of
basically food poisoning and um so no
i'm just not a fan
not a fan there's somebody up there uh
roberta says no wait let's see
sorry um they're going up so quick
anna anna says cruella made me so sick
god bless you i hope you got through it
i've known people i've known people that
have literally been
holding onto their toilet on the
bathroom floor
and and and like for days until they
ended up in the hospital
many didn't many did just awful
but you know what i could say it all day
long and it's
still out there and people are still
gonna take it and some influence are
still gonna be like i'm putting cruella
in my
acai bowl and i'm putting corelli in my
peanut butter smoothie and it's like
what
it's just like you can't you can't fix
everything
you can't fix everything out there i
mean i've been doing this third 35 years
and
i just can't fix everything um and all
the mess-ups so
if someone's high in metals
they'll have an aversion to cilantro
so you're not going to want cilantro i
put cilantro in here you guys because
you're high in metals you're not even
going to want cilantro keep that in mind
if it gives you a bad bad taste that
means you're really high in heavy metals
if you needed to keep the cilantro out
keep it out
okay keep it out three out of five ain't
bad
four out of five ain't bad if you gotta
do it that way
so if you gotta do the spirulina wild
blueberry powder
uh look got it if you can't get wild
blueberries do the wild blueberry powder
i forgot to put that in you gotta do the
spirulina the wild blueberry powder
the barley grass juice powder wild
blueberries bananas if you can get stuff
like that
but if you if you have to keep out
if you have to keep something out like
the cilantro then keep that out and do
four out of five
and you're still gonna get the metals
out but
there's gonna be an imbalance but you
live with it until you can handle your
cilantro someday
if you don't have wild frozen wild
blueberries the
bimmerjee wild blueberry powder
anyway still working on this
yeah corella seriously i just saw that
comment right there come up or
someone was laughing let's blend this
up
so
reading some comments
what's my opinion on cmos i think it's
fine
the cmos isn't going to replace dolls
there we go i think i've made this a lot
of times i'll tell you
let's get one going here
and then you could get a spoon and kind
of get the rest out
if you can see that
heavy metal detox smoothie right there
there's a question right there i have
got
extreme so anna says i've got extreme
eczema on my hands and arms
don't understand why i am doing
everything right
detox how many fats are in the diet
because the fats can get in the way
did you do a new pharmaceutical lately
at all is there a new pharmaceutical in
your life
something new that you might have got or
received
because there's a lot of metals in there
eczema is caused by copper and the
epstein-barr virus inside the liver so
i've talked about that in the books
and
are you doing the antiviral protocol you
can take the book to your doctor or
health care provider somebody that might
might help you with the protocol if you
want
and there's a protocol on here antiviral
for
eczema answer is this have you embarked
on it yet
how far are you going because you can go
really far
really far to the finish line with the
medical medium tools
and are you using the right ingredients
another thing too to consider are you
doing any nutritional yeast
get rid of it are you doing apple cider
vinegar get rid of it
you might not be doing any of those i
totally get it um what are you doing
caffeine are you doing chocolate all you
need is chocolate once a month the
eczema is going to stick around
and is the diet too high in fat because
it doesn't allow the
copper to leave so the higher fat your
diet is
the harder it is to get that metal out
to get the virus out so keep
them there's a lot of place to go don't
do any eggs don't do milk cheese butter
don't do any anything like that and um
have you done the 369 cleanse advance
have you done that have you done the
28-day cleanse of medical medium book
one by
you guys this is a new edition i hope
you you get a hold of it amazon.com
revise and expand it carl says thank you
anthony glad you're here
thank you for being here carls um and
you guys if you go to my director i see
questions about the kitchenware and
stuff
go to my directory medicalmedium.com my
directory on there
you'll find it you'll find kitchen
kitchen stuff juicers et cetera
everything
you'll know which one to use and all
that
drink your smoothie then if i drink my
smoothie i'm going to look like it did
on the tick tock video did you guys see
that the morning cleanse tik tok video
you didn't see that one the wee will
rocky song the queen song
um
because i will make a mess you guys know
how i drink my smoothies right
just watch that video and you'll see how
i drink my smoothies i'm going to ig
and tik tok at the same time now if you
go to ig
to watch me do this again talk about
stuff might talk about some different
stuff that i didn't cover i forgot to
cover
you go to ig just remember if you're
having any kind of glitch go to tick
tock i'm going to be on there live just
letting you guys know
love you guys bless your heart
and uh i can't wait to see you guys
again
i'll try to do one of these soon again
with everything else
um lorraine good to see you just saw you
go up
you guys so i got your back
want you guys to keep healing and uh
come on over to instagram
maybe i don't know maybe i'll say some
stuff all right love you bye