it's real get ready June 15th in La at
irwan it's going to be the heavy metal
detox launch party you don't want to
miss it I'm going to say hi to everybody
it's going to be incredible and I'm
going to be doing the book signing bring
your book I'd love to sign it I'd love
to meet you in person I don't know if
I'm ever going to do an official book
signing again it's the first official
medical medium book signing ever ever in
the medical medium book series or any
books that I've ever put out I'm I like
I never did a book signing ever
collaboration between Iran and medical
medium putting the heavy metal detox
smoothie in the store The Heavy Metal
detox made fresh I can't wait that heavy
metal detox smoothie is saving lives
around the world it has been for a very
very long time I'm so glad you're using
it the heavy metal detox is
powerful and what happened was the books
got out and this book right here
millions of this book got out around the
world and this chapter right here blew
people away and they learned how to do
the heavy metal detox and when they
learned how to do it they healed and
when they healed they spread the word
and guess what someone else got the book
and healed and someone else got the book
and healed right the one that works is
the one with the street cred the one
that actually has healed people around
the world and it changes lives and fam's
lives that's why the heavy metal detail
talks is incredible the one that irwan
is going to be making fresh every single
day starting June 15th at the launch
party I will be there I'm excited I
can't believe it actually can't believe
it can't believe it I haven't done
anything like this in in like almost a
decade I haven't done a book signing
ever thousands have already registered
for the event and I'm going to be there
and I'm excited to say hi I actually
can't believe it
[Music]