and that's important because a lot of
people they don't know
like the ebbs and flows of healing it's
three steps up two steps down
five steps up
one step down
seven steps up five steps back
nine steps up one step back
and now you're driving your car oh my
god i'm feeling kind of energetic i'm
driving my car i'm not having panic
attacks anymore my fatigue is leaving me
now i'm not feeling as dizzy
so i'm actually doing a little better
i'm not getting the heart racing today
it's a little better and then it's like
nine steps up
another step up
two steps back and what happens is as
you're healing
you over exert yourself so if you're
somebody
who is just on mattress island and you
were stuck on mattress island and you
were stuck there
for a while where you're like 20 hours a
day in bed 15 hours a day in bed couch
island 10 hours a day on couch island
right
and now you're starting to get better
because you're doing all this great
stuff you're taking the the right kind
of b12 you're taking the right kind of
licorice you're doing your lemon balm
tea you're doing some celery juice
you're doing some other things you're
reading some details on how to heal and
learning and you're getting rid of a
couple of foods that were causing
trouble and then you start going up and
then you start going up okay you guys
right
and as you're going up
you're gonna
do more than you have in a long time
you're actually
going to do more
and when you do more and that could be
just that you're in the kitchen so now
you're in the kitchen and you're working
more in the kitchen you're working in
the kitchen sink and now you're washing
more stuff and you're doing more and
you're 10 minutes more in the kitchen
sink and then you're doing some other
things too
maybe you're doing some other stuff and
what happens is i'll go take a walk now
i'm taking a walk now i'm taking a
20-minute walk
and then we do more
because we're getting better our nervous
system is getting stronger we're healing
and then we go back
we get kicked back
but we're still better than where we
were before
we're kicked back and then we panic oh
my god am i getting sick again
everything i'm doing is wrong everything
i'm doing is wrong nothing i'm doing is
right i'm panicking and then you you go
back but you don't know it
but you're a little bit better and one
symptoms getting a little bit better
this other symptoms getting a little bit
better
but you kind of forget a lot of people
forget they forget they could well wait
a minute what happened because i was
talking to somebody the other day i was
talking to a doctor friend that's
healing now through medical medium
information these doctors get sick
and
the doctors get sick
been helping a lot of sick doctors for
too many years and this this this doctor
friend said you know look i i'm i don't
know if i'm getting better anymore i'm
like
what's your old symptoms my old symptoms
was this this this do you still have
that anymore no i don't
you're right
it was a lot worse or what about this oh
yeah you're right that symptom was a lot
worse and then i said what have you been
doing well i went i took the i took my
kids out on a boat on sunday
i'm like you took your kids out on the
boat when's the last time you've done
that
i haven't done that since i've been sick
so you did a whole thing this sunday you
went out with family right you took
family out on a boat
was it you were in the sun well it was
really cold and i was freezing and i had
a jacket on
okay
all right
you did a lot that day well yeah because
then we went to a restaurant and
everybody was in there and i asked i
asked for some steamed vegetables in the
restaurant and i asked for an avocado in
the restaurant and then i did that and
then we went and then we went go visit
grandma and then i said oh my god is
that the most you've done in a while
goes yeah because you know i haven't
been working
a sick doctor that hasn't been able to
work i said so you did all this and now
come monday
and come tuesday you're kicked back a
little bit and now you're getting scared
because you you over exerted yourself
but that's normal because when we start
healing and we start healing a little
bit we start doing more
right you guys that's what happens to a
lot of people when they start healing
i've seen people that were bedridden
and then got the b12 in them they're
bedridden with chronic fatigue syndrome
me
right
brain inflammation chronic fatigue
syndrome they bend every doctor they're
on mattress island their legs feel like
sandbags they feel like they're they're
holding cement
can't even hold their body up they
atrophy because they can't exercise and
then boom they're they're in bed they're
on mattress island a lot and i'm like
well you've got to take your b12 and
they've taken the b12 each day each day
and all of a sudden
they're not hurting so bad and they're
elbow
and they're getting a little bit more
energy for about five minutes during the
day and they're like oh my god this is
amazing and then 10 days later they're
getting more energy and then they push
it too far and now they're often hurting
again for a little bit and they're like
what do i do what's going on i
understand i said you do three steps up
two steps back three steps up two steps
back the healing process it's three
steps up and then five steps up and then
nine steps up two steps back and then
you're further than where you were
before
further than where you were before when
you're doing the right things and you
know about the details to heal and
you're bringing in your cellular juice
in your heavy metal detox smoothie
you're taking the right kind of b12 and
you're doing these things a little bit
at a time whether you're an animal
protein person or a plant-based protein
person but you're doing a little bit of
time and you're bringing it in
and then you can you start to recover
and you start getting stronger it comes
to a point where eventually
you're living your life again
and
you're really pushing now the envelope
you're living your life again so now you
go to the beach take two hour walk
now you you go to visit a friend now you
make this whole you know you make a
dinner party for a whole bunch of family
coming over now you do this and then
you're like oh my god i'm getting my
life back i'm living my life and then
the next day or two you're just you're
zonked you ran on the treadmill and now
you're zonked
because you're doing the three steps up
two steps back there's so many different
scenarios it could be the most serious
scenario where someone's been bedridden
for a long time they had every diagnosis
from neurological lyme to ms or anything
else and they can't take a shower
because when they get into the shower
the water hits them on the back of the
head
head and they almost get knocked over by
it and after the shower they have to go
and just try to get like their robe on
and lay in bed and they're in bed and
they're literally shaking not because
they're cold but they're shaking in bed
because it was a lot for them even on
that scale they're still three steps up
two steps back and now you're taking a
shower now you're able to wash your hair
now you're able to do things like this
and it's like you get it's just up and
then you get kicked back a little it
could be on that
that kind of serious scenario
to
you're strong and you're exercising but
you're not at the top of the game
because you're rehabbing and getting
stronger and stronger right it's in in
the rehab process after an illness comes
so even though you're getting your
nervous system stronger and you've got
your b12 right you guys and you're
getting yourself stronger and you're
doing your lemon balm and your lemon
ginger and you're doing your lemon
ginger honey and you're doing all the
different tools you're aloe you're doing
your aloe vera water right the medical
medium aloe vera water and you're doing
all these things you're doing your lemon
water you've got your cucumber juice
you're doing your heavy metal detox
smoothie right
that's the wild blueberry powder you're
what you know right you're doing your
spirulina even if you're doing a little
bit of it you're doing your spinach soup
so you're blending your spinach soup you
guys and you're doing your spinach soup
you're doing these tools and you start
getting better
on your rehab you still need to rehab a
little bit
and say you're doing a mono cleanse for
your gastroparesis say you're doing the
cleanse
say you're doing the morning cleanse or
the heavy metal detox cleanse and you're
taking some of the supplements in here
too so you're taking some of the
supplements right
knowing the cause and the protocol so
now you're learning and you're like whoa
i can take a little bit of licorice root
anthony says inside here you can start
really slow because it's not one size
fits all it's customizable and you can
do a little bit of licorice a little bit
of b12 and then you start to move
forward
and as you're moving forward you're
getting stronger and you're gonna use
that energy you're gonna use it and
you're gonna use it
hard
that's what you're gonna do you're gonna
be like i'm gonna push it now because
and i see this with everybody healing
since i was age four i have watched
every person who has ever you know come
to me throughout since i was a child and
their healing process is same like even
sports people now like olympic athletes
that talk to me right that i've known
they've been friends with
for years they're like well i injured my
leg
and i want to go right back to full
throttle i'm like
you go back to full throttle right now
you're going to get kicked back so let's
let's let's build up so your three steps
up and you're going to kick back a
little bit and then you get a lit it's a
rehab process and a chronic illness if
there's something similar to that
and how long it takes for somebody to
heal
depends
on a few things if you guys got a second
to hear this for a second
how long it takes to heal
depends
on what's wrong inside
do you have just the shingles virus
giving you some aches in your jaw do you
have the epstein barr giving you fatigue
and brain fog
do you have streptococcus giving you
chronic utis at the same time and
chronic sinusitis or whatever do you
have three varieties of strep because
the doctors won't know do you have two
varieties of shingles you have three
varieties of epstein-barr or do you have
just a lot of heavy metals right maybe
you had a lot of dental work done and
you had lots of metal through that how
many fluoride treatments have you had
what kind of obstacles have you been up
against right
all these things matter
how many toxins are inside of us you
guys right
how many
toxins how many combinations of toxic
heavy metals do you have inside of you
too so how many
combinations of toxic heavy metals are
inside your brain
are is your epstein bar stronger than
someone else's epstein-barr you know
what happens in the medical medium
community
people come to the community
years ago or whatever and they heal
they heal
they go on their merry way
and then they get themselves sick again
they either contract another
new epstein bar
they contract a new
bacteria streptococcus maybe from a new
relationship because that's life that's
how we have to live we have to we meet
people whatever and now we got a new
book and all of a sudden now
problems are coming back
and that's the incredible thing about
medical medium information then it's
time to do it again and to get rid of
these bugs a lot of people
have a lot of different metals than them
and different bugs and different
combinations and different toxins and
chemicals right all these different
things they have inside of them
so everybody's healing process is at a
different time frame it's at a different
time
someone could heal one thing really
quick
jennifer pierce says my ibs was acting
up so bad been doing lemon water celery
juice and heavy metal detox today was a
great day finally out of pain and not
stop stopping thank you thank you thank
you with a heart bless your heart for
being here right
so you guys healing process and the
timely fashion of the healing process
also depends on
what
traps have been set that are taken
our butts down let's go into that a
little bit next all right
the traps rosemary says how do you know
what you have do you need a medical
diagnosis
medical medium information
originally started out for people
who've been to 20 doctors 10 doctors 15
doctors specialists you guys know
and they still couldn't figure out what
was going on so the books here
the medical textbooks are here go to the
library and get it for free
just like this lecture right now is free
okay i didn't want anybody paying for
this talk right now
we can do that we can do that all day
long i have people promotion companies
reach out to me and be like i noticed
you don't do any pr
you don't have any pr firms
why don't you let us run all your
promotions and then you lock all your
people out and you ring them all
together to pay a fee so you can lecture
to them and they can't see you unless
they pay i'm like get out of here
get out of here
it's free
so you can look into the book get free
the library or amazon.com if you want to
get it on sale there 51 off
talk about traps and obstacles
this is a big one
this one's critical just so you know
right and
this charcoal right here
i got this whole thing's filled with
charcoal i've been
drinking charcoal and you know i'm
kidding
prime example right there
somebody
wanting to get better and then them
they're taking something like charcoal
activated charcoal and they're
swallowing it
it's that kind of thing that could set
people back terribly who are struggling
and trying to move forward this is lemon
balm tea
there's lots of traps like that out
there so healing depends on how many
traps were set did you do all the coffee
enemas that could set you back in
healing for years
if you're not doing the right stuff
did you do the sodium bicarbonate game
it can set you back for years
guzzling all that sodium bicarbonate
in your intestinal tract
nightmare
did you do the apple cider vinegar
game could totally trash your stomach
that's just a start right
did you do the diatomaceous earth
particles did you do the chlorella
did you do the pearl powder
this pearl powder will ruin your
intestinal tract the problem is with the
pearl powder
is unfortunately there's going to be a
whole bunch of young adults
that are going to be hurting really bad
down the road in their stomachs and
intestinal tracts from getting sucked
into the pearl powder game right
did you do the alkaline ionizer water
machines with all the medical met the
metal particles that break free off of
the
right the metal plates all these things
they add up so here you are you're
trying to heal
and it depends on what the person has
done so it may take time to heal or at
least learn how to stop these things the
scale tips so someone's like well i'm
trying to get better and i'm working on
it why is it taking so long and you go
through their stuff they got natural
flavors msg and everything they got all
this other stuff going on
that i'm talking about so the traps are
laid
the bait and switches are laid
they're all sitting there so someone
who's chronically ill is just gonna walk
along and that's what they're gonna do
and they're gonna walk around because
they're stuck in the woods
when you're chronically sick you don't
have answers and you've been to doctor
the doctor and now you're trying every
trendy trap you're in the woods you're
walking in the woods and then you step
oh my god
[Music]
you step on a bear trap and you now got
a cage
going like this on your ankle
and you can see the light on the outside
of the woods but you can't get to the
other side of the woods you can't get
there
because the the bear trap
is crushing your leg and keeping you in
the woods for another two years
another three years another four years
right
so the bear traps are laid out there
some are harmless like chlorophyll drops
which won't get you better but it won't
hurt you that bad unless it's an alcohol
or some other garbage and then it can
hurt you but so just takes me to the
next level here fear-mongering let's go
into that right now
so every now and then i'll see a comment
from a hater or a naysayer right or
somebody from the medical medium hate
groups because there's a ton of them out
there they just love to hate on somebody
and
the kick kick me sign on my back really
you know is a great place to just you
know kick
but what people don't realize is that
it's not about fear-mongering
because i'll see somebody say that one
time
it's about saving lives if you're not
sick
you can play in that game for a while
until you get really sick so you can do
the chlorella
and the fulvic acid and the shilajit
doctor friend of mine calls it shallot
and you can do
all of these things and don't realize
though right
don't realize because you're not so sick
you don't realize that the coffee enemas
and the chocolate cacao 90 bars and 74
bars and cacao powder in your smoothies
you don't realize in the apple cider
vinegar and the diatomaceous earth
particles right
and then you don't realize the pearl
powder and
right and dousing mct oil you don't
realize that this is hurting more than
helping because you're not that sick yet
so the scale isn't really tipping you
can't tell what the coffee animals are
doing quite yet
so
those people might be like well fear
mongering i do my coffee enemas and i'm
fine yeah
when someone's on mattress island
they're really sick and they got real
fatigue real problems serious brain fog
they do coffee enema and they're trashed
trashed so i don't call it
fear-mongering i call it saving lives i
call it critical information it's just
that people who aren't sick enough yet
or aren't sick at
all they're just
ignorant to the information right
laura tong from youtube says michelle l
i'm
seizure free for many months now just
bought a few bemorgy products i'm
healing
incredible incredible
incredible
so
you know you want to know if you're
going to fall into a tiger snare
and there's jagged
wooden sticks that have been carved to a
point down at the bottom of the hole and
you want to know if you're going to go
down in that you call that fear monitor
i call it like dude i just i'm trying to
stop you from messing yourself up really
bad
so you have a shot to heal
if you're really sick you feel that
scale tip really quick
that coffee enema is one last coffee
enema before you're really screwed up
same thing with air fresheners
people will be like oh he's
fear-mongering about air fresheners
they're wondering about it
critical to make sure you pull those air
fresheners out of those walls and you
throw them out that's critical that you
take those and you throw those babies
out
because those air fresheners are
poisoning you and they will drop your
immune system down and they will fill
you with toxic heavy metals and
it's about protection
because guess what prime example if
someone says oh classic aw fear
mongering
how about this you don't know what it's
like to be sick you don't know what it's
like to be kicked down you don't know
what it's like to be really sick going
to too many specialists you don't know
what it's like to spend
tens of thousands and thousands of
dollars on all kinds of tests you don't
know when it's real what it's like to
get blood tests after a blood test after
blood test after blood test after blood
test
and then
over and over again oh sorry the blood
work was another 1200 oh sorry blood
work was another 700 oh you got your
copay you got your health insurance
what people don't realize is there's
this tipping scale
so healing
isn't just doing things right it's
making sure you don't do some of these
things wrong i've always said to
alkaline ionizer water machines
will make you mental it will take you
down a terrible path and it does to
people they don't know for a while and
then those metals get to the brain
because the metal plates
no one realizes it but the metal plates
are corroding and that's highly
corrosive material
and then they end up where they can't
even talk their tongues won't even work
things go wrong with them
and their tongue won't even work
and they get these crazy neurological
symptoms in vegas their problems and
they go downhill and they never knew
because no one ever said no one ever
said stay away from the alkaline ionizer
water machines where no one ever said
stay away from the charcoal powder
because that stuff will make you so
deficient you're you'll fall apart down
the road but it's not about fear because
you can correct what the damage was but
you got to know how to correct it you
got to get the metals out you got to get
the toxins out you got to know how to
restore everything alexis said this is
really motivational thank you anthony in
spirit of compassion let's thank you for
being here
ruby says
you're like a friendly signpost trying
to protect and guide people i'm honored
you're here thank you on facebook and
alexis on youtube
thank you for being here you guys truly
because i know you guys you guys got a
lot going on you guys trying to live
your lives you guys are doing all kinds
of things and the fact that you're here
and hanging out with all of us right now
and with me right now is an honor i just
want to say that i never say that enough
by the way i never say that enough
so
it's about making sure we can kind of
protect each other
and i think that's why the medical
medium community
gets picked on so much too
because you guys are the salt of the
earth
the better you are
as a person and as a soul the more crap
you get the more crap you get
because
the bullies out there they want you to
be in their bully pack right
and the medical meme community is is a
community that's just so just a heart of
gold really salt of the earth
people that actually care they really
care you know
and they're seasoned and that's the key
they're seasoned you guys
i trust the people in the medical
meeting community if i was sick if i was
sick and i didn't know anything right
and i saw your stories and what you guys
are doing and everything i would trust
in that because you guys are on a level
a whole nother level you've been through
it you've been through it
you really have so we're talking about
the healing process so we're live right
now you guys just letting you know right
and
okay
check out my free downloads
right medicalmedium.com or link right
there you check out the link in
description link in the bio check out my
free
downloads epstein barr download
my anxiety download my depression
download axima psoriasis download acne
download check them out when you guys
get a chance
i'm trying to produce as much free
information as i can wherever i can
that's the goal all the time okay
new exclusive videos on tick tock to new
exclusive videos on snapchat check out
my newsletter
right i do a newsletter video every
sunday morning
and i'm going to start doing some more
exclusive messages on telegram soon so
check that out too
right
and i'm on me wee and i'm going to be
doing exclusive material on me as well
so i want to let you guys know that
so anyway if you're wondering someone
just asked me like what's in the cup
lemon balm tea i love it
lemon balm is
a very very healing herb
right
so let's go into the healing process
it's not just about doing things right
it's about looking out for what we could
be doing wrong
no one's to blame meaning you're not to
blame
if you've been pulled into a coffee
enema
told you should be eating lots of cacao
powder
which blows out your adrenals and
nervous system
told to be doing apple cider vinegar
shots
told to be doing charcoal told to be
doing fulvic acid totally doing fulvic
minerals
told to be doing shilajit
now i'm not here to rip all those down
i'm just saying been there done that
most people who have been through the
healing process they tried all that
they've been sucked into each one and
then they're sucked into the next one
and the next one and don't get tricked
by the pearl powder people now
because the pearl powder people are
drinking celery juice and then they're
selling their pearl powder like as if
that's helping but they're drinking
their celery juice take their celery
juice away
and they're taking their zinc their b12
medical medium tools zinc b12 they're
drinking their celery juice and they're
like oh by the way i'm not going to show
you that but let me show you this pearl
powder right here oh my god this pearl
powder will make your skin so nice and
so great you'll look incredible you lose
all your weight even though i'm on the
treadmill for two hours a day i'm on my
peloton for two hours a day um yeah and
uh never been sick i've never been sick
but this is a great scam i'm gonna show
you this is jogger by the way i'm gonna
show you my pearl powder
right meanwhile i'm going to drink my
celery juice did not talk about that
don't get sucked in by that pearl powder
the stuff cakes on the inside of the
linings and it does damage the ins
inside the linings the testing track
which scars the linings over time
venom sweet says thank you for all you
do i'm pretty new to you but absolutely
love you and what you are doing and look
forward to my healing journey bless your
heart right on youtube thank you for
being here
and you know it's incredible incredible
community people that actually care
about others
and that's the thing and you know what
happens it gets mistaken like i noticed
that the medical meme community cares so
much about other people that when you
come on there and you say well i just
you know i'm doing this uh ionizer and
coffee enema and then somebody in the
community be like that's not good you
got to be careful to be like oh you're
too me and you're too mean
it's like what it's like no just trying
to save you deborah says i love your
newsletter yeah i'm doing these new
videos on the newsletter you guys every
sunday
so it's really it's really fun
it's medicalmedium.com you can find it
on there too so let's talk about this
let's talk about blood draw just for a
couple of minutes
okay
all right so blood draw i want people to
get their blood test if they want to get
their blood test
i like blood tests for people never was
against it
what happens is people get too much
blood drawn
this can make or break somebody's
healing process big time
getting too many vials of blood taken at
once
that is a big problem right there okay
so and what happens is people don't
realize it
and these are the small vials people get
the big tubes people are getting the big
tubes
right the doctor will will send some
blood to the lab or the phlebotomist
will you know will grab some blood from
you right
and it's like okay how many do we have
right here right
these are small ones these are like baby
tubes right 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12.
12 vials of blood right there okay the
small tubes and they don't take these
small tubes really
so what people don't realize is that's
one
of the ways we can't heal
if we're doing the right stuff
it gets countered
by doing the wrong stuff
blood tests are good
i believe in it but what happens is when
they keep on drawing too much blood and
you don't know what to do you don't know
how to tell the doctor can you please
just take two
vials
and then i'll come back another time and
you could take another two
but take two or three vials max at a
time
but they'll take no we'll take five
vials seven files 20 miles 30 vials
right and they're removing your your
immune cells
out of your bloodstream is what happens
so your immune cells are being sucked up
and tossed out
and that's what happens
then
the reason why you're at the doctors
with all your pain and suffering and
your diagnosis and your autoimmune
diagnosis and everything else
because of pathogens
your immune system is trying to protect
you from the pathogens
so it's keeping the pathogens down
you're still sick because you've got the
pathogens and you're still sick because
your immune system is weak
but then
we get all these
orally says i only allow three to five
vials at a time brilliant
brilliant
i tell my friends and family only allow
two to three vials at a time
or
three to five half vials that's what i
tell my friends and family to do but you
do whatever you know you want to do and
your doctor wants to
so you end up drawing out
from all the blood work
the very thing that protects you from
why you're sick
and then
you get sicker a month later could get
sicker a week later two months later but
then you've got to go to the doctor
again
and then he sends you to a specialist
and now he's taking this plus way more
and then the doctor's just gambling away
your blood right here
okay i think i got a deck of cards
sitting over there i think i'm gonna
grab in a second
on the table and
because i think we're gonna
you know we'll do a little gambling real
quick
we'll do a little i don't know we'll get
some cards out
we'll have some fun okay
because
this is how it works and these cards are
the cool cards because these are the
wyman's wild blueberry cards
you guys this is really cool
a stack of wyman's wild blueberry cars
haven't even opened these yet it's
amazing right there
pretty awesome we got a deck of cards
right here right
so what happens is
everybody starts to gamble your blood
away well
i think we're going to do a couple of
tests we don't really know what's wrong
with you
we don't know really why you're sick we
just think you got autoimmune
i'm gonna bet four vials of your blood
away here see we got here let's get some
right
what huh
oh
okay do some do some wait what lost i
lost you can tell i don't know how to
play cards
but
okay see you later
lost those four vials come back in a
couple of weeks i think i'm gonna gamble
let's do
do five vials this time right let's see
what we got here
that's funny that queen has a b on there
yeah and that jack has a lumberjack on
there
anyway
these are great cards
the bottom line is we're gambling with
our lives and the doctors right
mistakenly in the blood labs gambling
your blood away
for inconclusive tests mostly now i
believe in blood working you should get
blood work but you got to be careful
because they throw the blood away
and then we go backwards and we go
backwards right
i talk about this the medical media
podcast at apple podcast all the details
but the bottom line is i'm noticing
that people forget
they forget about the blood work thing
or they never learned it yet the medical
meme information
so they come into the community someone
doesn't remind them about their blood
work
and they just got 20 vials pulled
and now they're online and they're like
i don't feel good today i'm gonna just
try something else this celery juice
made me sick
not the 20 vials that was taken from a
specialist eight days ago
because people don't realize it so their
immune system is being drawn out of them
and that's the whole thing lorena says i
like cards but i don't gamble either do
i
look out for thursday i will be
announcing a special interview i did
that i will be releasing that will be
released on thursday
i won't be releasing it but it did
special interview
so i was interviewed
and it's going to be released on
thursday
i'll let you guys
know what it's about soon
ain't gonna talk about it
anyway you guys
quick run out real quick recap right
there it's not only doing the right
things get the right b12 instead of the
b12 that has something bad in it you
know high quality it's not just doing
like one b12 it's about methylcobalamin
dinosaur balance it's about
spirulina not chlorella it's about
right
it's about licorice fruit not a coffee
enema with whatever there's so many
different aspects it's about
right
vegan epa dha oil
not
fish oil these things add up right and
they add up it's about not doing the
wrong type of magnesium right
and then it's about doing
celery juice and other things and other
tools and getting metals out that we all
know that you talk about right and then
it's about
the details
and knowing how to protect yourself and
knowing what to look out for too right
so the details matter right here all of
it matters
so you guys just to quit that was just a
quick rundown a little bit about the
healing process you keep your hope up
you you take it one day at a time
you know that i i believe in you guys
i'm going to instagram and i'm turning
tik tok back on i'm going to turn
telegram back on and i'll see you just
in a few minutes so i hope you guys look
out we're gonna have some fun there and
i love you guys