the collaboration between aan and
medical medium because I'm going to be
there are you guys going to be there
this is getting Cra Crazy actually June
15th uh bring a book okay try to bring
one book at this point try to bring one
book and if you don't have a book
there'll be some books there I think hey
house is going to have some books there
in case you know in case you don't you
don't bring your book or something like
that but June 15th wondering if you guys
are going to be there at aroan the
collaboration heavy metal detox launch
party right
and they're putting the heavy metal
detox smoothie on the menu they're
putting the heavy metal detox on the
menu there and I just want to tell you a
couple things there's going to be some
speakers I'm just saying this thing's
turning into this thing has like grown
legs and it's turning into
something even much much much more
different and uh bigger than it was so
I'm just telling you guys right now so I
don't know if you're coming just
checking on that I excited aan medical
medium collaboration heavy metal detox
smoothie is going to be on the menu
there check this out check this out okay
first of all it's a free event but check
this out
okay my proceeds all of my proceeds are
going into a charity that gives it back
to the community the medical medium
Community I will repeat all of my
proceeds from the heavy metal detox
smoothie this is definitely I'm just
saying here all the proceeds
that are mine from the heavy metal detox
smoothie when you purchase the heavy
metal detox smoothie at aan goes to a
charity in the medical medium Community
to give back to people who are sick that
is incredible I wanted to tell you guys
also check this out there's going to be
free merchandise that's only issued for
this event medical medium
merchandise yes indeed I'm telling you
at this event but it's only issued it's
not going to be merchandise for sale
it's not going to be merchandise on my
website for sale that's not at all it's
only for this June 15th event free merch
for this event from yours truly given to
you guys I'm excited about this are you
coming or what Caroline cook says I'll
be there explanation points driving 45
minutes away my family and I can't wait
to meet you I'm going to tell you I'm
going to before we talk about how metal
speed viruses and all that I just want
to tell you about this for a second yvon
says be there awesome over there on
YouTube incredible so you guys are going
to be there but seriously just so you
know all of my proceeds from the heavy
metal detox smoothie on the menu at Awan
in all of their stores all of those
proceeds not just the 15th on the 15th W
with it being in the store after that
all of it is going to a charity to feed
it back into the community how
incredible is that s says coming from
London wow oh coming from London
incredible incred it's going to be worth
coming from London too I promise Bon
says can't wait coming from Fort Worth
Texas amazing it's going to be worth it
I'm telling you guys right now it's
going to be worth it so I want to tell
you free merchandise I'm not going to
say what it is it's a surprise it's a
surprise the free merch that's really
bitching that's really cool medical
medium issued stuff just for this event
it's not for sale down the road so when
you get this free merch you're only
getting it at the event how sick is that
and when you purchase a heavy metal
detox smoothie from
aan all of my proceeds go back into the
community of Charity to go back into
Community I'm not making a penny from
this I used my own money to buy all the
merch that I'm giving away for free okay
I used all my money to actually help
this thing you know go move forward
because it's turning into like a a
serious thing you guys real serious
things bring your book I'll sign your
book I'm excited about that and there
will be you know speakers I'll announce
who but there will be speakers there as
well how cool is that
whoa over there in IG whoa I'm coming
from Turkey
whoa that is that's crazy cool wow
coming from
Turkey now I'm nervous now I'm actually
nervous London turkey Texas for World
Texas how crazy is that so I'm trying to
tell you guys just before we talk about
metals and stuff like that I'm talking
about this make sure you sign up
medical.com link is in the profile link
is in the description make sure you sign
up to like to the event make you make
sure you sign up to this launch party
medic medium.com for more details so you
can get more details so make sure you
sign up if you're coming sign up
definitely I'm just saying if you're
coming sign up so bottom line let me
just give you the rundown on some of the
details okay airwan collaboration with
medical media the heavy metal detox
smoothie they are going to have in their
stores okay all the proceeds that I get
are going to go straight to a charity
into back into the medical medium
Community I'm not banking on this I'm
not making all this money because
smoothies are selling an airan every day
every every bit of my proceed goes back
into the community Lisa says coming from
Ohio so excited incredible I'm so glad
you're coming coming from Denmark whoa
Henrik that's that's incredible aing
coming from Ireland amazing I got to
practice my Ireland accent I got to work
on that shatu coming from Austria whoa
I'm excited you're coming from there and
then Christian you're coming from
Germany yeah that is really cool really
cool also Stefani coming from Germany
too well Perth
Australia Lilian Perth Australia you're
coming down that's a long trip I heard
there's people coming from Australia but
hey boom there you are exactly I'm
excited about this I'm so
excited I can't start the show yet I
can't start the show yet about toxic
heavy metals coming from Germany that's
amazing so back to this again you guys
there's going to be some surprise
speakers okay how cool is that yeah it's
going to be an incredible Day June 15th
it's coming around the corner so book
your
flights book your flights if you haven't
done it yet make sure you know where
you're going sign up to it's a free
event it isn't $200 a ticket it isn't
$300 a ticket it's free and then when
you purchase the Smoothie incredible the
heavy metal detox smoothie all that
proceed that goes to me goes straight to
a charity right back to the community
Nick Taylor says coming from New York
City NYC baby NYC
Vancouver
whoa treasure hunter that's actually a
really cool um are you metal attack and
doing fun stuff like that are you
looking for old bottles treasure hunter
that's amazing Sarah
t144 mom and I are coming from Kentucky
ky's cool definitely another Denmark
Suzanne Denmark what and coming from
Connecticut boots
McGee incredible and you're bringing
family as well whoa healing with Ana
coming from Santa Cruz
California that is really cool all the
way to Culver City so it's in Culver
City you guys just so you know if you
want to know the details Mattel says is
there parking in the area we'll get sign
up to the medical go to medical
medium.com or check out the link in the
bio description sign up so that you're
on the email list for that so we can be
giving you details like what the heck is
going on how does it work you name it
and I'm going to give more details um
eventually about the charity and so
forth all of that you guys there's so
much to cover and there's a lot of
information right now I'm just trying
we're going to do a heavy metal show but
I want to give you a four warning that
it's coming up it is literally we're
close to it we're on the heels of it
June 15th collaboration between aan
medical medium okay they're putting the
heavy metal detox smoothie in their
stores
which is incredible all the proceeds
going to me every penny that goes to me
every penny is going back to a charity
that's going to feed it back to the
community like it's really special
really special I want them to keep those
smoothies in the store long time so that
there's always money going back into the
community how is my dream how cool is
that and then there's going to be free
merchandise it's only issued for this
event June 15th okay only is issued for
this event it's not going to be for sale
it's not going to be on my website you
guys know I don't sell
merchandise maybe someday I will but I
but I'm not and and this is only issued
for this okay how cool is this Cosmic
medicine says just booked can't wait to
see you and the community Switzerland is
coming Switzerland is coming boom but
check this
out I can't give you all the details
right now but there's going to be
speakers there yeah some speakers okay
how cool is that and there's going to be
other stuff too and bring a book or if
you can't bring a book because you're
traveling and it's a pain in the butt
and you can't bring your book one of
your medical medium books uh Hey house
is going to set up a book store right
there and just just for people who like
it could be for anybody if you want but
it's for people who have traveling a
long way possibly and they just can't
bring a book and so forth it's too much
on the travel or you forget at least you
know you'll have that option which is
really awesome um with Hay House is
really awesome so I'm excited about this
and I'm going to try to sign some books
and I'm going to be talking and yeah
this is this is like a once in lifetime
thing for sure I that's all I could say
and I've never done a book signing
before ever so I'm just saying right now
that's another thing too brenon says is
this going to be like a festival indeed
it is kind of close that's right kind of
close yep I'm not going to say too much
but it is definitely very exciting and
uh-huh it's going to be really cool Aton
says Wyoming is coming whoa maybe there
will be all 50 states there it's very
possible there will be because what
we're hearing and what little birdies
are telling us is some people are coming
it's not going to just be a hundred
people there and so this thing is
definitely grown legs so I got the free
merch boom ready I'm going to have my
hand ready I'm going to sign right and
I'm going to have some speakers and Awan
is going to be stocked with some
smoothies because yeah people are going
to be thirsty I'm going to be thirsty
I'm going to probably grab a few of them
and tank them down and I'll just tank
them down in front of you guys because
that's probably what's going to happen
is you'll be seeing me tank them down
I'll show you how I drink them in person
in like real time in person I'll show
you how I drink them down
it's probably not the best way to do it
you know cuz I don't take my time I just
chug them okay we also have a camera
crew there interviewing the community on
their healing stories if you guys want
to do that make sure you sign up to get
more details which is really cool
there's so many cool things happening
anyway you guys I am pumped I am excited
so let's get on with it I want to talk
about some metals a little bit if you
guys don't mind it's critical to get
toxic heavy metals out of the body
that's why the heavy metal detox has
been so powerful and has helped people
move forward to such a degree and you
know it's
critical to remove metals because bugs
love Metals we're going to go into that
a little bit sound exciting it is
exciting understanding how it works like
when metals are in our body and they
enter our body every single day when
you're pumping gas at the at the gas
station metals are entering our lungs
and in our body you can smell them at
the gas station if you're driving an EV
uhhuh metals leeching from the battery
the 600 lb battery sitting underneath
your butt so metals are everywhere
doesn't matter if you got an EV it
doesn't matter if you're breathing in
the smog that's choking out of a car we
bring breathe in metals all the time we
inherit them from generations and
generations a people so we inherit these
Metals all the time and then we also
inherit pathogens as well we inherit
those that's a virus right there and
viruses love to eat metal so we're going
to go into that a little bit the whole
thing so let's cut into it and then when
that happens our immune system gets
burdened our immune system that's an
immune cell right there our immune
system gets burdened when we have too
many metals in us and pathogens are
feeding off of those metals so let's get
into it a little bit okay so let's
create a nice toxic heavy metal patch
right here a nice toxic heavy metal
patch right here one here okay we'll put
a few different ones around if you guys
don't mind all right you guys can see
that
right there we go and then we're going
to
put a pathogen a pathogen here we go
look we're going to put some spikes on
this pathogen how about that put some
spikes on this one too
all right we got some pathogens in the
bloodstream we got pathogens in the
organs we got them in the liver how
about that so we got some viruses right
here and then we also have different
kinds of pathogens too so let's do a
little bit of that here's a different
one okay all kinds of different bugs are
inside of everybody you want to know why
everybody's sick bugs and toxins what
are some of the toxins toxic heavy
metals bugs and toxins are why people
are sick it's bugs and toxins okay so we
got the pathogens we got all that these
are the toxic heavy metals I'm just
going to kind of circle them a little
bit okay lead Mercury aluminum cadmium
toxic Metals not even just heavy I call
them all Heavy because they do serious
damage on the body all right so we we
have that right there so what you're
looking at is a whole bunch of circles
whole bunch of different spots okay but
this is your body this whole thing is
your body right here okay your body is
this right here and inside your body you
got your organs and you can you got your
bloodstream you got your brain you got
everything so what happens all right so
toxic heavy metals break down over time
keep that in mind they break down over
time Metals shed so what you're seeing
right here coming out of deposits of
metals right what what you're seeing is
out gassing you're seeing oxidation some
metals oxidate in your brain and body
keep that in mind they oxidize in your
liver oxidize in your pancreas you know
how many people are getting pancreatic
cancer right now it's insane it's every
single day this person is diagnosed with
panc pancreatic cancer this person is
pancreatic cancer this person has a
pancreatic tumor this person has this
and that it's crazy to the to the degree
that is happening right now out there
okay this person is liver cancer this
person is colon cancer this person is
this and that and you guys know
pathogens are those cancer cells right
viral cells turn into cancer cells
that's how it works viral cells need
fuel to turn into cancer cells to turn
into disease creating cells just so you
know so Metals start to out gas out
pocket they start to oxidize so that's
what these Metals do so I'm putting a
little bit of a butterfly around all
these metal all these Metals right here
okay and you'll see you see that
butterfly around them that's what we
want to call it okay I'm putting a
little all of this is Metals breaking
down so we live our life we don't get
enough antioxidants that's right we
start to oxidize we get really acidic
and the acid starts to break down the
metals they start to outp poet they
start to break down those are the metals
right there and when they do that
they're leeching and when they're
leeching that junk and toxic crap coming
off of them are leeching into your
bloodstream and into organ tissue is if
it's your brain they're leeching into
your brain tissue right just keep that
in mind okay so that's your brain right
there if it's your brain they're
leeching into brain tissue if it's your
organs like your liver they're leeching
into liver tissue okay so there's liver
there's the brain right there so keep
your eye on those because they're all
part of it okay so now we got the bugs
we got the pathogens we got the viruses
the viruses that create cancer the
viruses that create all kinds of
inflammation takes a pathogen to create
inflammation critical to understand but
a pathogen needs to stay alive and a
pathogen needs to eat it has to eat to
stay it can't just
exist classified medical research and
science keeps pathogens alive in their
labs using
mercury classified medical research and
science uses Mercury to keep pathogens
alive it's a preservative to keep
pathogens nice and fat and happy and
alive so the
pathogen the pathogen can Thrive because
pathogens feed off of mercury public
medical research and science doesn't
know that Medical in medical medium
information published all the stuff on
how Mercury feeds pathogens feeds
viruses and so forth what happens is
pathogens eat the Mercury then they
release neurotoxins neurotoxins give you
all your different Vegas nerve symptoms
all your different cranial nerve
symptoms it makes you get ticks and
spasms aches and pains fatigue fatigue
where your legs are like sandbags your
arms are like sandbags you can't
function you get the brain fog you get
all kinds of bizarre depression you get
all kinds of bizarre sadness anxiety
through the roof panic attacks heart
arrhythmias that aren't heart problems
but instead they're like mysterious aibs
and everything all these toxins related
to pathogens from Metals right so
classified medical research and science
uses Mercury as a preservative to keep a
pathogen alive so they could study it
mess with it put it back out into the
environment in people some way some
shape some form so we can just kind of
all pass around every single bug
everybody could even imagine like the
herpes family simplex one Simplex 2 um
all the different herpes viruses
shingles Epstein bar hhv6 hhv7
undiscovered 10 through 16 and so forth
all this medical medum information you
guys know so here's how it works right
you got your Metals that's this right
here your metal Pockets they're
expanding they're in your liver they're
in your brain these metal pockets are
expanding they're in your liver in your
brain they're in your pancreas they're
in your spleen yep they are they're in
your colon lining how about that in your
colon lining right so these are pockets
of metal they're expanding and
outgassing let's go to viruses now let's
go to
bugs everybody has a virus in them
everybody has one if they're the one
person at this point on the planet that
doesn't have an Epstein
bar then they have a
shingles if it's the one person on this
planet that doesn't have a shingles
variety right then they have an
hhv6 if it's the one person that doesn't
have an hhv6 they got an
hsv1 they got the Simplex cold sore
fever blister
virus goes on and on and on everyone has
a bug in them
the key is how many bugs do they have in
them okay do they have three or four
varieties of epine bar that they picked
up along the way because they just did
do they have five Epstein bars do they
have three shingles do they have hhv6
ceglar virus what do they have in them
do they have three varieties of cold
sore viruses because a lot of people
they don't just have one cold sore virus
they don't know it but they have three
and then they'll have a canker sore
virus too which is also herpetic from
the herpetic family but it's not the
cold sore virus but they'll have the
canker sore kker stores will come out
all the time and so forth
right everyone has a bug I'm sorry to
say that it's just how many do they have
and which varieties do they have do they
have two shingles in an epscene bar do
they not have a shingles but they have
an hhv7 what do they have do they have
hsv1 okay so we're establishing that are
there bugs causing problems are there
bugs giving them aches and pains fatigue
all kinds of different brain fog all
kinds of different anxiety depression
are the bugs creating all these
different numbness feelings and tingles
is it giving them um ttis and ringing
the ears whooing in the ears popping in
the ears is it giving them tightness of
the chest tightness of the jaw pain in
the back of their head what is it doing
is it giving them vertigo and dizzy
balance issues are they dizzy are they
having problems did they have a bad
vertigo last year that is Epstein bar by
the way what are they having what are
they dealing with so that's the next
level and then we got
Metals metals and I'm not talking about
heavy
metal the music I'm talking about toxic
heavy metals and toxic Metals which
people also have they inherit it from
the family line Mercury all the way down
and so forth and we collect more and
more metal every single day like I said
you just go to the gas station stick the
gas pump in I took celery Force by the
way is it
showing is it showing cuz I'm like you
stick the gas pump in you breathe in
those gas fumes and those gas fumes have
metal in them you drive your EV around
you're like hey I don't have gas in the
car I'm doing good this way too and
you're breathing in and out gas over
time it's coming off the battery in the
car right regardless we're getting
Metals out of the sky in all of the sea
Trails we're getting Metals in
Pharmaceuticals that a lot of people
take I mean they take Pharmaceuticals
prescribed by their doctors for
different things they're getting metals
from there too it's just all part of
life here and then we get metals from
our food supply we get metals from all
kinds of different things and those
Metals sit inside of our organs they sit
inside of our liver they sit inside of
our brain that's where the metals sit
and then they pocket out they out gas
and eventually they spread now you can
get new metal exposures just say at the
gas pump or breathing in breathing in
fragrances colog perfumes you like the
smell smells so pretty it smells like
beautiful wild flowers in this beautiful
place I love the smell of this perfume
cologne and this air freshener that I
just sprayed on my couch filled with
Metals we breathe it in we smell it
we're smelling metals and they're
entering into our body we can't run from
it we can't hide it's everywhere right
of course we can pull our air freshener
out of the wall and toss it of course we
can pull something out of the wall and
toss it like that we can throw
detergents out and bring in you know
fragrance-free detergents in hopes that
we're actually bypassing a lot of them
we can do a lot of things we can avoid
fluoride at the
dentist we can avoid which is a
neurotoxin byproduct of aluminum we
could avoid that we can do some things
but either way we've had fluoride
treatments in the past maybe when you
were younger either way those Metals
build up and they out poock and then
Metals meet the road they meet the
pavement right here the metals meet the
virus see this Metals meet the virus now
here's what happens with viruses and
here's what goes on with viruses okay
Metals meet the
virus viruses are on the same frequency
as toxic heavy
metals same
frequency they're not
opposites okay pathogens like viruses
are on the same frequency as toxic heavy
metals they morph together is what they
do they bond so that's what they do they
bond and that's important to know the
metals Bond there's a b o n
d hope that's how you spell it Metals
bond together with pathogens they make a
connection So eventually pathogen gets
hungry it's looking for food and then it
finds it it starts to Feast on the toxic
heavy metal because we're all loaded
with Metals but how loaded are you how
loaded I get Metals in me every
day if I get Metals in me every day you
get Metals in you every day if I walk
outside and I'm breathing in a Sea Trail
and I'm getting Metals in how much crap
they're dumping on the out of the sky on
us every single day right now and then
you got you got regular crap being
dumped on us just just that alone from
all the all the fuel that's coming off
of planes I'm not even talking about sea
Trails just the fuel alone right so you
walk outside I'm walking outside I'm
breathing in toxic heavy metals you're
breathing in toxic heavy metals are you
in town are you breathing in that stuff
coming out of the trucks and everything
else when you're on the street did you
smell all that diesel fuel and you're
like whoa what is that I'm breathing in
metals you're breathing in metals that's
right but how many metals do you have do
you got multip sceris do you have
fibromyalgia do you have ra do you have
autoimmune disease do you have some
other kind of condition do you have
eczema do you have psoriasis what do you
have what are you what's ailing you
metals are behind a lot of that you have
ALS you got Parkinson's what do you have
do you have symptoms resembling any of
that Maybe not maybe do you just have
chronic fatigue syndrome whatever it is
that you have tixs and spasms and aches
and pains and fatigue and all that you
got whatever it is okay whatever it
is metals are
involved metals and the metals are
meeting the pavement baby the pavement
is the pathogen right they're meeting
the road they're meeting together
they're running into each other is
what's happening pathogens and metals
are running into each other so you got
Boom the pathogen sorry the metals Boom
the pathogen and they're doing this
they're meeting and when they're meeting
the pathogen is feasting so let's go
into that next next right and that's
what's happening here we're going to go
into that next okay there we go all
right so let's get into
this you're sick you're down and
out depression anxiety aches and pains
mysterious heart arhythmia no one can
explain a doctor can't you've been
through every test Tinkles and numbness
vertigo dizziness all kinds of other
weird
symptoms Tremors in the body feeling
like you're vibrating at night restless
leg syndrome insomnia what else do you
have
pathogens
Metals pathogens and toxins Metals being
one of the big ones right there
important to know this stuff is critical
to know because guess what if you don't
know why you're aing and you don't know
why you're sick and if you don't know
what's wrong how are you going to get
better the heavy metal
detox has saved so many lives over the
years the medical mem heavy metal detox
it is
Legendary Legendary what it has done
turned people's lives around I mean got
them out of bed got them driving again
got them back to work I mean it's
incredible what has happened all along
the way if you guys just came on here
I'm noticing a bunch of you guys just
came on here June 15th are you going to
miss it or you going to be there I'm
going to be there iners live okay Awan
collaboration between medical medium and
aan and guess what you guys they're
going to put the heavy metal detox
smoothie on the menu and guess what
every single penny dime that goes to
that meaning to me all the proceeds that
go to me are going back into the medical
Med Community it's being donated to a
charity every penny I'm not going to
receive one penny from the heavy metal
detox smoothie that's going to be inside
aan not one penny and if you guys just
got here I'm also giving away free merch
that I paid for myself don't put it to
waste be there I spent all this money on
some kill merch that's only being issued
for this event June 15th in Culver City
Medical
medium.com check it out you got to go
there see what you know see what we're
talking about so you can get the details
and so forth okay so um link is in the
profile link is in the description it's
going to be in Culver City that's the
airan I'm going to be at Culver City
California LA area how cool June 15th
free merch there's going to be speakers
few of my friends are going to stop by
and they're going to speak it's going to
be really really really [__] and it's
going to be really cool I'm excited
about it and it's taking legs I'm going
to be signing some books okay and it's
this thing is taken legs like it's grown
legs like I'm saying this because it did
so originally I was just like hey you
guys stop by aan I'm going to be there
I'll sign some books whatever the heavy
metal detox launch party but
now it has gone berserk so we're like
prepared prepared free merch there's
going to be speakers it's going to be
sick I hope you guys are there cver City
June 15th book your tickets
now and there is no ticket to purchase
to be there it's a free event that's the
way I like it but um book your plane
tickets obviously you got to do that
June 15th Awan opens at 7 a.m. book
signing event starts 9:00 a.m. to 300
p.m.
there's going to be some cool stuff I'm
going to
speak going to be cool all right back to
the metals so we know what's going on
medical m.com or bio you know check the
information you'll see the links in the
bio link is in the description all right
so pathogens need to eat okay by the way
you can show up and get your smoothies
as early as 700 a.m. in the
morning you can show up and get your
smoothies at 700 a.m. in the morning and
I'm going to show you how to chug those
smoothies down because that's what I do
see what I do is when I'm here and
everything I'm kind of like shy and when
I make the heavy metal detox smoothie in
front of you guys I'm kind of like
eating it with a spoon a little and I'm
sipping it a little but you know what
happens is that when I really when I
make mine or I'm going to get mine there
I'm just going to wait I'm going to send
it down and if it goes all over me I
don't care because it's going to be fun
we're going to have some fun it's going
to be actually killer just totally
killer and fun all right hey guys
Metals pathogens are on the same
frequency as mercury and the metals
classified medical research and science
uses Mercury to preserve pathogens and
keep them alive by feeding the pathogen
while it's sitting there in the in the
lab so they can study it work on it and
everything else pathogens are inside our
body everybody's got viruses in them
it's all about killing them off learning
how to do that through medical medium
information killing your viruses off
getting rid of them and so forth forth
knocking them back but everybody's got
bugs that they're that they're dealing
with keeping them sick giving them all
these problems and what you do is you
actually have to take food away from
those bugs you have to take Metals away
from those bugs okay are you coming to
Los Angeles I'm coming to Los Angeles
I'm going to be there in Culver City
somebody just ask that on IG I'm going
to be in Culver City in Los Angeles yes
myself personally there and I'm going to
sign books I'm going to talk there's
going to be some speakers there I'm
going to be handing out free merch which
is really cool yeah really cool I'm
excited about that and some other stuff
too kind of keeping some things
secretive cuz you know there's some cool
things that could happen you never know
you never never know who knows all right
so you guys let's keep on going with
this a little bit so why do we have to
remove these metals because we have to
take away the food from the past
pathogens and if you don't know why
you're sick how are you going to heal
you can do hit or miss out there I'll
try some intermittent fasting I'll try a
little bit of this I'll try a little bit
of that I'm feeling a little better but
not okay I did good for like a little
bit now I'm not I'll try this supplement
I'll try that I'll try this therapy I'll
try the cold Pune I'll try that I'll try
this I'll try and that's what people do
out there but in the end do they really
know why they're sick and what are they
really shooting for what are they trying
to do well I got deficiency and this
doctor told me this and this this health
coach told me that now I'm staying away
from this now I'm doing that but do you
know why you're sick how are you sick
because somebody else out there who
aren't sick yet they're doing whatever
they want they can go sit out in the sun
for you know hours with slathered with
lotion on they can do whatever they want
to do they're not tired they get up
every single morning they eat a loaf of
bread when they want they'll eat bacon
and eggs and a loaf of bread they'll
have an egg cheese sandwich from some
you know chain restaurant they'll do
whatever they're living their life sure
there's complications that could happen
either way but they're not sick yet but
then there's somebody who's really sick
and they're doing good stuff they're
trying this and they're trying that but
they're really sick and suffering but
why are you sick critical to know Metals
play a massive role to why people are
struggling why they're suffering and why
they're sick with MS and all kinds of
different symptoms and conditions just
one condition Lyme disease fibromyalgia
chronic fatig syndrome and so forth and
and then on top of that it's the metals
and the pathogens Right medical mean
information look people can do whatever
floats your boat you can do what you
want out there you can eat this way you
can go do this you can try this but if
you don't know why you're sick you're
going to miss out along the way and it's
going to hurt you down the road somehow
the medical medium heavy metal detox has
helped so many people has saved lives
around the world it is a re renowned
famous um heavy metal detox you know how
it is it's the ingredients it's the
combination the five key ingredients
that's what matters that's the heavy
metal detox and that's what we're
talking about okay pathogens and toxins
so we have we have pathogens we have the
bugs we have the metals and right there
it's that combination so what does the
pathogen do what does the virus do the
virus clings onto the metal the metal
clings onto the virus the metal sits on
the virus virus like this so the metal
sits on the
virus particles of the oxidation sit on
the virus just like this okay and then
the virus dissolves the particles
dissolves it absorbs it through the
membrane and feeds on it once a virus
has Metals in it and it's been feeding
on those metals and it's
absorbing those metals and bringing them
into into the virus you see this right
here the metals are clinging onto the
viral
wall a cell wall and they're being
absorbed right into the virus you see
that you guys once that
happens the virus gets fueled it gets
strength it awakens when it awakens it
becomes a beast depending on what kind
of virus you have it becomes a beast so
once those get in there the metals go in
it now the virus is awake and it's Fe
feeding once it's feeding it has to go
to the bathroom it has to go to the
bathroom it has to eliminate the virus
has to eliminate toxins now the more
fuel the virus gets which is the metals
the more fuel the virus gets which is
all those Metals the more bathroom is
produced the more
elimination is produced and when that
elimination leaves the virus now that
mercury that aluminum especially that
mercury aluminum the copper right the
lead the cadmium the
Arsenic right once that metal
leaves in a different form out of the
virus here it goes now those are
neurotoxins neurotoxic waste coming out
of those viruses epine bar herplex one
herp Simplex 2 cytomegalo virus shingles
herpes hhv6 hhv7 this is all particles
being excreted from the virus now you
see this stuff right here it's coming
out and when that comes out it's going
into your bloodstream now now you're
getting aches and pains tingles and
numbness now you're getting vertigo now
you're getting more ttis now you're
getting more problems here it is the
elimination is
neurotoxins being eliminated from the
pathogen because the pathogen fed off of
the metals so what you have here now
is toxic waste coming from the pathogen
the virus that toxic waste is now
trouble what that toxic waste
is okay that's your headache that's your
tingles and numbness that's your ex and
pains if it's been ruled out that they
don't know why you have any of that at
the doctor's office if they find an
answer it's obvious but if you're
somebody that like really doesn't know
no one really has an answer mystery
chronic illness for many years
you're dealing with the metals and the
viruses the metals and the
viruses and those viruses are leeching
out all of that now it's spewing out all
that neurotoxin when that neurotoxin
comes out goes into your bloodstream and
guess where it ends up it ends up in
here that's right it ends up in your
liver guess where else it ends up as
brain fog in your brain it ends up in
your brain as brain fog start getting
getting symptoms why do I have brain fog
how come I'm losing my memory how come I
actually can't think anymore how come
I'm like so fogged out that's the
neurotoxins leaving the pathogens the
viruses after the pathogens just
absorbed literally absorbed heavy metal
runoff in heavy metal particles right
here from all of this metal outgassing
and oxidizing you see it all all of that
and then the pathogen fed off of that
and it's releasing all those neurotoxins
those neurotoxins end up in the
bloodstream and here we go in your
bloodstream there it is right there in
your organs in your bloodstream all of
that neurotoxin and you're sick you got
me cff you got chronic fatigue syndrome
you got all kinds of different
conditions you got pots right you got
just so many different conditions that
you can have ra and so forth and that's
how it works okay all right
see uh Mela over there on IG these
changes have changed my life I was so
sick I was very close to Suicide Anthony
your advice saved me and you know I I
that [__] makes me it makes me so happy
to know that you are in such a good
place now and and but to think you were
suffering suffering enough where suicide
and to to to have to go there and to to
suffer that much it just it pains me to
know my heart pours out to you truly
truly truly
truly t uh Tamara says remember to give
thumbs up to give a thumbs up if you
like this show thumbs up if you don't
like this show what do I usually say you
can give the middle finger but still hit
a thumbs up if you can look you guys
okay the heavy metal detox the medical
medium heavy metal
detox it's been life-saving for so many
people for so many years there was
nothing out there when that was out
there saving lives there was nothing out
there the whole term heavy metal detox
now is because of the medical medium
information out there all these years
putting heavy metals on the map and
heavy metal detox on the map five key
ingredients is the heavy metal detox you
you can essentially have those in
anything you want you can have those in
a salad you can have those in some other
in a smoothie Bowl you can have those
five key ingredients in some other form
or some other way throughout the course
of the
day but you got to have those five key
ingredients I like them any way possible
okay but Awan medical medium
collaboration June 15th they're putting
the heavy metal detox smoothie on the
menu there which is insane
I'm so excited about it in all 10 of
their stores how incredible any proceeds
that go to me go directly to charity
back to the medical medum community all
right and you have to understand
something kation was dangerous years ago
the one thing about Spirit of compassion
about putting the heavy metal detox the
five key ingredients to get Metals out
of us so we can heal and move forward is
because there were dangerous cation
techniques and the information wasn't
because they knew Metals caused any
conditions they didn't think Metals
caused conditions they didn't think they
caused this or this or psoriasis or
eczema or anything like that this
medical medium information but they use
cation for like when you drank lead
water you know like lead water like
you're you're drinking tap water and
then the city declared an emergency and
that tap water was loaded with lead and
then what they would do is they would
try to do kelation on the person and it
was like that's all they had but I'm
talking about mystery chronic illness
and people suffering and struggling and
heavy metals that whole thing people
didn't know anything about that they
just didn't and spirit of compassion put
the heavy metal detox out there all
these years saved so many lives it's an
incredible incredible thing so I'm just
saying um but anyway you guys just want
to tell
you getting rid of metals is key if
you're not going to get rid of the
pathogens get rid of the metals if
metals get rid of the pathogens
medical medium information allows you to
do both getting rid of pathogens and
metals it's
critical Mayan's over there and IG says
what are the five
ingredients well um five ingredients
what are they does anybody know does
anybody know what the five ingredients
are I'm trying to remember I don't
remember I think the metals got to my
head and I think they've
created
Amnesia I think have amnesia or instant
memory loss cuz I don't remember the
ingredients do you guys remember the
ingredients youran is also stocking all
of the medical medium heavy metal detox
ingredients in their stores which is
insanely
incredible so youan stocking the
ingredients in their stores as well
which um I see somebody say cilantro
cilantro is one of them you're right
cantro is one of them I just remembered
incredible wild blueberries
limited edition over there on YouTube
that's another one you guys are helping
me I'm getting my memory back right now
my Amnesia is going away cilantro wild
blueberry spirulina somebody said
spirulina what spirulina 5K ingredients
somebody said banana that's not the key
ingredient five key ingredients United
limited edition said barley grass juice
powder that's another one you guys are
missing one wait my memor is coming back
here it is Atlantic
douls
incredible you guys yes orange juice is
in there but that's the Smoothie I'm
talking about the heavy metal detox you
have to have those five ingredients to
get the metals out are you guys
incredible you guys
amazing all
right just letting you know Culver City
I'll be there June 15th okay I'm excited
Beyond excited and um I'm going to sign
some books bring a book all right and
there's going to be some speakers I'm
giving away free merch which is really
cool free merch I took my own money and
I bought a ton of free merch that's only
issued for this party it's insane look
out on my telegram I will be doing
messages on my telegram so please look
out if you're not on my telegram I'm
going to go back to telegram I'm going
to do some messages on there a whole
bunch of different stuff including some
inspirational stuff but I'm also going
to be letting everybody know about this
June 15 thing Culver
City and my telegram is
t.me slmed
medium how cool is that you guys
seriously medical medium podcast look
for each new episode every week There's
a new medical medium podcast medical
medium podcast on Apple podcast look for
the new episode all the time keep in
mind that airwan collaboration with
medical medium this
collaboration every single penny of my
proceeds that actually come from anyone
purchasing that heavy metal
detox every single penny that's going to
me is going to a charity back into the
Community Medical medum Community just
letting everybody know
okay letting everybody know register for
the event go to medical.com please
register for the event
exciting you guys I'm pumped what the
heck whoa I'm going to take a photo of
that all right you
guys seriously I love you guys much okay
and I will see you guys
soon all right listen out for Stuff get
on my email list so we can let you know
what's going on all right love you guys
good to see you guys