I'm actually going to clean this really
quick so
quick what I'm doing is giving it just a
quick
rinse like this I don't know if you guys
can see me over there I know on IG you
guys probably can't see
me but I'm giving this a quick rinse and
a quick
cleaning that's is
great I'm just going to use it again
right here for the P hummus
all right here we
go check this out guys see the parts
coming back really quick I don't think
you've ever seen me do this
before
right I see him come back look at
that
boom all
right
cleaning the mm 1500 as we
speak has it been two minutes
already someone tell
me
okay has it been 2 minutes all right was
that 2 minutes was that 3 minutes was
that a minute and a
half okay let's get the part back in
that let's get this piece back
in see you guys all
right
on sorry guys I'm multitasking again Big
Time bear with
me showing you how to clean the mm 1500
and I'm getting the peas ready for a p
hummus you guys see this you see them
toasting up right here okay lost a
couple but that's okay all right
all right so that's in okay that's in
right this little part right here going
to put right there like
that that's in
done give it a quick rinse that's
in okay best sale ever in the mm1 1500
$140 off
$140 off get it for some for Christmas
if you waited all year and you don't
have the mm 1500 you guys know I work
with the mega link is in the description
link is in the
profile