pains nerve pain inflammation their neck
hurts their back hurts their elbows hurt
their shoulders hurt their feet hurt
their knees hurt their hips hurt
everywhere hurts and a lot of people
they have nerve inflammation throughout
their body they have chronic fatigue
syndrome they have fibromyalgia they got
ra they have psoriatic arthritis they
have all kinds of different conditions
and everything is hurting and they don't
feel good and then there's a whole bunch
of people that haven't been diagnosed
with a condition by their doctor and
they're looking at them like we don't
really know and your blood work shows
this but you might have inflammation and
these people have all kinds of different
nerve issues they have problems with the
vagus nerves tightness of the chest
frenic nerves going down through here
and they're having difficulties they're
having aches and pains everywhere
twitches and spasms and what we're
talking about today is hot packs cold
packs okay this is a really important
episode right here we're going to talk
about using water bottles how to use hot
water bottles we're going to talk about
even been using heating pads too so this
is an episode you don't want to miss and
we're going to cover cold packs as well
a freezer pack which I have it in the
freezer right now because I want it nice
and icy cold for a demo I want to show
you guys how to use icy cold um cold
packs and use them correctly so you
don't freeze yourself in a really bad
situation we're also making loaded
crinkle fries crinkle cut fries which is
a recipe right here out of brains saver
protocols which I'm very excited it to
do because this is going to be delicious
can't wait to eat it I'm looking forward
to it loaded crinkle cut fries are we
allowed french fries anybody are we
allowed french fries medical medium
allows french fries oh my God so
restricted everybody but yes we are
having french fries because you can eat
some killer kickass food that's really
tasty really yummy you don't want to
miss that as well now what you see in
front of me right here is is a
demonstration of different food items
it's for the crinkle cut fries you got
these scallions from the garden
beautiful you got black beans right here
wow that's going to be really fun you
got Tomatoes nice fresh tomatoes got
Cayenne hot peppers limes lemons look at
those Peppers right there wo those are
going in there too and what you see
right here very interesting is bacon yes
bacon pork fat pork rinds the whole bit
no kidding joking this is not Pig
materials right here this is actually
eggplant bacon which is another recipe I
already made before all this so check it
out right here you guys look boom nice
eggplant bacon that's the other recipe
now I made that recipe beforehand
because I wanted to have it done I'm
going to get to these nice crispy pieces
of bacon right here maybe do a close-up
too that'd be really really cool look at
that these are delicious bacon strips
they're seasoned just right they're so
good and this is going to be fun because
I'm using this in the crinkle cut fries
all right the loaded crinkle cut fries
this this is going to be the bacon on
top which is so Savory and spicy and
yummy it's like barbecue beef ribs the
things everybody loves to eat and
remembers eating sucking on those ribs
in those restaurants where at a cookout
right all that fat around the rib and
they're just devouring it and they got
all that kind of like what is that sauce
on top that rib sauce all over it and
their face it's all sweet and hot and
syrupy and they're like tearing into
those ribs and pull the meat off those
pork ribs those cow ribs we're not doing
that we're using eggplant which is so
much better for you you don't need pork
fat in your bloodstream people don't
really need that but eggplant really
exciting great food to work with
all right so let's get into it a little
bit and just so you know I hear a noise
in the distance it is my steamer and my
steamer is bubbling up
going and what it's doing is it's got
carrots in there because we're making
the nacho cheese correct we're using
cheese that's not the fake garbage vegan
cheese that's out there in the store
that's got natural flavors in it citric
acid and all this junk and all this
hidden stuff in there cuz they're
allowed to put up up to 10% ingredients
in into those vegan cheeses that are not
listed on the label so you're sitting
with those vegan cheeses at the store
and you're like this is great a vegan
cheese and it's loaded with all kinds of
different garbage and junk and
everything we're going to make our own
nacho cheese baby we're going to make
our own cheese and it's got carrots in
there and so forth so I'm excited about
that so don't worry about the steamer
you hear in the distance cuz I hear it
and I love hearing that sound when I
hear that sound it's like a beautiful
sound in the distance saying healthy
food is in inside that steamer and it's
sitting there percolating just right
anyway um I think we should get down to
it is what I think we should
do see guys if you just rolled in we're
going to talk about hot packs cold packs
you name it and I'm going to make a be
line really quick to the freezer and I'm
going to get an icy icy cold cold pack
out which is really important for this
demonstration so over here in my freezer
I'm opening it up right now I got two in
my
freezer because if you ever get an
injury or you need a cold pack for
somebody in the family or a friend or
anything it's good to have two because
one will eventually not be cold anymore
so when you're using it for a knee
injury or you're twist your ankle or you
sprain your ankle or you're somebody
with chronic illness that's just having
that unknown chronic inflammation and
aches and pains in the body that is
mysterious where you just feel like
you're 100 years old you wake up in the
morning you get out of bed and you feel
like you're 80 years old and you're like
why do I feel this way everything hurts
and aches and you're somebody like that
and you rely on cold
packs okay and when you rely on them you
usually need two so that's one tip all
on its own one doesn't really cut it
especially if you want to get a good
half an hour or 40 minutes into cooling
something down getting inflammation down
now I know some of you guys do ice baths
and stuff like that it's a trendy thing
but it I'm going to talk about how that
doesn't cut the mustard because it's
your entire body going into the cold so
it can't localize the area and get the
inflammation down that's important to
know athletes athletes actually can do
ice baths and stuff like that to cool
the body temp down if they're really
revved up and heated up like seriously
they were on the field and they go
straight from there or straight from a
workout practice and they go right into
a cold bath I mean that that's what
people do and of course there's other
therapies that require cold but when
you're chronically sick or you got an
injury that's in a certain area you
can't do the ice bath and medical mem
information I don't recommend the ice
baths because what happens is it drives
your adrenals into chaos so that's
something to know right there now I do
see un social a lot of people they're
trying out like ice baths and they do
the D they dip into it and they get
ready they get their suit on or they go
in their tub is filled with ice and what
they're doing is they're trashing their
adrenals and they don't know this I want
to go into that a little bit before we
go into localizing with cold packs and
so forth Uma says I hope you have these
listed on your website you can find a
link in the description and profile okay
at medicalmedium.com that's where you go
and you'll find the link that takes you
right to the directory area where you'll
see things like the the heating pad the
hot water bottle and the cold pack of
and all that so first all I just want to
just go into right away about the ice
baths that people are doing okay one
thing I don't like about the ice bats is
the body thinks it's in danger when you
submerge yourself in icy cold water so
your body goes into the chaos moment
fight or flight and as it goes into
fight ORF flight your adrenals are
totally just blowing out adrenaline
epinephrine everywhere because the
adrenaline is rushing through your veins
to try to stop you from going into
hypothermia keep that in mind so when we
do ice bath dips and we do them for
quite some time our body goes into
urgent urgent emergency
emergency something's wrong you have to
protect the brain the brain has to be
protected so then your adrenals flood
literally a big portion of your
adrenaline out at once a big portion 85
to 90% of adrenaline gets released and
spewed out of your adrenals that
adrenaline is circulating through your
body because it's there to try to keep
your blood circulating to try to
increase your heart rate so that your
heart rate doesn't go down as you go
into hypothermia so keep that in mind
when we do ice baths this is not an ice
bath demonstration or talk but I'm going
into that because so many people are
going to say whoa if cold p are really
good for me if localizing cold packs are
really good for me and they're good for
my AES and pains let me go do what
people are doing out there and let me go
hop into a tub with ice and water in
there but no that actually lowers the
immune system with someone with chronic
illness so anyone who's struggling with
any kind of condition the Deep ice bath
time you know that 5 minutes in the ice
bath that 3 minutes that's 10 minutes
that 15 minutes people do in the ice
bath is actually the worst thing they
can do with chronic illness because it
it hinders the immune system because
when all that adrenaline is released for
that figh ORF flate Mo moment when all
that adrenaline and epinephrine is just
coursing through the veins that wears
down your white blood count your killer
cells it wears down your lymphocytes it
breaks down your immune system and
that's what occurs when you do those ice
baths so I just want everybody to know
that there's a white blood cell right
there so when we go and do those ice
baths okay it's different when you're
someone and you got a raging fever
you're somebody that you have a raging
fever you can't get it under control
you're cooking at a 1004
105 and yes you get into the tub for a
little bit to try to drive that
temperature down but I'm talking about
therape you're talking to your doctor
and the whole bit about it I'm talking
about
therapeutically the ice baths create a
lot of Chaos in the body jack up the
adrenaline lower the white blood cell
count if you're somebody with chronic
illness that that is not going to fix a
problem it's going to set somebody back
it'll if they do it regularly it's going
to give them adrenal fatigue over time
so you know it's interesting you'll see
people out there you're like yeah my
adrenals aren't good and I got to do
things that protect my adrenals and
they'll jump into a cold bath they'll
sit there in icy water and they're going
to be hindering and damaging their
adrenals and they're going to set
themselves up for adrenal fatigue over
time so it's number one right there to
talk about when you're chronic sick and
chronically ill very important to know
so back to now cold packs and so
forth all right B vova says but how are
so many folks healing themselves with
the ice baths really they're healing
themselves with the ice baths I mean
that's not really what I've seen out
there so much and I've seen the ice
baths out there for many years that's
been going on like cold baths and and
Ice baths have been going on for decades
and people with chronic illness their
thyroid disorder order isn't healed so
you mean they do an ice bath and their
thyroid disorder goes away their
hashimotos thy thyroiditis goes away
their ra that they're suffering with and
they're on drugs for goes away when they
hop in an ice bath um their Lyme disease
goes away cuz I'm trying to figure this
out no disrespect seriously so when
someone's got lime disease and they've
they're pounding the antibiotics and
they're going to their 10th lime doctor
you mean an ice bath fixes it they're
all done boom you know and so what
you're hearing from people like that
you're hearing people who aren't sick
they haven't been sick sick they're
called not so sick very little things
going on with them maybe they got a
sinus infection they get periodically
maybe they don't feel good in other ways
but it's the they're The Not So Sick and
some of them with with a strong
Constitution because they've never
gotten sick yet hasn't broken down their
constitution they can hop into an ice
bath and they can get quick relief for
the moment but they get quick relief for
the moment cuz they're high on
adrenaline and that's what's happening
so here's what's going on when you're
not that sick of a person or not sick at
all and you want to do the ice bath okay
you're going to be on an adrenaline High
because your body is going to be
coursing coursing through adrenaline
when a plane
crashes in the Alps all right and
everybody's on that plane and the snow
is just coming down and they're their
way up in the mountains and the snow is
blowing and the wind is blowing and
they're in that plane and that plane is
crashed but they're still alive and
there's no heaters and they're not
dressed warm enough and they can't start
a fire and they start getting cold
that's fight ORF flight the body goes
into that crazy land of coldness right
adrenaline starts coursing through them
to keep them alive well when you hop
into an ice tub a tub filled with ice
and you hop right in your body thinks
it's the same thing it thinks that
something's wrong you've been left out
in the cold and you're in trouble and so
the body then supersedes and tries to
supersede by by launching and releasing
a tremendous amount of adrenaline that
adrenaline is to try to keep your
heartbeat going to try to keep you
moving it's the fight or flight
adrenaline so when you hop in the icy
cold bathtub and you submerge yourself
in you're like your adrenals are just
like flooding when you come out of there
you're high you like oh my God I can't
believe woo I can't believe I came out
of that oh my God that was an
experience oh my God I feel it I feel
really good I came out of the ice bath
oh my God right that's the adrenaline
surge that's what that is and when
you're not so sick and you don't have
chronic illness and you don't have Lyme
disease and every other condition out
there and you don't have Epstein bar
related conditions and cause conditions
you don't have all these other problems
and you come out of that ice bath you
like I'll do that again you know I'll
get working out next week or the other
day I'll do another ice bath it's
feeling good
The Not So Sick will swear by it you
stick somebody sick in those ice baths
and they're screwed they are screwed
it's going to tank them over time it's
going to waste what what adrenal like
adrenal strength they have left it's
going to waste it it's going to throw
away whatever adrenaline they have left
in reserves adrenal reserves right is
going to throw that away and over time
you're chronically sick that is going to
break you down knock you down and your
immune system is going to lower and
weaken because of it so your white blood
cells are going to start falling apart
because of it that's what's going to
happen they're going to explode and open
up so keep that in
mind Christen Burton says are cold packs
bad for adrenals no they aren't and I'll
talk about ways of using them they're
not because they're not putting your
body into hypothermic state if you're
being careful you're localizing with
cold packs you're not doing the ice bath
dip and you got to be careful there's a
huge difference between someone who is
struggling and sick with chronic
sickness and illness versus someone
who's not so sick or not sick at all you
see someone on social saying I'm doing
the ice bath again wow it's making me
feel good and you're somebody that's
sick and you've had fibro chronic
fatigue Lyme disease multiple sclerosis
you don't know what you got going going
on maybe you don't have any diagnosis
you're just fatigued really bad you got
aches and pains everywhere you don't
feel good you got brain fog that's
totally messing you up and making you
take a whole bunch of Aderall like crazy
because you got so much brain fog you're
trying to survive you're trying to get
back by you're on coffee you're on
chocolate you're trying to just keep
yourself going and push through the day
you go into the ice baths and do them
regularly it's a shock to the body
systems all of them because your body
says fight or flight Red Alert fight or
flight something's wrong something's
going wrong because your brain is
starting to get cold your whole body is
starting to get cold the adrenals are
just like fight our flight we're in
trouble oh my God your adrenals are just
going nuts like that's what they're
doing because they're saying don't go
into hypothermia something's wrong are
you in a plane did you crash in the Alps
what's going on is there a wind blowing
and you don't have a fire keeping you
warm you're not indoors you're not by a
fireplace you're where are you trapped
in Z degree weather out somewhere and
that's what your adrenals are telling
your brain your adrenals are telling
your brain your brain is communicating
with your adrenals saying I don't know
what this fool is doing your brain is
saying I don't know what this person's
doing I don't know what this person
who's got misinformation wrong
information is doing but I'm starting to
get cold in here and I need some
adrenaline fast and you better send that
stuff up and pile that stuff in because
guess what if we stay in this tub a
little too long that person's in trouble
you come out and you have a high now
you're jacked up instead of on chocolate
and coffee and caffeine and espressos
and green tea and matcha tea and energy
drinks instead of that you're jacked up
on
adrenaline that's how it
works big difference between not so sick
and chronically sick
big difference don't forget that one
very important critical I talk about it
in the books you should have the medical
medium books learn about the difference
between the not so sick and the sick
okay the rules change but what happens
is that not so sick they don't know what
it's like to be really sick they have no
idea so they'll tell you to jump into an
ice bath that's how it
works all right let's get into cold
packs right here woohoo these are are
getting nice and cold right now okay
different size cold packs I like this
size but you may have look at it Frosty
Frosty cold I like this size you may
like smaller sizes okay here's how it
works when you
localize cold to an area in the body
healing
stimulates the healing process kicks in
inflammation starts to go down if you
have somebody and you have knee problems
or a shoulder problem and it's
inflamed and you do say the ice bath
where it's whole body cold it's not
localized anymore so your body is not
going to look for the
problem critical piece of information
right there so let's go to it a little
bit my shoulders killing me right here
it's really hurting
bad I got a badge shoulder you know
something's really hurting in there been
to a lot of doctors he's saying maybe I
got tennis shoulder
whatever right what do I do right here
well let me do an ice pack and localize
it on the shoulder or around the
shoulder when you do that your immune
system does something
interesting it senses the cold in a
certain area of the body
it senses it it heads to that
area interesting it seeks it out it
seeks out the area you're identifying
your injury or your spasm or your
chronic mystery inflammation you're
identifying it you're helping your body
even locate it isn't that crazy and
that's what's
amazing when you do full body cold from
head to down to your toe there ain't no
finding nothing there ain't no
localizing there's no looking for
anything it's chaos adrenaline flooding
your bloodstream trying to stop you from
going to hypothermic your immune system
is lowering because it's dying off from
the adrenaline surge keep that in mind
adrenaline is
purging immune cells are dying that's
how it works adrenaline is surging
immune cells are dying when you localize
right cold pack on the shoulder say cuz
you got a shoulder
injury immune system is not
dying you have localized the area your
body isn't under a threat it's not under
a fight or flight
threat this means your brain is not
sending messages to your adrenals saying
save me I'm getting too cold too fast
something is wrong help help help send
adrenaline out out that's not happening
as you're getting your therapy your cold
therapy on your shoulder
area inflammation will drop
quickly
inflammation will reduce your body will
respond the cold will really help with
the area that you're localizing it to
and your immune system will find its way
to that area
after you remove the cold pack as
well keep in mind that when the cold
pack is off of you after you used it for
10 minutes 15 minutes 20 minutes your
immune
system goes rapidly to the area that the
cold pack was on your immune cells run
to the area the cold pack was
on That's The Power of healing with cold
packs and hot packs we'll talk about
that in a minute as well
okay let's talk about durations you guys
by the way if you just got here I'm
making loaded crinkle cut fries I got
eggplant bacon right there I got a whole
bunch of stuff I'm just preparing you
because we're going to make those right
after this I got some nice carrots in
the steamer I'm going to make some nacho
cheese without all the garbage just
wanted to give you guys a little just
rundown of what's
coming so let's head into this area now
durations you might be a sensitive
person one
size fits all no one size doesn't fit
all you're somebody that might only need
5 minutes on an area somebody that might
need a smaller ice
pack somebody can handle because the com
how comfortable it is or not they can
handle a really cold ice pack on an
injury or a problem their elbow is
swollen they have an elbow problem a and
payes they may only need a few minutes
of the ice pack on the
elbow they may only need 5 minutes on
the
knee this is where you become the expert
to what you're doing for
yourself here's another thing you have
to understand whenever using cold packs
you want to make sure you're
warm you don't want your teeth to be
rattling
[Music]
you don't want to have that happening
you want to keep yourself warm when you
use an ice pack somewhere on the body
you want to take a blanket and you want
to place it over you you want to have a
nice cozy warm blanket somehow on you
while you're doing your cold pack
something like
this so right now I'm looking for a
blanket I happen to have one here it
is
and what you do is you have a blanket on
you right let's try to get this blanket
on me it's a new dance it's called the
blanket
dance kind of like this all right you
take the coal back and you have it
somewhere do you have it on your lower
back de are you dealing with some kind
of back pain do you have it on your hip
do you have it on your upper back do you
have it on your side do you have it on
your rib cage are you putting a cold
pack gently on the chest for a few
minutes at a time I want to go into that
too with nerve inflammation Vegas nerves
problems when we have swelling nerves
frenic nerves vegus nerves and so
forth but you want to keep
warm when you're doing your cold packs
maybe you hurt yourself on a very hot
day and you really don't need it
possibly it's really warm outside and
you're not worried and you got ni nice
pack on your rib you got a nice pack on
your elbow your wrist and so forth but
if you're somebody that's using them to
just calm nerves down you want to keep
warm you want to make sure you have a
blanket and if you have to use cold
packs for even a bigger length of time
you may even want a heating pad involved
so right here I got a heating
pad okay here's
one
so I'm going to go into some different
tips and some different things and ways
to use heating pads that are important
so if you're doing cold packs on you you
can always lay a heating pad over
you you don't have to be laying on the
heating pad you can even have your
heating pad over the blanket that's over
you just keeping warm down into you as
you're using ice packs what this does is
it ensures that your body is
warm while the area that you're trying
to ice is cool and
cold okay and why is that important once
again you're
localizing if you're warm everywhere
else in your body and the cold is in an
area you're trying to really Precision
wise
get like on a Precision level then more
healing occurs
it's different if you're
freezing totally freezing you got the
shakes your jaws like quivering you're
cold and you have the ice pack on you
that doesn't help as much cuz now your
body is just
cold and now your body is going into a
different situation you want to keep
your body warm you want to be
comfortable and then you want to take
the cold pack and use it in the
locations you need to use it in
got a comment right here does it work
for nerve pain let's head into there
yeah it does work for nerve pain for a
lot of people it can put the heating pad
over here for a
second well I do want before I answer
that I do want to actually talk about
one
thing I never put heating pads High I
never click the button and put them
really really high something to know
it's an important tip keep in mind
I never fall asleep on heating pads you
never want to fall asleep on a heating
pad that's jacked up really
high I like heating pads being down
low I've talked to a lot of people over
the years a lot of doctors and
practitioners giving advice to doctors
and practitioners and healers when it
comes down to heating pads and one of
the pieces of advice one of the
important factors is you don't ever need
to have it so high you don't want to
cook or bake yourself you don't want it
cranking in an area too
long you don't want to do that you want
to keep it low you can drape it over you
you can drape it over you under a
blanket on low you can drape it on top
of the blanket un low the goal is to
send some warmth
in while you're actually using any kind
of cold or ice pack unless you're in a
situation where you feel comfortable you
feel warm and you don't need to right
now if you want to go a little higher on
your heating pad you can't many people
do that and that's what they like they
put it up a little bit higher and they
get a little bit of warmth and heat into
the area like a strained muscle or some
body aches and pains and the heat feels
good so people may do that but I'm just
giving some tips on heating pads now if
you're somebody that just won't go near
a heating pad you don't like heating
pads you don't like the electricity
factor I find that the electricity
Factor does not affect people it does
more good than bad for people when they
need that warmth it actually does more
good when you're chronically sick than
bad because I know people like heating
pads what's he talk what is he talking
about now you can use different hot
packs that you might like I'm not saying
you can't look for the hot packs you
want or anything of the sort so let's go
into the next thing right
here what's this
hot water bottle right here so somebody
who doesn't like heating pads can find
warmth with the hot water bottle so
that's an option all on its own now I'm
going to fill this hot water bottle
right here with my sink I want to give
you some different tips on
that one
is I don't like filling a tea kettle
with boiling scolding hot water and then
filling my hot water water bottle with
that this is something I don't like to
do okay got your tea kettle filled it's
scolding scolding hot water and you're
pouring it into your hot water bottle
reason why I don't like that is there's
a good chance you're going to burn
yourself and you're going to get thir
Dee burns on your hands your thumb your
fingers and even your arm okay so if
you're going to heat up your water to
put in inside the water bottle don't let
it get to that crazy hot temperature
where it's boiling and bubbling over and
it's at that crazy scolding level don't
let it get to that you can do it where
it's just you know it's hot like hot
where if you did it did hit you it's not
going to be a tragic burn it might be
you know hot too hot to touch but you
know what I mean that is what I would
recommend now what I like to do is take
sink water and put sink water that's hot
into my hot water bottle so I'm going to
do that now some of you guys might not
be able to see me over there on IG and
Tick Tock so I kind of put my hand over
here see okay so what I'm doing is I'm
running my tap over here so you guys on
YouTube probably see that and Rumble but
you guys probably just see my hand over
here hello I'm here not going anywhere
all
right okay I got my hot water bottle
right here tap water's
hot okay so I'm going to take this hot
water bottle I'm going to put it just
like this I am filling it right off the
to just want everybody to
know and it's coming out really hot but
it's not coming out so hot where this is
going to really burn me or any levels
okay there we go it's filled up could
probably use a little bit more but I
just want to get back to you guys I'm
going to screw on the top
okay feels good nice warm hot water
bottle okay put that
there here's a bigger one with a little
pad around it maybe you have one of
these already I will open it up there we
are that's a big one right there I will
take it
out big one okay you can put as much
water as you want in here as it will
hold you can also put just just half the
amount of water or a third of the
amount and then you can actually rest on
this on the couch you can put this
behind you on the couch you can get heat
to your lower back the hot water bottle
so you can do heat and cold
therapy by localizing areas so you got a
back issue or back problem or you got
some kind of nerve pain or just
chronically sick with aches and pains no
one can figure out why or what maybe you
don't know the medium information yet
and you're just watching this now these
are great you can put a little bit of
hot water in there you can set it up at
the couch put it behind you lean back
and be like okay this is nice you can
also do this where if you got a back
problem and you need a cold pack for
your back back
problem you can take the cold pack and
you can put this behind you like this
and you can lean back right on the
couch and then you can take the hot
water bottle over you like this and stay
nice and warm
especially if you're going to do a half
an hour or more with a cold pack link is
in the bio on some of the stuff you guys
take a look medical medium.com the link
is in the
bio and in the description if you're
interested on any of this maybe you
already have this stuff go to Personal
Care directory and medical me.com you
can do that
it all
right let's go into nerve pain
neurological symptoms and so forth a lot
of people have chest
pain a lot of people have abdomen
pain people don't know why maybe they do
know why but either way any kind of
nerve related pain throughout the body a
little bit of cold on it can do wonders
calms things down now you might be
really sensitive and you're sensitive
with your nerves you got a lot of
neurological symptoms and put in hold
this too
much that's why you can do
this okay just see is a
towel I'm going to open this hollow
up going to do a magic trick for you
right
now no I'm
not
and I have a cold pack right here in
this towel now what I recommend is not
going from cold pack out of the freezer
to
skin I do not recommend going from cold
pack to
skin no no no no no
no not a good idea way too cold it's
going to hit the skin really
cold you might feel even like a little
freezer burn touch not good so when you
pull your cold packs out of the
freezer I like to put put them in a
towel now you can do a thinner towel you
can do a thicker
towel maybe you're somebody that does
the thinner one but I like one that's
got a little meat to it it's a little
thick you can even go thicker than this
and then if you got the Vegas nerve
issues the frenic nerve issues if you
got all the different nerve pain
throughout your body your neck your
trigeminal nerve that's another thing
right here okay a lot of people have
that jaw pain they have that pain on the
side of their face their teeth
hurt what maybe it's a maybe it's a
Dentistry issue maybe it's actually a
problem with the tooth maybe it's an
abscess can put a cold pack on an
abscess not inside your mouth but you
can take the cold pack and you can put
it on the side of your
jaw that's a great place for relief for
so many people that have trigeminal
neuralgia
they have different pain in their neck
and face Facial Pain facial nerves
actually calm down when you put a little
cold to them now here's the thing you
want to be careful if you're somebody
who's chronically sick and you got a lot
of different pain throughout the body
I'm talking about just lightly touching
and not for a long time nice towel on it
and it's just getting some cold in here
you don't have to be on there for more
than sometimes 30
seconds 30 seconds
seconds so you're dealing with some kind
of trigeminal neuralgia jaw pain nerve
pain maybe you're somebody that just
grinds your
teethed real like stiff jaw maybe you're
somebody that has different pain in
different areas of the neck I'm just
talking about a little bit even if it's
30 seconds so when you're chronically
sick and you do 30 seconds of this it
can actually assist in healing and help
to drive down some of that mystery
chronic
inflammation same thing with headaches
and migraines just touching the forehead
with a cold pack with the towel on it
you don't want to sit there with a
freezer pack right out of the freezer
and you just shove it on your head and
you're like okay I'm going to leave this
on here don't don't do that but you can
just do little bits at a time in areas
that are hypers sensitive like the
cranial nerve areas so I want to get my
little thing
here okay so cranial nerves
do a little demo so many people have
cranial nerve issues all the different
nerves coming out of their brain stem
are inflamed so they're having facial
problems they're having teeth problems
and jaw problems and a little bit of
coldness to it can be wonderful just in
those areas the back of the head cranial
nerves in the back of the head cranial
nerves on the face with a towel over it
I'm just you Gentle quick ways you can
do this someone said there gerbon said
for me the ice baths made me sicker and
sicker glad mm told me the truth about
this so I finally started healing I've
seen this before in the past when
someone's sick and they're chronically
sick chronically
ill the ice baths aren't the answer and
either is a sweat tent that's not the
answer either either is hot yoga that's
not the answer extreme
temperatures that engulf the
body is something you want to stay away
from when you're chronically sick
chronically ill or you're just out of
the category of just being little bit
sick or something like
that the hot and cold
packs assist healing while you work on
the medical medium tools and you work on
the medical medium information so you
know what's wrong you know how to heal
and you have all those other tools but
this is a great way it's like a gateway
to healing for so many people right
there on IG how does this compare to
infrared sauna I like infrared SAA but
if you're chronically sick you don't
want to sit in there with the
temperature jacked up really
high you don't want to do that I give
direction about things like this in the
medical medium
books Medical medium new addition check
it
out you don't want to be in
there and just doing that way now I like
infrared saas but remember it doesn't
isolate so it's not like you want to use
it where you sit in there you bake
yourself all the time you got it really
high when someone's chronically sick
that's too
much and the same thing with a cold
shower I want to talk about like a cold
shower some people would say well take a
really cold shower that's going to help
me you can take a cold shower but
remember it's not isolating or it's not
localizing the area it's full body when
you do infrared sauna it's full body I
don't mind cool showers for some people
that's different than an ice ice bath if
someone wants to turn it cold and just
get a rush of cold water right out of
the tab and then shake it off I'm not
against that at all that's hydrotherapy
I'm not against
hydrotherapy someone wants to get into
an infrared sauna and they want to warm
up and they have that temp on just right
for their needs and they're not in it
for 45 minutes an hour or 2 hours you
can get in there for 5 minutes 10
minutes because if you're chronically
sick that may be all you need to do you
don't want to push yourself you want to
keep it very low for 20 minutes no more
than 20
minutes but you want to also brace
yourself be cautious and mindful that
you're not baking yourself like a
cupcake in the oven for like an hour
with a really high heat when you're
chronically sick and so forth and
honestly for just
anyone so cranial nerves get inflamed
and it gives everybody with cranial
nerve inflammation issues lots of
different symptoms ticks and spasms
aches and pains all kinds of different
problems why are the nerves inflamed
viruses toxic heavy metals it's medical
medum inflamation talked about that for
years and years so all the different
viruses and bugs along with toxic heavy
metals inflame the brain stem people get
all the different problems every
everywhere they get the Vegas nerve
problems going through their body they
have all this different like they feel
like they're vibrating they feel like
their frequency is off they feel tired
when they're not supposed to be tired
that's the neurological fatigue and they
have all the ticks and spasms and
twitches and then with that they might
even get some OCD and some other things
involved which are all neurological they
might get some blurry vision for no
reason whatsoever which is the optic
neuritis or optic nerve inflammation and
all of this
combined I talk about in all the books
so people have answers I'm just bringing
in though something that's really
powerful which is hot cold packs
different tips about
it and there we are all right you guys
I'm going to start making some
fries all right so first of all I'm
going to make some crinkle fries and I'm
going get rid of this hot water bottle
right here feels so good feels like a
nice warm cuddly just feels
good you
know
all
right so what you want to do is I have
steamed potatoes here now you can make
crinkle fries with potatoes that are raw
put them in the oven you can do it that
way I have them steamed right here so
I'm making my crinkle fries steamed so
I'm going to make a whole bunch of them
so let's see got a little window into
what we're doing here so let's start
here now these might crumble a little
bit these potatoes
you can make them as thick as you want
you can make them as thin as you want
it's up to
you some potatoes
might work a little better this one was
really flaky and dry but we might get
some nice fries out of that one there
there we go you guys see that I'm going
to move these over I'm going to make a
whole
bunch of fries here those are some nice
fries here's a another thing to know
which is really fun if your
fries come from a large potato you get
these large crinkle fries which are so
great if it comes from a small potato
like this you get small crinkle fries
how do you like that then I'm going to
do this maybe try to get one more out of
this we'll
see yep some of them are going to break
apart some of them will be just fine but
that's all right let's just do it here
we go
now I want them a little thick I want
some
thickness here we
are if you make them too small too
skinny there we go you might run into
problems now remember these are steamed
already these aren't the raw
potato I chose to steam them to make it
nice just so we can actually bake them
and make them nice and crunchy
I also chose to steam them so they don't
have as much cooking time in the oven
that's a big deal and I also like the
inside of the potato
soft I like the inside of the potato
soft so here we go let's get some good
ones here this a very large
potato and the inside has like a little
bit of space in there so these might
fall apart a little
bit there we go
there we
go they're coming out good I might have
more than my pan can hold but we are
doing it let's go there's another
one there a lot of information when it
comes down to hot and cold
packs information people don't realize
you can really get cold with a cold pack
where your whole body just gets really
cold and you want to keep yourself
warm another thing too if you're
somebody that has back problems hip
problems and you know you pushed it too
far you had a big day like say you
exercised and worked out a little bit
more than normal say you took a walk
that's longer than normal say something
else happened where you were you know
doing something and loading some garbage
out of the house say you were lifting
things bending down more than normal and
you're in your recovery and you know
you're not quite there yet but you're
getting better you might want to get
that cold pack on
there and you can C you can totally
Stave off an
issue you can actually save off an issue
from becoming something give yourself a
break the next day get that cold pack on
and you can save off an actual problem
that would have developed that's what I
like about about cold
packs okay this one's a little crumbly
and a little weird might not use much
out of that one and you could still eat
it it's all great all right let's get a
pan going let's see what we can
do all right I got a parchment paper
sheet laying it in the pan right here
now I'm going to start taking my my
crinkle fries and I'm going to be
dropping them in let's go let's pack
them in there really
good some are a little bigger than
others I just like that you don't want
them all exactly the same size it's no
fun when you start going when you start
you know how you like choose the fry you
want you're kind of going through your
dish you're looking for the French fry
it's like when someone goes to the fast
food restaurant and they get a box of
fries they start eating certain ones
they'll grab the little ones right
or they'll go for just the big ones and
they'll wait for all those little ones
to sit on the bottom of the
package some of these are just going to
be kind of crunchy pieces which I really
like here we go coming
together come
together right
[Music]
now
beetles all
right let's get some more of
these okay you guys don't like the
beetles all
right that's a really big fry right
there that's like a steak fry these are
like steak fries crinkle cut steak
fries can I get a steak please can I get
a steak Yeah yeah uh medium well done is
that okay can I get the the crinkle cut
fries the the steak fries is that okay
okay great great is it a steak at 12 oz
good good all right awesome thank you
thank you very much can I get a water
another water yeah all
right better yet can I get a beer sorry
about that can I get a
beer what do you
have all
right let put these crinkles cut fries
in
here wa look at that wait a minute here
take a look at this I want to get close
up on this check out this crinkle cut
fry is this
insane that's insane am I just so am I
the only one that's excited about this
crinkle cut fry am I just am I
entertaining myself here on this one I
mean this is like really cool right no
it's really good that's really
cool that's the one I'm going to
eat whoa
okay that's just sick look at that
crinkle cut fry right there look at that
it's got like the skin on it which will
toast up really
nice all right great song you liked it
Wendy says I have just listened to today
again your old podcast recovering from
the physical injury so helpful will do
the cold packs for my
mother-in-law incredible all right you
guys see I want this kind of like evenly
done but I'm going to stick a few more
of these in some strange places like in
the corners here you know just kind of
off the beaten path if that's okay I
just want to get as many of these babies
in here as I can toast them
up all
right maybe a couple
more all right let's season these these
I'm going to push these to the side I'm
still going to cook these later you
better believe it those are
definitely going be cooked
later all
right so what do we have let's get some
seasoning on here let's go a little
onion
powder let's go going to pop some onion
powder in here oh this is going to be so
good you can be
generous if you like onion powder be
generous
there you go you don't like it don't use
it that's fine but it really brings that
flavor up into these fries really good
onion powder go up
AA no actually no we're going to go with
some oregano let's find that oregano
let's do garlic powder I have to find
the oregano
powder my bad I think I forgot that one
let's get some garlic powder on here you
don't have to do so much garlic powder
you don't want that exactly like so
crazy all right now I'm going to season
both
sides I'll probably do that by just
moving these around a little
bit I could take it out of the oven flip
them around then too but I'm going to
move some of these
around here we
go going to flip them over
nice
let's get both sides of many of these as
many as we can there we go
nice when you steam the potatoes and you
throw them in a bowl see I have to
season them on the plate right here
because they're steamed potatoes cuz
what happens is if you just throw them
in a big old bowl and you toss it around
with all the with all the seasonings
you're just going to bust them
up but when you cook them raw you just
don't end up into that kind of situation
so that's why I'm just playing with it
right here I'm going to do some more
onion powder on the other side
nice I think I'm going to sneeze I'm
going to
sneeze hold on I'm trying to hold in the
sneeze
on just kidding I'm kidding kidding let
me just get some oregano um it's nice we
have oregano
all
right little bit of oregano in here too
you
guys now I have fresh oregano in the
garden you can go as far as
that little bit of oregano on there it's
hard to come out all
right putting them in the oven
going to pop them in here I got the oven
at
400 let's get them
in
boom looking pretty
good crinkle fries are in the oven so
let's start making some of the fixings
let's go I'm going to chop up some
Tomatoes that's going to go into this
all
right clear out the deck let's go
here now now when it comes down heat
packs and stuff like that I want to go
into that a little bit um and talk about
the timing and and the order and
everything about hot packs cold packs
how to use them so we're going to go
head into there as well so let's do that
before we start chopping some stuff up
okay so let's get the hot and cold packs
out again you might have a different hot
pack I'm using a hot water ptle that's
what I'm using for this I'm also using a
heating pad too also now you can
localize areas with a heating pad if you
really want want just be careful and
don't have it on full blast like I said
earlier you want it on a lower
temperature so if you're going to use a
heating pad to localize an injury
localize just body pain and aches to
localize nerve problems whatever you're
dealing with just don't have it on full
blast and don't keep it on too too long
you don't want to cook yourself you
don't want to cook your organs you don't
want to cook yourself you don't want to
go into that hypothermic place so you
just want to be careful to I've seen
people where boom they have heating
blankets they got them on full blast you
know sometimes it's just way too much
all right so let me get a cold pack out
here okay what I like is warmth in the
morning if you're somebody dealing with
chronic illness on in any way shape or
form where you're having chronic aches
and pains you feel like you need
something you feel like you need warmth
if you want to therapeutically use it
the right way it would be heat in the
morning warmth in the morning now that
doesn't mean it's warmth in the morning
and then you have to wait all day long
to do cold at
night it's just that first thing first
like right away warmth in the morning
very helpful very healing the body
responds to it differently so that means
if you're dealing with some aches and
pains you got a sore back you got a sore
shoulder you're feeling problems all
over the place your neck and so forth
you bring warmth to it in the morning
that's what you
do okay now TimeWise totally up to you 5
minutes 10 minutes 15 minutes 20 minutes
anything like that an hour so you can
have a hot water bottle and leave it on
an area in the morning where you're
leaned up against a couch or you're in
bed with it and it eventually gets cool
because you've had it for an
hour and so you've been using it for an
hour and that's fine you can do that
if it's the same spot you want to use
other things therapeutically on like
cold for instance if it's the same
spot the cold can come after after
you've done warmth and you done warmth
in the area it can come directly after
if you really wanted to or you can give
it some time you let the warmth in that
area kind of seep in and then over time
whether it's an hour later half an hour
later 20 minutes later ler 3 hours later
you bring the cold pack into that area
and that's fine too and you can do it
even right after if you really wanted to
but you want to start with warmth in the
morning when you're dealing with hip
pain back pain leg pain leg spasms
cramps whatever it is that you're
dealing with nerve pain different ticks
and spasms and issues knee
pain am I missing anything arm pain
elbow pain right you do the warmth for
in the
morning cold can come later late morning
is fine midday later in the afternoon at
night and so forth now here's the thing
it doesn't mean you can't do warmth
again if you want to go to cold and you
go to cold an hour later and you're
doing a 20 minute half an hour cold
pack right here in this towel and you're
doing this in your back or any of that
other place places talking about hip leg
knee shoulder you can do that and
then afterwards you can do warmth again
you can switch off on and off all day
you can go one and the other one and the
other all day long if you'd like but you
want to start out with the warmth in the
morning if you
can and then you bring in the cold layer
now a lot of people get knee swelling
their knees swell up they get ankle
swelling knee swelling and that's what's
great about the cold packs localizing on
the areas much different than if if you
cool down the entire body like I was
talking about
earlier much different when you localize
it and you hit those areas so if you're
dealing with some kind of knee
pain and you
got the cold pack right there on there
if you're somebody that's walking around
you start out in the morning you're not
swollen you're not that swelled swelled
up on the knee and Ankle wherever it is
and you're doing you're you're doing
your business throughout the day you're
functioning you're being as productive
as you can and then by the end of the
day you're swelling knee leg something
swelling you bring the cold pack out can
wrap it in a towel get it icy cold out
of the freezer put it in that area if
your body's starting to get too cool you
bring in your hot water bottle or
heating pad like I was talking about
before a lot of people can get back pain
and pain in the lower abdomen during
their cycle this is all great options
for that too you can put heat on the
abdomen ice on the the lower back so
when menstration happens and there's a
lot of discomfort you can be doing cool
packs anywhere you'd like like in the
back area you can even do cool packs in
the abdominal area and then warmth on
your back you can switch it and that's
an option too for so many
people so much to talk about so much
information all of these tips are
important and then you become an expert
on how
to help manage some of your pain and
your aches and your swelling and while
you're doing other tools you're doing
your celery juice you're doing your
heavy metal detox maybe you're doing a
monoc cleanse medical Med monoc cleanse
maybe you're doing something else maybe
you're just doing like like boom the 28
day cleanse and you got the spinach soup
in there every single day which is
really healing and really powerful and
maybe you're doing a supplemental
protocol that I talk about in the
medical medium books you're doing your
B12 you're doing your zinc you're doing
your vitamin C right and you're doing
these things but you can also bring in
all these different therapies this is
one of them right here that really helps
now I want to go into like the mental
health aspect of hot and cold let's head
into there now for a couple minutes why
are crinkle fries are
cooking all right I'm going to cut up
some fixings in just a little bit this
is an important piece I don't want
anybody to miss
okay so when we're doing hot and cold
therapies we're braak
a cycle we might be in Han cold
Therapies in the way I'm addressing it
the way I'm showing you is really
helpful for
OCD really helpful for
bipolar really helpful for a lot of
different emotional and mental
PTSD occurrences a lot of people are
suffering from post-traumatic stress
syndrome they're dealing with it
post-traumatic stress issues they got
the the PTSD they're suffering they're
struggling and cold and hot like meaning
a hot warm bottle a hot water bottle a
hot
pack a cold pad like this where you got
that right the cold pack out of the
freezer it can break Cycles it can even
temporarily shift
depression temporally shift
sadness and temporally shift anxiety
that's how powerful the simple little
therapeutic option is that's so helpful
that people who are dealing with I've
seen people in the past totally manic
they're they have they're actually
engulfed in
Mania where they're about to just hop in
a car and just drive off a bridge
somewhere and you put a cold pack on
their neck and what happens is the
neurons
start to shift the electricity through
the brain starts to
shift and literally I've seen people
come out of manic
moments I've seen people that were just
like so up so up where they were losing
it I've talked to a lot of doctors and
practitioners and heers over the years
and I've had a lot of
doctors ask me questions about this
about patients that had mental health
issues emotional
struggles and I would say do hot and
cold have it on hand make sure they have
it on hand since someone's dealing with
any kind of like struggle emotionally
and mentally if you bring in a cold pack
and you just rest it on the abdomen
something starts to
shift you rest it in the lower back
something starts to shift you put it on
your thighs a cold back on your thighs
and something starts to
shift because what happens
is your neurons start to
reroute electricity that's going to
neurons to neurons start to redirect and
it heads into different parts of the
brain that it wasn't heading
into and so it's shifting that pathway
that electrical grid sending it into
different neurons it's not normally
headed for
and so when we're dealing with things
emotionally emotional struggles we're
dealing with mental
stress you come home from a really bad
day or you've been home and you got some
bad news or you've had a struggle and
you bring out a cold
pack it can help alleviate and even
shift that of how you're feeling in that
moment so things calm down or maybe
you're like a hot head and you get some
bad news and you just want to explode on
someone a friend or something and you
want to hit them with all kinds of texts
and tell them how they did you wrong if
you stop for a moment and you get a cold
pack out of the
freezer and you start putting a cold
pack on the top of your head on the side
of your neck for a little bit on your
chest for a little bit watch the
difference 10 minutes 15 minutes later
you're going to take your phone and
you're not going to fire out like what
you were going to fire out to that
friend to that loved
one so maybe maybe a sibling did
something to you and they took your
car maybe you know a parent told you you
couldn't do this or that you got really
upset maybe a coworker this so maybe a
spouse maybe a loved one maybe a friend
maybe a friend totally backstabbed you
and started dating your
ex-girlfriend maybe something happened
or your ex-boyfriend and you're
literally going to go bananas you feel
totally betrayed you feel totally
wronged or you feel like something
coming on you can't explain it you're
about to have like an episode where
you're going to have some anger develop
like anger is starting to steam you
don't know why you're so pissed off
maybe you maybe it's been just stirring
up inside of you because you've been
chronically sick for a long time and
struggling and maybe you're just like
getting triggered by something on social
media and anger's actually getting fired
up you take a cold pack and you put that
to a spot in your body your chest for a
minute your abdomen the back of your
neck and all of a sudden it starts to
shift and that anger spell you can
actually
avoid and the anger is not like tearing
into you and tearing you apart you can
actually avoid it that cold pack can
shift you into a different direction
think about how powerful that
is really
powerful J says thank you aw for this
healing tool I am a psychotherapist and
this tool will be a game changer thank
you for being here truly
catac says this is so unbelievably
helpful right
now I've seen people where they're on a
verge of on on the verge of anger and
depression and a cold pack rerouted
things and shut it down I've seen people
betrayed like cheated on and they were
going to go bananas they're they were
calling their friend 20 30 40 times
within an hour saying you call me back
calling calling calling because somebody
betrayed them or something happened and
instead of that happening they brought
the cold packs out and they started
putting another body and it shifted him
and they said wait a minute I have to
rethink this I have to rethink this and
I have to calm down Lis free accelerate
333 this information is incredible I
never heard of this for anger or bad
moods wow it's from Spirit of
compassion I certainly didn't come up
with
it it's from s
so like all the other medical M
information educating myself says or
your wife invited the in-laws that's a
really good one educating myself that's
a really good one and so true and just
I've seen cold packs where you're about
to get heated up emotionally say say
it's family or friends you feel like
you've been wronged or you're
misunderstood what about you're you're
not Mis you're totally not understood
you're misunderstood and so you're you
can't even get your messages outright
and you start getting emotional and
angry and upset you take a cold pack you
put that to your
chest you sit you sit down
somewhere watch it all shift you
wouldn't believe what could happen it
can change your life change your life
cold pack
therapy medical medium tools when you
know what they're for and what you're
doing Charlotte Courier says I needed
this info so desperately today thank you
aw ands so I've been teaching about this
information for many many years it's one
of the medical meme therapies I was
going to do a whole book just on it
alone and too many people are
chronically sick with so many problems I
just can't write a 100
books just can't do it anyway let's get
going let's move let's get this recipe
done I want to make these sprinkle fries
let's check the oven let's make sure
they're not burning what if they're
burning man not good what if they're
burning no they're not they look good
temperature 400 they're cooking nicely
let's
go all right going to chop up some
Tomatoes ranada ranada 144 good to see
you a w can cold packs be used in the
chest for Vegas nerves pressure and
tightening yes they can be used it's
original mm info it taught that for
years certain practitioners and doctors
they can be used for that for Vegas
nerve issues we not to thank you for
asking that this is what you can do you
can take the cold
pack and you could be wearing something
this way you're not putting the freezing
cold ice on top of your skin you can put
a towel hand towel so forth and you can
put it right on here you don't have to
do it long this is important Right Here
length of time does not roll here it
doesn't it can
2 minutes that take that take that home
with you definitely take that feather
put in your C take that feather two
minutes put it in your cap don't lose
that
one Stephanie Strow says I'm a physical
therapist I'll use this thank you thank
you for being here truly I'm honored
you're here by the
way corny says I'm literally mind blown
all
right
all right I got to chop up some stuff
let me do some green onions if you guys
don't mind right now I'm going to take
these these came from the garden man
when they come from the
garden it's a whole different thing
right a lot of reason right on here
there's elevated biotics by the way
medical me Med information on produce
that's grown in your backyard in your
garden in a pot somewhere on your stoop
or your window
sill there's billions of bacteria like
little tiny microorganisms all on here
if you eat this raw piece right here
right from the garden just like
this that elevated that elevated biotic
that's covered and coated all over here
goes down and it doesn't die off in your
stomach acid it finds its way down
here in this region of the intestinal
tract it camps out and it produces
vitamin
B12 it's a really good piece of
information I wish I could be here all
day and just sit on here all
day and just talk about everything and
anything let's not use the crinkle knife
on
this let's see Dr car
Dr Caravan says totally using this as a
psychologist boom just mind-blowing
information thank you ma'am for being
here
um I'm happy to have psychologist here
and Dr
Nesbit is happy to have a psychologist
here too Dr Nesbit is a certified
psychiatrist Dr Carrie nean thank you
for being
here so what I'm doing is I'm cutting
these nice little scallions
here's chop this
up and I
am going to pop these in I might put
them in a smaller Bowl I think that's
what I'll do all right I could chop them
up quicker but I'm going to chop them up
slow let's see how quick I can chop them
up do not play around in the kitchen
with knives whatever you do it's a
stupid
idea it's a stupid idea don't try to
race don't try to be
funny do not try to be
funny with with knives in the kitchen
take it serious don't drop one on your
foot whatever you
do do not joke around
I'm making my loaded crinkle cut fries
if you guys just got on here hey I just
got on here now what's you talking
about all right let's get some Tomatoes
going
now so these are gorgeous Tomatoes they
taste really good so I'm going to cut
them here's the thing with tomatoes
right I like to cut them like that where
the inside is is going to the surface
you see that okay
I like to cut them that
way all right let's just get a couple I
don't want these too big don't want them
too small so I think that's actually
pretty good cut some
more it's like it's a meditation when
you're doing this right there we go cut
these a little
better it's like a
meditation I can sit here and I can chop
up
Tomatoes I can chop things up here and I
can just get so lost that I I'll forget
that I'm even
live I'll get so lost in this process
I'll forget I'm even
live couple hours later I'll be like are
you guys still on
there
whoa all right let's get these Tomatoes
going I think I'm G to do more Tomatoes
than that so I'm going to drop this
right in
here okay get a couple more
Tomatoes all
right I'm
working all
right here we
go I'm
working you
guys
I'm working for you I'm working for
you I work for you guys
man um it's
just it's nothing
more honorable I'm honored to work for
you guys I'm
honored honored every one of you are
here
and I'm just getting these Tomatoes done
that's good we got it chop up the pepper
now get some of this off here all right
check out these Peppers you guys here
right there we
go all right the peppers came from the
garden too
peppers are a little hot it's not a
jalapeno but it's darn
close it's a hot pepper I'm a little
scared of
it do you ever get scared of peppers
because you're just like that's going to
be
hot that is going to be scary so I'm
going to chop this up I'm going to go
with that kind of see that right there
there's some pepper seeds there you can
take them out I'm going to leave them
there now I want some nice pepper pieces
here so I'm just going to here we
go here we go okay all right in you
go Julie Tuesday on YouTube I actually
read your comments I read everybody's
comments on YouTube you guys just so you
know if you guys leave a comment it
doesn't mean I don't read them I
actually read them Julie Tuesday says
I'm I'm in survival mode and medical
medium tools are keeping me going thank
you for all you do for us so I'm so
happy to hear that I mean I'm I'm I'm so
sorry you're in survival mode it breaks
my heart really
does I could only imagine
seriously people don't know what that's
like unless they've been there unless
they've been you
know okay got some nice pepper pieces
here I want to make sure these pepper
pieces
okay do some round pieces
here and I'll cut these up
too all
right and I got another pepper
here
okay nice chop up
these unless anybody's ever gone through
something really like a real struggle
something really
difficult you just don't know what it's
like all
right let me check these crinkle
fries they're coming
along they are coming along long all
right so we got some peppers here want
to show you we got some Tomatoes here we
got green onion scallions from the
garden peppers from the garden we got
some black beans right here we're going
to use
too okay we got our
lime now I'm going to take this really
hot pepper
here I'm going to put a little bit of
that in the cheese the nacho cheese
sauce so let me just move move these
over a little
bit and now I'm going to flip the fries
those babies are going to be
like toasting oh
yeah all right hang in here you
guys we got a full kitchen going
here bear with
me
yeah this stuff's getting
crazy
okay all right let's flip these let's
go
[Music]
mhm flip them with a fork but I have you
flipper here it
is take hold on hold
on just give me a second you
guys got a cold pack at the back of my
neck that's actually an amazing place
for it I'm just letting you know I got
the oven cranking it's hot in here I
don't think I got you know think it got
hot in the house today I got fries
steaming
up I'm not overwhelmed at
all this cool pack feels good nice cool
pack right
here
nice do I need any hot water bottle or
heating at all oh no I think I'm good
for now all right let's go let's flip
these so got these flipped around a
little bit these are hot that one's nice
and
toasty okay we're going to flip these
around you guys don't mind move them
around here so what I like about these
there we go nice and brown on the bottom
that's what I want okay going probably
do this with my hands a little bit
there you go flip those there flip these
here that's the big one right there
that's the big
one definitely those are a little stuck
all right that one's
actually okay yeah where we go flipped a
bunch of them we're good they actually
look good let's get them
in you can name your crinkle fries this
one's Frosty I'm gonna name this one
something else I'm gonna name this
one all
right just what I
thought just what I
thought yeah now we're
cooking now we're
cooking let's answer some questions here
Sophie wow looks incredible yummy
it's it's going to be Beyond yummy I
think I got things in check here what
I'm going to do is just make sure this
is
warm a little of that going on
there using my head I'm using my head
you guys I
am can't eat Frosty if you name it if
you name your crinkle
fries
can name your crinkle
crusty yeah you guys all right so
listen
so I want to I want to talk about a
couple different things one is I want to
let everybody know I I have a feeling
some of you don't think I read your
comments but I do I do so I want people
to know it's important like on YouTube a
lot of people leave comments on there
you know I read
them so that that I mean I want you to
know I can't read every comment in the
world on all the platforms I'm just
letting you know but on YouTube for sure
I've I read every single one of
them so if you want to say something
terrible to me that's a great place to
do
it e
w why do you do this why do you do that
I'll read it I'll have my cold packs
ready all right so my crinkle fries are
cooking once they're cooked making the
cheese sauce putting on the fixings and
we're going nacho crazy
um now I want to bring out one of the
books
here do you have brain saver protocols
the amount of symptoms and conditions in
here really really incredible and
helpful and the Protocols are in here
too I see a lot of
people they look at a protocol and
they're like what do I do and there's a
chapter in here that covers that where
you can start out with just one thing or
two
things or three things and you can start
out small and just keep it to that you
can also go as far as you need to go and
that's in here too sometimes some people
be like whoa wait a minute he's got a
protocol in there there's a lot going
going on how do I do that what do I do
and what people don't realize is if you
read the instructions in the book If you
read the chapter about supplementation
and protocols for symptoms and
conditions what you'll find is that you
can start just with some of the key
foundational
tools key foundational supplements and
you can start there and see how you feel
along the way but you know you can go
further and further the thing about
medical medium information is you can
take it as far as you need to go but a
lot of people don't do that so a lot of
people will do some celery juice for
like two weeks and then they'll claim
they did medical medium especially if
they're a hater so you got to keep in
mind is you'll see out there people
scream I did medical medium and this
terrible thing happened to me it's like
you did do med you did medical medium
really or did you do a whole bunch of
other stuff you mean you weren't eating
chocolate you you mean you weren't doing
this you weren't doing that and so
people just they will just scream at if
they're a hater like if they if for some
reason someone convinces them I'm a bad
guy or something they like okay and they
did celery juice for like a week or
every other day for a month and they're
doing all this other stuff right and
they just like I did medical medium and
it doesn't work he did this he did this
it did this look out for that because
it's ridiculous and people don't realize
that there's a lot of exposures people
are up against
too so every day we have all these
exposures that we're up against and
every day we also have things inside of
our body that have been sitting there
for like 20 30 40 years wreaking havoc
on our body that people haven't gotten
out of their body because they're not
doing the right stuff to get the junk
and garbage out so they have a drain on
them of what's inside their body that's
toxic and then they're getting outside
exposures on a regular basis
I've seen over the years like doctors
tell me I thought my patient was doing
medical medium and it turns out they
were drinking on the weekends every
single
weekend I
had a feather for every time I heard
that I'd be like flying
away to a tropical
island and never coming back again like
seriously and I mean this like I can't
tell you how many practitioners I've
talked to where they're like I thought
they were doing medical medium but when
I really asked them and I really went
into it cuz I thought they were doing
what they were supposed to do that the
doctor was guiding them on and they
weren't they were doing so many other
different
things and it was affecting
them so what you'll see is a bunch of
situations that are occurring in the
medical M community and one of them is
like I tried medical medium and it
didn't work but yet the person didn't
try they didn't do the monoc cleanse for
their digestive problems they didn't do
the 28 day cleanse and they just stay
off all the heavy fats they were eating
they were on fat all the time and
there's nothing wrong with that there's
nothing wrong with trying something and
not doing all of it there's nothing
wrong with trying one or two medical
medium tools and then keeping the others
out what's wrong is screaming
that I did medical medium when you
didn't that's wrong and I see that a lot
out there and it's sad because you might
be this other person that's like a new
person that just came in like I heard a
whole bunch of people healed on medical
medium they got the most healing stories
in the world out of any
single you know whatever out there in
the health world so let me try something
and then all of a sudden they get
bombarded with someone that's like
trolling
I tried medical medium it didn't work
for me my whatever got worse than I
would ever I go and try this and this
helped me over here and then they're
screwed they're like they don't try
medical medium they're off to doing the
same old stuff that everybody's ever
done and whatnot hopefully they find
their way back but that doesn't always
happen so there's nothing wrong with
trying one thing and there's nothing
wrong with also dabbling and other
things out there but when it's not
working for you don't blame what you're
dabbling in on medical medium so if
you're doing bad zeyt cuz they're all
bad now don't blame medical medium when
something's not working for you if
you're doing the Pearl powder the bad
zeits the charcoal ingesting it the
Bentonite Clays you're doing all that
plus 100 sodium
bicarbonate don't blame medical medium a
year later after you did all the stuff
that damaged your health that medical
medum doesn't doesn't recommend that's
wrong and that's what people are doing
if you're eating a chocolate bar every
week and another chocolate bar every
week don't say you did medical medium
when you're sick and the chocolate bar
got you more viral cuz it just blew up
your immune system and nervous
system don't then say it was medical
medium that did it that's what's wrong
same thing with Medical Treatments if
you go and try a medical treatment cuz
that's up to you I believe in doctors I
recommend doctors all the time I love
doctors
everybody should have one but what
happens is if you're doing a medical
treatment that went wrong don't blame
medical medium and the celery juice
that's where that's just and
the same thing if you got into a new
relationship and you caught 10 new bugs
and now you have a new bat of chronic
fatigue syndrome and a new UTI don't
blame medical medium that's just
just keep that in mind I know
you guys don't do it I know you guys
aren't doing that I'm just saying that
and then it's not you guys but it's
people out there that are that are you
know that do that okay they'll get into
a new relationship but they won't be
honest about it you know and which is
fine we we should be able to get into
relationships if we want to get into
relationships but if you do if you do
get two or three more viruses and three
varieties of strep and you all of a
sudden got UTI and sinus infections
again don't blame medical
media if you're somebody that's doing
ice baths all the time then 6 months
later you get into adrenal fatigue
because your adrenals just got drained
from the ice baths don't blame medical
medium if you're using the alkaline
ionizer water machines the ones that
sound like
kangaroo the ones that sound like
kangaroo if you do those and you're
getting metals and metals and more
metals and more Metals in your system
because it's rotting off the plate
inside the ionizer machine if you got
suckered into buying a three $1,000
alkaline ionizer water
machine and you're contaminating your
system with all that toxic water and you
get sick in two years like everybody
else did 20 years ago with that water
don't blame medical medium that's just
icha is saying therea is
healing they always say I did it
perfectly which odd a huge tell to me
and they
didn't so I'm checking the crinkle fries
yeah we're still
cooking if you're doing Bentonite Clays
and you're doing all these scratchy
detox like powders and you're doing all
these probiotics with all this garbage
and junk in
them and you're
doing the ionizer water and the zeolites
and everything
else and you get
sick don't play Medical medum
is it too much to ask I know you guys
don't but I see it out there I see it
out there yeah yeah rhymes with
kangaroo kangaroo all
right um I just want to take this thing
get this ready I might make this soon
possibly all
right double check this whoa couple more
minutes fries are almost ready I'm going
to make the cheese right now
though Demmer some
hot some hot potatoes
here I'm going to bring this over a
little
bit going bring this
here okay what is see in the steamer is
some
potatoes and you're seeing some
carrots I'm going to take the skin off
the potatoes because I want that cheesy
cheese I don't want the potato skin
involved in
here that's some hot stuff that is hot
so what I'm doing is scraping off the
skin you're not going to be able to see
it too easy so I'm going just push this
up so I'm getting the skin off this
potato
that's really a hot
one and what you'll find is the people
that actually get involved with trying
to sell something tend to be
interestingly enough like oh yeah I know
medical medium medical medium caused
that problem it causes that problem
don't do it it caused my problem but hey
buy
this but hey go buy this El hey go buy
this go buy this water machine hey go
buy
this by the way I'm selling this
this yeah but don't do medical
media all
right it's a dog eat dog world is what
it is I'm making sure all the skin comes
off this potato I don't want pieces of
the potato skin yes potato skin is
healthy for you it's really good for you
you should leave your skins on the
potatoes if you if you desire but um
actually for this cheese sauce I'm
trying to avoid having the skin in there
keep that in
mind all right so I'm going to do this
I'm going to put this baby in I'm going
to cut it in pieces like
this and it goes in that's
hot it's about 1 and 1/2 cups of diced
potato I can measure
it and those crinkle fries are almost
done I was making a bigger
batch
okay okay I just put that in there now
I'm going to make a little bigger of a
batch so I'm going to add add another
one cuz I want a decent amount of cheese
if that's okay here we go we're going to
peel the skin
back it's awfully quiet in
here all right let's get this in
here have you guys made this yet just
curious
all right we got some
cheese let's get the carrots in
here carrots are going to be about one
cup of diced
carrot
so these are really steamed nice you got
to make sure your carrots are soft you
don't want to put like carrots that are
like half cooked in here you can't make
a cheese sauce with a carrot that isn't
cooked well
I'm just letting you
know that right there is an important
tip very
important let's grab a few more of these
carrots throw that in nice and soft and
good it's about one cup but I'm going
with two cups I'm trying to make it a
little
bigger and that should do
it
y I think I have three cups of potato in
there cuz I'm trying to make double the
size
okay I'm going to get a little bit of
garlic powder in there
now just follow
me so half a teaspoon garlic powder
there we
go what else onion powder half a
teaspoon onion powder this is going to
taste so
good it's going to be so good little bit
of cayenne I'm going to put a fresh one
in please if you don't
mind I'm going to put put a fresh
cayenne in here because I have them so I
don't okay keep in mind when you use the
cayenne
powder or you put Cayenne in
there sometimes a pepper can be really
hot so I'm going to pop a little bit in
here but not go too
crazy there we go push that to the side
don't rub your eyes don't rub your face
after you have all that hot pepper on
there let's go with a tablespoon of some
squeezed lime
lime nice it's
easy these limes are
ripe and need one more I want to make
sure we get a tablespoon
there
cool
yep
one tablespoon of freshly squeezed lime
or
lemon but we're going to do two cuz I'm
making a bigger batch of
course that's what it
is yeah nothing like a good lime maxwood
good job it's true so
true now listen I like my fries a little
extra crunchy I I like them like a
little bit you know browned nice right
okay there we
go that's how I like my
fries all right what else is in here
little bit of water if we need it so I'm
going to I'm going to be careful with
this
because you put too much water in there
then you got a cheese that you may not
want boom
boom
we're going to add some water in
now guess what we're not using
nutritional
yeast you know many people do
nutritional yeast and they mess up their
health because of
it I'm doing medical medium but they're
taking down all that nutritional yeast
it's on everything they're buying stuff
with nutritional yeast in it but I'm
doing medical medium and it hurt me but
they're doing all this nutritional
yeast it's okay to actually do one
medical medium thing and only one
medical medium thing there's nothing
wrong with
that you can do one or two medical
medium
things like I challenge people to do one
medical medium thing it's
fine but if something's not working for
you look at everything else you're doing
or you did look at everything before you
start screaming from the roof
rooftop about like celery juice giving
you the
runs anyway it's just something to think
about I keep on for forgetting to bring
it
up let's take a look at this I want to
see the
consistency it's actually a good
consistency right there I actually
really like that let's give it another
run
okay and what I'm going to do is is sprp
the
sides and I might put a little bit more
potato in this one which I like I think
it's a good idea I put a little extra
carrot in there versus
potato look you can have the cheddar
cheese look right there where it's that
like but what I'm going to do is just
lighten it up a little
bit with another
potato and I hear my crinkle fries are
calling well there we go
that should do
it bigger
batch a little bit
water I'm so
hungry I am excited I am like psyched
and pumped about eating
this let's see the consistency that I
want for
cheese I don't want
it
that's all
right
you want to do is put the cheese on
First on top of the crinkle fries before
you put your
fixings and let's clean things up a
little bit and make some
room yep yep yep yep if you guys don't
mind I'm going to do a little clean up
right
here I am the kitchen cleaner by the
way I just want people to know that
there isn't a service or something that
comes in after this is done it's not the
medical medium team that comes in and
has to clean this mess I make this crazy
mess it's actually me I sit here right
when we shut down right when we shut
down everything I sit here like putting
everything away cleaning it up scrubbing
everything down vacuuming the floor
washing the floor cleaning everything up
running the dishes and that's what I
do all
right
okay all right take a look at these when
you close up real
quick I'm going to put the fries
in this right
here this pan is freaking hot you got to
be real careful with this
pan real
careful
okay we're going to get these
in there's that big fry right there can
you guys see I'll give a closeup
too
here look at this huge
fry don't worry though there's small
fries here too but there look at that
right there oh man is that not
sick dude that's
sick look at
that seriously right look at I love when
it's like that check that out
right
right or what whoa crunchy not look at
that that's going to be like insane
don't worry I got some small fries here
you know like the little
ones crunchy little ones right there oh
yeah look at that look
at do I right did I do it right
today cuz usually I'm just
multitasking I'm trying to um entertain
you guys give you guys really good info
groundbreaking information at the same
time I'm trying to like you know trying
to
cook this is this is just coming out so
good I don't even know what to say and I
made so many good ones here okay let's
get the rest of these on
here let's stop talking about it let's
go get down to some
eating you going to talk about it or you
going to walk the talk
man cuz you can talk about it but I'm
going to do some
eating
yep
yeah oh yeah let's do
this
uh-huh
whoa that that's just like that's just
wrong it's so wrong it's
right it's so wrong it's right what is
that's
crazy all right I'm not just trying to
like I'm not just trying to talk this
up sorry look stealing that little
one all
right all
right
okay how's that
look guess remember when I did the
Easter baskets remember when I did the
Amazon I was on Amazon did the Easter
baskets you guys remember
that I'm going to give this a quick
fresh blend real quick a little bit of
this there we
go all right cheese is coming
now
okay all
right I'm going to drop a little bit of
this cheese down on here
okay now how much cheese do you like on
your natural
fries I'm not going to try to like cover
them all like crazy right but I do want
enough of that cheese because that
that's the good
stuff that's the good stuff how's that
look you guys like it how does that look
okay I got a mess ahead of me
tonight got a freaking
mess bacon bits are next dang check this
out no
bacon bacon slices straight pork fat no
they're not they're not pork this is the
the uh eggplant bacon that's inside the
book one of the recipes all right let's
just get this
going I'm going to chop them up yeah
that's what I'm going to do I'm going to
chop them up I like the sound of that
I'm going to make them into little
squares okay you
guys I'm going to chop them up like this
into little
squares who bacon
pieces look at
that here we go it's like a
crispy oh so
good so good I'm going to put a few more
on here here's a little bacon bits on
here and a pig didn't have to die for
this it's
amazing
amazing poor little oinker didn't have
to die for this this is
incredible um now I'm going to drop some
black beans on here I'm getting these on
here so good all right get some black
beans on here
now get
spon
woo okay get some black beans on
here
sir would you like some black beans on
there yes ma'am you would you like black
beans on
there
okay I've been working at aw's bar and
grill for about 2 months
now black beans on there come on what's
next
tomatoes
some
Tomatoes I mean this is
insane just a couple more okay just to
get a good good few in there okay we
doing green onions
next we do some hot pepper
next oh look at
that whoa look put those hot peppers on
there I could just see it now I'm going
to be
like I'm going to need some cold packs
with this one this is
like okay here we go I'm going to put
some green onion now
next you don't have to go too crazy with
the green onion just
right some of you guys might not want
green onion scallions here we go
is this thing actually done did I do
it did I actually do
it huh oops let's miss it all right
let's
go we are doing it that's what happens
when you're looking at the camera and
not at the
plate okay there you go you guys IG take
a look Tik Tock take a look
you guys
here you can actually use a bacon strip
to dip in there you can use a fork to go
in here
too all
right oh man you can take a crinkle fry
you don't need a fork you can take look
at that three black beans on there like
that and then that pepper on there this
is is okay this is the way to do it
green onion what else is there a tomato
I can get on here look at this this big
old fry we're calling this fry
Titanic this fry is going down into my
mouth right
now
mhm amazing
amazing Marina Maran it does look
amazing it is amazing
it's that
good it's so wrong it's right that's
what it is it's so wrong it's actually
right I am probably not going to eat it
I'm just going to admire it
today I'm going to eat it I'm going to
tank this thing this thing ain't going
to stand a
chance I'm going to take a piece of
bacon you guys don't
mind so I went to this doctor guy and he
said eat a whole bunch of bacon in the
morning says you need your protein and
you need your fat and I said make sure
you eat a lot of bacon every
day I can't tell you how many times I've
heard people
say Bacon's really good for you you
should be eating
[Music]
bacon no judging no offense bacon is not
good for
you this is the eggplant
bacon
mhm so
good follow medical medium on
telegram follow medical medium on Tik
Tok get the medical medium newsletter
sign up follow medical medium podcast
give me a thumbs
up please or give me uh what a green
light I don't know what's on here
now is it like green light
like I'm looking here on social media
just give them a green light give me a
green light give me a thumbs up give me
a heads
up whatever you want leave a comment
letting him letting me know if you like
this
show or if you thought the show was
terrible all
right never have somebody do that you
point they take whatever they're eating
at the table and they're like this is so
good
so good I you got to try
this all
right r