we're live on telegram
live on rumble
facebook youtube tick tock
we're talking about supplements when
we're sick
when we get sick when we have problems
how do we take supplements which ones do
we take how does it work and that's what
we're talking about today this is really
exciting i just took some just now
you guys on telegram might have saw me
do it i just took celery for us because
what i do is i'll take a bunch of celery
for us before i'll start alive and then
like eight minutes after i take it
something starts happening and i just
i still to this day
i laugh about it all the time i mean i
laugh about it all the time like eight
minutes
nine minutes after taking the celery
force i don't know if you guys have
experienced this the first day i took it
it was like something like 12 minutes or
something and all of a sudden
i was like rearranging the freezer i was
rearranging the refrigerator like
something was happening so what i do is
before some lives i'll take some celery
force and then after about five minutes
or something next thing you know what
i'm on the pink phone
and i'm on the pink phone but anyway
hey guys i'm glad you guys are here
we're doing a live today
as you guys can see i got cleansed heel
in front of me right here and i have the
symptoms and conditions part opened
right
so you'll see in here i have that and i
have
pages marked because i want to talk
about different conditions like i have
autoimmune disease marked right because
everybody's getting an autoimmune
diagnosis everybody
everybody is going to have an autoimmune
diagnosis you don't have one now you'll
have one mark my words that's not
negative thinking it's just a fact of
what's happening
you know
it's not like it was years ago you live
your life
nothing really happens
you're 85 years old you got heart
disease and kidney failure and that's
how you go or something right now it's a
different world now we got you could be
12 years old 13 years old 15 years old
19 years old 25 35 38 39 40 and you get
the autoimmune diagnosis it can hit at
any time it happens all the hashimoto's
thyroid problems boom autoimmune
i mean fatigue once it's chronic fatigue
autoimmune alopecia autoimmune i mean
eczema autoimmune psoriasis autoimmune
vitiligo autoimmune it just it's endless
right
and so yeah so autoimmune it's just it's
unbelievable but
hundreds of autoimmune conditions right
so that's the whole thing you don't even
need a condition
just go to your practitioner go to your
doctor with some aches and pains they do
an a a c reactive protein
and you got autoimmune with no diagnosis
you can actually go to your doctor and
they can just look at your markers
and they can just be like well we don't
know exact you're now going to have to
go to an autoimmune specialist
because we took you this far and we see
you have autoimmune markers you've got
your ana is up your c reactive protein
is up something's up right there right
and
and so they'll be like now you got to go
to your next doctor
and find out what autoimmune disease you
might have
you don't even need a diagnosis anymore
to get the autoimmune label
not at all so anyway that's just one
thing we're talking about so you guys
see right here some i might do some zinc
shock therapy i might do a little bit of
uh vitamin c shock therapy too good to
see you guys
i'm going live exclusively 6 45 on
rumble later eastern
3 45
okay pacific so i'll be on rumble later
it's just gonna be you know a little bit
of an exclusive rumble that's like we've
been doing lately so i hope you guys all
come there later so check it out when
you get a chance so i'm going over
symptoms and conditions i'm talking
about supplementation how to take them
what you see out here are some a whole
bunch of different supplements right
and you see my celery juice you see that
right there you see my celery juice you
also see aloe
it's just some aloe vera right there
every single day
i take a knife
hack off a piece
hack off the tail right here and then i
flay it cut off two inches flay it open
section it like that i take it i just
eat it
every single day
and that's actually a new that's a
that's a therapy that's part of a
protocol
so i have that right here
okay so let me tell you show you how to
use
cleanse the heel how do you use the
supplements chapter how do you use the
supplement section and
the dosage and everything dr faun md
good to see you
yep amazing hello is it me you're
looking for
so
here we are you guys so let's start i
got the little shot glasses
now you can take tinctures
straight just in your mouth you can do
that you know i mean i'll take b12
straight like that
every single day i'll do
lately with everything because i'm i'm
working really hard right now lately
i'll take more b12 than i usually do but
you can do them straight in your mouth
like this
right that's two dropper falls right
there
and you can also do it this way too i
just want to show you a couple little
things before we go into symptoms and
conditions
this is going to be an interesting
live
so what i did i just put two dropper
holes of b12
right in here and put a little bit of
water too so i recommend that too i
recommend you put your tinctures in an
ounce of water
definitely you can do that
send that down
okay
talking about using goldenseal too we'll
go into that a little bit different
conditions so here we are
all right we're in knowing the cause and
the protocol of cleanse to heal now if
you guys don't have cleanse to heal it's
a critical life-saving tool
it's important to have in your life
even just small pieces tidbits taken out
of this book and applying it into your
life can make changes
in your health
it's really incredible what this book
has done so this and if you want to know
where this book is it's on amazon.com us
right it's it's also a book depository
other places around the world i think
it's at target other places
but amazon.com us is running a sale 51
off it's 16.99 you could also get it
free at the library if you go to library
every now and then you'll see somebody
say hey i went to the library i got it
so i'm in knowing the cause and the
protocol section by the way millions
millions of copies
have been sold around the world with
this cleanse to heal book it's changing
lives no marketing campaigns no pr and
marketing firms
didn't hire any companies to buy a whole
bunch of books
so you can make some lists or something
like this is
hardcore
organic
just grass roots
people healing and telling someone else
that's how medical medium information
gets around doesn't get around by
running a whole ton of this and holdton
and marketing campaigns so that's
important to know millions of copies
have already gone around the world
people are getting their lives back
and and it's it's just incredible and
they're learning how to use the
supplement protocol section
i mean it's just when you think about it
it's so amazing knowing the cause and
the protocol that's the part we're in
right now what you need to know about
supplements
this is important in order to heal
sometimes we need to go a little bit
further
critical detail
sometimes
we can
take ourselves through our healing
process
through just some foods
definitely if we know how to use them
and the right tools are there like the
celery juice people knock out their acid
reflux boom i'm done as the reflux gone
i got my celery juice and my acid reflux
is gone
right
nina says this book changed my life and
healed my eczema
my brain fog and chronic neck pain
so the book healed your chronic helped
you heal your chronic neck your neck
pain your xml your brain fog amazing
that's incredible so
sometimes we need to go further right
the book can do so much for you because
you can do a mono cleanse heal the
gastroparesis attacks heal the gastric
attacks heal the spasms heal the
constipation heal the intestinal tract
disorders heal the celiac heal the
crohn's heal the colitis heal the ibs
sometimes we can just go that we just do
that
and a lot of people have all kinds of
different things of neurological
symptoms
crazy heart palpitations going on
ringing in the ears and all the tinnitus
we'll talk about that in a little bit
and they got the dizziness and the
balance issues i won't do that to you
guys because there's so many of you that
do have vertigo and balance issues and i
don't wanna
i don't wanna throw you off
but
there's so many different conditions
right and we have to go a little bit
further
to our healing process and that's when
we can start to learn some protocols
with the supplements that's how
incredible this book is
every morning i wake up
and i'll say the spirit of compassion
did we do it
i mean did we really
finish cleanse the heel and put that
book out for people
and and when i hear the reports of
millions around the world already have
the book i'm just like did we do it
are we changing lives are we saving
lives because that's all i care about
how many lives are we saving so we're in
the supplement section right here
supplements to avoid while cleansing let
me read that for a second you guys and
we're going to go into this a little bit
more
if you are on supplements that are not
medical medium recommended
for instance whey protein powder
that's not medical medium recommended
that's a terrible thing
plant protein powders don't worry about
those plant protein powders you guys
they're filled with natural flavoring
they filled all these natural flavors
and msg they're filled with citric acid
they're filled with really cheap
ingredients
there's so there's all kinds of things
you got to worry about that okay fish
oil
disastrous somebody said in a youtube
comment they said why does it get so
dramatic
and i said
disastrous
i say that because what happens is if i
just go yeah it's bad to do some fish
oil what no one heard it
i'll just take more fish oil let me take
more where's my fish oil
i i thought he said no fish oil but i'm
gonna take more fish oil
it's that bad fish oil right
collagen
useless absolutely useless why do you
think all the collagen collagen powders
change you guys you know i wrote about
collagen the medical medium book series
and then it changed collagen now now
they're putting vitamin c in collagen
powders zinc
they're putting nettle leaf in collagen
powders
let's just keep on ripping people off
more and more with little bits of bad
zinc and little bits of bad nettle leaf
right they're they're you know high glow
quality low quality whatever now they're
just collagen powders are now building
blocks of collagen because medical
medium information taught everybody that
you can't create collagen by eating
collagen
i'm gonna
i'm gonna i'm gonna create
straw i'm gonna get my skin nice and
strong like this pig so i'm just gonna
have more pork
i'm gonna eat more pork
i'm gonna pork ears
maybe that'll fix my ear
you know
i'll just have i want to fix my nose i
don't really like my nose that much so
i'm going to just i'm going to
i'm going to eat some pig nose
and that's that's going to grow i'm
going to heal my nose that way you know
i got
you know i got all kinds of problems i
got a
my brain fog if i eat a pig's brain my
brain fog will get better
i think my brain is going to get better
you know i got feed issues you guys
and my feet are loaded with nail fungus
so i better just
eat the pig hoofs
i don't
pick ups
my feet are already better i think i got
my feet better
let me just have some collagen let me
have some collagen powder
fix my collagen it doesn't work that's
why
collagen is changing now there's there's
a thousand collagens out there now that
that turn the corner because the medical
medium put it out there that you can't
fix your collagen by eating collagen
you have to have
building blocks
all right we got to get into this that
we're talking about we're talking about
supplements how to use them what to do
all of it important to know okay
so fish oil collagen chlorella
terrifying
terrified
it could kill children
chlorella i think i'm doing really good
for my kids and i i got the chlorella
that this practitioner told him or what
this would ever told me and i saw it
online that chlorella is so good
nightmare
multivitamins
yeah junk multivitamins out there hair
skin and nail supplements scam of a
scam of a lifetime
my god
it's just sad it's just heartbreaking
heartbreaking when you think about it
and gut powder blends
let me have this next good powder blend
here and let me what's in here bentonite
clay
jesus christ you can rip your guts apart
with bentonite clay you can really get
hurt
really get hurt with bentonite clay
destroy your lining
see why this is here supplements to
avoid while cleansing in hopes to god
that you actually don't take something
so bad
that you hurt yourself while you're
trying to do a medical medium cleanse
that's actually healing you
if you guys just got on here
i'm reading the section out of cleanse
the heel supplement section make sure
you have the book get it free at the
library get it get it amazon.com us 1699
51 off the angelic price because it
costs more to print it
right
so you got to look out for these things
okay that's important to know so let's
get into some supplement parts too right
okay
i'm just there's so many great spots
right here if you're dealing with more
than one symptom or condition at the
same time i'm reading right out of here
pick the one that looms largest in your
life
what is looming largest in your life
okay
is it your tinnitus
you guys like this ear
is it is it is it the labyrinth of the
inner ear that's inflamed that nobody
knows about that's what your tinnitus is
the labyrinth of the inner ear
is it the labyrinth of the inner ear
that's inflamed is it tinnitus if that's
the one that looms the largest the most
is in your way then tinnitus is where
you go inside the book
supplements for hot flashes please
so
there's a hormone like that there's a
hormone part two in the supplement
section
right so let's just take a look there's
over 200 symptoms and conditions
in here right so let's go see if we can
find hot flashes
is this the situation where i was i was
thinking hot flashes was in here out of
the 200 conditions and for some reason
it's not
so i'm going to keep on looking here
so
okay here we go hot flashes
phew
sweating it out i was sweating it out
right there okay
i was
i told you it hits the celery force hits
after something like between 8 and 12
minutes 8 and 15 minutes and then it
hits it's it's just it's what it does is
just i still can't explain that
i know a lot of you guys have like have
used that celery force right the bemidji
celery forest
right so hot flashes right here
this is in the section of hot flashes
chills night sweats running hot body
temperature fluctuations right you guys
true cause a sluggish stagnant liver
filled with a variety of toxins
including toxic hormones from years of
fight or in flight toxic heavy metals
such as mercury aluminum and copper
poisonous viral byproduct and other
waste matter from
epstein-barr
right and all the different varieties
shingles and all the different varieties
or many other varieties hhv-6 herpes
simplex 1-2 all these different toxins
from these viruses that everybody has
inside of them plus old pharmaceuticals
white old pharmaceuticals and is looming
inside of your liver
sitting there cold medicines antibiotics
you've taken into anxiety pills
anti-depression pills right
benzodiazepines uh what else the pill
the pill
the pill just sits in women's livers it
just sits in there it sits in it you
take the pill you know here's a pill
every single day for 30 days and 30 days
go by another two years go by another
three years go by i'm on the pill for
three years now i'm on the pill for five
years your liver is just feeling it's
being filled up with this filled up with
this
and then when the hot flashes come it
wasn't the pill and i'm not saying maybe
you know everybody has the right to do
whatever they want to take the pill they
don't whatever happens in their life
right whatever they decide but the point
is is that it builds up it builds up
people don't know and then when you get
the house flashes or anti-anxiety meds
among anti-anxiety meds for two years
straight bam you got those hot flashes
five years later
five years later right
and then old pharmaceuticals like i said
that pesticides herbicides fungicides
fresheners air fresheners scented
candles perfumes colognes yeah
perfumes colognes are the trojan horse
of hell
perfumes and colognes is how they can
take you out there's pesticides in that
stuff i'm not talking about pesticide
residue
i'm talking about that smell you smell
is a pesticide it's crazy how it works
okay so let's talk about how this works
we got we're in the hot flash section
hot flashes chills night sweats running
hot body temperature fluctuations right
you guys stagnant sluggish liver because
of a host of different problems i talked
about cleanse the heal if you just got
on here you've got to have a copy of
this someday i say that all the time
because i know people go i'll get it
next year like okay
i'll get better next year yeah i'll get
my life better two years from now
yeah i'll get i'll get i'll heal myself
five years from now i'll start working
on it down the road yeah i don't need
the book i'll just stay sick and
work on it later
fresh celery juice that's in there right
there part of the protocol boom the hot
flash protocol fresh celery juice why
because you're cleaning up the liver
grogue just scared me just now i thought
i had an alien in here
you're cleaning up
the liver with the celery juice part of
the protocol right there okay
okay ashwagandha is in this protocol
ashwagandha right so this is the vimergy
ashwagandha
this one's a new bottle i just brought
out because these are supplements i take
too obviously quality matters
so
it really matters
this is a
incredible product they have i'm not
sponsored
right i'm putting a dropper full right
there what does it say here it says ash
we've gone to one dropper full right
there there's no alcohol no additives
nothing bad like that incredible stuff
but it's
i don't i don't want to waste your time
talking about the quality quality levels
incredible but i want to talk about the
protocol
i just did one dropper full of
ashwagandha in there so this is where
hot flashes this is for
chills and night sweats running hot body
temperature fluctuations this what this
is what i would do if i had any of that
if i had hot flashes all through the
night
i would go in here and be like okay what
do i need to do
what do i need to do
that's what i would do
so i just did that i put a little bit of
ashwagandha in there let's see what else
is in here though okay that's the
vimergy product
v is in victor i am as mary e r g y dot
com i saw somebody ask so it's
vimrgy.com i'm not sponsored by these
guys but the quality
can't be it can't be beat anywhere yet
i'm waiting for companies to actually
try to supersede the quality here on
this because if when they do i'll start
recommending them i'll recommend them
right away if a company can match
vimergy or beat them i will recommend
them
check out the medical meme directory if
you want to check that out
medicalmeme.com the directory there so
okay that's one thing right there right
cat's claw interesting
why is cat's claw in hot flashes chills
night sweats running hot body
temperature fluctuations why is cat's
claw in there that that's an interesting
thing right there cat's claw one dropper
full
twice a day
i'm gonna pop that in there i'm popping
that in there with the ashwagandha
do you know why cat's claw is in there
because a lot of people's hot flashes
is viral pathogen byproduct which means
pathogens are living inside their liver
cat's claw is going in there to knock
out pathogens
all right let's keep moving along
lemon balm
right there
lemon balm two dropper foals
one dropper full two dropper fulls
you might be somebody that's like well i
don't have hot flashes
then maybe you have autoimmune maybe you
have fibro maybe have lupus maybe you
have something else that's the
autoimmune section there right maybe you
got ms maybe got neurological lyme maybe
you got tinnitus vertigo we've got
eczema psoriasis
maybe got something else and the
protocols are in here
i don't know what i can do
i can work i could work i could talk the
spirit of compassion i could break all
the rules in the in the health world in
the sense where we got more people
healed than ever before in chronic
illness history which breaks all the
rules
because you're not supposed to get
millions of people better but yet
medical medium information did that it
can do all this
but i can't i can't do any more than
that you have to sometimes say you know
what i think i'm gonna go to the library
i'm gonna get the book out for free
and i'm going to work on it i'm going to
work on it
or whatever get the book amazon or
something so there's the lemon bump
licorice fruit why licorice fruit
okay
licorice fruit's a big one for those hot
flashes what does it say for licorice
fruit one dropper full
i just put the one dropper full in okay
right and then it has a couple more
things it's got the chaga mushroom in
here it's got the curcumin right there's
the curcumin
so
that's what's incredible about this i
see vitamin b12 so then there's the
vitamin b12 it says one dropper full
daily
with the hot flashes just showing you
guys how this works
right and then zinc
best thing there is on the market i know
people ever since medical medium got the
word out on the zinc
because no one used ink it was very
rarely used anywhere
um store shelves would have some old
zincs on there like like in whole foods
it would sit there for two years
i've heard from people that literally in
health food stores where they have they
years ago they've had to throw away the
zinc off the shelves because it always
went out of date nobody used zinc
and then what happened is medical medium
information taught everybody about the
viruses and talked to everybody about
how to use zinc and it exploded it now
every single person's coming out their
own zinc and it's got junk in it and
garbage in it that's the zinc that's
important so one dropper full of zinc in
there i'm gonna add a little water to
this protocol
okay
and
that right there
is an example
of protocol use right there
and it tastes pretty darn good
doesn't taste that bad at all
all right let's move on so that was
something you guys let's go to
neurological issues
let's see here we are neurological
symptoms right
we're cleansing heal if you just got
here we're doing supplement protocol
we're using vimergy supplements i got
alo2 in front of me right here i don't
know if you guys can see this i'll show
you how i can cut this open and do this
right
all right
might do some vitamin c shock therapy
while we're at it
so what i do anyway i'll show you with
the aloe in a second i just want to cut
the tail off i always cut the tail off
the plant right
you know i'm not going to use
that bit of aloe i mean you can you can
squeeze that tail out absolutely you
could put it on your skin you can do
anything like that but i usually cut the
little piece off the bottom there
all right now i'll go into that a little
bit more too
now listen
at 6 45 eastern
3 45
right pacific i'm going to be on rumble
exclusively exclusively i'm going to be
talking about
the tragedy of urine therapy
tragedy of urine therapy so i'm going to
talk about urine therapy
at but it's only on rumble at 6 45
eastern
3 45
okay pacific time
all right we're neurological symptoms
now if i had
tightness of the chest
like you just feel the tightness in the
chest whether it's anxiety
exactly or not
or just you feel tightness in the chest
and you don't know why
if i had trembling hands
or had moments where it's in the middle
of the day and the trembles come or
three o'clock in the afternoon the
trembles come or they're just there or
you don't maybe they're maybe your hands
are really still and there's no
trembling
right but yet what's happening is you
feel like you're trembling inside
neurological symptom
fire twitches and spasms
you know my eye
or twitches and spasms here here
twitches and spasms okay good to see you
guys by the way we're live on telegram
that's a thing medical medium just lives
we don't we don't like to pre-record
anything
we don't like to pre-record anything we
want it live live live
that's how we do it i've been very
blessed to be able to do live
performances
and people wonder how does he do it
because the podcast doctors won't do it
no one else will do it they all
pre-record everything and edit
everything because they say the wrong
thing every other second they don't know
what they're saying and they have to
kind of pre-record everything i
understand that
how does he do things live
one reason is because spirit of
compassion that's one reason because i'm
hearing spirit of the compassion at the
same time i'm working with you guys
reading your stuff hearing spirit
working in here and i'm able to do it
for some reason it's all kind of you
know
all put together
plus i'm not a lot of celery force right
now so anyway
twitches and spasms muscle weakness
that's one right there your legs feel
like sandbag you got you got the chronic
fatigue syndrome your legs feel like
they're sandbags they feel heavy your
arms feel heavy
you know all of that any muscle weakness
at all or you're just feeling muscle
weakness right neurological symptom
maybe you had it once in a while in your
life
what about
numb fingers tingles and numbness you
just called it right here tingles and
numbness in here
right the tingles the numbness fingers
toes numb toes numb fingers they go numb
easy everything goes numb easy sometimes
just randomly goes numb it's not just
about how you're sitting or what you're
doing right
restless legs
the nighttime restless legs right guys
on telegram the nighttime restless legs
that's a big one right there
restlessness in general
weakness of the limbs right
right we talked about that a little bit
with muscle weakness but weakness of the
limbs too
muscle spasms and aches and pains random
aches and pains i feel like i'm 80 years
old i feel like i'm 70 years old when i
shouldn't be because i'm a young person
i'm a young woman i'm a young guy aches
and pains right
and then so
if physical injury has not occurred
neurological symptoms are caused by the
viral explosion of the 20th century that
means that the viruses that we've been
passed down from our family lines that
we also contract that we pick up in
restaurants that we pick up wherever we
are we pick up in public bathrooms we
pass along to others sexual transmission
or intimate transmission or however we
want to deal with the viral explosion
that's happening today the simplexes the
shingles the ebv's the hhv-6 the
cytomegalovirus that's what we're
talking about there okay that's part of
the whole neurological symptom problem
people don't realize their mononucleosis
their mononucleosis is now their
neurological symptoms now years later
their mono that they had
camped out inside their liver
sat in there
and then left the liver went to the
thyroid and the reproductive system
causing endometriosis and pcos in women
with that went to the thyroid
right
started causing the hypothyroidism the
hyperthyroidism the cysts and the
nodules on the thyroid people don't know
this the epstein bar and then the
epstein bar leaves the thyroid
it does leaves the thyroid and creates
the neurological symptoms every body's
dealing with and they get the fibro
diagnosis the ra diagnosis they get the
lupus diagnosis they get all the
different diagnoses the neurological
lyme over time or just have these
symptoms
that's the epstein bar
so what do we do we want to kill off the
epstein bar so i'm in the book right
here so basically what it is is i got
neurological symptoms that are
unexplained it's not from physical
injury the doctor checks out
everything's okay
right
whether they give you a autoimmune
diagnosis or not so what do i do so i'm
in neurological symptoms and it's just
aloe vera aloe vera two inch piece right
so what i do is i cut this piece off
first okay
i'll cut that per piece off first right
i'm gonna move the book for two seconds
right here
now i'm gonna cut a two-piece two inch
i mean it's a little bigger than two
inch maybe that's a bigger piece but
somewhere around there right nice hunky
piece off this aloe vera leaf this is
part of the protocol right here you know
i noticed that people say i did medical
medium i didn't get better and then
someone asked him like would you do
well i don't know
i was doing something i did i did celery
juice for two weeks
or
i was on this guy this other guy's
youtube and he he said to do this and to
do that but i was still doing medical
medium oh you were
i think you were a dabbler and it's okay
to be a dabbler there's nothing wrong
with being a dabbler just
realize have you really done the
protocols have you learned have you done
have you done the book right i just cut
this big piece off right here huh
and
i forwarded it hey then
what i love about the aloe
it tastes so good so i just filleted
this and this is how i filet it right
here
i think you just swallowed it almost all
right
now what you could do is you could take
it out and you can throw in a blender
flay it throw it in a blender and blend
it up with some water you don't have to
do what do it like i just did what i
also do is
i take a spoon
and i'll i'll also scrape
a little bit to the leaf right here and
go like this
so good all right so that's the aloe
right there and that's in the
that's amazing for gastritis
celiac
ibs
what you just saw right there
can help so many people with crohn's
colitis celiac ibs gastric spasms
gastroparesis this is really an
incredible
tool right there right
so two or more inches of fresh gel skin
removed boom we just did it right
barley grass juice powder got it right
here
that's the that's the uh
the medical medium dosage is one
teaspoon or three capsules daily that's
the vimergy barley grass juice powder
right there
cat's claw
back to that again neurological symptoms
it's calling for cat's claw cat's glock
kills viruses
okay
but this is a lot to pick up right now
throughout this live the book has the
details
make sure you're just you just have the
book
right
i mean
it's dirt cheap at amazon.com us right
now
i wake up every morning and i check and
i go thank god it's still they're still
doing this there's they still have it so
priced so low
for this book all right
two dropper fulls twice a day of cat's
claw
two dropper fulls give you a little bit
of run down what's a dropper full
a dropper folds whatever goes into the
dropper
that's it that's a dropper full it's
whatever goes into the dropper
really important to know
okay
a half dropper full would be whatever
that half of whatever you just came in
there so that would be a half dropper
hole right there
that's an example so i just did two
dropper holes of cat's claw right it
says curcumin that's on the list what
does it say about curcumin two capsules
twice a day because what curcumin is and
this is a high quality one so what
curcumin does is it has
anti-inflammatory properties it doesn't
mean it kills viruses
but it acts as aspirin
curcumin
acts like aspirin quality matters too
it's critical right it's to help bring
down a little bit of that viral
inflammation that's why that's in there
what else is in there right d-mannose
so d-manos
one tablespoon
actually i mean that was in the wrong
one right there sorry there's no d manos
in this one
all right we're in the right one now
okay
so yeah you got the cat squad we got
that in there we got the curcumin that's
in there too now we're going into
goldenseal
team i was an overactive bladder by the
way for a second
which is really an important one so i
want to go to oracle that's why we're
live that's why we do this live
in hopes that happens
the fun stuff happens right so for
interstitial cystitis that's what the
the demanos powder was but we'll talk
about that in a minute so golden seal
let's hit the golden seal one drop or a
full
twice a day
put the dropper full in here
that's the
vimergy golden seal right there
okay
so we got that in there next one lemon
balm lemon balm is antiviral but what i
love about lemon balm is it calms the
nerves
so the lemon balm would be
four dropper fulls
four dropper fulls of the lemon balm for
neurological problems so i just did four
dropper folds right there now if you're
sensitive you can take a drop if you're
sensitive you can take a drop look at
this ready
one drop
two drops
three drops if you're sensitive look at
that four drops
okay
i'm gonna give you guys a quick run down
i watched it for decades
no one healed no one healed from
whatever they were diagnosed with
candida whatever it was they had
neurological problems didn't even know
it was that they just stayed sick for
decades i watched it out there when i
was young and people came up with with
glorious ideas you can try to eat this
you can try to do this
but people stayed sick
the way you heal is you really know the
details of intricate protocols that
actually work and have a history of
working and getting people's lives back
that's how you heal
intricate critical protocols that get
people's lives back that have a history
and a street cred
that have already healed people around
the world that's how people really heal
because i've watched it for years people
go into this place in this clinic and
then they go here and then they go there
and then they're trying this and trying
that and they just stay sick
it's so sad when i think about it
it's so sad so we just put that in there
let's see there's a few other things
there's b12 there's vitamin c vitamin c
is five capsules twice a day
five capsules twice a day
so
i almost says but he's 31 years old
so how does he how how has he seen it
for decades when he's 31 years old
i wish i was 31 years old that would be
really awesome
you know i wish spirit can do that for
me spirit of compassion i wish he can
just put me in a time machine and bring
me back to when i was 31
that was
that was more than two decades ago more
than two decades ago like
way more right anyway
zinc right there
one dropper full twice a day i'm in the
neurological symptom protocol you guys
lucy says
i'm new here what is the brand of these
supplements this is vimergy is what it
is it's v as in victor i emma's and mary
e r g y vimergi.com
i don't even call them supplements
privately like privately in my head
privately in my family i don't even call
them supplements because they're above
supplements that's what i've learned
supplements even though i use the term
supplements and everything because
that's the technical uh term
but but
when you see people heal when they do
protocols using high quality stuff like
this it's like beyond it's like above
that it's it's it's a whole different
thing happens when you do zinc shock
therapy which since you're new here you
don't know what zinc shot therapy is but
it's inside this book right here it
saved a lot of people a lot of people's
lives the zing shock therapy when you
use the right zinc for that
everything changes it's such a great
thing anyway you guys i'm just using
some of the stuff in here you can just
do
i tell people all the time you when you
read this section in the book about
protocols you can just do three
supplements
three
you start there you start with two
two supplements you start with three
supplements you start with four
and i talk about the top four
the top three the details are in here
don't get overwhelmed don't whatever you
do if you don't even want to start in
the supplement protocol section you
start in the cleansing section 369 maybe
the heavy metal detox smoothie cleanse
right maybe the mono cleanse
maybe something like that you don't have
to get overwhelmed
the whole point is
something happens when you have the
knowledge in your hands even if you
don't dive deep yet and you say you know
what i'm gonna try a little bit of this
i'm gonna empower myself and try a
little bit of this you know i could do
this right now
you know and that's that's what's
incredible really
all right
we got the golden seal in here the cats
go on here lemon balm and four drop
rolls the lemon balm we got a lot of
stuff in here the zinc in here
knock that down right there
boom it's down you want that glass
bottle
i just saw that
over at the bladder let's cover that for
a couple of minutes
new little a news flash quick news flash
right now while we're live
okay the tragedy
of urine therapy
exclusive talk on rumble later today
6 45 eastern 3 45 pacific
we're going to talk about your own
therapy
all right
you guys
it what i love about protocols at work
you can save years
and thousands and thousands of dollars
even if you don't venture into the
supplement protocol section in here but
you just start one thing celery juice in
the protocol section right there one
thing celery juice you do a little bit
of the aloe you learn some of these
medical medium tools
you can take yourself to that place
you're getting yourself to that place
right tammy strangs asks a question
where do you start if you have multiple
symptoms i have hot flashes ringing in
the ear and nerve issues really good
point you pick
the one that looms over you the most
which one looms over you the most right
you got multiple symptoms is it hot
flashes by the way you should you should
watch this from the beginning the hot
flash part maybe you did but you're
wondering where should you start right
ringing the ears say you're something
you got ringing in the ears which is the
inflammation of
the labyrinth of the inner ear okay
and it gets inflamed by epstein-barr
creates um tinnitus get popping
fluttering
buzzing
noises in here right whatever's going on
or you get the ringing and that ringing
people don't realize it when a fan is on
the ring could actually change and make
when different noises are happening the
rain can get louder at night instead in
the morning in the morning it's lower
for a lot of people it gets louder at
night this is viral nerve inflammation
inside the ear i talk about it tinnitus
is in here now which one looms the most
that's the one you can start with if you
like and what you'll notice
when you work on the symptom
that looms the most
other symptoms start getting better and
you're like what the heck is going on
here why is everything starting to get
better because guess what
that epstein barr you had or that
whatever that you have it's causing
other problems that streptococcus you
have that's giving you overactive
bladder it's causing other problems
let's go over overactive bladder while
we got a chance
okay
there's protocols for over 200 symptoms
and conditions we're going to go into
oab
is where we're going next
you know i heard a commercial on the
radio i was in the car the other day and
are you suffering from oab
overactive bladder
come to our clinic we have different
therapies
and i'm like yeah i heard those
therapies before i heard a lot of people
going there too
i've heard that for years they said you
may be one of the very few people that
find relief at our clinic for oab
make sure
you see our clinic for oab this message
was brought to you by pictures
and then all of a sudden the radio went
on and some music went on you know the
music went on and i'm like
dear lord does anybody even stand a
chance
anyway oab i got it right here all right
chronic inflammation of the bladder is
due to a low-grade infection either
years past or years present
maybe not years present but present
right interstitial cystitis right
oab overactive bladder utis yeast
infections bv bacterial vaginosis like
all this stuff gets all tied in to
overactive bladder by the way
okay so
one or more of the over 50 groups of
streptococcus bacteria
or even epstein-barr can fall into the
category of oab because epstein-barr has
so many toxins coming out of the liver
that it gets into the kidneys eventually
causing the the uh the pudendum nerve
and other nerves around the bladder to
get inflamed and then you have
overactive bladder that's how it works
right
normally both a virus and bacteria are
present in combination you guys
working with each other in the same
environment neurotoxins that the viruses
release can irritate the lining of the
bladder like i just told you
while bacteria nestles themselves deep
in the bladder lining deep in the
bladder lining both causing inflammation
at once
i don't think i have a bladder prop
i don't think i have a bladder oh yeah i
do have a bladder prop i had to remove
the bladder prop because
because someone complained on tick tock
that this was like
sexual contact content or something or
whatever on take the like the just
having the anatomy dummy here
so it's like well what do i do how many
parts can i remove off this anatomy
without a problem so yeah no i can't
even show you the overactive bladder now
the prop
so in in the oab we got the fresh celery
juice work up to 32 ounces right here
we got the aloe vera
right
two inches
i cut it right there before i don't want
it dripping on the book i cut it on
right i cut it you saw me eat that
we have that in here
barley grass juice powder one teaspoon
that's the vimergy barley grass cheese
powder i'm not sponsored if you guys
just came on here
right you're watching cat's claw
right two dropper fulls twice a day
curcumin two capsules twice a day d
manos powder one tablespoon three times
a day
gaba isn't that interesting spirit of
compassion wanted gaba
for oab
right gaba
and i can't tell you how many times
i've used that information family
friends people throughout the years when
you use gaba for oab
something changes because a lot of
people's oab over active bladder is
neurological
nerves they feel like they have to pee a
hundred times because nerves are
sensitized
and gaba helps with sensitized nerves
you can't find this information anywhere
you can't medical medium information
isn't common sense
it's above common sense because common
sense is actually just sense that
everybody just naturally knows right
you're raised like don't cross the
street while the traffic is is really
bad
like when you're a baby when you're a
child and you're holding on to mom's
mommy's hand
it's like don't cross the street yet you
see the cars coming that's called common
sense
right everybody has common sense medical
medium information just makes sense
it makes sense when nothing else makes
sense out there that's the difference
between between medical medium
information it's not common sense common
sense is like
don't
jump off the cliff
onto those raging rocks and water down
there and and you know and waves
you're gonna die if you do that that's
common sense right you don't do a selfie
while hanging on a tower
don't do a selfie while hanging off a
building you know hey guys wait hey wait
i'm holding on here no wait wait guys no
wait i'm doing a selfie yeah
common sense is that
right medical medium information makes
sense
and that's the whole point right it's
above the common sense line you won't
find information about how
to
heal oab by using gaba because medical
research and science doesn't know that
your
overactive bladder could be neurological
which is your pudendum nerves but more
than that all the nerves going around in
and out of the bladder and what you're
what you're feeling what the reason why
you have to pee every second is you're
actually you're feeling sensitized
nerves you can't find that anywhere and
that's why people heal around the world
it's incredible
so we got the the protocol in here it's
magnesium glycinate is in that protocol
so that's the vimergy magnesium
glycinate right there if you guys just
came on here two things someday you
might want to get in your life
one is the cleanse the heel book another
is high quality subs this is vimergy you
find this stuff at vimrgy.com whatever
and high quality subs and learn
protocols to move yourself forward right
but either way if you have the book
that's an incredible start because you
can start with the cleanses you can
start with the knowledge there the
information so i'm an overactive bladder
so magnesium glycinate so here we are
melatonin
is in overactive bladder
interesting
i'll tell you why
because you get ocd
with overactive bladder if you're
somebody
that has the ocd overactive bladder i
peed
but i know i'm gonna have to pee again
in five minutes
i can't go to bed yet i'm just starting
to fall asleep
and i have to pee again i'm just
starting to fall asleep and i have to
pee again wait i'm falling asleep but i
have to pee again i just peed five more
times it's now 11 45 at night and i'm i
think i can just i think i'm good i
don't have to pee again
and then you have to pee again and now
you're off doing that right there okay
the melatonin is helpful for that
helpful for the brain to try to break
the ocd aspect of overactive bladder
look if i didn't cover your illness
today i didn't cover you know if i
didn't cover ms if it didn't cover fibro
ra or whatever that's going on or your
autoimmune or constipation or or cysts
protocol in here or multiple sclerosis
or like i said autoimmune
if i didn't they're all it's all in here
i'm just covering some of them if you're
somebody with overactive bladder great
if you don't have overactive bladder
fine i mean i'm in here right now and i
just see pandas right here just right
here it's pandas
yeah people are like what this medical
medium doesn't know anything about
pandas just our pandas community does
really
and then you know you go into the pandas
community and you look and it's like
everybody's clueless
and you feel so bad you feel bad for the
moms you feel bad for the kids you feel
bad for them all because they don't even
know what to do
and and it's so sad and here's the
pandas section right here
no you know this is it right here it's
it's streptococcus infection right
associated that's the whole thing where
they say it's associated with
streptococcus infection true cause
a co-infection of one or more strains
from over 50 groups of streptococcus
bacteria plus a virus most commonly
hhv-6 you know why kids don't heal with
pandas it's rare they can do unless they
use like certain protocol like pieces
that they've gotten from medical medium
in the last 35 years the reason why kids
don't heal
well at all from pandas is because they
just think it's strep and then their
strep protocols aren't even correct
that's why because pandas is hhv-6
co-infection
is strep to coctus see the difference
right there
so
the co-infection
even epstein-barr in hhv6 right and
that's medical medium information okay
and then toxic heavy metals is the other
aspect of pandas that's how you heal
pandas you get the metals out you get
the co-infections down
right does it have anything to do with
mycotoxin poisoning that's a trigger so
so so so mycotoxins that's that's an
actual trigger so any kind of mold any
kind of mold exposure that's an actual
trigger to lower the immune system and
then the real infectious problems about
pandas are the real problems that creep
up
look
maybe right now this isn't important to
a lot of people and they're just like oh
just go
look for some other info or whatever but
you know when i'm gone down the road
and and it's gonna be a bigger sea of
confusion than anyone's ever seen before
in history because i've been told this
over and over again by spirit of
compassion and it's the biggest sea of
confusion ever
someone's going to have this book
and they're going to be able to save
their life
and that's what i think about every day
you guys
um
check it out when you get a chance
i can only cover a few things right now
but you know what i'm going to go and do
another live
but i just want to give you this other
thing too okay you guys
rumble i'm talking about urine therapy
on rumble 645 eastern 3 45 pacific
exclusive on rumble make sure you
subscribe there it's going to be where
i'm going to be spending a lot of time
in the future right so make sure you you
find me there okay i'm doing cool stuff
there also check me out on me we check
me out on telegram too of doing private
exclusive messages on telegram right
and um yeah check me out there so i'm
covering more
covering more illnesses symptoms and
conditions and protocols i'm letting you
guys know right now
in 10 minutes 15 minutes 10 minutes
whatever so in 10 minutes i'm trying on
instagram
i call it sensagram
sensorgram i'm turning on sensorgram
because they're either going to mute me
out on you guys or kick you guys off i'm
turning them on
i'm turning telegram back on
i'm putting tick-tock back on
all right so i'll see you soon i don't
know maybe 10 minutes so let's do it and
we'll talk about other conditions
all right i love you guys