[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now
and I'm serious about that I really am
cuz you got to put your fast in your
seat belts you got to put your safety
belt on on this show cuz this is this is
really serious what we're talking about
we're really going in to some things
that you just need to know so just you
know stay tuned for this you know you
know I've always said who has 10 or 20
or 30 years to wait for answers or
information to protect your family you
know you know someone said to me the
other day they said you keep on talking
about this whole family thing like you
know it's all about you're always saying
it's all about protecting your family
and your friends or whatever you know
and and I've never heard that before
they said to me I go yeah yeah it's
about protecting your family it's about
protecting you your family your friends
your loved ones it's about making sure
you have information it's about you
becoming an expert for re though like
for real an expert meaning you don't
need to do 8 years of medical school to
know information it's just isn't even
out there it doesn't even exist you need
to know this information so you become
that expert and so you can protect your
family protect your friends and be there
and be there and have that information
so this person said well you know it's
all about you just you're just all about
into protecting family you know and
that's something I haven't heard before
yeah that's right because you haven't
heard it before and you're not going to
hear it out there because it's here it's
right here it's really important that we
look out for our loved ones and we look
out for you it's not just ourselves it's
about for anybody around us having that
information you know you name it it's
important so today's show is about how
to protect yourself and your family and
loved ones and friends from the
unforgiving for the unforgiving four
what is the unforgiving for the
unforgiving four are four
things the groups but they're four
things that are in our way every day
keeping us from getting healthy keeping
us from staying healthy keeping us from
being able to protect ourselves you name
it that's the unforgiving for and we're
going into that today so don't miss that
if you just logged on you know don't
miss this show cuz this show is for you
and it really matters it really really
matters you know when I was younger and
I know you guys heard this before when I
was younger when I was you know I think
it was around 7 8 years old somewhere
around there 7 8 n years old in that
realm I had a couple of you know couple
of things hit me and one was why should
I care why should I care about anybody
why should I even care why bother you
know that's that's what was hitting me
and I was telling spirit because I was
already talking to Spirit since Age 4
and I was saying to Spirit why do I have
to care who car cares about everybody
being sick or what's wrong with them or
what's going on why do I even need to
care you know and and I'm 8 years old
what does it matter and spirit said you
have to care you have to know that now
you have to care about others and what
they're going through and what's
happening in their lives and what
they're suffering from and what they're
struggling from what they've been
through you have to care it matters
matters it matters the work you do down
here matters and you have to care and I
clicked on the care button I said all
right I said okay I clicked it on I
clicked it on I mean it was there
already but I was getting IR irritable
because I was a child that was hearing a
voice perfectly clear which was spirit
and spirit was telling me everything and
it was really hard to deal with so and
it seeing every every illness in people
and you name it and you know seeing
people that have brain tumors seeing
people that have all kinds of different
problems it was you know always coming
through people that had cancer it was
always coming through and and I was like
you know what I I I don't want to care
anymore this is just too much and spirit
said you have to care and so when it
comes down to the unforgiving for which
we're talking about today you
guys it's important to know what is in
our way what is in your way what is in
your way of healing okay and what's in
all of our ways of healing like in in
the way and so we're going to talk about
all that um hey you know um go to
Medical medium.com if you ever get a
chance if you're interested in going to
any of the events um you know check
check it out uh the whole bit got one
coming up real shortly it's coming up
literally it's around the corner and um
so if you get a chance get down there
we're doing the light blast it's when
Spirit sends light literally from heaven
right on down on the crown of
everybody's head and it rushes through
their body and it's a rush it's a rush
and I say right after it after the light
blast I say no operating heavy machinery
for a few minutes after that light blast
because it is really intense it's there
to ignite the healing process to lift
people up to ignite the healing process
what it does is it that light rushes
through the body and builds up the
immune system it builds up the immune
system the lymphocytes the basophils the
monocytes the neutrophils the platelets
it just goes through the body and it
starts to get rid of any kind of
Darkness any kind of bugs in people's
bodies and toxins and it helps to ignite
the it's the ignition of healing and
that's what we're doing I don't care
what it takes how we're going to do it
how we do it I make sure I'm there and I
make sure spirit and I get it done and
so everybody gets that light blast and
that's what I'm saving my reserves up
right now for I know what it's going to
take I know what it's going to take to
get on that stage and do it I'm saving
my reserves and spirit and I are going
to do that and make sure it happens so
I'm really looking forward to that I
can't wait to check that out and of
course we do more I do the re live
readings on stage and uh and that's
really fun it's really fun um and all of
that and don't worry if I look look a
little funny on the stage if you do get
down there it's because by the time I
get through those readings and I'm and
I'm getting readings on everybody that's
just automatically coming in as spirit's
giving me that information and I start
going what's called snow blind I start
losing my my sight don't
worry it's just fun and it's great and
it's it's great it's great so that's
something about me lifechanging Foods
book check it out it's it's basically
about to come out just you know grab
yourself a copy and um and get your
gifts get your new gifts to get your
free gifts with the lifechanging foods
book just you can instantly get the
gifts that we offer um by just you know
ordering a copy right now and then you
could get those don't miss out on that
okay because that's really great and
that book is packed and you're not going
to be disappointed if you're
disappointed I want to know personally
because I because I really don't think
you're going to be when you when you
open it up you're going to say he did
not let us down he did not let us down
he said he wasn't going to and he didn't
let us down this this book is and you're
when you open it up you're not going to
say okay this is just a you know a rag
that's got a couple of tidbits in it and
he let us down you're not going to do
that when you open it you're going to be
like oh my God I see his Blood Sweat and
Tears and it is definitely it definitely
is is helping and when you start reading
that and seeing what's in it you're
going to be like okay no no no no he's
got her back he's got her back and one
way I got your back cuz we're talking
about the unforgiving for and that's
what we're doing today hey if this is
the first time you know you've logged
into the show and you're like what is he
talking about because all of this seems
different because it is it's not in any
other show anything I've ever done is
not in any other show I don't care how
many copycats or whatever's going on out
there it's not what we got here so if
you just logged in give it a minute and
take your time so I can help so I can
help you heal get the information you
need so you can help others and become
that expert and become that health
expert become all that kind of the whole
thing and so stay tuned it started with
a gift at ag4 for me I diagnosed my
grandmother of lung cancer and spirit I
heard spirit for the first time I woke
up that morning and heard Spirit
perfectly clear in my ear and I've been
doing this ever
since so anyway look and as I've always
said before we don't have 10 or 20 or 30
years to wait for answers so let's start
the healing now let's learn how to
protect our ourselves from the
unforgiving four yeah you heard me the
unforgiving four so we're on it so what
is what is this the unforgiving for what
what am I talking about I mean some of
you might know already I've hinted I've
talked about it you know I've said
something about it I think I've even put
some stuff about out there maybe in the
newsletter or something so you know you
Pro some of you probably gotten you know
that but you know a lot of you may not
have heard about the unforgiving for the
unforgiving for is what Spirit calls
this group of things that get in our way
they interfere with our
lives they poison us they poison us they
inhibit us from healing they stop us
from healing or try to and they wreak
havoc and they're basically a threat
they basically a deception a threat a
deceptive threat you know you know
here's the deal you know when we grow up
when we grow up it's all about you know
it's all about safety when we're a child
it's all about safety your parents hold
your hand I talked about this before
they hold your hand before you cross the
street right I mean that's that's the
that's the goal in school there's these
different monitors in school they look
after you there's playground monitors
there's you know or whatever there's
just you know and now there's security
in schools and when you start getting
older and then you get insurance you
know you get car insurance you get all
the differ insurances you're always
trying to protect yourself you're always
doing all these things it's all about
protection on so many levels we
inherently talk about and we know about
in our
lives but what about and these are all
things we can see protecting ourselves
from any thing we can see so if a bus is
going down the road and we don't want to
get in the way of it we move
away okay or or our our parent or
Guardian pulls us away from that bus so
we don't get hit all
right or you know angels are trying to
protect us all the time too and they
might even if they have a chance can
pull us away from a
tragedy but it's always things we can
see you can see see it all you know you
got to be careful you got to be careful
if you're going swimming that you're not
in a in a you know too rough of a water
patch or Too Deep whatever it is it's
things we can see no matter what but
what about the things you can't see what
about the things we don't hear about
talk about much because or talk about it
all because you can't see it what about
those things
well they exist and that's what we're
covering that's what we're covering
because it's all about what you see in
this world it's all about got to see it
to believe it got to see
it got to see it to believe it you know
I'm not going to believe it unless I see
it right it's all about it's all
about it's all about what you can see
I'll see it if I I'll believe it if I
see it right is that what happens well
what you know there's a funny thing it
just reminds at me that's what happens
when people come to the event and they
never seen what I've done before what
Spirit does before I can't take any
credit for it that's what Spirit does
I've learned my lesson I tried to take
credit for it years ago you heard the
story you heard the story many times I
even told a story in my book in a
medical medium book the first book and
um you know I can't take any of the
credit I've learned my lesson I've
learned it well but you know when when
people go to the live event and and they
see me do my work on the stage where
Spirit or our work spirit and I our work
where spirit's telling me what's going
on with each person and what's wrong
with them and what's inside what kind of
illness they're dealing with you name it
and spirit's doing it for me and I'm
doing that and then people who have gone
there that maybe never seen or heard
about this but they go they they hear
about the event and they
come and they walk out and they're like
I don't know how he did that I don't
know how it was possible possible but
yes I I believe it because I've seen it
and so that's the kind of world we live
in and and that's fine there's nothing
wrong with that because we we like to
see things in order to believe them and
and the problem is with mystery illness
you guys with mystery illness the
problem is is that we can't see
it we can't see it so when you're sick
you get told hey you know you're fine
you look fine yeah you're laying in your
bed you're catatonic but you look fine
and you're probably making it up because
we can't see it the doctor can't see it
on the blood test no one can see it no
one cares because they can't see it so
um you just go off on your Merry way
Faker you faker right that's who I've
heard people tell me they've been called
fakers oh that makes me so upset that's
why I got to laugh about it because if I
don't I'm going to just be so you know
disheartened by it and it's saddened by
it and and I'm already it's already
saddening as it is because when I hear
it I get like welled up in inside and I
get emotional about it because it breaks
my heart if someone's called a faker
when they're really sick and the world's
getting a little better we're getting
we're finally getting to a place you
know the internet and a lot of
practitioners are are you know are
looking out
practitioners are are looking out for
people more and all these different
things are happening we're finally
getting to a
point where you know we're not told
we're faking it anymore in many aspects
of medicine but that's not entirely true
because there's still there's still some
leftovers um and you know and that's the
whole thing the process of of Planet
stress is you know it just if someone
doesn't experience it themselves they
think it doesn't exist
if they don't experience it themselves
they think it doesn't exist that's
planet Earth that's planet Earth here on
planet Earth I'm sorry to say and I'm
sure you know and you sure you lived it
I sure you seen it I'm sure you name
it if someone doesn't see it then they
don't believe it you get called a faker
cuz you're sick um you know mommies that
can't get out of bed and take care of
their kids there you know they can't
find anything on the test
and then the problem is is even if they
go to a good doctor and the doctor says
yeah you're sick so they get validated
they get validated with the wrong
illness in the wrong direction that's
still happening and we're trying to
change that at the medical Medium show
and the books and everything we're
trying to change that so but the bottom
line is it's a see it to believe it
world right
so if there's this unforgiving
for no one sees it then who's going to
believe
it and then we just get these different
tags and labels and I want to go I want
to go over a couple of things I've done
this before but it applies here so much
that I can't not do it and just ignore
it but
autoimmune autoimmune being told we have
autoimmune because medical research and
medical science doesn't know what's
causing your symptoms or your illness is
a
tragedy telling us that our body's
attacking and this is the first time you
logged on to this you don't know
anything about me you better believe it
you better know right now and I'm just
saying this for your own health and
wellbeing and your friends and your
families your body doesn't attack itself
you have to trust me on this and I even
hate saying trust me on this because
we're not even allowed to say this in
this world right now because there's a
whole thing going on out there if you
say trust me then people are like oh
I've heard that don't want to trust but
you better trust me because I'm telling
you right now you're body does not
attack itself it stands behind you it
works for you it won't hurt you it's
there helping you and medical research
and medical science has no clue about
this yet including alternative medicine
the best alternative medicine books
about autoimmune literally are rags and
need to be thrown in the garbage because
they say the the foundation is still
your body is attacking itself they
haven't even left that simple you know
mistake or that great mistake they
haven't even left the great mistake yet
of knowing that your body is not
attacking
itself okay and I'm giving you that
information now because it's important
because we're going into the unforgiving
four and there's four big things that
are causing the problems and in
completely tricking out the medical
research and Medical Science World so
they turn the whole thing around on you
telling you that your body is attacking
itself when it's not okay do you see why
I'm so serious about this did you put
your seat bels on you better put your
seat bels on and you better not be
driving an antique a 1960 you know
Cadillac that Cadillac that has no or
1955 Buick or something that doesn't
have a headrest on the back like the old
days so when you got hit from behind
your head wrenched back and you broke
your neck on one little bumper bumper
you know one little fender bender so no
antiques make sure you're in make sure
you're in some safe cars but just you
got to know something you got to know
something your body doesn't attack
itself it's not there going against you
it's because the unforgiving
for is on our
butts okay it's on our butts and it's
interfering with our lives and it's
tricking out medical research and
medical science sence so that they put
the blame on you it's so critical to
know this we're going to get into these
unforgiving for just but you have to
have the foundation you have to have a
foundation and the problem is in
alternative medicine I like conventional
medicine I like alternative medicine but
I work for you so I don't take
sides and I don't fall into to their
false belief systems like the body
attacking itself because I have Spirit
telling me what's really going on with
people because we work for you that's
who I work for I get up in the morning
and you know what I work for God but God
says if you're going to work for me
guess who you're going to be helping
you're going to be helping everybody
else so technically yes I'm helping you
I'm working for you and I got to watch
your back if I don't watch your back
then you know then what then you're
going to think your body's attacking
itself that's what so it's important to
know that research and science hasn't
discovered what's causing problems and
then alternative medicine you know God
loving God loving absolutely thank God
for any of our doctors alternative andc
conventional medicine but alternative
medicine some of the best trendy you
know lit you know literature that's out
there books that are out there is still
antiques it they're still it's old time
it's still old I don't care what fancy
talk is in there about gut biome and
about you know about you know the whole
thing with um probiotics and about you
know um about mot toxins I don't care
what's in
there if they still think your body's
attacking itself and those are just
triggers then it's it's
behind because I'm going to give you
today what's causing all our trouble
another thing is mystery illness
we're
told that all your different ailments
your symptoms your conditions are not
mystery we're told that they're not
mystery that they've been figured out if
they've been figured out then why are we
still sick why are 300 million Americans
with symptoms and sick right now if we
figured it
out so they deem mystery illness just
for like a handful of rare cases once a
year once every three years you know
like just a few people fell down with a
fever somewhere and or some children
were sick and because of some you know
polluted pond water or something and
it's just okay it's a mystery illness
we're trying to figure it out they're
trying to troubleshoot it here's the
thing it's all mystery that's chronic
illness
related and what's behind all the
mystery are the unforgiving for once
again I'm going back to that cuz that's
what we're on today
and then it's all in your head it's
another thing like you created it it's
your fault you did it you you manifested
your
illness you know that's not true that's
not true don't believe that either
you're a good person you didn't created
it the UN the unforgiving for is what
creates it so you need to know that
that's so important to
know okay it doesn't mean we can't be
our own trigger sometimes when we get
hit with things and you know we get
breakups in relationships and it hurts
our heart so bad and we're so upset
that's a trigger it's an emotional
trigger but where we have to be able to
experience emotion we have to be able to
feel emotion so we can't be blamed for
feeling emotion and having it kind of
weaken us a little bit because that's
just life the idea is to be able to have
feel all the emotion you want whether
it's good or bad and survive it and the
unforgiving for is responsible for why
we have a hard time why we're triggered
by more things because the unforgiving
four is behind it all so when you go
through a hard time you can feel sick
afterwards and then we blame ourselves
when it's not
ourselves because it's the unforgiving
for see how it works very important and
then here's a big one I just have to
tell you genetics genes we're told it's
our genes we're told it's your genes now
that's why you're sick it's it's your
jeans you got faulty jeans you're a
faulty person that's demented cuz it's
not accurate and it's destructive and
poisonous these things are like weeds
they're like weeds of poison in a
beautiful garden and these are like
weeds of poison that are taking over and
they're going to hurt you because it's
not genetics that is why you're sick or
feeling sick research and science
doesn't know it's the unforgiving
for and and that's what it is not
genetics our genes didn't go bad in the
last 20 years that's why literally alone
half the US is more sick than than
meaning a whole half more of the US is
more sick than it was 20 years ago no
wondering 300 million Americans with
symptoms that didn't exist years ago I
promise you that didn't
exist the American dream was you lived
your life you did this you did that
here's you got older here's what you did
and sure you can have health problems
along the way they always existed but
nothing like they are today we're
struggling young and younger and younger
and younger and it's not genetics it's
the unforgiving
for so let's talk about that part now
let's talk about it the first part of
the unforgiving for is the viral
explosion the viral
explosion
viruses understand the viruses have been
in our way especially in the last 100
years but now in the last 30 years in
our way like never before in
history they're in our way just take the
Epstein bar virus which for the first
time ever I brought to everybody's
attention about what the Epstein bar
does what symptoms it creates that alone
from fibromyalgia chronic fatigue
syndrome multiple sclerosis rheumatoid
arthritis these are all varieties of
Epstein bar and different varieties of
Epstein bar tingles and numbness um
blurry eyes brain fog uh ringing the
ears vertigo dizziness aches and pains
severe fatigue it's all Epstein bar
related Hashimoto
thyroiditis and the list goes on and on
and
on all from Epstein bar varieties alone
that are exploding and you're becoming
the expert and you're healing from them
cuz we're helping everybody we're we're
teaching everybody and we're helping
everybody so everybody every body learns
from it we all get better together and
then there's other viruses too there's
the shingles family that causes all the
other stuff going on burning mouth
burning tongue syndrome you know I'm
burning you know vaginal area burning
legs burning feet neuropathy in the feet
and legs ciona trigeminal neuropathy
trigeminal nerve problems all these
things are shingles Bells Palsy um
droopy eyes droopy you know all of that
is the shingles
virus and and the shingles does even
more but the these are the things that
I'm talking about and then there's other
viruses too like hhv6 hhv7 HH the
Undiscovered hhv 9 10 11 12 that Spirit
knows about and they're in our way they
create different types of heart problems
uh myocarditis endocarditis kidney
problems kidney failure all the
different problems and these viruses
exist it's part of the unforgiving for
and everybody wants to ignore them and
now that we're also bringing it to light
um some some leaders are taking the
information Spirit brought and they're
using it for their own game for you know
a claim and notoriety but skewing the
information so it ends up not helping
people anyway so thank God I have you
guys behind me because you guys are
taking the information and I and trust
in you and I trust that you guys you
know know the source and I trust that
you guys know it's never been talked
about out there and I trust that you
guys know you know how to spread the
information wisely and help others
whenever you can over the years and over
the time and I thank you for it and I
thank you for it okay because you guys
are the real deal the real
deal so here's the deal we got the viral
explosion there's always been bacteria
bacteria causes problems we talk about
that in the different shows we talked
about in the stret show we talk about it
in you know the STP aaka show we talk
about it in the different shows that
bacteria is a problem we know that but
the viral explosion is why we're dealing
what we're dealing it's why mommies lay
in bed and can't function and they got
three kids they can't feed and you know
it's it's literally like that kind of
thing all the time out there now it's
why we got the fatigue we got the
mysterious weight gain it's why we have
the thyroid problems and it's why people
are got the brain fog and the memory
loss and they're just having difficult
times and they have all the different
neurological symptoms it's a viral
explosion so and what we're about is
about cleaning that up and getting that
better in life-changing Foods I talk
about the unforgiving for in detail and
I talk about all the foods to help
eradicate the unforgiving for in your
life so when you go through there and
what I meant you're not going to be
disappointed when you go through there
you're going to see the unforgiving for
in
detail and then
you're going to know how to get rid of
the unforgiving for throughout that book
so that you can protect your family and
your loved ones and
yourself it's that serious so wait till
that's in your
hand the um because you're going to be
happy about it the next part of the
unforgiving for the next part is
radiation
radiation we're not looking at radiation
we ignore it we ignore it distance is
falling out of the sky and that's okay
same with the viruses you have to
understand all this is okay because we
got answers we got ways to protect
ourselves we got ways to heal now if I
just try to play the positive crap talk
where that this stuff doesn't really
exist and I just want to talk about hey
how you can turn your life around in
three great steps and not tell you the
truth not tell you really what's going
on not tell you what's happening that
would be the worst that would be
insulting that would be totally
insulting to you I'm going to tell you
what's wrong out there because it's
there whether I like it or not or you
like it or not it's there it's in your
way and I got to protect you so you get
out of your symptoms you get out of your
illnesses so you get better so just bear
with me while I talk about radiation a
little bit it's fallen out of the sky
okay from literally World War II never
mind Fukushima which is falling out of
the sky because of Fukushima 2o it's
starting to you name it Chernobyl you
name it it's been falling out of the
sky and it still is and it's in her way
and it's not just that our forefathers
our family like our past
relatives that we come from were
saturated in radiation as well during
the first x-rays during the first the
birth of the x-rays when we were like oh
my God this is exciting hop in front of
this machine get completely radiated
from head to toe where you see a
complete skeleton you know you see a
complete skeleton up against the the
screen the flat screen that's in front
of the person and you just just slam
them with tons of
radiation and women were getting
radiation treatments to their faces and
they were getting radiation severe
radiation Burns because they were
getting radiation treatments and the old
Dental the old dental work the radiation
it's shot right into everybody's neck
and head it was all in the past but the
problem is it gets passed down cuz it
lasts a million years and it's in our
forefathers then we we're conceived
we're birthed we have it it's just down
the line from all the way back down the
line since radiation was even figured
out and discovered now we could just
ignore it and forget about it and not
realize it's breaking down our immune
system and we're going to fix it there's
people that come to me like and say I
been to every doctor I've Been
Everywhere why is my immune system still
breaking down I've seen everybody I've
paid
$500,000 a half a million dollars to
travel around the globe and around the
world to try to fix my immune system and
it hasn't
happened and spirit would be like you
you got some radiation because your
forefathers were saturated with it and
died early because of it and like oh my
God yeah but we can fix it we can get it
out we can get it out with the right
Foods the power of the foods can get it
out if you know what you're using and
know what you're
doing we can get it out of the
body it's that simple but it takes a
little bit of work takes a little bit of
food it takes a little bit of time a
little bit of energy but you can do it
but the radiation is falling out of the
sky it's definitely hindering us it's
landing on our food sources and that's
okay because food gets rid of it and can
cancel it out the right kind of foods
can get rid of it and cancel it out we
can pull old radiation out of us that's
been in there for for a century from our
forefathers and it can be
done okay that's part of the unforgiving
for next part of the unforgiving for
toxic heavy
metals yeah toxic heavy metals Mercury
we have mercury in us that's a thousand
years old that's been mined out of Minds
thousand years ago and it stays in our
line it's not genetics everybody I'm
sorry to say it I don't mean to break
the hearts of the leaders that are
taking the genetic movement where they
are and the leaders that think that all
of our problems are genes I'm sorry that
all their funding and all their hard
work is not for the right thing I'm
sorry that's not my fault so I just have
to tell you the truth I can't protect
them I have to protect
you and it's not jeans it's Mercury
passed down generation after generation
hundreds of years of Mercury from when
our forefathers were drinking Mercury
Elixir just in the 1800s when all the
medical universities were closing down
because nobody went to doctors anymore
in the
1850s and the 1840s and the
1860s no one went to doctors anymore
they went for they went that's how
alternative healers were birthed they
were birthed out of the Mercury the
Mercury uh bomb of the uh 19th century
when the me when the conventional
medical world just gave you a big glass
of mercury when you went to the doctor's
office didn't matter who you were when
you left the doctor's office you were
raving you were raging mad Insanity
occurred you went home and your life was
over your family's life was over if you
were a working father and and you were
dependent on and you went went to the
doctor and drank a big glass of mercury
solution came home your wife would be
just
mortified and that was it you weren't
going to work the next day bills weren't
paid families crashed and that happened
because of the Mercury Elixir we still
have that in our bloodline it's not
genetics we got the Mercury in our
bloodline see how it works sometimes
going all the way back hundreds of years
all the way back going hundreds of years
Mercury all dating back to the Mercury
man and it's Mercury it's just
everywhere it's in our water it's it's
just you mean it's in the ocean it's
just everywhere it's all over the place
so the point is is that that Mercury's
responsible for so many things
depression Mercury responsible for
anxiety it feeds Epstein bar it feeds
the viral explosion they work together
the heavy metals and I'm all toxic heavy
metals and they feed the viral explosion
working together to help take us down
but guess what it won't take us down I'm
telling you my friend I'm telling you
folks it won't take us down because we
have have a way to fight it clean it out
I talked about the Frozen wild
blueberries removes heavy metals I talk
about the heavy metal detox check out my
heavy metal detox check it out it's in
book one the heavy metal detox from
Spirit to remove that heavy metal out of
your system so you can get rid of your
symptoms that correlate with the viral
explosion you can get rid of that out of
your
body okay and and I'm going to give you
some tips first of all if you get heavy
metal tested and it shows really low
doesn't mean it's not really high cuz
they can't test inside your nervous
system they can't test to see how much
mercury you have in your nervous system
this is a mistake made all the time you
know Spirit told one person that I know
a while back Spirit told one person
you're really high in heavy metal you're
high in mercury that's why you're you're
feeling like you're feeling and they're
like well I don't believe you because I
had a test and the test said I was low
first of all the test for heavy metals
is not even accurate because it cannot
test how much heavy metal it's inside
deep in organ or inside the central
nervous system or inside your brain it
can only test if you've been freshly
exposed to heavy metal in the
bloodstream that means you would have
had to eat a can of tuna the day you got
the blood test so the can of tuna would
leech the mercury into your bloodstream
the day of your blood test or the day
before your blood test to show up a
little bit of mercury a little
bit and nobody knows that information
but you know it now
you know it now because of spirit and
that's how it works so we get the toxic
heavy metals they go inside our liver
they're inside our brain they're deep in
our system and Mercury is a big big
piece of it all never mind the alloy the
alloy that occurs you guys what happens
is when they make steel they mix it with
Metals when they make when they make a
bicycle they have an alloy different
varieties of metals to make the bike
lighter and stronger it's called an
alloy right when we get these Alloys
inside our brain in our body I talked
about it in the brain health show we get
these Alloys they're a mix of metals
disturbing our function giving us a low
quality of life giving us
symptoms and even some
conditions and this is the the the
movement of mean this is the Wrath
of the toxic heavy metals part of the
unforgiving
for and once you start taking these
things out with the foods you need once
you start taking them out with the foods
you need and you start taking the
radiation out with the foods you need
radiation that's not even yours not even
yours and you end up owning it when it's
not even yours it's pushed on you same
with the toxic heavy metals toxic heavy
metals from the past that's not even
yours it's somebody else is all the way
back and it's not even
yours okay and we get these things and
we have them and it's time it's time to
get them out of our body and out of our
system so we can get rid of the
unforgiving
four we're going to recap a little bit
cuz we still got one more to go still
got one more unforgiving four to go
we're going to recap a little bit we got
the viral explosion all the upstein bars
I was the first to break to the table
that there's over 60 varieties of
Epstein bar in six different groups and
they date all the way back to the late
1890s and they've mutated they've grown
in different strains that's what we're
up against and you are cleaning it out
and you're kicking but because you're
getting rid of those viruses right now I
got people all over the world getting
rid of their viruses getting rid of
their Epstein bar and they're gaining
they're getting their life back and you
can too and you're already doing it
you're you're already working on it and
so it's the foods that that starve out
the viral explosion get rid of it help
clean it out you name it we talked about
that on the Epstein bar webinar recently
we talked about that on the Epstein bar
show and that's what we're doing and
then we got the radiation the radiation
going all the way back we since World
War II it's falling out of the sky we're
getting rid of that too out of our
bodies all the different you know
radiation that was passed on from the
forefathers getting it from old x-rays
and everything we're getting rid of that
and then the toxic heavy metals we
talked about that just now let's talk
about the number four of the unforgiving
for it's
DDT would you believe it
DDT why would DDT even be possible isn't
that something from the past isn't that
over with isn't that done right I mean
is DDT like you don't hear about it
anymore right right I know you don't
hear about it anymore and it's DDT where
is it what's it doing it's first of all
it's not gone and there's other
pesticides and herbicides and fungicides
and insecticides that are its cousins
that are here every day being sprayed
everywhere else but even DDT itself is
not gone it's not gone what of the most
evst chemicals of all time one of them
and it's still being put on
food it's still being sprayed in all
kinds of different countries around the
world and it's still in the air it's
still in the air it's still in our water
it's still in our ocean it's still
everywhere and it's in our way the worst
part about DDT it's Everlasting you guys
it's
Everlasting we it comes from our for
forefathers our family of in the past
our families would eat it sleep in it
breathe it bathe in it we were washed
down in it Parks were washed down hosed
while all of the children were just
saturated in it and sued up in it and
rolling around in it it was sprayed on
food it was considered a nutritional
supplement it was in every Garden around
everyone's
house and it killed all practically
every single bald eagle in this
country okay and it's done worse than
that it's done terrible things and it
sits inside people inside their livers
and it's passed on to generation and
generation and we still have it in US
hey look I'm not going to I'm not going
to cookie cut this and just pretend this
is just a you know a cute little
positive talk show about how this and
that you know like I know it's getting
done out there and I get it I respect it
but I'm saying I'm not going to hold
this back from you I got to help protect
you and help look out for you and so you
can get the DDT out of your liver you
can get it out of there so it's not
giving you exmos orasis so it's not
causing problems so you can get it out
of you so it's not breaking down the
immune system and we can do that and
that's what I talk about in the book
especially life changing foods to 50
foods and I Mark which ones take out DDT
which ones take out DDT and eliminate it
and pull it out and extract it from our
livers DDT that you don't even get I
mean DDT that's from the past that's
literally from your
grandfather or
great-grandfather playing with it in the
garden or or just getting it all over
him because it was sprayed in every
neighborhood every neighborhood in the
streets they used to wash the streets
down with it wash the streets down with
it literally it didn't matter if you
were walking on the street as it
happened it was a movement of
destruction of the worst way it's one of
the worst unforgiving for but hidden
away it's in it's in the closet you go
to the doctor's office you got all these
symptoms no one's going to know they're
going to blame it on your jeans why not
it's the easy way out blame it on
you I mean hey look I'm not blaming
you I'm not blaming
you okay cuz it's not your fault it's
not your fault here's the problem though
you know our youth is coming up and they
just they know know they don't know
anything about any of this they have no
clue about the viral explosion they have
no clue about how Epstein bar Works they
have no clue about any of this and then
they go to then they go to different you
know practitioner schools and Doctor
schools and everything and they come out
of it and they still don't know it's not
nothing bad everybody's trying
everybody's working on it and then and
then our youth in general our children
grow up and they they just they just
don't know so we have to look out for
everybody and ourselves it can't just be
you it can't be about me me me me me you
know when I was putting out the first
book medical medium someone said to me
hey you're going to be an author
now you know it's going to it's it it's
all about you okay it's not about me
it's not about me what are you saying
it's it's about everybody else and
getting them better and I stand behind
that I still do I still do
and it's about you guys that's what it's
about it's not about me I said you know
what I'm changing the rules I said to
this person I'm changing the rules it's
not going to be about me in my life it's
not going to be about me in my life I'm
changing the rules it's about everybody
else for real but for real it's about
everyone else and it's not being cookie
cuted it's not going to be held back
it's not going to be ignored I'm going
to make sure people get better hell high
water I don't care what it takes I'm
going to make sure people get better I
don't care What It
Takes we're going to do
it so DDT is one of the ones that snuck
up on us along the way and we can get it
out of our system and the pesticides
today and the its cousins the pesticides
insecticides herbicides rodenticides
fungicides you know those are in our way
too and they add into it and we can pull
all that out with the right foods with
the right
foods and and you know give you just a
rundown it's why celery juice is so
powerful the mineral salts in it bind on
to these poisons and help remove it out
of the liver you know I you know I heard
the other day someone else said because
people like to say things to me and I
don't blame them because they're
confused someone else said to me hey you
know why do you like the celery juice so
much I'm getting sick of it I'm getting
sick of this whole celery juice talk you
do I mean come on it's getting old I
said you mean people getting better is
getting old that's what I said to this
person it was a health professional I
said so people getting better is getting
old is that what you're saying and they
said I didn't mean it that way I go okay
you know people are getting better from
it they go yeah true I go so is that
getting old they said no it's not they
put their head down they said no it's
not and they actually apologized which
took Integrity I said look I'm sorry I'm
on board 100% with the celery juice I'm
totally on board with you 100% I said
yeah cuz it's life-changing like in
life-changing Foods I don't care if I'm
called the celery juice boy I don't care
if I'm called the celery juice King I
don't care if I'm called the celery
juice guy I don't care if I'm called the
guy here's a voice that loves celery
juice it's going to get you better it's
going to move you forward it's going to
help with the unforgiving for and I list
50 foods that help with the the whole
unforgiving four 50 foods that eradicate
the unforgiving four out of your bodies
when they're used right so you start
healing it's the Frozen wild blueberry
says one of the 50 it's decelerate it's
one of the 50 and it goes on and on and
going to make sure you guys get cleaned
up and you're healing it's Ginger it's
turmeric there two other ones it's natal
Leaf it's another one helping me clean
things up and get rid of things it's the
aromatic herbs the Rosemary the thyme
the sage you know put sage in the
guacamole it's all of these it's the
avocado oh yeah sure I've heard this
before actually no you haven't I talk
about what the food does and how you
have to use it how you have to utilize
it how you have to eat it how it works
and in conjunction with the other Foods
so you can get rid of the unforgiving
for so if you have a symptom or
condition you need to know which foods
out of the 50 foods and you put them
together and you start extracting the
unforgiving four out of your lives out
of your bodies we protect our families
we protect our friends we protect our
loved ones we protect our
colleagues we protect
ourselves we move forward together and
we're healing we get the Mercury out of
our system the Arsenic the lead the
aluminum the cadmium the copper we get
it out of our system by the way the
right kind of zinc doesn't lower your
good copper just know that the right
kind of zinc doesn't lower your good
copper you know on my supplements page
and I don't sell the supplements they're
on my supplements page at
medicalmedium.com you can see the list
of all the supplements that Spirit deems
worthy or Spirit deems safe Spirit deems
correct so you can pick out the ones
that you know you know you need and one
of them is the right kind of zinc till
this day even the most advanced book
coming out on thyroid or anything else
coming out literally this year that's
still that's just coming out this year
and early next year still doesn't even
know about the real zinc yet the one
that helps stop the viral explosion the
Epstein bars still doesn't even know the
right zinc
yet so you have to understand it's about
watching your back for real and
protecting you making sure we're getting
you better and getting you moved forward
so seaweeds the Atlantic coast seaweeds
I like at I like the main lantic Co sea
vegetables and you know here's another
thing too you can't worry about what's
in a seaweed especially the main Coast
seaweeds because there's not enough of
the problems in it there's not enough
heavy metal in the seaweed in fact what
happens is when you eat the seaweed like
the dolls it removes more heavy metal in
fact any trace of ocean metal that could
be in a seaweed like douls stays in
douls never leaves it until it leaves
your body in fact what happens is a
miracle happens the seaweed absorbs more
and more of it out of your own body
pulls it all in one you know one group
out of the body in case someone's ready
to had you know another question that
came up actually was you know how do
seaweed work if it's in our ocean well
I'll tell you how it works it holds on
to whatever what was in it and then it
takes out double triple quadruple more
right out of the body and we pull the
heavy metals out of our
body so we got that we got the seaweeds
we got and and I talk about that in
life-changing Foods too that's another
way of getting rid of things spirulina
make sure you're taking your spirulina
that pulls out toxic heavy metals it
helps pull out
radiation and it does help pull out a
little bit of DDT get the hne spirulina
that's another Inc incredible tool but
when you go through everything you're
going to see all the different things
all the different um foods and herbs and
other information to help get rid of the
unforgiving
for I woke up this morning and I said to
Spirit I'm still in the game I'm still
here and I'm not giving up until
everybody has what they need until we do
a million shows and do what we got to do
and get the information in books cuz I
want you guys better and I want you guys
to protect your family and your loved
ones and I woke up this morning I said
to Spirit I'm in the game I'm not
backing down I'm not leaving I'm staying
in it let's get everybody better I stand
behind you I love you remember you
didn't create your illness you're a good
person okay you didn't manifest your
illness these illnesses are here because
of these unforgiving four I stand behind
you I love you I believe in you be easy
on yourself have compassion on yourself
you take care talk to you next time
bye