that's the vimer gb12 so I want to show
you okay what you can do is you take a
tiny drop and you put it on your hand
tiny drop right on your hand and you let
it sit there and you can just dab it on
there like this your body starts to
acclimate it starts to prepare and get
ready for something that's going to help
change your life you can leave it on
there just for a couple of minutes once
a day when those couple of minutes are
up you do this what happens is your body
is now recalibrating rewiring your brain
your nervous system your entire body is
rewiring to that B12 now I like doing
this with B12 because B12 is
fundamentally how we exist it is
fundamentally how we exist on this
planet we need B12 or we die what this
does It prepares your vus nerves that
are inflamed It prepares your central
nervous system your brain your liver
which is the converter of supplements
and what I love about B12 I'm not
speaking for all B12 out there I'm not
because I don't know the crap that's in
beachall bottles all across the land
I've seen it all out there that's why I
support Vin that's why I work with them
because of this fact that that's what
the companies do out there but what I'm
trying to say is the methab balam and
the sto silic B in right this these
co-enzymes right here in this bottle so
what I like to do is put it on a hand
for people who are sensitive and you do
that once a day and then this
acclamation process happens this goes to
the skin it's heading into the liver
already drawing it in from this process
but in such a minute amount on a level
that is actually Awakening your natural
ability to absorb assimilate and
methylate supplementation because if
you've been that sensitive where you're
in that place where you're super
sensitive you've been through a lot
exposures Galore this is a way to get it
to really go into your system and get
you rewired re acclimated redirected
your body wants this stuff it wants B12
because guess what we need it it's
critical