metal detox cleanse challenge
this is about empowerment this is about
getting
metals out of our lives right getting
them out
metals who's got metals
why should we get metals out anxiety
depression depersonalization
schizophrenia bipolar
dementia alzheimer's brain fog metals
anyone metals
everybody's packed with metals and
that's just a few things eczema
psoriasis vitiligo
right
worsening of neurological symptoms how
about that ticks spasms tremors
how about that right there that's how
many things and that's just some i'm not
even mentioning like a host of
hosts of symptoms and conditions out
there including
how metals add to pathogen
issues neurological lyme neurological
lyme disease people they got metals and
they got bugs metals and bugs
right take away the metals with somebody
with neurological lime and they start
getting better
take away the bugs they're even better
but the point is is the metals play a
role in all of it
it's a big deal everybody's just jamming
with metals and
i get it people think hey you know i
don't cut any metals where did i get
metals i'll show you in a little bit
where we get metals we'll talk about
where we get metals in a little bit so
we're doing the heavy metal detox
cleanse challenge this is day one which
is really exciting i'm pumped up about
this do you have the cleanse to heal
book
right there go to the library get it for
free if you don't have it now have it
for tomorrow or have it for when get it
now so you can do the next one with us
or you can just do it yourself on your
own the heavy metal detox cleanse is in
this book right here cleanse the heel 51
off at amazon.com us
right now 16 costs more to print it it's
a medical textbook it's packed with
information it's got the metal cleanse
in here or go to the library and get it
for free
all right so we need that that's number
one because the details are in here
we're gonna cover a lot of stuff anyway
right here but still the book is
critical there's more stuff in the book
that i can't cover here all right so
what do we have right here we got our
supplies we have our things for the
cleanse have you guys already done your
lemon water have you done that you've
done the 16 ounces the 32 ounces of
lemon water first thing in the morning
right we got our lemon
okay incredible and then uh
we got our
cilantro you guys got the cilantro it's
the beautiful herb right here this leafy
green
so we got the cilantro gotta have that
you got your lemon for the lemon water
where's your celery
celery right there okay we got the
celery
all set we're going to do the celery
juice too i'm excited 16 to 32 ounces of
celery juice
frugivore bear how are you
uh youtube over there right lemon water
and celery juice done already frugivore
bear i'm proud of you incredible
uh courtney and may i had mine this
morning proud of you guys this is
fantastic so we're live on tick tock
we're live on rumble we're live on
youtube we're live on facebook we're
live on
we're live on everything right now
telegram
we're just live this is great so good to
see you guys you're all set with
everything you got it all on hand too
all right
so
we're on it let's get started a little
bit but we're just covering a couple of
basics okay why do the heavy metal detox
uh cleanse why do that
a lot of okay keep in mind right now too
new exposure happens as well so even if
you get rid of your metals
from three years ago or two years ago
you can get re-exposed it's easy to keep
on getting exposed over and over again
so just you know just know that that's
how it works you can easily get
exposed you're drinking your heavy metal
detox smoothie now
dana white amazing
proud of every everybody so
we're going to talk about how these
metals cause these problems a little bit
michael scoots
so we're going to talk about how these
metals actually cause this stuff like
what happens in our body we get metals
in our brain
we get metals in our brain stem
that's where we get metals if you guys
just came on here with day one of the
heavy metal detox cleanse challenge
that's what you just entered right now
so if you're here you entered into the
free
challenge notice how you didn't pay
anything to enter into this free
challenge right here
pretty funny i didn't block it out from
the world and
try to you know make this thing into
this big thing where you got to pay to
come in and do the challenge i just want
everybody to have fun i want everybody
to do this for free
and that's all things you'll see people
new people come on he'll be like what's
going on here what's going on dude you
just entered for free it's like it's
like entering a concert just walking
right in you don't have to buy a ticket
right so
so this is great here we are
do you have your book
do you have your supplies let's give a
supply run down right now what do we
need okay we need lemons because we need
lemons for lemon water we're gonna make
it a little bit we need that
we need celery for the celery juice
okay we're gonna make that a little bit
too
we need the five key ingredients for the
heavy metal detox smoothie what are the
five key ingredients you guys
cilantro
right we got that down cilantro that's
one right there
dolce
right that's the vimergy dolls liquid or
i got the atlantic dulce right here the
whole form here it is that's the whole
form right
we need the cilantro we need the dose
that's the dose liquid
we need the spirulina
spirulina powder we have to have the
spirulina powder
so that's the next one right there do
you have the spirulina powder that's the
vimer21 that's the one i trust i'm not
sponsored but these guys are incredible
it's the best one out there do you have
the barley grass juice powder broken
record coming broken record coming not
barley grass
barley grass juice powder
last night when i went to bed last night
right
like literally even after working on on
the book i was working on proofing the
book i was doing some proofs on the book
because the books getting closer and
closer right to getting out
and i went to bed last night
and all i saw was
like
barley grass
don't do barley grass juice powder don't
do barley grass barley gras like that's
how many times i think i said it
yesterday
it's got to be barley grass juice powder
not barley grass you can't get metals
out with the barley grass it's not going
to happen it has to be the juice powder
because the juice pattern i'll just tell
you
travels
the juice powder it actually absorbs
assimilates
that's what it does it gets into the
bloodstream it travels to the brain it
travels to the nervous system it has to
be the juice powder these are the
differences these are the details that
matter in order to heal
if you don't believe you have metals but
you're suffering with anxiety
we still got to have it right
so we can get the metals out even if you
don't believe it's a metal causing it in
order to get better the details have to
matter they have to be right so we got
the barley grass cheese powder right
and then last but not least we need the
wild blueberries right here
is it the frozen wild blueberries okay
that's one option right there you can do
the wild blueberry juice which i'm gonna
grab a wild blueberry juice in a minute
too
so we need that
so we need a wild blueberry juice and
then
we got the
we got and if you got a wild blueberry
powder that's great too
that's great right i'm looking around i
can't find my wild blueberry juice
all right so i'm gonna have to just go
get it
so we got the wild blueberry juice right
here
so that's the wyman's one all right so
that's an option there so the five key
ingredients is critical it's critical
it's cilantro it's spirulina it's barley
grass juice powder it's dulse
and it's
the wild blueberries right
now here's how it works
when you have all five key ingredients
you can get the metals from deeper
places out of the body
and you can get them completely out of
the body
and then when you do the cleanse
you're really taking it to that next
level to get the metals out of the body
because when you're doing the cleanse
you're not eating any fats in the
morning to block
to block the metals from coming out
you're not eating any fats to block the
metals from coming out we're still
censored on facebook big time you guys
so we're not that's what happens when
you don't do
the fats in the morning you don't block
the metals from coming out
so that's what's key about it right
there so if you're not doing bacon
you're not doing eggs you're not doing
nut butters you're not doing oils you're
not doing
you know whatever you're not doing
chicken in the morning a lot of people
eat they're not doing cheese in the
morning you're not doing milk in the
morning milk butter eggs cheese
kefir
sour cream you're not doing any kind of
fat in the morning
cottage cheese whatever you're not doing
any kind of fat in the morning when you
hold those off and you don't do fats in
the morning you can get the metals out
if you're doing the actual metal remover
stuff you got the heavy metal detox
smoothie you got that going on like you
got your cilantro your your spirulina
broadly grass juice powder your wild
blueberries the whole bit the dolls you
do that and you're not doing any metals
i mean sir you're not doing any fats you
can get the metals out of the
bloodstream
so the reason why the heavy metal detox
cleanse
right
doesn't have any fats in the morning
it's so
the metals don't stay in the bloodstream
and then
go back into your liver
or go back into your brain or go back
into something
that's how it works that's what's
amazing about it right so we're in the
cleanse right now we're day one
so let's talk about what we have to do
first of all we'll make a little lemon
water right now before we talk about all
kinds of other stuff
get the lemon water going
so i got one lemon right here
so listen you guys if you're getting
kicked off you can go to tick tock
you can go to rumble you can go to
telegram
you can go to getter
you can go there so getter telegram
we're live on getter telegram
we're live on tick tock we're live on
rumble we're live on youtube
just letting you know just in case
you guys are getting kicked off of
facebook because
facebook has us kind of
blocked out
so we're doing a lemon right here so i'm
just showing you guys there's the lemon
i just cut one in half
right i'm gonna make some lemon water
really quick
here's how here's how easy it is
do not do hot water
you want to do hot water
you just lost
boom you don't win
yes you can do lemon in hot tea but
that's not going to give you the flush
that's not going to help hydrate you and
give you the flush
when you cook your lemon
in hot water like
hot lemon tea
right
you don't get a flush
it doesn't hydrate either it doesn't
have that hydration power
this is really important to know
okay so that's what i did i just put
fresh lemon juice right into this cup
just like that
okay
amazing
now i'm going to add some water look at
this you can have lukewarm water you can
have room temperature water you can have
cold water
you don't want hot water
keep that in mind right so there you go
lemon water right there
voila all set that fast
so when you think about how hard is this
cleanse like how hard is it to do like
what what do i have to do for this
because i'm not i'm not into anything
hard to do
yep k says i'm seeing you on facebook
yes of course there's a few people on
there it's just that they're holding
back the other you know few thousand
easy
so why not hot water the question comes
through why not hot water
the reason why hot water doesn't work is
because you kill the phytochemical
compounds the living water because
that's what it is
you kill it
and that's important to know right there
so
if you're if you're using hot water
you lose that
flushing agent that's in it right so
here's how it works
a lemon
is not boiling hot on the tree
so when the lemon's on the tree it's not
boiling hot you don't go to the lemon
tree and you pick up pick a lemon you're
like oh oh my god so hot oh my god it's
hot well whoa whoa it's hot whoa
you don't do that
so
you grab it
a lot of times especially when the
lemons are actually on the lemon tree
it's cool out too
it's cool
it's around that time of the year where
it's cool okay
so when you you have living water
living enzymes living water
phytochemical compounds that are alive
in that lemon you don't want to cook
them you cook them you change it
is what you do
you change it if you cook them
they don't flush
it becomes something different
so that's important to know right
so
um
if you're sensitive if you got teeth
that are sensitive
can't handle cold water on your teeth
right then do lukewarm warm temp like
you don't like room temp or anything
like that okay
if you get sensitive teeth from lemon
water
from you think the lemon if the lemon
that's not the lemon giving you
sensitive teeth that just means you have
sensitive nerves
that means you have sensitive nerves
so keep that in mind
the calcium in lemon restores the teeth
is what it does it restores enamel
you know that's what it does
like
lemon will showcase you have a problem
but it doesn't create a problem that's
important to know so lemon does not
create a problem
it just showcases that you have
sensitivities you have inflammation in
your jaw inflammation in your teeth
inflammation in your gums
right that's what it could do but lemon
itself kills pathogens in the mouth
and around the gum line
keeping you from getting cavities
keeping you from these kinds of things
so that's that's what happens there so
i'm just letting you know okay
so lemon water is the first thing
right we're going into
and then we'll do before we go into
anything else we're going to talk about
other stuff right here
so when it comes down to symptoms a lot
of people have anxiety they have panic
they have heart palpitations they have
racing heart
a lot of people are struggling
struggling with all of that a lot of
people have that diagnosis of bipolar a
lot of people
are up and down that's what the bipolar
diagnosis means it doesn't give you a
real answer it just says well that
person's always either manic or that
person's just depressed
so eventually they get it they get a
bipolar diagnosis
power of compassion says when i started
medical medium i used to have very
sensitive teeth
after drinking lemon water now i don't
feel anything i love lemon water power
compassion because you're because you're
doing medical medium
and medical being protocols you're
restoring your nerves
you're strengthening your nerves
that's why so you're strengthening your
central nervous system so everything
strengthens your entire
central nervous system that's what's
incredible about that
sandy says celery juice it helped
restore my gums
it does despite what people who don't
drink celery juice say they don't drink
it out there they just they're naysayers
because they want to just destroy
anybody's chance of healing
so they'll say hey
you know don't drink celery juice i
heard it's bad for you it's like okay
that's great you just ruined a chance
for somebody to heal their gums like
sandy so thank god you you're actually
you're listening you're drinking your
celery juice you heal your gums that
that's amazing that's incredible
so our central nervous system can get
inflamed easy
pathogens inflame our central nervous
system metals have a big role in it too
but metals do other things too metals
get into
the brain
is what they do
eventually a lot of people though
they'll like bang their head in their
car door
they go
to the hospital
they get an mri on their head
to make sure they're okay
and then the doctor says i see something
on there
but we don't know what it is but we see
something we see gray area we see
a dark spot we see something there
people don't realize
okay that
a lot of times toxic heavy metals create
these oxidative places in the brain like
dark spots little different spots in our
brain
okay so we get these marks inside our
brain so there's millions of people
around the world that eventually when
they get an mri they have these little
you have these little dots that show up
a lot of times it won't even show up but
they'll have these dots that show up
right they'll show up somewhere in the
brain anywhere little black spots and
stuff like that
so metals tend to hide in a lot of
places right
adhd
autism
metals go right here i'll show you on a
close-up on that right there metals go
right here midline canal right there
so adhd autism
right there it is
right in between the left and right
hemisphere
on tic toc you guys i we're doing a
camera close up over here so i know you
guys can't see it but that midline canal
right here
that's where the metal settle
when you're a child
they settle in the midline canal
so
so when when um
moms and dads are giving their children
the heavy metal detox smoothie they're
seeing progress
because the heavy metal detox smoothie
is removing metals out of the midline
canal
and so progress is occurring
because we're getting metals so with
autism and adhd the metals that gather
in the midline canal right here
they interfere with information
traveling back and forth from the left
and right hemisphere i wrote about that
in the medical medium books
so there's information that travels back
and forth
and when that canal is filled up with
metal right here so the information goes
back and forth to left and right
hemisphere
so
when that is filled up with mercury
when that's filled up with aluminum
information doesn't travel across easily
and so you end up with the autism
diagnosis you end up with all the
symptoms you end up with the severe adhd
that's the metals in the midline canal
okay
now here's the thing a lot of people
have metals
sprinkled about
and that ends it ends up adding up as
the years go on and we get the brain fog
so how many people have brain fog
or how many people had brain fog i know
a lot of people using medical medium
information
and and brain fog proto uh protocols for
brain fog they actually fix it
right
so miriam says my teeth bled in every
pregnancy but not this one means you're
getting stronger getting healthier
incredible
so with brain fog you can have metal
sprinkled about
so you're wondering like where do i get
mercury and all these metals if word is
like where does it where does it come
from well i notice a lot of people like
tattoos these days
a lot of people like ink these days
and i'm not against getting ink at all
if you got ink don't get it removed
you know i mean if you have ink it's
fine that's fine but what people don't
realize is that's a huge one for toxic
heavy metals that's why the heavy metal
detox cleanse is so important
that's why the heavy metal detox
smoothie is so important because what
happens is that this tattoo's really
cool too
this tattoo says germany this is really
cool
so
you got the skull on there a lot of
people get skulls on their arms
a lot of people get skulls on their arms
i'm going to get a close-up on this
right
well
a lot of people seem that cool this is
germany isn't that cool
we got a lot of german uh uh
uh fans and followers and that do the
medical mean protocols anyway
i thought i'd put this one on for today
a lot of people get roses
right it's like plant a rose garden a
lot of people get roses
so there's nothing wrong with getting
tattoos
it's just that there's no heavy metal
free
ink
so when you get when someone's like hey
i know this great tattoo parlor i know
this great tattoo artist
they use cruelty free
ink they use animal cruelty free ink
it's vegan
it's vegan ink
it's filled with metal you can't have it
any other way and i'll tell you why
when you get your ink
right and i'll show you this right here
you see this rose you can see this rose
up close
the reason why you can see the rose on
your arm when you get the ink or you get
on your wherever you got your tattoo
maybe you just got an excrep inscription
maybe you just got some wise words
you know like some wise words written
across maybe you got like
you know the name of of something
written somewhere whatever it is that
you choose to get
you see the rose it pops when light hits
it right
when it's in your arm and the only way
that can happen is if that ink is filled
with metal
that's the reflective nature of the ink
so what happens is when light goes into
your derma
anything like any kind of light not
sunlight any kind of light goes through
your derma it hits the ink and it
reflects back out
that's how you get that pop
so when you walk out of the tattoo
parlor
and the dude there or whoever gave you a
tattoo
they said it was animal cruelty free ink
maybe it was animal cruelty free free
ink but it's not heavy metal free ink
because the metals
make it so you can see it
and so here's how it works as the metals
go into your bloodstream every day from
there on out
and they go to your brain over time as
the metals travel into your bloodstream
and get to your brain over time
okay
your your tattoo fades it's not fading
because you're getting older
it's not fading because you've had the
tattoo for 10 years or 15 years 20 years
it's fading because all the metal is
slowly leaving through your derma that
pass through your derm into your
bloodstream and ends up in your
liver and ends up in your brain
that's where it's going
right and it's not about getting them
removed
it's about just being proactive and
catching the metals as they're leaving
i always tell people who are inked up
heavy metal detox smoothie for life man
heavy metal detox smoothie for life
because what you're gonna do is you're
gonna be catching the metals as they're
going to the brain you're gonna be
catching them
arena park says mm tools have healed my
really bad teeth and gum sensitivities i
no longer have nerve pain in my cavity
that's incredible on youtube amazing
amazing
so what happened the other day i think
it was not the other day but like a
month ago or something i mentioned about
tattoos and someone was like i gotta get
them all removed just like no you don't
have to get them all removed you just
gotta be proactive and catch the metal
as it's going into the
stream they're like okay i'm gonna get
more tattoos then now i'm gonna get more
tattoos you don't have to do that either
you don't have to get more tattoos i
know it's addictive but you don't have
to get more more tattoos right
but the point is the bottom line is i'm
just saying you guys
that if anybody has any ink
that metal and some ink is way worse
than others for sure but either way
they're all packed with metal that's how
you see
the
picture
you see the picture because you're
watching light
hit the metal and reflect back out
through your skin
that's how you see the picture that's
how it's done
lots of metals so the bottom line is
where do we get metals
that's one place right there
one
kimberly miller your info has helped my
teeth so much too
i'm so happy to hear that what happens
is okay let me just tell you something
about teeth you guys real quick we're
first of all we're day one before i go
into some teeth information which is
interesting interesting but we're day
one of the of the medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse right we got all our
stuff here we're doing we got our
spirulina we're about to make a smoothie
in a minute we made some lemon water
we're about to make celery juice too and
talk about all the do's and don'ts and
all that all right we'll go into teeth
for for a second here and and listen if
you're coming on here you don't have the
book you got to get the book if you can
gra gabriel says i healed my
neurological asthma only with medical
medium tools after 15 years of being
asthmatic love from romania
right there on youtube
gabriel thanks for being here
neurological asthma i'll talk about that
in a little bit too
and and neurological asthma it's really
good to get metals out when you're
dealing with that as well make sure you
have your book right here here's the
cleanse to heal book 51 off amazon.com
us that's the 51 off there it's a
medical textbook or get it free at the
library having this is critical because
the heavy metal detox cleanse is in this
book so keep that in mind right there
all right let's talk about teeth a
little bit a lot of people come to
medical medium information brand new off
the press and their teeth are about to
fall apart
their teeth are about to fall apart
they're coming into
the medical meeting community
they get a book
they're starting their first process
but their teeth are time capsules that
are about to all fall apart
you know what i'm saying you guys
they've already screwed up throughout
their life
it's not their fault they just didn't
know they already did too much caffeine
for too many years which
eats your teeth from the inside out
and i'm not picking on anybody drink
caffeine or whatever i'm not that's not
where we're going today but i'm saying
they already did vinegar years of
vinegar
they've already done years of vinegar
okay
for years
okay they've already done lots of dairy
products
they've already
created an acidic environment in their
life
they've already done these things right
they've already eaten all this msg and
nutritional yeast and everything else
they've they've already done all this
charcoal and made themselves deficient
because charcoal actually clogs up your
highways and your intestinal tract so
that you don't get any nutrients so you
essentially get nutrient deficient when
you eat charcoal
right they did all these things and then
they come into the medical medium
community with time capsules that are
about to freaking explode
they're about to need a lot of dental
work in a year or six months
they come into the medical medium
community
literally like time capsules of all the
crap they did before
they come in
and their teeth start falling apart
and they're like ever since ever since
i did the medical medium lemon water my
teeth are all falling apart ever since i
did the medical medium celery juice my
teeth are falling apart i started eating
celery sticks for the first time in my
life and my teeth started falling apart
i did the spiruline and my teeth are
falling apart i did his orange just eat
one orange and eat three apples a day
and my teeth are falling apart and they
just all of a sudden now they have no
idea that they came in here
with time capsules and they just started
falling apart cold white spring may
what's going on mine fell apart before i
found medical medium
how lucky is medical medium that they
fell apart before instead of during like
right when you got here like in your may
may have you got here and you started
doing everything
then they started falling apart you
might be like that anthony you might not
like me anymore but i don't know may you
you know a lot of stuff so you probably
would never be like that i know that
about you you're awesome but
and so the thing is is that it all
depends when you're arriving into the
medical meeting community
that determines what's going to happen
with your teeth
you can come into the medical meeting
community and do stuff and your teeth
can still fall apart because it was
years and years of bad stuff you got to
hang in there to keep them from falling
apart and and even get them better
right
what happens is the reason why teeth are
depleting out there is because
everybody's losing the insides of their
teeth and their enamel because they're
doing all the wrong stuff they're
drinking their coffee they're drinking
their espressos their green tea their
matcha tea they're doing their kombucha
tea
it's not that i have all this stuff
against kombucha tea where i hate
kombucha tea or something so bad the
problem is it's got caffeine in it it's
also extremely acidic and it kills your
teeth you've got all these yoga mamas
out there and yoga papas that they're
all into yoga studios and they're all
doing their yoga they're drinking their
kombucha tea and they're just they're
about to kill their teeth give it just
five more years get them out of their
early 30s get them into their late 30s
and all their teeth are going to need
work and start falling apart because of
their kombucha tea
but every now and then someone will be
in their late 30s about to lose all
their teeth and they come into the
medical meeting community because they
got brain fog and all of a sudden their
teeth start falling apart and they're
like oh my god it's the medical media
these time capsules
they rot from the inside out and they
just start crumbling and that's what
happened sun moon love says lost all my
teeth before finding medical medium so
it all depends on where you land how you
come into the medical medium community
if you come in and the timing is just
right with your teeth you already
destroyed your teeth and didn't know it
for two decades and you came into the
medical media community and now they
start falling apart
that's the confusion
marisa spiritual says my teeth on
youtube my teeth all all fell apart
before medical medium but after starting
medical medium protocols i have healed a
dark spot on my tooth i had for years
it's a power of spirit of compassion's
information
andrea says my teeth actually whitened
on their own just from starting medical
media
i've heard that so many times over the
years
andrea on facebook i've heard that so
many times
like people's teeth whiten
because
of the medical medium information and
people they'll say to me well hey your
teeth don't look so great because
they're not all perfect they're kind of
crooked aw
dude i have all my teeth and i'm an old
dude
i got all my teeth with nothing wrong
with them
i don't have all the podcast doctors and
i say this all the time all the podcast
doctors now they got all veneers and
just look anybody can do what they want
i don't care it's fine they got all
veneers
they get all implants
they literally have all their teeth done
they sit there and they spend thousands
i know one podcast doctor tens of
thousands of dollars on dental work to
make them look nice and great
and everybody looks at it and doesn't
even question it
they all wear contacts too all wear
contacts their eyes were shot back when
they were in their 20s and they all have
contact lenses everybody thinks and they
all have filler now all the podcast
doctors all have filler
like the male podcast doctors all have
filler in their lips
it's unbelievable and they got filler in
their face and they try to get the
masculinity filler filler where they're
getting injections and they all get
botox now
it's like yeah i don't want to do any of
that so you think i'm ugly fine whatever
but my information will help you it's
critical information so let's go into it
a little bit we talked about tattoos
if you guys just came on here saw a
bunch of people come on tick tock
right we're doing the heavy metal detox
cleanse challenge we're day one right
here you guys we're day one you need the
cleanse to heal book amazon.com 51 off
16 it's a medical textbook the cleanse
is in here you guys
and
right we're going to need the other
things too so you're going gonna need
supplies you're gonna need the spirulina
and the barley grass cheese powder you
guys because we're gonna make the
smoothie in a little while so that's the
spirulina that's the barley grass juice
powder that's the vimergy visa victor i
m e r g dot com i'm not sponsored i'm
not sponsored by these guys there's no
multi-level marketing there's no pyramid
crap i'm not sponsored amazing credible
stuff right here
so
yeah yang says oh gosh me too my teeth
got white
drinking celery doing the heavy metal
detox incredible let's make some celery
juice now
and then we're going to talk about
metals a little bit more how metals get
into our brain
we'll bring the dummy out too as well
right
so let's make some celery juice really
quick we'll knock some out
so i'm excited you guys
make it a little celery juice right here
celery juice is part of the class
gina manzo thank you aw for all your
free information i've been healing a lot
of symptoms thyroid vertigo whoa vertigo
burning feet
burning feet that's an annoying one
right there
burning feet stopped
and tumor in my neck
whoa
i've been following you for four years
now and i am a vegan incredible
i want to let everybody know there's
vegans
here
there's plant-based people here
there's plant-based vegan people here
there's vegetarians here
there's animal protein lovers here
right there's macrobiotic people here
there's
mediterranean people here that just do
they do fish but they do everything
medical medium
it's all about all walks of life here
because it's about the tools to heal
it's why you'll notice going all the way
back medical medium never went against
animal protein because because
it wasn't the problem it's not like it's
the problem dairy is the there is a
problem dairy products
but yeah vegan is great i support
plant-based and vegan
magnus says my brain fog is long gone
medical meaning thanks for your
information and your work
and your works for me and my friends how
we follow your advice never felt better
you are super
you're super too
you truly are
so what i'm doing is i'm making a little
celery juice it's part of the heavy
metal detox cleanse we're day one we're
on the cleanse challenge you guys i'm
excited today
and just to get the point across you
don't have to remove your tattoos
if you got tattoos what it is is you're
capturing metals from your tattoos that
are traveling through your bloodstream
every day
and you're capturing those so they don't
get stuck inside
your brain and inside your liver you
guys that's important to know right
there
so make it a little celery juice you can
do 16 ounces listen you can do eight
ounces you guys if you're sensitive
you can do just a little bit of celery
juice a little bit of lemon water and
you can do a little bit of the heavy
metal detox movie you can do four ounces
if you want
if you want you can do four ounces
right
and then you can work yourself up
work way up over time six ounces eight
ounces 10 ounces
you can head there
so the cleanse is you drink 16 to 32
ounces of lemon water first thing in the
morning give it 15 to 30 minutes and
then you drink 16 to 32 ounces of celery
juice
give it 15 to 30 minutes you know head
into your smoothie which we're going to
talk about a little bit eat a couple of
apples later on in the morning if you
feel up to it
someone just asked what's wrong with oil
pulling
so check out my newsletter if you guys
can sign up to the newsletter
all right
i did a little oil pulling talk on my
newsletter
sign up to my newsletter video where my
videos get your free with like a free
video
like exclusive free video every sunday
that's what i'm doing right now on my
newsletter so if you sign up you'll see
the newsletter link in the description
all right we got plenty of celery juice
right here we got plenty of celery juice
you guys i'm doing exclusive videos on
snapchat which is really cool that i'm
not doing anywhere else i'm doing
exclusive videos on tick tock i'm pumped
up about
so i posted a snapchat
exclusive video
about the gallbladder check it out when
you guys get a chance
all right
so we're making some celery juice right
now 16 to 32 ounces of celery juice
you want to strain your celery juice i
always say that no matter what kind of
juicer you have you want to strain it
let's try to make some room back here
so you want to strain it
[Music]
that's the key
so
there we go
after all these years
all right you got 16 and 32 ounces of
celery juice right there
okay
wondering about the blender
you can make celery juice with a blender
if you want if you don't have a juicer
make it make it with a blender but you
got to squeeze it through a cheesecloth
or a nut milk bag
and that's okay if a blender's all you
got throw celery in the blender but
don't add water
don't add water so if you do the celery
juice in your blender don't add water
you still got to strain it squeeze it
through a nut milk bag you don't want a
celery smoothie it's not going to work
where it's just a celery smoothie right
you don't want to do that
all right so that's your celery juice
right there first thing in the morning
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water right
there i showed you guys
boom then we move on to 16 to 32 ounces
of celery juice right there let's make
the heavy metal detox smoothie now
[Music]
let's do that
let's make some room
[Music]
so it's
smoothie time right now
so i'm going to bring this i'm going to
keep this look this right here i'm going
to bring this over
all right
so the heavy metal detox smoothie all
right
okay we got the wild blueberries right
there
now it's about do you have all five
ingredients do you just have three
ingredients
try to get all five if you're gonna do
the heavy metal detox cleanse and
smoothie if you can't get all five and
you got four we do four if you've got
three we do three
okay so if you only have cilantro and
spirulina and dulse then that's your
three okay the goal is though for
maximum pull maximum pull
right
we want five if we can for maximum pull
if we we want five if we can right
so let's go so we're gonna take
some wild blueberries right here
right
i'm gonna do about two cups
in here it doesn't have to be perfect if
you want to do less you can do a little
less if you want to do more you do a
little bit more
right
there we go
i got a wild blueberries in there
i'm gonna put some cilantro in here
okay
about a cup of cilantro i like to put a
lot more always that's just how i am
with cilantro so i'm going to break it
up here
i'm going to put
i don't know over a cup in here
there you go
this is i love this smoothie because i
not only love the way it tastes but i
love what it's doing for me
and i love what it's doing for you guys
two bananas
[Music]
let's throw in two bananas
we got that going on
right
christina says in the beginning i hate
the taste of celery juice and heavy
metal detox movie
but now i love it
awesome
just glad you don't hate me
wait who knows you might like the
smoothie and be like i don't like him
all right thank you though thank you for
doing the smoothie thank you for taking
care of yourself so we got the bananas
in here we got the wild blueberries
power of compassion how much juice
if you don't have frozen wild
blueberries
two to four ounces if you want i'm gonna
add some in anyway because i usually do
in mine
if you don't have the frozen wild
blueberries but you've got the juice
it's the wyman's one right here you guys
know i work with these guys though so i
do work with these guys
that's the wyman's one
right and you can get it at shop
s-h-o-p
dot wyman's
w-y-m-a-n-s dot com
right
so
i buy it by the case
it's what i do
and you can do two it's really really
intense stuff i mean it's incredible
and you can do two to four ounces i'm
just going to drop a couple ounces in
here because i have the wild blueberries
in there there we go
it's in there
now i'm going to put some spirulina in
here i'll put some barley grass cheese
powder first
you have to have the barley grass cheese
powder
not the barley grass a mistake made all
the time
right so i'm gonna put a teaspoon of
that in there
just gonna crank some in
right that's the vimergy
these invictor i am as in mary ergy
best supplement company hands down in my
opinion out there
with what they do it's just it's
unmatched they got a new msm they came
out
with which is incredible
they got the best cat's claw they got
the best licorice out there to date they
got the best lemon balm for all kinds of
anxiety disorders and everything else
i'm not sponsored by vimergy i'm not the
owner of the company i'm not sponsored
and i'm not an ambassador just letting
you know but the stuff is that
incredible it's the purest there's
nothing like it out there
this is the spirulina right here so i'm
showing you guys the spirit lena this
stuff is like incredible so i'm going to
give you a little window into them to
show you
this is the best spirulina there is
hands down
i used to promote other spirulina
companies in the past
okay i don't anymore
because this stuff doesn't compare to
this one
right doesn't compare to this one so i'm
just going to tell you right now and
but this is the best best one on the
market
the ones the ones i used to support in
the past
their quality
doesn't touch this but it's not just
that one of the companies i used to
recommend all the time in the past
something went down
in in their product and they never
wanted to talk to me about it and ever
since then i would never even recommend
them
chris has said i was using vimergy
products in my heavy metal detox
smoothie and saw incredible results in
such a short period of time when i ran
out of energy i had to go to cheap
brands and the rate of healing is
significant uh significantly slower and
and that's on facebook charissa chrisa
i i have heard that and watched that
over the years it see what people say is
you always recommend vimera gaw
i get you're not sponsored but you
always recommend vimergy give the other
supplement companies a chance
but what happened was vimergy made the
product so good all the products
that what happened was people healed
faster
and
like healed faster but not just healed
faster healed things that i didn't see
heal with the other products so it's
like it's like so what do you do you
give the other supplement companies that
are lower quality a chance
or do you promote
something
and recommend something that you know
heals somebody faster that's the
predicament i got in
it's like so you see me always like it's
always like vim rajiv energy
but if it if you heal faster from what
i've seen from what you said and from
what i've seen everywhere including
family and friends
that i know
and they heal quicker
and then they when they don't use energy
they don't heal as fast or heal at all
and when i see that it's like what do
you do you have to just be like you know
what you work for the light
hands down you just have to let people
know what's the best stuff
so anyway
that's the spirulina right there
i mean for neurological problems
that's a that's a huge one right there
for for helping people neurological
problems catherine elizabeth love wild
blueberries juice i buy it by the case
also yeah buy buy the case
i buy buy the case and and i'm actually
working with them and i buy it by the
case because i want to support them to
make sure this never goes away
i gave for christmas gifts last year so
right i bought a bunch and gave them out
for christmas too last year that's
amazing
it's amazing
i just took a swig off the bottle hope
you guys don't mind
ryan what's your thoughts on using the
metal spoon on a scoop
okay
good question
that's a metal strainer
okay
that's a metal knife
i don't have to worry
because whatever steel
comes off of these babies
i'm crushing
that's that's how it works
okay
will i
jump into a pile of mercury molted
mercury no
will i go get a fluoride treatment no
no
because i'll still need this to get the
fluoride out and anything else
right
you still have to live on planet earth
and if you want to go to my amazon live
shows afterwards
right
if you want to go to my amazon live
shows if you check out my amazon live um
platform right
i got the ceramic spoons but you should
check out the amazon live show so you
can see which ones and you'll see the
links and all that
but i'm not afraid of a metal spoon
because i'm crushing it this will grab
whatever came off of this times 10
times 10. this will go
to the brain
and grab stuff deep from out of the
brain
never mind whatever's happening with the
spoon or what's ever happening with this
knife i use what's ever happening with
the strainer i'm using
so that's why
all right what else am i missing here
orange
missing in orange oh some dolls
let's get some dolls in here so what i
do with the dolls is this i got this one
right here i'll show you guys close up
on this too
it's got two dolls options right what
you're going to see is you're going to
see the whole leaf form right there
right
so the whole leaf
[Music]
let's not break it and then we got the
atlantic dulce
dropper right that's the vimergy
product which is incredible right there
so i'm dropping two of those in there
you can drop one in there you can do two
i just do two
there
okay
and you can use the whole form as well
if you want you can use one or the other
i mean you know i'll throw that in there
too but that's incredible product right
there
let's pop an orange in here
cut open this orange
right there
i'm going to squeeze some orange
so yeah
we're making heavy metal detox movie
this is day one of the heavy metal detox
cleanse challenge you guys we're live on
tick tock we're live on rumble we're
live on youtube we're live on facebook
we're live on telegram
right we're even live on getter
even live on getter
so i'm squeezing this in right here
okay so i got bananas in here i got
cilantro you saw spirulina you saw
barley grass juice powder right you saw
the wild blueberries the frozen
blueberries and i put the juice in there
too
that juice was really good by the way
really good
when you're talking about antioxidants
you're talking about antioxidants okay
you're talking about that right there
you're talking about that
that color right there that's straight
anthocyanin right
so what you're looking at with that
juice is straight anthocyanin right
there
that's what you're looking at
so
i'm going to
pop this on here give it a
swirl all right
let's go
stir it up
i love this blender nice and quiet
does the celery take out the metal as
well
christine the celery juice
neutralizes and loosens up metal i'm
going to talk about that in a second too
that's important as well you guys
[Music]
penny ryan any reason why not to put the
whole orange in there
i just blend the whole thing right you
can play the whole arc you can put the
whole orange
that's fine
you can definitely do that you guys
don't tick duck you can do that you can
play
that's done right there
[Music]
you know sickness really
as you guys know is just terrible having
severe brain fog adhd
having anxiety having severe depression
depersonalization getting a diagnosis
like ocd or having ocd have crippling
ocd people have crippling ocd out there
right
having any kind of condition like that
eczema psoriasis having terrible eczema
psoriasis
all of that
when we can do something about it and we
can get metals out of our body and out
of our brain and out of our liver
we really move forward
you know what i've learned all these
years
since i was a child
i thought
that if you had answers to why someone
was sick
and you had things that really did work
i thought the world would just be like
oh my god
this is unbelievable
chronically ill people healing people
getting out of wheelchairs people with
neurological conditions healing people
with the worst neurological life getting
their lives back
but no one cares
no one cares
it's unbelievable
no one cares no one cares if celery
juice has changed and shaped the lives
of so many people around the world no
one cares if children are talking again
that couldn't talk before
when they did until they did the heavy
metal detox smoothie no one cares
like industries don't care media doesn't
care
it's actually sick
it's actually sick when i was young when
i was eight ten years old eleven years
old i thought that oh my gosh surely
surely they would care
when people are getting better that
couldn't get better any other way
surely they would care and
the media doesn't care that the
industries don't care it's actually
incredible when you see it all and then
that's when you know darkness really
does exist
layla
are these products all on amazon go to
medicalmedium.com to the directory
that's the best place so if you go to
medicalmedium.com you'll see a directory
and you'll see the spirulina you'll see
the barley grass now i'm not sponsored
by these guys but you'll see
you'll see this right there you'll see
this here the dulce liquid you'll see on
the directory you'll see that as well so
you'll see the stuff that you need this
is the heavy metal detox smoothie right
there this is day one of the heavy metal
detox cleanse right there here's all the
different products we're talking about
that we need here's the cilantro right
over here we got our bananas we've got
some so let's go into the apples next so
you have your smoothie now you're on to
apples
now i recommend drinking a little bit
more water if you'd like or some coconut
water is fine too or some regular water
you can drink you can even have another
lemon water later on
in the morning you could have another
one late you can have another one later
on in the day i recommend having an
apple that morning if you can if you
can't have an apple in the morning have
it right in the afternoon have two
apples really at best that would be
incredible two apples sometime during
the day whether it's late morning or
moving on to the day right
that's what i would do but try to keep
this
in right try to keep this feather in
your cap keep the fats out that morning
you're doing the cleanse
you can still do fats in the morning if
you want to do the heavy metal detox
smoothie on a regular basis of upkeep
and getting the metals out and helping
yourself get better but keep the fats
out during the cleanse this is day one
of the heavy metal detox cleanse
does everybody have the cleanse to heal
book critical book for
this the heavy metal detox plans is in
here amazon.com
you can find it 51 off or get it free at
the library for even better results
right you can check out cleanse the heel
and you'll see the troublemaker foods i
talk about troublemaker foods stay away
from them if you can bring in some of
the recipes in this book and do the
heavy metal detox cleanse and do it a
little longer than two days and
look out
look out some serious healing going on
you guys we're gonna be heading off to
instagram live
this has been incredible
you guys on tick tock i'm gonna turn you
guys back on we're gonna be on instagram
live and telegram
so we're gonna be on telegram too and
what i'm gonna do is i think i'm gonna
i'm gonna talk about this guy more i'm
gonna talk about the neurological system
i'm going to talk about brain
inflammation brain stem inflammation i
think i'll go talk about that on ig
because i didn't get a chance to cover
that we're talking about other things
here so i'm going to talk about the
brain a little bit more maybe i'll talk
about some things i didn't talk about
with tattoos that i forgot to mention
i'm going to talk about other things too
like neurological symptoms we get from
toxic heavy metals like heart
palpitations
and i don't know we might talk about
some other stuff too so we're going
there in a little while
and you guys if you get a chance
oh by the way just don't spill this
juice
on anything
you will not have you will have a blue
carpet you will have a blue
sofa you will have a blue chair you will
have a blue shirt keep that in mind when
you're using
when you're using a wild blueberry juice
make sure you have a book make sure you
have the stuff you need i'm going to see
you over on ig pretty soon
i love you