even if someone seems like the most
confident person their confidence is
over the top even if someone's ego is
just way up here they're still
soul-searching is there an end to the
soul searching and how many lifetimes
are we soul-searching people don't
realize it but we take all of our
experiences all of our knowledge we take
it with us when we leave here because
the physical brain isn't the only place
that harnesses information the neurons
and the glial cells isn't the only place
that's harboring information the soul is
harboring but experiences and
information our soul that resides here
is harboring information from every
single lifetime I hope that no one's
offended if I even say that because
someone might say no there's only one
lifetime that's it I pose a question to
you with tremendous respect and no
judgment if someone believes it's only a
one-time thing we're here we're gone we
have no soul everybody has their right
to believe in anything they believe in
but keep in mind we're in the present
time right now how is it possible we're
all here on the front line think about
that for a minute how is it possible
that we are on the front line of time
itself right now think about it every
minute that clicks forward every second
that clicks forward is the front line we
are on the front line right now you're
not in the past right now 500 years ago
you're not in the future 500 years from
now you're on the brink The Edge you're
on the front line pushing forward into
the future second by second by second by
second well how did you manage to end up
here after billions of years and
katrillions of people that have passed
and gone their life they died they're
gone centuries and centuries of people
thousands of years of civilizations how
is it possible with all that you think
we were just chosen to be on the front
line right now
at the very second that's pushing
forward into time out of all the
trillions of people the billions and
billions of people and the centuries and
the thousands of years Civilizations for
some reason were just picked to be on
the front line of time aren't we special
no it's because we came around again
which means we've most likely been here
before and before and before our soul
carries information you might not be
able to tap into it and tap into your
soul and the information that you've
taken over from Lifetime to lifetime
I've learned all this from Spirit of
compassion by the way you may not be
privy to the information that's passed
on over and over and over again meaning
into boom another body your soul you
live a life you get all these
experiences in for information you die
your soul contains that spiritual
information all that knowledge and you
may not be able to tap into it that you
think we're all here by chance just by
chance with all those people who have
been on this plan it alone never mind
how many people have been on other
planets you think
we've just suddenly have all just we're
here right now by a fluke registration
is open for the collecting Stones
meditation Journey it's going to be a
part of your soul in such a good way
it's gonna be so cleansing and so
healing and by the way it's free