foreign
we're talking about how to protect your
brain
which I think is a very important thing
when you think about it because we live
in a world where
no one really cares about protecting
people's brains well you know we don't
want to get hit in the head
so there's always that right
football players wear helmets
right
boxers wear gloves even though you could
mess up somebody really bad the boxing
arena either way
the point is is protecting your brain
it's more than that it's more than just
our head getting clobbered on a ski
slope because of an accident or anything
else
I'm talking about protecting our brain
in so many other ways
you guys we're also talking about the
life last a little bit because I just
want to give you the forewarning right
now
tomorrow 12 o'clock Eastern nine o'clock
Pacific you're gonna get the invite
so you're going to get the link to sign
up to the light blast
there's only going to be 20 000 people
allowed
at this light blast event
the only way to receive that invite or
that link
is to be signed up to the medical medium
newsletter
so I want you to know that's how it
works
so that's tomorrow so sign up to the
medical medium newsletter now so you can
be there alive
for that light blast but you're going to
get the invite tomorrow and only 20 000
people are going to be allowed to sign
up for this light blast event
now an important question because people
are asking that how much is it going to
cost how much is it going to cost it's
free it's free
the question is how much is it going to
cost for me
and that's the question
I have a team of people working I have
to pay them it's costing thousands of
dollars
I have to get the whole system set up
for it it's a major Endeavor it's a
major project it's going to cost me a
lot of money I still don't even know
that's how much it costs it's free
for everybody else that that's attending
this light blast
so I want to make that clear
um it's going to cost me tens of
thousands actually
so but the thing is it's just like all
medical meme information it's free get
the book of the library
it's like all medical the podcast it's
another thing it's free and that's what
we do it's a mission that I have in my
heart and soul
it's critical that I can do as much free
as possible
whatever I can in this lifetime
the light blast will not be tomorrow
I just want to make that clear the light
blast
will be another time it's the
registration is tomorrow
so you have to be on the medical medium
newsletter you have to sign up for the
medical name newsletter so you can
receive the invite
keep that in mind the invite is tomorrow
and I'm only going to allow 20 000
people because that's all our system can
actually hold that we're building and
doing right now the system that's
costing thousands of dollars for me to
get done so I can do this lifeblast for
free
now
I'm not trying to throw
like a guilt thing about it's costing me
a lot of money that's not it at all it's
because people are expecting to pay
and I want them to know they don't have
to pay it's free so I want them to know
that that's important but yeah it's not
free for me of course I mean that's just
the way it works but
anyway so there's all kinds of questions
coming through
what is the light blast so that's a
question a meditation
please let me know so if you've learned
okay
if you've been following medical medium
for years you'll know that during Live
Events
I would do a light blast
now the light isn't coming from me
on the messenger I'm guiding it I'm
helping the process the light comes from
Spirit of compassion so when we would do
lectures where there would be thousands
of people in the audience
we would actually Spirit of compassion
and I do a light Blast for everybody so
everybody's sitting down in the audience
or standing up in the audience would
receive this light
and it would hit the top of their head
and come down from above so if you have
a question about what is the light blast
now it is a it is a tool from above that
I have been taught to be a part of since
I was a child
going all the way back as a child
if I would come across a wounded
creature
like a turtle that got hit on the side
of the road
or an animal that was injured or a
grasshopper with a broken leg when I was
a child Spirit of compassion taught me
how to do this light blast
and that and the how Spirit of
compassion would send the light down on
the grasshopper on the injured turtle
I'm the injured creature and so forth
or on the person when I got a little
older and I was working on people
one-on-one
in my office
many many years ago
I would even I swear to compassion do
the light blast
on specific people in the office
for what was ailing them and and hurting
them emotionally mentally spiritually
and physically and so that late last
would happen in the office now
I would do it also at lectures
throughout the years too that was the
other thing
so and some of you guys might have been
around long enough to attend a lecture
that I've done in 2013 or 2014 or 2010
or whatever and you might have been
there to one of these events where
Spirit of compassion sent the light down
during that event on top of thousands of
people
and then people have these profound
experiences because of this light
so that's the light blast now but I just
wanted to because I'm seeing more and
more people come on right now
the only way to actually be a part of
this light blast
is you have to sign up to the medical
medium newsletter the link is in the
profile link is in the description so
sign up to the medical medium newsletter
I'm saying this because here's what's
going to happen and here
here's the sad part A whole bunch of
people are going to miss it and they're
not going to be there and it breaks my
heart
because this is not like this easy thing
to do
it's going to take a lot of energy out
of me I'm going going to go blind during
the process so I don't know if you guys
know medical meme information
I don't know if you know medical medium
books right that's the uh I talk a
little bit about how things work
in the first book medical meaning right
an expanded New Edition
but so it's really intense but the sad
part and this is not a public event
very important to know
it will not be broadcasted on my normal
channels like I am now here on IG
like I I'm here on Dr nesbitt's you know
page on Tick Tock Dr Nesbit stick talk
like I'm here on YouTube
it's not going to be the normal
situation where it's that kind of thing
where you just kind of wall sign in and
anytime you want you see I'm live or
something and you come in you're like oh
great what is this delight glass you
talked about this it's not going to be
that at all it's not a public event it
will not be broadcasted on any of my
channels and there will not be a replay
this is going to be a live event in the
moment
Spirit of compassion is going to send
the light down on everybody who has
signed up
so this is important to know
so in my profile and in my my bio my uh
description there the link is there the
newsletter link is there but you have to
sign up to the medical medium newsletter
and then tomorrow at 12 o'clock Eastern
nine o'clock Pacific
you will be getting an invite in only 20
000 people are going to be
accept it into this live event
it's important to actually be on the
medical meme newsletter so you don't
miss other opportunities if I do another
live event and I may not do another one
I really don't know
I do know because because one of the
reasons why it's so costly because I
don't want to charge I don't want to
charge
and I know that there's a lot of people
in the spiritual movement there's a lot
of people out there and authors and
things and people and they charge for
everything everything doesn't matter
what it is and they do groups of people
and they charge for this and that all
that stuff and I get it
but this we're talking about the
chronically ill and I have made a vowel
in this lifetime to offer as much free
healing tools as I possibly can in my
power
for the chronically ill
and that's what medical medium's mission
is so if you want to know like what's
behind the mission like what is really
behind it is it putting out incredible
books so people can heal that way is it
what what is the mission the mission is
to offer
free information and free healing tools
the light blast is one of those healing
tools I don't want to charge for
and I don't know if it's going to be the
only one I do that um whatever next year
or whatever whatever year I don't know
what I do know now though that so if
you're saying so I'll sign up to the
next one if you're someone sign up to
this one is what I'm saying don't say oh
he'll probably do 10 more because that's
medical medium he'll do he does so many
things for everybody
sign up to this one
I don't know when the next one is going
to come if there is going to be a next
one I'm just being honest so
make sure you sign up to the medical
meme newsletter so you can get the
invite tomorrow 12 o'clock Eastern nine
o'clock Pacific so you can know when
and how to do it be there and all that
now this is going to be a live event
it's not going to be broadcasted on any
of the normal channels it's going to be
a private setting
if you're having trouble getting the
newslett getting on the newsletter check
your promotions and spam and junk
folders and junk mail in your desktop
sometimes Gmail hides the emails
a lot of the time actually they do
so keep that in mind right there this is
all important information now we're here
right now to talk about a couple
different things I want to talk about
swelling I want to talk about the
medical mean podcast the swelling
episode a little bit I want to talk
about how to protect your brain a little
bit too I got the books out here
little medical medium school going down
today
but I wanted to make sure you know this
now
medical medium podcast
uh there's a new episode I released it's
this it's about swelling right
lymphedema all of it and it's an
important episode it's really
enlightening a lot of powerful
information in there you'll be mind
blown when you hear it and since we're
talking about a couple things keep in
mind that my podcast
has no commercials or advertisers and
advertisements keep that in mind
so
it's I can actually make millions of
dollars in advertising on the medical
medium podcast at Apple podcast
I'm just letting you know
I refuse to do that
I don't wanna do that I want The Chronic
allele to have an experience when to
listen to the medical meeting podcast
free
of commercials and advertisers and
everything else
do you guys see the mission now do you
see the mission
that's been the mission
that's what it's about
and very important to know
I think Dr nesbitt's page is actually Dr
nesbit's thing is frozen there so we'll
take a look at that but anyway
so let's let's talk about um the medical
meme podcast for a couple of seconds
more it's a swelling episode which is
really important it's body swelling
fluid retention edema lymphedema tissue
expansion so what you'll hear on that
episode
is it's not just about when we get
bloated
it's not just about when we have weight
gain
and there's a lot of confusion with that
we're talking about tissue expansion
that's medical medium information just
so you know so it's not like oh I can
hear about swelling or bloating
somewhere else or let me go look online
and find something about oh 10 ways to
de-swell or whatever that's not what
we're talking about first of all medical
meme information does all that
so you can actually get rid of a lot of
people heal their bloating they heal
their sibo they heal all their different
problems they heal their HCL problems
and all that
but what this episode is and it's a
mind-blowing episode information from
Spirit to compassion of course it's all
original unique info is in that episode
that you're going to hear a medical meme
podcast at Apple podcast
is that
it's about tissue expansion
I talk about how everything enlarges in
us as we get older
we enlarge
we're not supposed to enlarge and then
people will pass that off as being
overweight now you can have weight
issues and be overweight and have tissue
expansion so you can still have tissue
expansion and be overweight
but what the health professionals do not
know and doctors and other health
professionals out there all kind
alternative health professionals
everybody what they don't know
is that there's an actual deep rooted
tissue expansion
and that's happening inside our body and
it's not doesn't even have to be linked
to inflammation you might be like oh
that's inflammation no it doesn't
doesn't actually equate to inflammation
it's real physical tissue expansion
occurring
and so when you listen to the medical
meme podcast
okay talking about lymphedema edema
tissue expansion all of it when you
listen to that
you're going to hear information that
nobody knows and it's mind-blowing it's
important to know this is why people
get bigger
even if they're not even overweight they
get bigger everything gets bigger
Everything grows on them as they get
older this is critical information that
is new and original from Spirit of
compassion about how the lymphatic
system and fluid actually works inside
the body and that's mind-blowing too so
what you're going to hear about
lymphatic information you don't hear
anywhere else is going to be in this
episode
so if you just came on here to see a
bunch of new people coming on right now
I'm talking right now about the medical
mean podcast a new episode I released
about tissue expansion swelling
lymphedema all of it
but what's really incredible is I talk
about the lymphatic system information
nobody knows about the lymphatic system
that when you hear it you'll go like it
makes so much sense Happy Lemon healing
says on IG right now the podcast was
amazing
incredible
I talk about how everything expands
joints connective tissue tendons
ligaments
your head
all of it such important information
says I learned a lot about swelling such
an important info explained beautifully
incredible
and then Anita says your podcasts are
super informative fun amazing and
encouraging incredible
so I I really hope you listen to the
medical name podcast at Apple Apple
podcast Sophie says should we prepare
for the light blast somehow
you don't have to prepare
I mean you can do look you can do a lot
it doesn't it's
the kind of thing where you don't of
course want to
be out of your head before it meaning in
a sense where you just rolled in off the
road you're
you know you just came from the store
you're putting away groceries while
you're trying to do the white while
you're trying to receive the light blast
you can do that if you want you can be
rolling right through the door putting
away groceries while it's happening and
you're listening you can do that what
I'm saying is preparing would be
probably just really basic stuff
it would be relaxing
sitting down and chilling
whatever getting your your lemon balm
getting your lemon balm out you know
like the lemon balm tea that I always do
now which is this way instead it's
taking the lemon balm and actually
putting it right in uh water like that
that's what I'm going to be doing you're
watching exactly what I'm gonna do
before it happens
laughs
santara's healing said that podcast is
mind-blowing brand new info you won't
find anywhere else thank you sundar's
healing and by the way appreciate all
your support as usual
um you're out there like a beacon of
light
um helping other people understand
medical medium information and the
journey you've been on and the journey
that others have been on so it's it's
really enlightening too the information
that she actually put out there
um
so anyway let's just do just a little
recap before we go into the Brain book
and talk about some really cool things
on how to protect your brain
I just wanted to announce the light
blast
I don't know if this is gonna be the
only one I do or I'm going to do many to
follow up you know that are going to
follow this light bless you don't want
to miss it get on the medical medium
newsletter
medicalmedium.com
by the way I'm enhancing medical
medium.com I'm putting tremendous
amounts of resources into medicalme.com
there's no paywalls
there's none of that no subscription
fees free information killer recipes
amazing amazing stuff at
medicalmedium.com but besides that sign
up to the medical medium newsletter
please at medicalme.com here's what's
going to happen I already feel this
I know what's coming
I know
that a whole bunch of people aren't
going to know about this medical medium
light blast
and they're not going to sign up in time
they're not going to know about it or
they're going to think I'm doing a bunch
of them
it's not a challenge where I do 10 days
in a row brain shot therapy challenge
it's a live event that's closed out it
has to be in a private setting
we have to do in a way that everybody
could be there live but there's only 20
000 people allowed
so please get into this light blast if
you can get signed up tomorrow at 12
o'clock Eastern 9 o'clock Pacific you
will be getting a notice
you will be getting an invite
that invite is the link
so you can get into this live light
blast now the live light blast won't be
tomorrow
but the only way to to know is you have
to sign up to Medical medium.com medical
medium newsletter get the invite
tomorrow 20
000 people will be allowed
if you don't know what the light blast
is because I see a bunch of people
coming on right now then please watch
this this replay after this live right
now so you can know what it is I talked
a little bit about it
podcast link is also in the bio and in
the description and you can listen to
the medical meeting podcast said Apple
podcast and Spotify on the swelling
episode that is mind-blowing don't miss
the swelling episode if you can
by the way just a reminder some hearing
it every minute
every minute I'm sick
I got mucus there's a flu and cold going
around
there's sea going around
like the whole bit it's what I'm hearing
out there every last second so just
realize okay
that there is a cold and flu tool kit
you can download for free
once again it wasn't free to make it or
design it and prepare it for you guys
and have it ready that cost me a ton of
money but it's free for you guys
so once again that's here I would
download it I would print it out like
like I did right there and I put a
staple right there and so there it is
keep that in mind too all right another
incredible free resource free free free
free
and that's what I love
okay so let's get into it a little bit
quick recap talk about the light blast
and how to sign up to make sure you're
there live light blasts tomorrow the
light blast tomorrow the email will be
going out at 12 o'clock Eastern nine
o'clock Pacific
so keep that in mind
all right
but you won't be getting the light blast
tomorrow you're signing up 20 000 people
will be all that's allowed into it it's
private it won't be on this platform
here or anything like that keep that in
mind too you guys I'm excited let's get
into it a little bit I'm reading out of
brain saver are you guys ready for a
little mm School
come on let's do it let's have some fun
doing it I mean how awesome is this
right
it's actually incredible information
from above nobody has
and if you don't know about medical
leave information but it has saved a lot
of lives
people who have been there done that
been through hell and back tried
everything you name it
and if you're somebody that's a quick
critic or a skeptic or something
or a hater when you do get sick down the
road and you realize that all the things
you're using aren't fixing you you can
come and get the information
and learn how to heal
even if you don't pull the knife out of
my back you leave the knife still stuck
in my back where you put it a long time
ago and then you got sick down the road
and you grabbed the information for free
but you still left the knife in my back
it's still here for you all right let's
talk about this a little bit this is
your protective Guide chapter 17.
page 187
so if you guys got the books right get
the brain saver book right there there's
two of them by the way protocols in this
one can I just say it's over 40 off
amazon.com us
how insane is that it's 26 or something
so check it out
so we're at page 187 right now
our brains and bodies have not betrayed
us
but that's what you guys are taught
you guys are taught even by alternative
medicine that's your brain and body
betrayed you that's what everybody's
taught
let's just be honest and let's just face
it
that's what we're taught all the time
it's not medicine that let us down it's
not anything else that let us down it's
you that let you down
that's you
it's your body it's faulty it's bad so
let's kind of be honest about the vibe
out there because that's the vibe out
there and alternative medicine and
conventional medicine that your brain
and body betrayed you that's what's set
out there in so many words
heck obviously too
by the way the cold and flu to answer a
question I just saw there the cold and
flu tool kit it's at medicalmedium.com
make sure you download it for free
very important right now
and guess what we are heading into some
serious cold and flu Seasons coming up
it ain't no joke so if you're somebody
that's like I don't have one now uh
better download it
because a storm is coming storm is a
coming
out there
that's called being prepared not about
creating fear
like living in like Bliss and denial
doesn't help it when you get whacked by
something later when you could have been
prepared and got yourself out of it
and can I just say one more thing anyway
you guys you guys if you're coming on
here please watch this replay if you can
I talked about the light blast a little
bit the free light blasts incredible
medical meme light blast sign up for the
medical medium newsletter if you just
came on here I'm seeing more and more
people come on check this out watch this
free play so you understand what you're
missing if you don't know because it's
going to be so many people that are
going to miss out on this like blast I
don't even know what to say and it it's
sad I actually start getting sad
because I know how it's going to go
that's the sad part it's like okay 20
000 people will be there
yes and we'll be able to do the light
blast and it's going to be incredible
it's going to be absolutely incredible
but there's gonna be a whole bunch of
people
that did not even know about it or
thought they didn't have to sign up
it's sad right
okay our brains and bodies have not
betrayed us they've they've been
betrayed by industrial chemicals and
other contaminants in our everyday lives
that have only accelerated in
development in recent years so just in
recent years the air fresheners have
gotten deadly
people don't realize this if you're
somebody who really is sensitive that
you have been sick already and
struggling and you're breathing in the
air fresheners that have been created by
the chemical Labs that are happening
today I can't even tell you how bad that
stuff is it is horrendous on our nervous
system on our central nervous system
it is
horrifying on our central nervous system
very important to know the air
fresheners and then they're making
detergents now that last extra long
oh you don't have to worry our detergent
even gets stronger when you touch your
garment when you touch your shirt then
you get a smell it all over again these
chemical concoctions are unreal and
we're under assault right now from these
chemical concoctions
the detergents the air fresheners the
scented candles you know what happened
with the whole thing
right a couple years ago scented candles
have always been out there poisoning
people but what I noticed is they
exploded on Instagram they exploded on
social media platforms scented candles
Galore exploded everybody was just
burning them because they were all felt
like they were stuck at home
right in the last couple years and
they're burning their scented candles
and what they're doing is they're
burning out their brain they don't know
it
they don't know it but they are
literally burning their scented candles
and taking years off their life for down
the road
years of quality living off their life
and they're burning all their scented
candles so our brains are under this
attack this assault
it's not our brains and bodies that have
betrayed us it is the industrial
chemicals and other contaminants in our
everyday lives that have only
accelerated the problem in the recent
years
what we're going to explore in this
chapter ahead in these chapters ahead
are the brain betrayers we're up against
every day the ones that challenge and
defy our immune systems like killing our
immune systems the one thing isn't oh
low immune system oh you need immune
system support oh immune system immune
system how about
we're killing our immune cells they die
they explode they die they can't handle
the load and that's what's happening too
is people are under siege their immune
systems are their white blood cells are
dying their lymphocytes are dying their
monocytes their neutrophones they're all
of it is dying in people and then the
bone marrow can't produce it enough and
then when you're sick what do you do you
go to the doctor and you get more blood
drawn and you weaken your immune system
more this is Advanced information only
in brain saver brain saver protocols
right here
guess what's on the menu today I know
many times we have all kinds of
different wild foods and fruits and
herbs all placed in the front of the
medical medium lives but on the menu
today is brain saver we have brain saver
and brain saver protocols they're very
delicious I hope you enjoy them
wait till you sink a fork into those you
will be
and you guys there's a lot of
information in here it's too much it's
incredible too much it's just absorbing
one day you can be reading these books
for years
Sophie said I just spent two weeks
with my dad he's a nutritionist and he
thinks that weight gain is only due to
excess calories and lack of exercise he
thinks I eat too much
that is a common mistake
made by so many people nutritionists and
RDS
right that registered dietitians I love
when registered dietitians say uh you
shouldn't drink celery juice celery
juice is not good for you offers nothing
because science never whatever science
doesn't know I mean science hasn't done
a study on celery juice yet so how is in
a registered dietitian even able to say
anything about celery juice when science
has even done a study that's a whole
other story but it's really a joke when
you think about all of it
all right
let's go into it
the ones that take up residence in our
brain tissue the ones that contaminate
our neurons and neurotransmitters so
we're talking about is brain betrayers
the ones that destroy our immune system
and blow it up and kill it
the brain betrayers that get into our
neurons and absolutely short-circuit and
Destroy neurons that actually kill
neurons
rainbow traders that get into our
central nervous system as well just
incredible information
if he says after two weeks of taking the
brain shots for nerve shifter and Trauma
shock loss stabilizer incredible I am
proud to finally be free of my addiction
to psychedelics like mushrooms in
ayahuasca
thank you mm
that made my day to be free from the
chains of drugs
to be not a slave to drugs
oh my God and don't be telling me
ayahuas is not a drug
I'm not judging anybody for being on it
I'm just saying it actually is the point
is is you're free from it
that is worth every Blood Sweat and
Tears that went into these books getting
information from SOC making sure you
have those brain shot therapies so you
can be free of Ayahuasca I have heard
stories from moms and dads about their
teenagers getting their brains blown out
from Ayahuasca and some psychedelic
mushrooms where the kids just sit in
their rooms and they're so depressed
they can't even formulate words because
of an ayahuasca ceremony done by us you
know whatever by a really carefully done
by carefully by a shaman or something
the point is and no no offense on
anything I'm not saying Shaman's this
whatever I'm just saying that I have
seen over and over again moms and dads
complaining over Ayahuasca damage on
their 16 year old 17 year olds 18 year
olds you name it and no one talks about
it
all I know is that's amazing
gotta read the psychedelics you've got
to read the micro dosing chapter inside
brain saver
if you want to make a judgment call on
me now and say he's a bad guy
he doesn't understand it we micro dose
stuff we carefully do it if you're one
of those people I totally respect that
that's all good please read brain saver
read the micro dose chapter it will blow
your mind in a healthy way in a healthy
way
seriously
all right
we're having a lot of fun today
you guys just got on here sign up to the
medical medium newsletter because you
don't want to miss the light blast
please don't miss the light blast
even though we're only taking in 20 000
people
sign up today sign up today so that you
don't miss out
these brain betrayers can also defy our
brains from afar as in the case with
viruses that take up Residence at cider
liver so what that means is a virus can
take inside residents inside your liver
release their neurotoxin the neurotoxin
go whoop up to your brain and get to
there and then we got brain fog and then
we don't feel good and then we don't you
know and then including balance issues
we feel like we're on a boat we feel
like we're rocking we feel like we got
the vertigo we feel like all of that
because those neurotoxins are shooting
out of the liver and getting to our
central nervous system our vagus nerves
and making us dizzy and feeling
imbalanced and all that brain betrayers
cause all this
you can't get that information anywhere
by the way like every second it's like
boom like boom boom boom
we're talking about the brain betrayers
that whether from near or far scatter
our brains
you know anybody that's scatterbrained
fog our brains do you know anybody with
brain fog they got a foggy brain inflame
our brains
how many people go into the doctor's
office neurologist's office and
everything and the doctor doesn't even
know their brains are inflamed they have
no idea there's inflammation of the
brain it's so mild it's so discreet but
it's there
undermine our brains yes these brain
betrayers these toxic chemicals and
everything else can undermine your brain
disrupt your brain fatigue our brains
any fatigue going on neurological
fatigue that's a medical medium phrase
that's a medical medium understanding
and a medical medium
um definition is neurological fatigue
see before that definition doctors of
all kinds both alternative conventional
signs of research did not know that
fatigue was actually neurological they
thought you were tired and they thought
you were faking it in the 1950s and 60s
and 70s and 80s and 90s and 2000s I hear
it today people are told women are told
that they're faking their fatigue
because they can't see anything on an
MRI
but there's something called
neurological fatigue meaning it's an mm
term
pollute our brains yeah we pollute our
brains scramble our brains I know a lot
of people they're like scrambled eggs in
the brain it's like all scrambled in
there everything's scrambled the
information that comes out information
that goes in
distract our brains burn out our brains
can't tell you how many people have a
burnt out brain they're just burnt out
heat up our brains Rob our brains scar
our brains did you know you could have
scar tissue in the brain developing from
injuries from brain betrayers that no
one understands real physical injuries
inside the brain that science and
research has no idea about
drain our brains you guys if you just
rolled in this is really Advanced
information I'm reading out of brain
saver get the book amazon.com 40 off us
do not miss out on these books if you
don't have the 26 or whatever it is the
Amazon's charging for
go to the library get it for free
it doesn't matter at this point they
lowered the price so much it's not going
to help me either way go to the library
get it for free I want you to have it
for free addict your brains how many
people's brains are are addicts or
addictions that are happening in their
life their addicted brain I have a whole
chapter on this
shrink our brains did you know your
brain can shrink did you know in
atrophies
do you know how many people walk around
with a shrunken brain doesn't matter how
much protein they're getting in their
diet doesn't matter how much protein
they got going on they can talk protein
all day long their brain is shrinking
it's atrophying that's what's happening
they can be like protein protein protein
and their brain is for is still
shrinking
of this one age our brains oh there's so
many aging anti-aging experts out there
talking about telomeres or whatever else
and so many anti-aging experts
talking about collagen to stop your
brain from aging good luck
green tea yeah okay
what about all those people that are
bedridden so sick came from hell and
back green tea did not get them out of
bed
greens he did not save their lives green
tea did not get rid of their tingles and
numbness aches and pains jaw pain back
pain they're burning tongue burning skin
rashing eczema psoriasis their vitiligo
green tea didn't get rid of that
all right
and even rot our brains a reading out of
here your productive guide page 187 your
protective guide right here in my hand
the chapters to come are not meant to
make you fear life here on planet Earth
we can't avoid everything that isn't
great for our brains and our life we
have to live in this world I understand
that we do have to live in this world
there's no question
these chapters also aren't here so you
can accept everything listed and move on
with life ignoring these brain
portrayers as if they don't exist
we can make life in this world better by
learning to stay away from even a
handful of these brain portrayers in
here so what I'm saying is you don't
have to change your whole life in one
minute
but you can be aware of some of these
and the differences that can happen is
powerful
all right
Heidi Floyd The Heavy Metal detox
changed my life no one ever talks about
that except for you brought in celery
juice supplements no more chronic
sinusitis keep on doing what you're
doing so Heidi chronic sinusitis so my
guess
would be or my estimate would even be
you went to a lot of doctors
you went to a lot of ears nose and
throats doctors right you went to a lot
of different practitioners and probably
Healers
and somewhere along the way you found
medical medium
whether it was an angel that led you
there
or a spiritual Source or a magical force
or anything right or God
or the or Heaven above whatever it is
something LED you to the medical medium
information
and it could have been that person
that was at the store when you were
getting stuff you needed it could have
been anything but you found the
information and now your chronic side
you say this is gone and you learned how
to use the heavy metal detox
you learned how to use these
life-changing life-saving tools I just
want to say just I'm proud of you
every little bit counts when it comes to
avoiding or decreasing the saturation of
your brain with these contaminants you
guys every little bit counts
every little bit you can get counts
mm info is about customizing so you can
go further and further and further with
your healing process and learn that
every little bit does count and ready
and learn that all the details matter
every little bit counts when it comes to
avoiding or decreasing the saturation of
your brain with these contaminants you
may be able to easily avoid the ones you
never realized until now
were the most detrimental
you may be able to say I'm not gonna
like the scented candle anymore because
it's doing some bad stuff I can go into
detail sometime I got a podcast episode
about it but you can like get rid of
things in your life that are the most
obvious and the most important in the
moment there's so many
or you may be someone that looks at the
category of brain betrayers which is in
this book Brain betrayers means bad crap
I'm just just straight out let's just
put it in a nutshell brain betrayers
means your freaking brain was betrayed
by bad crap created by the industries
and I'm reading about that in this book
right now
for example the domestic Invasion brain
betrayers is a category called domestic
invasion
foreign
ways to replace or cut them out what's a
domestic invader
let me give you a little window into it
it's that plug-in air freshener that
you've got to unplug out of the wall
and you gotta throw out
Gotta Throw It Out
sometimes we can't stop ourselves from
being exposed to brain betrayers it's
true we can't stop it
but we can sure clean some of it up and
then do some healing around it
viruses especially we can still take
steps to lessen exposure and kill off
those viruses with medical medium
information to get better
when we do get exposed we can do plenty
About It by strengthening our immune
system removing viral fuel from our body
and staying hydrated
rather than
being here to scare you the chapters
ahead are your protective guide
I heard it for years oh he's just a fear
Monger okay how many people got out of
their wheelchairs because of medical
game information and you know what they
were told a lot of bad stuff
not from mm info but from the medical
establishment from the alternative
establishment
from other sources
they were told they would never walk
again
you want to talk about fear-mongering
chapters are they're here to protect you
not just for your brain or even your
body it's a guide to a better life the
information in these books are a guide
to a better life but without the
if you guys been around you guys tried
this tried that done this done that you
guys know about the out there
in the cult
you know what a cult is a cult is when
everything is all the same
they all talk the same they all do the
same in the alternative industry
every single aspect of the alternative
industry is all blended into one big
seed confusion because it's one giant
big cult that still wants you to eat
your chocolate
the keto people tell you eat the
chocolate the vegan people tell you to
eat the chocolate you'll see how big the
cult is
right Chinese medicine doctors should
tell you to eat the chocolate the cult
is huge
I'm not saying they're bad people I'm
just saying it's one big cult and
they're all in it together
one massive cult
and the brainwashing occurs do you know
what it takes to de-brainwash out of
that cult and Define answers and to
learn why people are sick it's
unbelievable you guys Holly B says I
agree
you guys couldn't believe
Saint Sue says raise your hand if mm
saved your life mm information which is
Serena compassion saved your life
what you'll find
is that here you'll find the truth about
why you're sick
that's not a cult that's finding the
truth of why you got sick answers you
couldn't find anywhere else and then you
find the answers and what to do and when
you end up doing those answers you're
like wait a minute I'm breaking out of
the cult status out there in the world
the alternative cult status
and then you find the depth and the
details in here but you don't find the
depth and details out there you find
just cultism out there here it's like
you find the depth in the details
foreign
and you know what you find in the Colts
out there nothing's for free man
you pay for it
not you guys
man there are the out there that
do it the point is it's like what
happens is
gotta understand something that in the
Colts out there they make everybody pay
pay and pay
and that's the attitude they have
they have the attitude is like no just
make them pay
and that's the attitude that's what it
is
I know
because I know the people out there
I know of them they don't like medical
medium information
they want everybody to pay pay for
everything doesn't matter what it is and
they try to learn in they make you pay
pay of course is subscriptions
description more subscription fees more
of this more that you just pay you pay
you pay that's how it is and that's how
they that's how they feel about their
people not everybody but that's how they
feel about their people
they're just like no way you're not
escaping that
no way sucker you're not escaping that
no way
that's how they do it
meanwhile they're not consistent either
they change they morph they shape-shift
into something else and then they're
shape-shifting to something else they're
all anti-fruit now they let you eat a
little fruit they were all this now they
let you do that in other words all
changing because they're making mistakes
and they're trying to learn along the
way on your dime and they're trying to
learn all the way they're along the way
on your pain and your suffering
nothing's consistent medical medium
information was consistent from the
start all the way back it was still
consistent it doesn't contradict itself
and it stays like that they change their
writings they change their books they
change their courses they change their
Direction two years later they change
something else they say oh it's this now
that's causing a problem or it's this
and it keeps on going and that's how
it's done out there and that's the Cults
that's what it is right there
and their attitude is exactly like that
they can't we don't care suckers you pay
we don't care you pay that's
their attitude and that's what they do
because I know and I know many of them
out there and how it works
what you will find is medical medium is
consistent only grows
with new information and it builds upon
itself where it's just more unknown
never before information more details in
depth and it never could contradicts
itself that's how it works but if and
I'm under the microscope if they were
under the microscope oh my God every
book's different everything about it's
different every belief system they take
in is different every podcast they do is
different and then when you look at it
all
it's all the same thing everybody's
doing out there because it's one big
coal and here's how you know it is when
you get too sick
game over because they don't have the
answers
you get too sick game over
that's how it works out there
so
the thing about mm is just like when I
just read in this one little paragraph
there's so many paragraphs in here to
read
rather than being here to scare you the
chapters ahead are your protective guide
why are we trying to protect everybody
why aren't we trying to just protect
them
and give them the answers they need in
Direction like really protect them oh
that's right they don't know what to do
to protect people
because they don't have the information
from above so I have to give them that
credit they don't know
it's a guide to a better life with
little with a little knowledge about
what we're exposed to on it on an
occasion or constant basis and the role
that plays in harming us even if it's a
simple thing as aspartame triggering a
migraine we're so much better equipped
to live the lives we see for ourselves
rather than get sidelined by symptoms or
illness
if this is your personal copy of the
book
feel free to Mark the crap out of it get
your pen out get your highlighter out
highlight what you can what you want
what's what calls out to you
and if you highlighted the book so much
because there's so much information in
these books that blows your mind and you
highlighted everything to death like you
just highlighted all get another one
and highlight that one too
and be like all right well that book
has this in here this book has this in
here and that's a really good thing to
do
maybe for instance you're finally ready
to remove the air fresheners and the
scented candles in your home and you can
switch to a natural fragrance free
laundry detergent then in a few months
maybe you'll be able to check off a few
more items in these brain betrayers
right here
it's these simple yet powerful steps
that can protect your friends your
family your pets your children and your
own future and that matters
that's what it's about
Karen Hartman says I have worked 35
years in the medical systems hard to
watch Anthony's info saved me
that's incredible
here's a brain betrayer's list right
here this is interesting viruses and
viral waste matter well first of all
science research didn't know viruses
created waste matter
that alone is MM info right
Julie I brain I've been brainwashed
after having worked 10 years as a
neurologist whoa you're a neurologist
that's incredible a lot of relearning
when I got to Medical medium information
Julie what's incredible is
you're actually here you're learning the
information you got the books obviously
you're highly intelligent person
and I just want to lay down this for a
minute I got respect for all doctors I
got respect for people who are working
on you know on on helping people the
compassion's there they want to get
people's lives better and I got the
ultimate respect for you
as a neurologist to come in here and to
get the information and to read it
I got tremendous respect for you
so here's the brain betrayers list she's
the short list this all the information
it's all in here right we could sit here
for days days with this information
viruses and viral waste matter like I
mentioned Pharmaceuticals that's a brain
betrayer right there now I get it I'm
not anti-pharmaceutical for certain
occasions and for certain things if
doctor the doctor says this is what you
need whatever listen to your doctors
right
but there's a lot of pharmaceutical that
shouldn't be in a lot of people I talked
about the stadium with 80 000 students
watching college football game and
cheering and the majority on
antidepressants anti-anxiety meds and
Adderall right
Pam says let's see what that went up
Amanda says after two years on your
protocols my Eczema is fully gone
incredible
that's that's actually incredible and
that matters if somebody knows with
eczema and psoriasis with the suffering
that occurs it's not just itching you
know when I see like a commercial or
advertisement somewhere on social media
or something from Big Pharma right doing
a commercial on somebody's eczema
psoriasis it's like uh you don't even
know what they're going through
big Pharma doesn't even know what
they're going through the kind of Agony
we're talking about the pain they're
acting like a little discomfort and they
show this huge huge slosh right this
whole spot of right psoriasis or eczema
but they don't even know what the
person's suffering but they have no idea
what the person's actually really
suffering with how bad it could be
I learned from SOC but you know
frankly and said I was gonna die
medical medium saved my life no medical
information can do
that
that they're big time Cults so you
understand the Cults out there
incredible and and you got your life
back
getting me some teary eyes right now
Tara Appleman when people say medical
medium info is fear-mongering I could
only think that person doesn't know what
it's like to Suffer Without answers and
lose all control of your life
foreign
I need some lemon balm
because it breaks my heart
it just does
tomka says you are the only one who
explained my condition thank you soc for
what you were doing
Toma on YouTube
I'm gonna pop in a little bit more
lemon balm into
this right here Erica says everything
that is not MediCal medium contradicts
itself you see it all the time Erica
it's unbelievable and then you wonder
how like people don't notice it
hmm
it's just unbelievable by the way you
guys
you guys know I endorse uh emerging I
won't go into it but
these guys are just insane that's all
the products are just insane I mean
nothing like them exists on this planet
so all right
toxic heavy metals no one cared about
toxic heavy metals they spent 35 years
teaching about it nobody cared
I practically got dragged out of a
dental conference over 30 plus years ago
because I was talking about how the
Mercury fillings were bad and it was an
alternative Dental con conference that
actually still appreciated Mercury
fillings
unbelievable
alternative
holistic
took a lot a lot of hardship throughout
the years to to get that info out
fragrances bacteria and other microbes
yeah streptococcus is wild in people
right now it's the new superbug I'm
sorry but it is and it's in everybody
and it gets out of control and they get
the acne they get the sinusitis the
chronic sinusitis they get the lung
infections they get the eye the styes
they get like conjunctivitis they get
UTIs bladder infections kidney
infections streptococcus is a big one
right there
they get the Itchy rectum strep is the
big one for I mean seriously and that's
that's what I talk about in all the
books not communion books right you guys
chemical industry domestic Invaders you
got your laundry detergents that blow
out of people's dryer vents and just
Poison every creature
out there
you got your petrochemicals and solvents
you got your Chemtrails and rainfall
exposure
you got your radiation and EMF
you got your harmful food and supplement
chemicals the bad stuff the stuff that
the Cults love out there you got your
harmful supplements the stuff that the
Colts love out there if I listed 10
harmful supplements right now you would
be like wait a minute I never knew that
get the books so you know meanwhile all
these people
about the climate but they're spraying
their perfumes and their colognes and
they're using their detergents
climate's going bad climate's going bad
but let me keep on spewing all this
toxic crap out of my dryer vents it's a
Twilight Zone here man
let me keep on spraying all that perfume
and cologne
but I'm worried about the climate
did you know if you spray perfume
on top of
a wasp
a bee
if you sprayed it on them they would die
anyway listen I want to give everybody a
little halftime reminder half time half
time reminder
you guys watch this from the beginning I
talk about the light blasts you have to
go to medicalme.com
and you have to sign up to the medical
medium newsletter please know this
and then tomorrow you will get an invite
from the medical medium newsletter it's
going to be a link that's your ticket in
to the light blast now if you're
somebody just came on here it's like
what's he selling now
it's for free and it's going to be live
it's a live event you don't want to miss
it twenty thousand people are only
allowed in
it's costing me thousands of dollars
to create and do so that and it's
costing me my resources of energy
internally because that light blast is
no joke including I go blind when I'm
doing it and if you guys know medical
medium
um Origins you'll know what that means
so anyway don't miss the light blast
please another thing too if you don't
mind since you know I gotta let you know
incredible swelling lymphedema
tissue expansion episode
Apple podcast please listen to that
episode and what you'll find on there is
no advertisers no commercials no
advertisements
it is the only podcast on that level
meaning a number one podcast in health
that has no advertisers
and advertisements and commercials
and I'm hated for it by the industries
Margarita says I believe ew being in
health field and health care provider I
have realized it's all about the money
yet aw guides Us for free
so I want to talk about brain saturation
for a couple minutes since we're in mm
school for a few more minutes here
any of these toxins and poisons I've
mentioned in any amount can reach and
saturate any aspect of the brain some
more commonly ending up in certain
places in the brain than others so all
those different things I mentioned
Pharmaceuticals everything else I
mentioned right Chemtrails radiation EMF
right all of it harmful foods supplement
chemicals harmful supplements right
chemical dust industry Invaders toxic
heavy metals fragrances Pharmaceuticals
right I mentioned that again all of that
can go in different areas of the brain
that I was just showing you here
different aspects different areas I mean
different locations is what I mean
for example petrochemicals often end up
in the cerebral cortex
in outer layer of the brain although
some petrochemicals can also end up
deeper within the brain
the amount of exposure has an influence
if it's a fair amount of exposure at
once or extended exposure meaning for
more than just a few minutes you could
get deeper saturation of petrochemicals
or other brain betrayers entering the
brain when exposure is small tiny
occasionally here and there you may not
reach or experience symptoms you may not
react or experience symptoms if you are
not sensitive can I read can I read
Spirit compassion's information correct
I missed the word
so you guys I'm reading out a brain
saver right here
do you I just want to ask you guys a
question Whoever has this book is it not
the greatest book of all time
or am I or is it just me or something is
are these not the greatest books of all
time
I just want to ask
okay
these are two massive Bibles right here
that's what people call them they call
them their Bibles
too massive right is it not the brand
these not the greatest books that that
will ever be did you ever read all the
other health books do you guys know like
you can't go back when you go into these
or the medical meeting books right are
these not the greatest books you have
ever seen right you guys I mean
seriously I'm not just talking about the
brain shot Therapies
I'm talking about the information and
right and the heavy metal detox cleanses
but seriously the breast the best books
ever in history right
yeah
for real right
I mean seriously
we've we've never had books like this
out there in the health world or the
other medical medium book Brett winter
says I wish they were longer goat
g-o-a-t
you wish these were longer
that's like 12 pounds right here
is they're not small books too they're
big books greatest books of all time
someone might say like hey he's biased
he wrote the books uh no
I get the information from SOC I'm a
messenger and I could judge the book I
have an opinion just like anybody else
Malin says they are so rich I haven't
been able to go through them yet but
what I've read is mind-blowing a modern
truly
uh
they are the greatest incredible
all right so I want to read a little bit
more if you guys got a second right
someone may be on a pharmaceutical for a
month or they have been on
Pharmaceuticals for 10 years someone may
be exposed to fumes for a few minutes at
a gasoline pump
or they may have some gasoline spilled
on their skin that they're also
breathing in as fumes everybody has
different exposures and that's why
penetration of the brain varies smaller
amounts built up over time larger
amounts speed up the process and
sensitivity I'm just reading a couple of
different things when brain betrayers
settle in the cerebral cortex they may
not affect critical brain functions
right away unless someone is already
sensitive and living with brain betrayer
complications such as a low-grade viral
infection and symptoms in that case the
smell of fresh paint you guys fresh
paint the smell of fresh paint could set
them back for days or weeks I've seen
people paint like
a friend of mine they're they're
um college student son
is repainting his dorm room
and
just you know sat in those fumes just
repainting it real all that paint and
everything right
and it was just for three weeks was like
fatigued and basically bedridden
because it's all it took to tip the
scale for that for that um person it's
all it took to you know to tip the scale
on the other hand someone who isn't on
the verge of that Tipping Point that I
was just saying who hasn't been
saturated with brain betrayer toxins
isn't dealing with low-grade viral
activity or doesn't have a diminished or
challenged immune system won't
necessarily see immediate effects from
exposure so that's that person like I
could do anything I want I can get any
exposure I want it doesn't matter their
scale hasn't been tipped yet you see how
it works you guys this is MM school for
a little bit their scale hasn't been
tipped
but don't don't take that the wrong way
it eventually does get ticked if you
don't do things about it like cleansing
and doing the right stuff
you know what's really disheartening is
when someone
gets really sick
they've tried everything out there they
tried the vegan diet
they tried a raw food diet a vegan diet
they tried an animal protein diet that's
what they came from
they tried different supplements they
went to naturopaths they went to
acupuncturists they went to registered
dietitians they went to neurologists
they went to whoever
and then they find medical medium
information
and medical medium information is
different
it uses wild Foods
and fruit and leafy greens differently
it uses the combinations differently it
uses supplements that are actually
really good for the healing process in
specific ways designed in certain ways
right
and then they find out how they were
sick and why they were sick and then
they found out that they can customize
what they want to heal and then
they want to pretend it wasn't medical
medium after all
they want to do their own thing
I get it they want a health coach or
they want to do something they want to
do their own thing
and they pretend it wasn't medical media
and they boil it down to it was just
some fruits and vegetables
that happens all the time
it's funny when people
you know it's it's it's really actually
heartbreaking meanwhile
they wouldn't have found that
information understood did you know just
knowing what caused your problem and
your sickness to begin with is a huge
massive part of your healing process to
Discount that is insane
to actually say
oh yeah no it really wasn't medical
medium he's just fruits and vegetables a
vegan whatever I I found my own way of
doing it with vegetables now and I don't
even want to mention his name anymore I
don't even want to mention medical
medium anymore I found my own
supplements that I want to do in the way
I wanted you and then I want to teach
all that out there because it wasn't
medical medium and I'm not going to say
it's medical medium anymore
it's it's actually insane to think
that just finding out what was wrong
with you
is a huge part that's a huge part of how
you even heal it gives you peace of mind
like nothing else when you're out there
and you're struggling and suffering and
you tried everything and then you find
medical medium and the first thing you
learn is why you're sick healing starts
to happen from that alone to actually
discredit that is insane
just because you want to do your own
thing and do your own stuff and not be
part of the medical medium Community
anymore you want to be doing your own
thing I get it I understand that but to
then throw medical medium kind of like
as if it's oh that would have happened I
would have healed anyway even though I
tried everything out there I would have
healed anyway
he's just fruits and vegetables and I
would have figured it out anyway
I get it you want to be somebody in
health probably or you want to be
somebody this or you want to be a life
coach or whatever it is and you don't
want to give claim to Medical medium
information anymore
and so whatever
but healing happens by first knowing
what's wrong with you that's how
something occurs instantly if you've
been out there bearing you know out
there in the desert wanting to know why
you're finally sick like wanting to know
what's wrong and you finally get the
answer that's part of the healing
process you can't deny that as being
something that helps you heal
all right
then it's also not just a vegan diet
medical medium is not vegan
it's not about vegan
unbelievable the vegan doctors out there
how they say oh medical medium's just
vegan you know everybody knew that
information medical medium is for animal
protein people you can still keep your
animal protein if you want it's for
vegans who can't get better either who
can that have been doing their vegan
diet wrong
then nobody had answers for it's for the
vegetarians that do other stuff like
fish it's for everybody it's medical
medium information is the tool so you
can heal and still do what you're doing
and one of the parts of healing is
knowing what the heck went wrong why are
you sick because let me tell you what
that does for your soul and your brain
and your peace of mind when you know
what's wrong you instantly start to get
peace and you instantly start to heal
and start to sleep and start to know
okay
but the people out there get it they get
greedy they want to take credit for
medical medium information but their own
credit I get it they want to cheat other
people from finding the information
anymore they don't want to like cite
medical medium anymore they want to make
it look like it's all been out there in
the vegan movement all the info
it's so sad
Becky Lynn says they get this
information and then they use it all to
put out their their own version but
don't want to anymore say medical medium
they want to do their own version
lupus free with celery33 says I get the
comment he is not saying anything new
the medical journals I cited about EBV
now say it has been known for decades
that EBV blah blah blah it hasn't been
known for decades
the true cause of Lupus was never
Epstein-Barr in any medical form
anywhere it was published first by
medical medium
it never said anywhere anyhow that the
cause of Lupus hypothyroidism
multiple sclerosis Ra was Epstein-Barr
that never existed
that was post-published material and
backdated material they backedated
material that never said it was the
cause reactivated Epstein-Barr wasn't
even a thing
until medical medium
the medical Arena both alternative and
conventional medicine believe that once
you got Epstein-Barr it went away and it
was mono and that was it they never knew
it caused the problem post mono
it's only medical medium information
that put it out there that Epstein-Barr
reactivates and causes problems years
later giving you ra
and a whole bunch of other conditions in
fibromyalgia that's original medical
medium information
foreign
verse taught first understood first and
nothing else existed for that if you
were sick all these years you would know
that if you were sick for many years
before you would know it didn't exist
and no one had answers
but when millions of people go to their
doctors every day because guess what
millions of medical medium books went
around the world and they people
millions of people went to their
doctor's offices asking them to test
them for me for actually Epstein-Barr
because of medical medium and they
brought their medical medium books in
millions of people around the world
brought them to their doctors right
there and then
everybody started learning the true
cause of their conditions and then
science research got very upset because
they were looking like idiots science
and research and the clinics looked like
they didn't know why people were sick
and they started now saying well maybe
it's Epstein-Barr maybe it's possibly
Epstein-Barr way post medical medium
laughs
the books go into depth on The
Housewives and what the information is
in the details and they still don't have
that today there's no article there's no
anything there's no nothing out there
that actually shows you the details of
how it works and it does in these books
and that's how it works
guys we're having some fun today
just a reminder don't miss the light
blast watch this replay from the
beginning this is a live right now but
watch it from the beginning
centauri's healing says absolutely
breaks my heart so many people miss out
on their chance to heal because of
people doing this yes and they will
continue to miss out and continue to
miss out
and that's what's gonna happen
right but they still got to go through
all the torture they have to swallow
charcoal they have to do butter in their
coffee they have to do what what else do
they have to do uh diatomaceous earth
particles that destroy their gut lining
what else do they have to do oh they
have to do ionized water alkaline
ionizer water and get nettles in their
brain what else do they have to do
before they find medical medium
information oh they have to dissolve all
their teeth with apple cider vinegar
oh no it's medical medium information it
makes your teeth go bad not all the
vinegar you had and the caffeine you had
all these years
and everything else
hmm
I have all my teeth
all the podcast doctors by the way that
are younger than me and older than me
don't have their teeth
half their mouths are filled with
implants but they're green tea they say
is sure helpful
you know it's kind of crazy when you
think about it all
all of it when you think about it
hmm
but what do people go through
apple cider vinegar gummies which
totally annihilates their stomach acid
their stomachs actually destroys their
stomach glands to Charcoal right
destroys our Linings and makes them
deficient what else nutrient deficient
just keep on going down the path of that
like
but that's the Colts out there and
that's what people do
and then they destroy their bodies with
all the stuff out there
and have no idea
and they'll never know to go to Medical
medium information because the Cults
have them so controlled the goal for all
the Cults out there okay
in the medical industry is death by a
Thousand Cuts and then to discredit
Medical medium information because it
would take over
medical medium info would take over if
people actually knew why they were sick
and knew they can heal think about that
people knew why they were sick and they
can heal it would actually go like
really crazy
what's up
all right
some lemon balm in my hot water there so
good oh you guys were reading out of
brain saver what did today turn into
because I'm trying to figure it out now
it was about the late blast it was about
also the episode on medical meme podcast
at Apple podcast the swelling episode
you guys gotta check it out
you you gotta see that episode you gotta
hear it I mean you have to hear it it's
mind-blowing right medical meme podcast
at Apple podcast
so what they do is they put out bad
articles out there and then talk about
like talk bad about medical medium in
the Articles right
so they can discredit medical medium and
then say medical means information
already was out there which is not
it's not I have a team of people
that monitor that
to look for it
they screed shoot everything in the
article land going all the way back they
know when someone backdates something
they know when there's trickery they
know when something like is published
things you know like oh yeah sure uh we
knew that they actually did it
it's crazy how it works all right you
guys
um
I think we had a good time I don't know
I had a good time
Jody says just knowing the root causes
of things have given me such peace of
mind right there and empowerment now I
want to talk about that it's worth more
than gold
so what happens is there's people in the
medical immune community that were out
there in the sea of confusion right they
were out there in the Cults they were
sick
and then they found mm info
and then they used mm like
supplementation
info they used mm
food info right detailed information all
of it they used it to heal and then they
were like well I want to do my own thing
I don't want to cite mm anymore I don't
want to say mm did it
so I'm gonna kind of curtail my own way
of doing it and hey and them didn't
create a fruit or vegetable fruit and
vegetables have been out there in the
vegan movement so I'm just gonna say
whatever
but what happened is the person found
answers to why they were sick and it
gave them so much peace and relief it
already ignited their healing process
right there just like you're saying Jody
just like you're saying I know you're
not doing what they're doing I'm just
saying you said just knowing the root
causes of things have given me such
peace of mind and empowerment it's worth
more than gold
and then they got that peace of mind and
they started healing and then they
applied the tools that weren't out there
celery juice wasn't even in the vegan
movement no one was doing it
I know the vegan doctors out there I
know the vegan people out there they
weren't doing 16 32 ounces of straight
celery juice they didn't even know it
restored anything they didn't know
anything about it the point is is then
they apply the medical medium tools and
they start healing but because celery is
a vegetable which is an herb it's not
even a vegetable they're like wait a
minute hidden Creed celery celery
existed out there I need to do my own
thing now meanwhile they're canceling
out the fact that they healed by finding
the peace in their heart of what was
wrong
and then they applied the tools that
didn't exist in the vegan movement I'm
sorry but they didn't
you know what existed in a vegan
movement chocolate lots of chocolate
lots of vegan fat lots of nut Butters
you know whatever lots of vegan cheese
so and trust me these people tried all
that and the whole point is they come
into medical medium they learn how to
really navigate
and heal
and then they want to stab medical
medium information in the back they want
to stick the knife in
and they don't want to they just want to
do their own thing stick the knife in
and twist it
and I get it
the traps are everywhere pay attention
to the details
it's in the books good information here
brain shot therapies are really powerful
you guys
the brain shot therapies come from above
all the information comes from above
and I've been in this for over 30 plus
years
I have fed
the good stuff into the vegan movements
for over 30 plus years
what you won't find that I do is I don't
attack people by their name
right
because as much as I want to say
what happened and what's going on
I don't want to do that
but I can tell you this okay
you wouldn't believe
what
they were doing
in the vegan movement
along the years that I had to be like no
you got to do that because that's not
good no you got to do that you wouldn't
believe how much correcting
and fixing to get the vegan movement to
where it is today and it's still cracked
out there it's still cracked
and they're not doing what they need to
do if you want to be vegan but you can
be animal protein and heal
I welcome all animal protein people in
fact medical mean Community is what like
probably 60 animal protein people or
something 70 and they heal with all the
information and the tools
and I've never attacked animal protein
ever
if you knew the people I helped it would
shock you
if you knew the people I helped in the
vegan movement
it would shock you
you guys would just be like what
all right right
on that note
little curtsy
you guys know that uh
you guys are the greatest oh I think
somebody wants to see you guys
um I gotta open the door say hold on
hold on
come on in so you guys somebody wants to
see you
so Dr Nesbitt Dr Nesbit you're you're
you were taking off your
uh your scrubs what happened
your scrubs are coming off Dr Nesbitt is
yep we are using your Tick Tock platform
are you okay with that Dr Nesbit says
it's okay to use the tick tock platform
um that's okay
yep and you got yeah Dr NES Uma do you
like Uma you do why
she's cool okay you want to do an
operation no you don't want to remove
her gallbladder
or anything Dr Nesbitt says
he says he likes doing surgeries on
people he likes and thinks he's quite
she want to help him heal he says yeah
wants to help him heal
um
Dr Nesbit we are talking about medical
medium information yeah
um okay cold white spring did what LOL
I saw that
okay let's help you get your scrubs back
on
okay
Dr Nesbit just wanted to say one thing
to you guys
uh live long and prosper
isn't that Star Trek
he's been trying to catch up on Star
Trek episodes
um he likes Spock for some reason it's
Dr Nesbit watches Spock
on
television
Jaime says the reason people steal and
twist medical medium info is because
Anthony doesn't monetize his info and
hasn't created an Empire
Jamie that is 100 correct
don't yell in your ear sorry
maybe that's 100 correct Dr nesbit's
getting upset because I'm screaming and
Doctor husband's here
that's true
um
yeah well by the way Dr Nesbitt
what doctor is but what do you have to
say
drinks are on me
Dr Nesbit says free drinks really no
nobody drinks alcohol here well I'm sure
some people here in this live drink
alcohol but they're working on quitting
someday so do not say anything bad to
them because everybody has a hard life
then we all just try to get by
he's talking about wild blueberry juice
by the way that's different
got your ass ring soil blueberry
juice with some vodka in it he said
transferable reduce with vodka in it no
thank you I do not want any vodka please
um Lizzy says sorry no more booze for us
oh
well you guys
um we are going to have to peace out
so
everybody take care and be good
one day at a time
all right guys
Nicole says Thank you for everything you
do and all the information you share
selflessly well you're welcome
gotta do some good
got to make sure I got
chronically ill on my mind and make sure
that we do what's right
I agree
yeah that guy has been said good point
all right guys I will see you guys soon
next time watch this
in the replay so you can know how to
sign up to the light blast check out the
medical meme podcast and sign up to
newsletter please
um and make sure you download your free
cold and flu toolkit
uh Dr espet says he's coming down with
sniffles
he
wait a minute you're you've had a cough
when
Dr Nesbitt said he's got a cough this
morning
you're like in my face right now
why didn't you tell me I don't want to
catch anything right now
sing shock therapy
yeah you're right well I have to do what
just do the same shot family
Goldenseal
wait what up
uh vitamin C shock therapy
okay all right I feel better now no one
I could do something
is on medical medium.com
all right guys