happens every day every time I talk to a
friend or somebody I know or anyone it's
like they've gone through something
whether it's Mercury retrograde causing
problems whether it's
something happening in their family
their personal life their work
relationships any kind of friendships
something's always happening and if it's
not that it's something else and I hear
it all the time out there it's like not
only do people have to deal with
different struggles different emotional
hardships trust issues right so many
people carry these trust issues because
they've been wronged
and betrayed that happens out there all
the time and people will be like what do
you do what do you do you know I'm so
stressed out when it's crazy how
stressed out I am and I'm like lemon
balm I have to say it like a zillion
times I think I've said it a billion
trillion times in the last whatever
years
and it's like really lemon balm like
yeah lemon balm so you almost can't even
you almost can't even say it one
trillion more times but that's what I
use myself all the time right and I find
so much peace in it because you can when
it's a good lemon balm you can feel it
like I mean you feel it right away and
there's a huge difference so that's the
beverage you guys know I backed these
guys 100 with my endorsement I stand
behind this company because I'll tell
you
dispose my mind is that
there's never going to be something
hidden in here and by law supplement
companies are allowed to hide a small
percentage of ingredients they don't put
on the bottle
and that's what they almost all do out
there and this company says uh-uh it
ain't gonna happen we're never sticking
something hidden in these and then
they're third independently tested the
quality is off the chart so what they do
is they go for the highest quality tier
so if you started a supplement company
tomorrow and you said hey I want to do
like whack-a-mole supplements or
something or I want to do like you know
greatest supplements on the planet
company and you want to start one
what's going to happen is you're going
to look at all these options with
suppliers and you're going to find oh
here's our this is good quality but it's
going to be still at the bottom tier
right to go to the highest tier highest
quality of lemon balm or the highest
quality of ashwagandha or the highest
quality propolis which is incredible
from Memphis right
you like Bemidji only goes to the
highest where they're like you are the
only ones
like sourcing this out you are the only
ones asking for this the highest quality
and it's incredible and these are the
differences so it's those very things
and so anyway
stress which I'm under a lot right I
mean you guys know
you guys know right it's a Lemon Ball
that's what gets me through like that's
one of the things that gets me through
and you may be under like another kind
of stress or a different kind of stress
something different and
and so yeah I mean I recommend lemon
balm for like anything like it's a nerve
Vine it's good for the nerves all of
that and then you got the ashwagandha so
I like these two both of these together
you can have them together you can have
them separate at different times
but I like them together as well right
so there's the ashwagandha ashwagandha
is popular out there
a lot of people take ashwagandha
but until you've taken the best do you
realize
what ashwagandha really is and that's a
whole leather that's a whole nother
thing anyway any kind of stress and
people go through so many emotional
hardships and maybe their adrenaline is
just off the chart because you're going
through something maybe they're just
dealing with any kind of thing that's
you know where you need something for
the nerves but lemon balm right there
you got ashwagandha I'm gonna take some
right now you guys I just did a live I
just made a killer dish from the brand
saber books right here and I'm going to
send this down
thank you
and when it's really good like this when
it's that strength and that amazing you
feel it
and you feel it quick too
and that like right there alone and
that's the difference and I told you
about the continuity test that I do all
the time right I told you about that
I'll talk about that another time anyway
guys
I just want to let you know if you're
somebody dealing with crap
MBS
fees are incredible anyway many
blessings you guys love you much