for day one of the medical medium wild
blueberry drinks challenge I'm excited
actually glad you guys are here we're
going to talk about how alcohol destroys
the brain so that's going to be one of
the topics the main topic really it's
going to be really fun but we're making
three drinks get ready brain detox tonic
which is actually really cool we're
gonna make the wild blueberry apple
cider we're gonna make the wild
blueberry sangria I'm pumped up I'm
excited let's get down to it you guys
and just so you know we got a lot of
cool things over here I'm going to tell
you right now we've got like some killer
stuff right here I got oranges because
I'm gonna be squeezing some orange juice
we've got the wild blueberry juice we
got everything ready and rigged we got
some fruit we're gonna need we got it
all I'm excited I got the burner right
here
I got a pot on there so we're doing good
but I want to talk about alcohol for a
couple of minutes and by the way day one
of the medical meanwhile blueberry
drinks challenge just so you know
so I'm in the alcohol chapter right here
in the brain saber book as you guys can
see
and I know people are drinking they're
drinking during the holidays I'm not
judging anybody okay if they want to
drink they can drink that's perfectly
fine but what happens in my house right
I don't bring out the alcohol I just
don't I don't bring out all the alcohol
and everything like that you know go
somewhere else and you can drink right
my house it's bringing out the wild
blueberry drinks that's what I do okay
it's anything but alcohol all right
anyway so
yeah I know total down all right anyway
brain saver I'm gonna read a little bit
out of here then we're gonna make some
drinks three drinks I'm pumped up I'm
glad you guys are here I'm excited
let's do it so alcohol right throughout
the centuries all the way up through
today we have Associated someone who's
had too much to drink with slurred
speech
I had a lot to drink wood speech right
the inability to walk in a straight line
the inability to think or speak clearly
we call it being drunk
anyway you guys I'm into brain saver
books I'm on page 158 if you want to
read along so got the brain saver book
right there
158 the alcohol check have you read the
alcohol chapter it's sick it's insane
the information is just mind-blowing
about what alcohol does to the brain so
let's get into it a little bit
we call it being drunk if it becomes
more severe and that person is vomiting
or anything right incapacitated we may
call it alcohol poisoning you've heard
that right well that person has alcohol
poisoning yeah that person drank too
much they're they're holding on to the
toilet and they're throwing up and
they're vomiting all night long that
person has alcohol poison that person
was hospitalized because of alcohol
poisoning right
so that's that's what we call it and
that's how it works we may call it
alcohol poisoning do we really know what
happens when our bloodstream is
saturated with a high volume of alcohol
do we really know what's happening we
don't
and we never did
mind-blowing information I'm about to go
into I'm in the alcohol chapter right
now out of brain saver you just if you
just landed here where day one of the
medical meeting wild blueberry drinks
challenge we're making three drinks
without alcohol which is really cool
we're making a brain detox tonic which
doesn't have alcohol in it duh we're
making the wild blueberry apple cider
we're making the wild blueberry sangria
which I'm really excited about
we assumed because medical research and
science assume
that more alcohol in the bloodstream
leads directly to these actions and
symptoms
that alcohol itself affects the brain to
cause these experiences
here's the truth
no one knows exactly what happens inside
the brain with alcohol
that is the truth they don't know
medical science and research does not
know what happens when someone's
drinking
and alcohol enters the body they do not
know what happens to the brain they
don't have a tool to figure it out they
don't have a way to measure it they
don't have a way to understand it they
don't have some kind of technology that
actually shows the brain under alcohol
and what occurs to the brain they don't
have any of that
all these centuries up until now modern
day science right this minute does not
know what happens when alcohol gets to
the brain and we're going to talk about
part of what happens is we got a lot of
info in here
foreign
so
this is really cool this information
okay
and so
when alcohol goes to the bloodstream and
leads directly to these actions and
symptoms they don't know what causes
that and what that means that alcohol
itself affects the brain to cause these
experiences here's the truth no one
knows exactly what happens inside the
brain with alcohol
intoxication is not fully understood
it's only one aspect of what happens to
the brain when someone drinks so they'll
be like that person's intoxicated that
person has alcohol poisoning that's as
far as they can go but what happens
inside our brain another story
entirely another story
so medical research in science is not
going to also put 250 million dollars
into trying to figure out what happens
when someone gets alcohol in their
system and it goes to the brain
but we're going to talk about it right
here because it's really interesting
it's one of the reasons why alcohol in
tinctures alcohol and supplements of all
kinds is a bad idea not only does the
alcohol destroy all the different
phytochemical compounds in tinctures and
pill form and anything that alcohol's in
right
but alcohol alone is bad for the liver
bad for the brain
so
alcohol's effects start out with what is
called a little tipsy
hey that person's just a little tipsy
I'm feeling kind of Tipsy some say
alcohol helps them loosen up and speak
their mind right so when you drink it's
like no I'm getting looser now now I can
say what I can say now I can you know
now I got some confidence back so a lot
of people be like okay well I have to
drink to loosen up I'm around some
people I'm around I'm at a meeting
whatever with a bunch of people
um you know I'm at an after-hour party
it's time to loosen up and be more
myself and that's what people do they'll
they'll do alcohol for that some say
alcohol helps them loosen up and speak
their mind some say a couple of beers
helps them relax
some say wine helps numb them out right
have a hard day you come home you have a
glass of wine and then it numbs you out
yet how does alcohol seem to loosen them
up relax them or numb them out how does
it work
and that's where medical research and
science is completely unaware they don't
know how it loosens the person up
when they say that how it numbs them out
when they say it numbs them up
how to help relax them so they don't
know those answers it's as simple as all
they have right now on record as you
drink
and a person says it helps me loosen up
that's as scientific as it gets the
person drinks
and they're a little tipsy that's all
they have they don't have anything else
in medical research and science or the
person drinks and it numbs them up
they can have a team of scientists
all this money right lab technicians and
they still won't know when someone says
whoa yeah that drink helps to relax me
or that drink numbs me up they won't
have an answer that's scientifically
proven or accurate or anything else
because they're completely in the dark
so you guys if you just got in here
we're talking about how alcohol destroys
the brain I thought it was a great topic
we're in brain saver we're on page 158
if you guys want to read along with me
and we're doing three drinks today so
I'm excited too we're day one of the
medical medium wild blueberry drinks
Challenge and we're doing the brain
detox tonic we're doing the wild
blueberry sangria okay and we're doing a
wild blueberry apple cider here we go
this next section is called brain
charades
as we've discussed throughout this book
your brain survives on glucose that's
what it runs on
our brain
lives off of glucose right that's an
orange
right so
we need sugar for the brain if you take
sugar away from the brain the brain
starts to deteriorate it starts to die
it has to have glucose as fuel it has to
have sugar blood sugar that's what keeps
our brain alive and active
a lack of glucose to your brain can
slowly starve it over time
that's why when people literally remove
everything that's a carbohydrate
everything that's a sugar whether
natural not natural whatever everything
possible that's a glucose or sugar they
literally hit the wall they can't
function they can't work and they get in
big trouble they can't be productive
and if glucose were eliminated from your
bloodstream and never entered your brain
you could go into brain failure within
moments your brain starts to die within
five seconds without getting sugar to it
so without getting glucose to your brain
it starts to die within seconds think
about that for a minute
get ready for this
alcohol
is the all-time trick on your brain
that's because your brain believes
alcohol is sugar
sugar it can use so when you drink a
drink with alcohol in it
your brain gets tricked out
it believes it's pure sugar or sugar of
some kind
so it's an actual trick on the brain
it believes it's like the glucose that's
created by the foods you eat so when you
drink an alcohol beverage
your brain believes that the alcohol
is like a natural sugar like a sugar
from an orange an apple a sugar from
anything
okay
so it believes it's like the glucose
that's created by the foods you eat that
contain carbohydrates and sugar really
alcohol is methyl sugar this would be
mind-blowing when you hear this it's a
hybrid of what sugar
what was sugar
so think about that
so your brain thinks alcohol is actually
usable sugar
and instead
it's not it's methyl sugar it's what
sugar was
which is this is incredible it's more of
a vaporized sugar versus a usable sugar
so when you drink an alcoholic beverage
it's a vaporized sugar
not a usable sugar
alcohol's Essence is sugar yet it's not
and this is really cool where it goes
right here you guys I'm reading out a
brain saver on page 158 still
incredible information right here you're
also here with me right now day one for
the free medical meeting wild blueberry
drinks challenge we're making three
drinks hang in there for the ride it's
gonna be fun I got the burner on right
here I got all kinds of stuff around me
right here stuff over here stuff all
over here it's gonna be really cool
actually exciting I love this
so you guys this is incredible
information it just blows my mind
okay
as a result of this charade that's
played on your brain that leads it to
identifying alcohol as critically needed
glucose several things go wrong
so when you drink the alcoholic beverage
and remember medical research designs
that they don't know this
they don't have a study they don't know
what happens when you drink they don't
know why someone loosens up they don't
know anything
so as a result of this charade plate on
your brain that leads it to identify
alcohol as critically needed glucose
several things go wrong
check this out
the more alcohol in your bloodstream the
harder it is for your brain to use any
real source of glucose in your
bloodstream
this is original Advanced information
from above it's not stuff that you know
gathered off the internet and thrown in
a book this is unique information from
above always proven right or or never
proven wrong so keep that in mind the
medical medium book series has never
been proven Wrong by science research or
scientists yet instead just poached and
proven right constantly
so this is a really important section
right here probably one of the most
important parts right here so when you
think about this I just want to go over
this with you one more time because it's
that mind-blowing
so
the sugar and alcohol is really not
there it's the ghost of sugar but your
brain thinks it's sugar it's glucose
just like something from a fruit or any
food
as a result of this charade play it on
your brain because it's a trick played
on your brain so when you have a glass
of wine when you have a shot when you
have alcohol when you have a tincture
with alcohol in it yeah a tincture with
alcohol in it
herbal tincture with alcohol in it
terrible terrible
your brain identifies alcohol as a
critically needed glucose so what your
brain thinks is that it's critical
so when you take that alcoholic tincture
when you take that supplement that has
alcohol in it when you drink a drink
when you have a glass of wine whatever
form of alcohol you're doing
your brain
thinks it's actual usable critically
immediate glucose
but several things go wrong the more
alcohol in your bloodstream the harder
it is for your brain to use any real
source of glucose you know what that
means
what that means is without usable
glucose in your bloodstream you die
your brain runs on sugar
it starts dying within five seconds
without glucose
so you see where it's going
the more alcohol in your bloodstream the
harder it harder it is for your brain to
use any real source of glucose in your
bloodstream so what happens next
if it's hard for your brain to use any
usable glucose resource in your
bloodstream your brain starts to starve
the more alcohol you drink the more the
brain
cannot use a glucose to keep it alive
how crazy is that
in alcohol dominates over any glucose
storage left in the brain so here's
here's how it works your brain has
glucose storages
that it pulls from so that if you don't
get glucose to your brain within five
seconds you hopefully won't die because
your brain has enough glucose storage to
get you by a few more seconds before
that next round of glucose gets the
brain to save it
but what happens is the more alcohol
inside your bloodstream the less chance
your brain is going to be able to use
any usable glucose in even including
stored usable glucose in the brain it
won't be usable anymore less and less
becomes usable you guys just got here
we're talking about the brain starving
the starving of glucose because of
alcohol use
drinking anything with alcohol that's
what we're talking about
we're on page 159 of the brain saver
book's greatest book of all time books
of all time if you guys have checked him
out and read them there's also
brain saver protocols okay
and we're day one of the free Wild
blueberry drinks challenge which is
really cool
all right let's get into this a little
bit more and more because this is really
incredible
so alcohol dominates over any glucose
storage you have left in your brain
your liver is your main glucose storage
bin so our liver
is the main glucose storage bin
it's supposed to Harbor all this glucose
that helps to protect us
its job is to release glucose
congruently as your brain needs it so
your liver releases that glucose as your
brain needs it
there are moments when we aren't getting
enough sugar or glucose or fructose or
any kind of carbohydrate in our diet and
we go into glucose deficits in the
bloodstream
your liver's job in that case is to
release glucose so your brain doesn't
completely starve
so your liver has a job and that's why
it's critical to keep our livers healthy
that's why medical medium information
has advanced liver knowledge like a
Liver Rescue right and and all the other
medical medium books
and so the job of the liver is to Harbor
and keep healthy glucose storage bins so
that when you run low
yeah
when you run low
that glucose gets needed and used how
incredible Lorraine L says this chapter
put me off
ever having another drop of alcohol
incredible
this includes circumstances where you
aren't getting you weren't eating for a
long period of time if you don't eat for
a long period of time which could happen
for instance say you get food poisoning
say you're one of those lucky people
or unfortunate people however you want
to look at it that gets food poisoning a
bad case of food poisoning how about a
stomach flu too and you can't eat
anything
for a while food poisoning especially
where you can't even drink anything
you're in the hospital you're hooked up
to Morphine you have the worst stomach
pain you ever had in your life because
you got E coli poisoning or some other
foodborne illness
and you're suffering for a day and you
can't really get any glucose then your
liver releases glucose Darcy Lee says I
was drinking vodka because I was low
carb what a huge mistake
you're on Facebook that's really
interesting I know wait to hear the rest
of what I have to read you guys it's
like mind-blowing
so this includes circumstances where you
aren't eating enough in a long period of
time remember without glucose your brain
can't survive your brain
cannot survive
without glucose it dies fast and it gets
us in trouble
the liver fulfilling this role is why
someone can do a water fast and their
brain can survive the experience
and that's the problem even with water
fasting
water fasting so-called experts don't
even realize it
the person and how much glucose they
have in their liver or glycogen storage
they have in their brain determines if
they can even water fast but no one
would ever know that there's no way to
measure that there's no way to
understand that that's why some people
go into a water fast they bottom out
real fast
and they hit the wall and they're in bad
shape and then other people can seem
like they go longer and longer on a
water fast because what they don't
realize is they're living off of glucose
storage that's sitting inside their
liver
so the liver fulfilling this role is why
someone who can you know can do a water
fast and their brain can survive the
experience because the liver is
releasing ample glucose for the brain
our liver releases glucose for our brain
glycogen reserves in the brain and
glucose reserves in the liver determine
how long someone can withstand a water
fast now not everybody's liver functions
that well and that's another thing too
I've seen people do a water fast
and they can do it longer
because their liver was functioning
better and they had a large glucose
storage bin and then I've seen other
people do water fast
and they were just boom down for the
count
the liver wasn't a healthy liver didn't
have a large glucose storage they had no
glucose to feed the brain why they were
just out of water
and they just went
[Music]
even like into psychosis
where they just went into psychosis like
boom
it's that person you hear about
through somebody for somebody right that
was at a fasting clinic and they were
literally
in a psychotic episode when they weren't
ever psychotic before
it's because
they didn't have enough glucose storage
bin inside their liver to get to their
brain while they were water fasting but
I'm just using water fasting as an
example
I'm talking about everyday living we
need that glucose and our liver releases
that glucose to the brain on everyday
living too
many people's glucose storage bins can
be minimally due
to the liver being sluggish or stagnant
wrote a whole book about that
taught about that for years
so drinking alcohol can affect these
people more than alcohol affects people
with strong livers you ever hear that I
just want to go over this for a second
because this is really an incredible
point
you heard that person where I can handle
alcohol no I can't handle alcohol
I can handle more than a few drinks I
can't handle more than a half a drink
you hear that right
so I want to talk about this in a minute
but first I want to make an announcement
we are in the medical medium while
blueberry drinks challenge
we're day one it's a free challenge you
still have time to go to
medicalmedium.com download the
information you need
we are live right now this is not a
pre-recorded episode on any level we're
live live live and
we're going to be making three different
drinks a wild blueberry apple cider
a brain detox tonic
and while blueberry sangria sign up to
the challenge get your free grocery
shopping list go to medicalmedium.com
you'll see the link also in the profile
and description
all right you guys
check this out right you heard someone
say before I could handle alcohol
right
my friend Bryce
my friend Bryce says he can handle
alcohol
like it he can handle a few shots easy
right then I know people they can't
handle alcohol on any level
there's a reason for that
it's Whoever has the stronger liver
can handle alcohol
longer or more larger amounts of alcohol
if someone has a weaker liver stagnant
sluggish problematic
that's another story that means we got a
liver that can't handle alcohol but
there's a reason for it because that
liver is dense that liver is hardened
the liver stagnant sluggish
it's also why as people age they can't
handle alcohol as much either well you
know in my college Years
I could just totally get shit-faced in
my college years and just whatever I
could drink drink drink I could put a
tube down my throat somebody could be
standing on the bar and dumping down
like gallons of alcohol
but then their liver gets stagnant and
sluggish over time and when they get
older they're like I can't handle that
much no no that's good she can stop
pouring it from there well I could just
have one shot you hear that right
so I'm back to the book I'm on page 159
a brain saver I'm reading right out of
the book now this is unique information
by the way about how alcohol destroys
the brain how it works science and
research does not know they don't know
what happens when you drink where that
alcohol how it goes to the brain and
what happens inside the brain they have
no idea
but they will now because this
information is getting out there
that's why some say I can't handle
alcohol
or he can't handle his liquor
because their livers are weakened
especially as they age
regardless if someone's alcohol
tolerance when enough alcohol is
consumed the effects are all the same
that point right there is mind-blowing
regardless of someone's alcohol
tolerance
right besides that when regardless of
that when enough alcohol is consumed for
anybody any individual whether they can
handle their liquor or not
the effects are all the same as you're
drinking alcohol it starts to poison and
numb the liver
so the first thing is they say right so
you heard science say this well you
drink too much you hurt your liver that
part is known
so as you're drinking alcohol it starts
to poison and numb the liver but what
they don't know is it starts to numb the
liver
they don't know what it does to the
liver they don't understand what happens
to the liver so science research doesn't
know what happens to the liver when you
drink they just guesstimate that a
person lifelong drinking
gets cirrhosis of the liver but that's
not even totally accurate I've known
people that do lifelong drinking and
don't have cirrhosis of the liver see
they don't even know that
as you're drinking alcohol it starts to
poison and numb the liver and your liver
is your defense mechanism to stop
alcohol from getting to your brain that
part they don't know
so science and research does not know
that your liver is your defense
mechanism to stop alcohol from getting
to the brain they don't have that
information
it is your line of defense to stop the
poison from getting here
that's what your liver is
by the time you start getting tipsy or
whatever you personally call the
beginning stages of feeling alcohol's
effects because everybody has a
different term somebody might say I'm
tipsy someone might say I'm starting to
loosen up someone might say I'm starting
to get drunk everybody has a different
terminology when they're drinking
no matter how mild your liver is already
at its saturation level for protecting
your brain so that is something medical
research and science has no idea about I
know this is going to get poached the
minute you start feeling whatever you
call that name Tipsy or feeling a little
drunk or feelings like loosening up
whatever the term is that you use when
you're drinking
that means
your liver is at its level it's at its
Tipping Point
so keep that in mind so it could be
anybody that's just like oh I'm getting
a little tipsy
oh I'm kidding I'm feeling a little kind
of you know loose now I'm feeling like
okay I can you know speak my mind
whatever it is that you feel
so whatever you personally call the
beginning stages of feeling alcohol's
effects no matter how mild your liver is
already at its saturation level for
protecting the brain so that means your
liver
can't protect your brain anymore you
bypassed it
and that right there
is incredible information from above
Nobody Knows the minute you feel that
sensation
you already bypass
your liver's defense mechanisms
that's what occurred
when we talk about moderation with
alcohol we miss the crucial point
I know you guys people are people have
been slamming moderation at me again I
noticed some of the haters out there
they'll use that one they'd be like well
I think moderation is just a healthy way
of doing things tell that to a
chronically ill person
who literally can't heal because they're
letting the whole moderation right
gaslighting the moderation gas lighting
take over and then they're stuck in the
moderation game and then they're afraid
to do the right things to heal because
they're thinking they have to be in
moderation like that's a healthier
Pursuit
alcohol is toxic in any amount so the
liver's job is to soak up every last
drop it can when your liver is being
poisoned by alcohol it can't release
glucose anymore
that's something to know right there
remember I was telling you guys earlier
reading out the book here brain saver
the minute
your liver
starts to get that that alcohol
poisoning it can't release that glucose
anymore
because the liver's job a healthy
liver's job or even a liver that's
actually stagnant sluggish and
problematic
the liver's job is to release glucose to
your brain so your brain uses glucose
that comes from your liver
but the minute your liver is being
saturated by alcohol and you hit that
saturation point the liver cannot
release glucose to your brain anymore so
when someone's drinking no more glucose
gets to the brain anymore
I want to show you the book right here
guys by the way because someone is
asking they're saying show the book
cover
that's the book cover
right there it's brain saver and brain
saver protocol so make sure you get both
books
right
Luke Roger says mm info took me out of
suffering appreciate you aw appreciate
you too
so we're taught you guys let's just
let's just uh talk about this we're
making three drinks pretty soon hang in
there I'm reading straight out of brain
saver we're talking about the topic how
alcohol destroys the brain
we're talking about how it does we're
going into incredible unique original
information from above about how alcohol
has effects on the brain and how it
works
so we're doing that we're also making
three drinks pretty soon so hang in
there we're making a wild blueberry
apple cider which is actually really
cool one of my favorites by the way
some pumped up about that
but we're going to read a little bit
more
even if someone has a large storage bin
of glucose eventually the liver becomes
Paralyzed by the by the alcohol
in this vitally important function so
you can be a dude
you can be somebody it's got a strong
liver you're young you got a liver
that's not oversaturated
and you could be drinking and the minute
you hit that point where you start
feeling the effects of the alcohol do
something for your body that means your
liver is at its saturation point now for
one dude that could be like 10 shots of
whiskey for someone else it could be a
sip of whiskey but the point is is
that's when the liver stops
feeding the brain and releasing glucose
to the brain
because the liver's job of releasing
glucose is halted it stopped its job
instead becomes soaking up alcohol so
here's how it goes
the liver's there to protect your brain
the more we drink
the liver is trying to stop that alcohol
from getting to the brain it can't
release glucose anymore to your brain
because it has to quit all its jobs it
has to stop working and it has to now be
just a sponge for the alcohol
here's the question right here I like
his recipes and some of the stuff he has
but saying that professionals don't know
about the liver and alcohol poisoning
and acting like the frontier of science
with no scientific findings very
interesting okay well that's kind of
funny
because I published how the cause of
multiple sclerosis is Epstein-Barr virus
but I published it also in details so
listen to this
almost eight years later Harvard took
that information and put it out there as
if they discovered it when it was
already published
and in New York Times best-selling book
and millions of those copies went around
the world and it became the number one
health book in the world so I got no
credibility you're saying when literally
science is poaching information which is
illegal
that's what legal tells me
and they're poaching that information
for their big universities out of little
old me a guy who knows nothing
out of his books that are best-selling
books New York Times bestselling books
and how about this one the true cause of
long covet
is reactivated Epstein-Barr another one
two
and that comes out of all this right
here
this book
so why is science taking all my
information because I published that
first
that long-haul covid is reactivated fcmr
why is science taking my information if
I have no credibility
why are they using all my info and how
about this why is alternative medicine
stealing all of the medical media book
information too those are just a couple
of examples
so before you say something like that
kind of like learn about this and learn
about the medical medium history right
read the books learn find out what's out
there
so think about that right there so yes
this is original unique information that
comes from above it gets published in
the medical medium books first and then
poached later and yes I'm sorry but
medical research and science doesn't
know what happens to the brain with
alcohol they still don't know
doctors even drink and they don't know
why they get tipsy or drunk and they
don't know what happens to the brain
while they're drinking so yeah sorry
but I really like the question though
because it it's great because it helps
me plug the fact that science is always
stealing all medical meaning books and
information so that's kind of cool all
right check this out
here's a cool part right here and I'm
glad you love medical medium information
because that was part of your comment I
love this info but
all right that's what people do now too
it's like I love I love his info uh but
um yeah that's what they do like you see
it every day now
I bet you love the info because heck
it's saved a lot of lives
all right let's go into it man because
we got a little bit more and then we're
gonna make some drinks okay ready at the
same time at the same time alcohol
pushes aside any glucose that is in the
bloodstream so alcohol becomes the
brain's number one choice for fuel
and you can you please tell me where
that is in science research
[__] can you find that somewhere that
alcohol
actually pushes glucose out of the
bloodstream and then alcohol itself
becomes the brain's number one form of
glucose
meaning fuel can you tell me where that
is is that in a research paper somewhere
no but it will be in five years and I'll
be proven right
because alcohol seems like glucose even
though in the end it isn't so remember I
was telling you alcohol is the ghost of
sugar your brain gets tricked out and
believes that alcohol is actually
glucose a fuel
the more alcohol you put in your
bloodstream the more your brain
identifies
the alcohol instead of glucose and
here's another problem when you get
alcohol in your bloodstream and this is
unknown to research in science when you
get alcohol in your bloodstream it
pushes glucose out
it pushes glucose away from the brain
your brain can only identify that
alcohol down
you guys I want to ask you guys a
question can you just be frank with me
and can you just be like open with me on
this okay I'm just sidetracked right now
completely
if the information from these incredible
eight books in the medical medium book
series is original and unique
and most of you guys know that because
you've been there and done that and did
everything
am I supposed to hide that and never say
that
like am I supposed to pretend that I got
all this information in these volumes of
books from some other source like some
study or something when it doesn't exist
and there is no study with all this
information am I supposed to lie and say
that my information isn't original
so I can fit in everywhere and not get
like kicked you know kicked in the back
I just want you to people okay let me
just ask you guys this this is just a
heart to heart I I know what a lot of
you guys are here for the drinks and I'm
about to make them but this is a heart
to heart what would you do please tell
me
if you woke up at the age of four one
morning and you heard a voice and it
gave you Advanced information
that has saved
countless lives you put that information
in incredible book series
there's not one eat better book out
there and this isn't an eat better book
there's not one healthy book out there
in the in the alternative genre anywhere
that has this information and that much
right
what would you do would you sit there
and be afraid to actually say it comes
from above
would you be afraid to tell the truth
that the information is unique and
original
and it can't be found anywhere but the
books
and you can prove it
would you lie so you can fit in with
everybody
would you lie so you could have
so-called credibility with everybody I
want to know what you would do tell me
what you would do
because
because as a humanitarian because that's
what a humanitarian is someone who saves
lives right I'm a messenger for Spirit
of compassion to get the information out
there and on a humanitarian way
am I supposed to lie
I want to know what you would do if you
had all this original information that's
never been published anywhere no study
no science no anything tell me what
would you do would you lie and say that
you got it from a research paper when it
doesn't exist just to make somebody
happy or would you say it was unique
original and pure and untouched and it
comes from above like the truth
because I still get punished every day
by somebody saying how dare you say
that your own information
is not original or unique and you
shouldn't be saying that so I would like
to know what you guys would do would you
hide it would you live a why would you
pretend it wasn't coming from above and
then pretend you got it somewhere where
you didn't
all right if you just got here we're day
one of the medical medium wild blueberry
drinks challenge we still got something
to do the amount of hate and attacks I
get is unreal you guys have no idea
and a lot of you don't see the amount of
pushback I get for sharing this
information so people can heal it's
unreal
it's unreal and I could stop tomorrow
I could literally stop tomorrow
and just call it quits
easily and just say I'm done
but I'm in it for the chronically ill
and I'm gonna fight fight for The
Chronic Leo and that's what keeps me
doing it
and you know and that's why you guys
when you share this information and
everything citing Vector medical means
important of course all that
and it's all free I don't charge for it
am I doing groups and you know and
charging five thousand dollars for a
group three thousand dollars for a group
of people to join in and then give them
some like packet and a bunch of info and
right am I doing that no it's free it's
in the books but I do notice that a lot
of people don't read the books and they
did a little celery just for a little
while
they tried maybe a little something but
they didn't read the books and learn and
then they go join these groups that are
charging three thousand five thousand
dollars two thousand dollars they join
these groups to learn information that's
not even medical medium it's a hosh posh
and mishmash of everything else
it's just so sad
okay so let's go at the same time
alcohol pushes aside any glucose that is
in the bloodstream so alcohol becomes
the brain's number one choice for fuel
so this is really important right here
because alcohol seems like glucose even
though in the end it isn't so here's how
it works alcohol when you drink it
seems like glucose to the brain but it
isn't but yet the brain only chooses
that glucose when it's saturated in the
bloodstream because alcohol pushes all
glucose away including numbing up the
liver shutting it down so it can't
actually release glucose alcohol is a
byproduct of glucose it's a byproduct of
sugar it's a ghost of what sugar was
so the brain becomes a victim of the
ghost effect of alcohol so when you see
somebody drinking and they're getting
tipsy their brain becomes a victim to
the ghost effect of what was alcohol
that piece of information when I got
that from Spirit compassion I was just
like blown away because how crazy is
that
it's a ghost of what sugar was
it's mind-blowing information
so the brain becomes a victim of the
ghost effect of alcohol
that's what happens as more alcohol
enters the brain a person exhibits more
drunken
that is
Behavior when someone gets to the point
of drunken Behavior slurred speech
inability to function normally that
means the brain is already starting to
starve to death
check this out
this is how mind-blowing this is
when you're at the point of slurring
your speech when drinking
your brain is already starting to starve
to death so what you're witnessing from
the person is a person's brain starving
to death so if you're hanging out with a
bunch of friends and people are slurring
their speech because they're drinking
what you're witnessing is their brain is
starving to death
it's dying
it's actually dying if you have a party
filled with people that are drunk or
getting drunk what you're seeing with
them walking around and kind of like
walking around like this and slurring
your speech what you're seeing is their
brains are actually dying they're
starving to death how insane is that
and here's a key understanding most of
the symptoms we associate with
drunkenness and alcohol poisoning are
only from alcohol itself
most are symptoms of the brain starting
to die
you guys when someone is experiencing a
symptom of drunkenness
what it is it's a symptom of the brain
starting to die
unbelievable anyway you guys we're day
one to Medical mean and while
blueberries challenge we're gonna make
three drinks
Deborah says this information is
mind-blowing the more alcohol you
consume in an evening or day the less
glucose the brain absorbs and then fuels
itself with if we think of the Optimum
as 100 of glucose entering the brain and
keeping it alive then drinking alcohol
brings that glucose performance down to
five or ten percent
depending on how drunken someone is
that means that we're supposed to be
getting a hundred percent glucose
Optimum levels of glucose to the brain
on a daily level when you're drinking
and getting drunk you're only getting
five to ten percent levels of glucose to
the brain as your brain is starving to
death
it's like taking a fish out of water
watching it gasp for air on the beach as
it takes in oxygen instead of water then
putting it back in the water to revive
it and then taking it back out that's
like putting a fish
on the land or pulling it out of a tank
watching it gasp as its brain starts to
die and then dropping the fish back into
the water and letting the brain revive
then pulling the fish back out of the
water and watching it gasp for air and
then dropping it back in the tank and
watching it revive
the fish will stay alive although it
pays the price for being thrust into
survival mode this is what happens when
someone drinks alcohol regularly just
enough glucose is getting to the brain
to keep the person alive yet it's so
little that the person loses the ability
to function because they're drunk you
become a walking talking example of a
Dying brain
alcohol dominates our over glucose
getting to the brain because not only is
the liver intoxicated paralyzed and
cannot release enough glucose to get to
the brain but the brain chooses alcohol
over glucose
this is not because the brain needs
alcohol or because alcohol is good for
the brain again it's because the brain
is being tricked into thinking the
alcohol is the most accessible viable
form of glucose I want to make some
drinks you guys
just blows my mind the information
I can't even tell you so we're making
the brain detox challenge so that's
actually next not challenge brain detox
is what we're making all right so it's a
tonic so I'm excited you guys then we're
making a wild blueberry apple cider and
we're making also why blueberry sangria
so I'm excited okay so it's on three
page 320 on protocols let's do the brain
detox tonic
right here so if you got your protocols
book
okay page 320 and there's the recipe
right there
guys check it out
really pumped up about this
to put the book over here for a second
let's get going
so
that's right here
so in this one we're going to take some
coconut water and I'm gonna put it in
here so we're looking at two cups of
coconut water
starts with two cups of coconut water
right
and then we're going to start adding the
rest of the stuff in it let's put some
spirulina in here
one teaspoon of spirulina
let's get the teaspoon out
a little bit
okay one teaspoon of barley grass juice
powder
right that's the Bemidji stuff you guys
know I endorse these guys the best stuff
really incredible
you guys probably know why because I've
talked about it before
for the grass juice powder a teaspoon of
that goes in there as well now two
teaspoons of wild blueberry juice
let's crack it open
I like I'll measure it
there's one
there's two
boom I might need a shot wow blueberry
juice shots what I'm gonna use in a
second you all right we got that
okay now what else is going in here is a
drop of lemon balm
dropper
there we go now non-alcohol
no alcohol in here keep that in mind so
someone might say oh I'll put a lemon
balm in there I'll make that and then
it's an alcohol version right you don't
want to do that so that's the Bemidji
lemon balm that I use all right so
that's in there now
cool
and
um I'm gonna mix it up
now listen here's the wild blueberry
juice you guys Wyman's actually is on
sale right now 10 off check it out if
you get a chance this is day one
mixing it up
nice
you guys know I work with Wyman's
I endorse that incredible product right
there I want to keep that around forever
I want people to know about this I want
people to have this in their life
because it's that incredible
this was simple to make
powerful tonic
how easy was that one right there
that's the that's a drink I make when
family comes over
and everybody's everybody's doing the
brain detox Sonic
okay so here's the thing drink this and
15 minutes later do a chaser the Chaser
is eight ounces more of coconut water so
just letting you know
I got a chaser right here some coconut
water here we are that's the chaser
so you don't you know you don't drink
this all in one shot it's whenever you
finish this
15 minutes later
you do an eight ounce coconut water
chaser
there's a reason for it Spirit of
compassion with how it works and how it
works in the bloodstream and the body
this is a different form a way to do it
it's a brain detox tonic so you don't
have to send this all down in one shot
tastes delicious too which is incredible
so what you can do you can nurse it
you can take your time you can you can
drink it quick if you want to but either
way
15 minutes later you want to do the
eight ounce Chaser which is just eight
ounces of coconut water
so that's cool so that one's done
we got one drink down
foreign I'm going to turn this on get a
little hot we got the next one we're
gonna do
so one cup of wild blueberry juice
let's do that
let's get a cup
it's going into the pot
okay and then we're going to do a cup of
fresh apple juice
got the apple juice right here
nice okay
then we're going to do a little bit of
Honey or maple syrup I'm gonna do one
two three tablespoons of maple syrup
that's the one I want to use
one to three you can do one you can do
three
I'm gonna do
roughly round two a little bit more
nice
I'm gonna throw a cinnamon stick in
there
voila
I'm gonna turn up the temp I had it warm
it was already kind of like you know
going a little bit so I just turned up
temperature more I'm gonna put three
cardamon
pods in here
it's one
two
three that's whole cardamom right there
well you guys I'll show you on the
close-up too that's awesome Yep
see these are whole cardamoms right here
check it out those are strong by the way
they're really strong I put three right
in there because believe it or not
it's got a kick to it
one star anise
so there we go
there's the spiders these are the
dehydrated spiders right
they got a kick that's going in and
let's see four or five cloves
ah we got some cloves right here
four or five of them is good
boom
half inch piece of Ginger let's actually
get a paring knife out really quick
you can peel it
if you don't want to peel it you don't
have to if you don't want to I like to
peel it thinly slice it
one of the reasons why you want to peel
it too is just you know because if you
have company over and everything and
someone gets a peel in their mouth and
they're just like I mean some some of
the ginger skin in their mouth that's
not as fun
I've seen that happen so I was like all
right all right let me just peel this
back
thinly slice it
there we go
that's going in see these pieces you
guys
incredible
simmer for 10 to 15 minutes let it get
simmering for a little bit I'm gonna
move
some of this around
nice
all right so we're gonna make a wild
blueberry orange sangria if you guys
just got here this is day one of the
medical medium wild blueberry drinks
challenge
okay
so we're gonna make the sangria
looking around for Stuff
we're going to need this too
all right I love drinks
so I got the picture right here so I'm
going to use this so I'm actually going
to start out with making simple let's
let's just start by putting in three
cups of wild blueberry juice in there
actually I'll hold off for that for the
moment let me start with
no no I'll do that I think it's a good
idea
all right so we're gonna do three cups
you guys we're making these fast this is
like insane
like seriously we're making them pretty
quick right or
three cups right there
nice
I still need a shot
you guys don't mind right
bartender give me another
all right
if there's a feeling you get it's
different than like with alcohol
poisoning right or alcoholic beverage
beverages right the more I slurring my
speech because I'm getting glucose to
the brain instead no it doesn't work
that way I'm not learning my speech
here's how it works
when you get like real glucose like a
high quality glucose something like this
to the brain that has all that
anthocyanin in it it's an entirely
different experience
and it's it's incredible you know a
friend of mine who drank his whole life
I finally got him to quit right doesn't
drink anymore he's doing the wild
blueberry juice and he says it's like he
feels an entirely different Rush
but he you know he does it that he gets
on his treadmill and he's running on his
treadmill he's running on the wild
blueberry juice the wild blueberry juice
is getting to the brain the glucose the
whole bit I tell him it's anthocyanins
that are actually in the glucose from
the wobble regions that are getting to
the brain it's a really incredible
feeling all right let's go
all right I'm going to pour this in here
if you guys don't mind
just made a mess
but that's okay
AWS Bar and Grill gets a little messy
you guys we are not closing down AWS Bar
and Grill no way
only spilled a little bit
that's why I like the whole live thing
too because it's like
I don't know I don't like all that
pre-recorded stuff where they edit out
everything because they want the person
to look perfect they want everything to
be perfect I don't like that I think
there's something wrong with that all
right
now I'm going to start doing some
oranges I want to actually
um
we're gonna get some orange juice going
here so what I'm gonna do is squeeze
a bunch of oranges here so just give me
a sec
I want two and a half cups of orange
juice that's what I want so I'm going to
slice a whole bunch of oranges
if you guys don't mind
right
I'm gonna hand squeeze them you can use
uh you know citrus juicer if you want
I'm going to do just a little bit of
squeezing this way
I'm going to cut a few oranges
you guys don't mind
you know when I think about that
information about what alcohol does to
the brain
and it's starving the brain to death so
that when you actually have
when you actually have symptoms I call
them symptoms when someone's feeling
Tipsy it's a symptom it's not just
because it's a fun thing and it's
alcohol sure it might feel fun but it's
a starting of a symptom because their
brain is being starved to death when you
think about that it's incredible really
I mean
nothing is
seems which is
prime example of that how come research
in science doesn't know right
that these are actually symptoms because
the brain is starving
how come like they don't know that when
you think about that
I mean another Century can go by and
they'll never know what happens when
alcohol is go you know is is actually
um
what alcohol is doing in the brain and
the Damage that's being done another
Century could go by and they still won't
know
so I was like having this Advanced
information I like knowing all this
stuff if someone says well I don't drink
that's not really important to me that
piece of information aw because I don't
drink anything well then get other
important pieces of information from the
medical medium book series
get all the the anti-viral information
get the symptoms and conditions and the
causes information
get the different get the like
information on like how to get medals
out how to protect yourself get all that
information that's in there
if alcohol is not like your important
thing because you don't drink or you
don't care think about all the other
information that's in the books
so I mean that's important to know
Brenda says they call it sedating but
don't make the connection with the
glucose
foreign
they still don't know why it's sedating
they don't make the connection with any
of it
and they don't know that the brain is
actually being injured
they just observe things they don't
actually see inside they don't know
what's happening inside your bloodstream
in your brain they're sitting there
observing someone's reaction as they
drink alcohol like anybody can do that a
five-year-old can do that does that make
the five-year-old scientist
think about that right
I mean when you think like a
five-year-old can observe
a parent drinking
right
think about that for a second and still
have the same observation
as a 40 year old scientist
observing someone who's drinking
think about that one right there
is that five-year-old now a scientist
foreign
because they're still not going to know
what happens in your brain when you're
actually consuming alcohol if you guys
if you guys are doing like
keep in mind when you like see things
like the lemon balm I put in right
in the drink and stuff and all that keep
in mind you don't want alcohol in your
tinctures it's something I see every day
someone would be like I I I've done this
protocol from this guy or I've done this
this method or this you know protocol
and there's alcohol in all of the herbal
tinctures
and it just proves that alone is such a
huge mistake it's incredible
you guys I know I'm I'm wasting juice
out of some of these right here what
we're trying to do you know what
happened
these aren't juicy do you ever have an
orange that's actually not juicy so I'm
actually squeezing
like the heck out of these more so than
normal which is actually really funny
foreign
you can actually really squeeze like a
lot of juice out of it really easy
yeah Envy Doom says oh no not juicy yeah
that's your Bane
so you you actually experience that not
juicy oranges
yeah I know sometimes oranges are dry
you know totally
all right
we're gonna do obviously some more so
hang on you guys
driest set of oranges
yeah but that's okay because you know
because I got this drink right now
that's heating up
it's getting warm so that's cool
all right there we go now we're cranking
out the juice
I I squeeze my hand for a reason because
I when I do it for myself and everything
the reason why I like to squeeze by hand
is because it's the connection to the
food it's connection to the fruit on the
tree it's all of that it's connecting to
the food that's going to enter into my
body so there's I don't talk about it
much but there's all these spiritual
connections that I actually have with
the food and I talk about a little bit
of that in life-changing Foods right if
you've ever had that book or or read
that book
there's always these spiritual
connections with our food
and I never have time to talk about that
I never have time to go into that or
into a lot of details of that because
I'm really busy making sure that
everybody has the information they need
to get out of chronic illness and then
the spiritual stuff is you know is is
fun about food for sure the connections
and everything and we can talk about
that but there's a lot of people
suffering
they're in so much body pain physically
they're suffering mentally
and I just try to get out that
information because I want to save lives
I want people to heal I want their lives
to be saved right it's a lot of juice
coming out of these big ones right here
so this is great
so I do it by hand because I want that
connection
rise of Melton says I love to eat with
my hands as well
yeah so definitely
all right you guys
we're in AWS kitchen right here
making a mess like we always do
lupus free with celery 333 someone just
said to me you don't believe
my antidotes why should I believe yours
meaning me curing my lupus with mm and
him losing weight on intermittent
fasting like it's equivalent
yeah
totally get it I totally get it
I do
Michelle L says impressive hand strength
thank you
here we go
we're almost done that's it
you know what
foreign
here we are
cool you guys
we got it
coming together
I will eat these oranges later
foreign we got our orange juice in there
okay we're gonna put uh some maple syrup
in this one
I'm gonna put a little bit of this in
two to three tablespoons of maple syrup
now you can do honey keep that in mind
I was just doing maple syrup today but
there's nothing wrong with honey
absolutely that's a great way to do it I
do it all the time with honey so that
works
not a problem at all
okay
and then I'm going to add some sparkling
water that's next actually
so I'm going to put one cup of sparkling
water in here
nice
I'm gonna give it a little stir
okay now I'm gonna chop up an apple
you guys thanks for hanging out with me
during all this I really appreciate it
without your support
I don't think I could have gotten
through that without your support
all right so I'm gonna pop some apple in
here okay
so here's what I'm going to do with this
apple
you guys see that right there
I'm gonna do these thin slices like this
I can put a decent amount of Apple in
there if you want
I don't care about the core in this I'm
totally fine with that so I'm just gonna
do this seeds pop out on their own if
you guys take a look
nice thin slices right there
[Music]
so one apple chopped
you can chop them any way you want to
chop them
I put them in like this these
nice half slices right
and the seeds just come out perfectly
take a look at that if you guys want to
see
there we go
all right I got that
so now I'm going to do a pair
nice got two different kind of pairs
here
so I'm going to do the same thing same
chopping method I'm going to do these
slices
all right if I get this in focus
nice
so I'm doing the same kind of style this
is the way I like to do it but you can
do it the way you want to do you can
chop up your pair anyway and put it in
there
there we go
that's the way I like to do it so I'm
going to pop these in
credible all right we're gonna do some
strawberries next
foreign
just going to cut off these green tops
right here
I'm gonna eat those later
and so I'm going to give this a nice
slice
in this way
okay
cool
it's a nice strawberry right there
check that out
I'm gonna do a couple more
nice
let's get these in
maybe I'll do a couple more too just
maybe
slip for this one here nice big one
right there huh
these are incredible drinks because when
you're consuming them think about what
you're doing what you're putting in your
body that's a whole nother thing too
it's not just about enjoying them and
enjoying the flavor
it's about what you're doing for
yourself
that's the whole point so good for the
brain
okay and then I'm gonna do some orange
slices next I'm going to take this
Orange right here and cut off the bottom
of it
and then I'm gonna
pull these nice orange slices right here
you guys can take a look
okay
there we go
he's going here too
this is
guys what do you think
are you doing this recipe with me some
of you guys doing it right now
as well
and I'm going to mix it around right
here
this is actually almost to a
boil it's been lightly
cooking there
you mix up the flavors when you move it
around a little bit I'm just separating
some of these apple slices there we go
pear slices are all coming together
just incredible this is
right here
now I'm going to put a whole cup of
vodka in it
no I'm not of course not this is really
an amazing drink I'm gonna tell you
right now
all right now I'm going to serve it
would you guys like some
um
it's like a bowl
you can see
all right hang in there we are serving
you guys right now
I got a lot of serving to do because aw
bars Bar and Grill is actually opening
any minute so you guys just a wild
blueberry
sangria is what this is that's what I'm
serving
an aw Bar and Grill is going to open
soon so let me just
foreign
look I do make messes
if there's something you want to learn
you guys we just opened crap
I thought it would get done in time
before AWS Bar and Grill opened
and
cheese
guys hang on
oh you guys first
I didn't make it in time so
like AWS Bar and Grill just opened up
hey guys I know you've been waiting
I know
all right
yeah you want a shot okay okay you got
it what's uh
what's your poison
[Music]
shot
okay
how are you guys holding up okay all
right
chickadees here chickadee don't get too
close to the pot last thing I want is a
baby chick in that pot cooking
you guys it's the wild delivery apples
wait that's next we got to do that hold
on here
oh it's this one now this is next
too much going on
AWS Bar and Grill is open guys you're
making me nervous please hang in there
all right
this is next we're going to strain that
right in here
can I just make a mess
are you guys okay all right just hang on
there I know you guys need all drinks I
get it
I got the
wild blueberry apple cider right here
I'm gonna put it back in the pot
actually
I strained it
back in the pot
and I'm going to get it
this is the apple cider
but it's the wild blueberry apple cider
have you guys tried this yet
it's insane
you know
this is just incredible
a little cinnamon stick in there
star anise
for cinnamon stick right there and you
put the star in these right in there too
right
what would you like
put a little bit more in here too
there you go
there we go incredible
I got a lot of drinks to drink all right
what do you guys want
we have to get as many drinks served for
you guys as possible before Mrs Ferguson
comes downstairs
all right dehydrated spider it is indeed
I see that comment right there you guys
we have our drinks here I'm going to try
the wild blueberry apple cider spare
with me
oh my God
that is freaking amazing
that is amazing
have you guys tried this I'm serious
like this is incredible
hmm so good
Michael Carrington says is that the
phone ringing
God so wild blueberry juice is what
makes it happen
you guys know right 10 off right here is
the Wyman's wild blue Bridges
link is in description profile
stuff is incredible
this stuff is amazing it's like it's
liquid gold man
it's incredible
but I like to think what it's doing for
me too what it's doing for my brain you
guys know I work like 18 hour days
Bar and Grill yeah a lot of [__] is
happening
yeah it's crazy over here
onion rings again okay all right onion
rings I don't have anything to write
this down yeah we don't have computers
here
I usually have the pen in the paper
onion rings right what else chicken we
don't know
no it's not that it's a vegan place it's
not a vegan place we we serve everything
to everybody that's not it it's just
that the chickadees here
yeah chickadees here
chickadee don't fall into there please
okay chickadee wants a shot
tickety
okay we don't serve chicken when
chickadees here at AWS Bar and Grill
yeah exactly we have a
all right this is just
Mrs Ferguson just be careful that last
stare at the staircase is slippery
don't fall oh oh my God Miss Ferguson
just fell
oh my God I gotta call 9-1-1 right now
miss Ferguson just just
Miss Ferguson hang on
Emergency Services yeah what's my
emergency Mrs Ferguson was walking down
the staircase
and she slipped yeah we were just
we were just washing the staircase one
of my helpers she's on the ground right
now she's complaining her back is
hurting
yes getting um yeah get Emergency
Services here as soon as you can
all right Steve Davis Bar and Grill is
actually out of control right now
I think I'm getting tipsy
I do I think I'm getting tipsy but in a
good way
really good can I try the sangria does
anybody
all right
well let me just try
what happened
germs
they don't like the double dipping they
don't like me sipping off it they say
I'm Jeremy
I didn't know it was that Germany
sorry you guys
okay uh
if he says time to call Dr nesbian Dr
nesmick
you need Dr Nesbitt to save me huh
you want to call knock Dr Nesbitt
Dr Nesbitt is around when chickadees
around so you don't have to worry about
that because Dr Nesbitt knows that if
chickadee is here then Dr Desmond wants
to be here
Dr Nesbitt has to
look out for chickadees make sure
chickadees end up in this pot right here
doctor nurse but what would you like
would you like a shot okay W's Bar and
Grill is becoming quite crazy right now
Chris don't tell me the phone is going
to ring too
God
you guys
you guys calm down
please
Dr Nesbitt wants a real shot of alcohol
he does not want wild blueberry juice
right recognizant would you like some
wild blueberry juice Darkness but does
like his wild blueberry juice
Dr Nesbitt Dr Nesbitt the last time you
did this something went terribly wrong
and
Dr Nesbit
up your Nesbit there we go Dr Nesbitt
oh my God
sane Sue says my daughter is glad she's
homesick today she was so sad missing
school today and this has helped make
her day better
um doctor asked me what do you have to
say
Dr Nesbitt says hi
Dr husband says get better soon
please get better soon as fast as you
can
okay
oh crap
Dr Nesbitt just hang on
hey Debbie's going bro yeah
oh yeah no we're packed
no yeah I got everybody here I haven't
even served everybody drinks yep Dr
nesbitt's here too
Dr Nesbit sipping on his uh blue Bridges
Dr ass [__] you're gonna get yourself
all dirty
where you're going to get stained with
wild Uber juice do not wear white when
you make these drinks yes
you will have blue shirts
okay so what time we open to it's open
all day
exactly
okay
well Deborah says I drank almost two
bottles of wild blueberry juice last few
days and the aching knees I have been
experiencing the last few months is 90
gone love this stuff and the recipes
see
this isn't just juice
Lana says our Wyman's juice order is
arriving today I cannot wait will
tomorrow's day two of the medical mean
and wild blueberry juice
drink challenge so you will have your
wild blueberry juice ready for tomorrow
I'm gonna put this down Dr Nesbitt
because I know that's gonna spill
Bryce Melton says king of multitasking
I'm multitasking
I got to make a call Mrs Ferguson is not
off the floor yet 9-1-1 did not send
anybody yet
oh
well we got to be very careful Dr
Nesbitt
Dr Nesbitt your tail is in the wild
blueberry juice shot
your feathers are in the wild
blueberries you shot and the chicks are
really upset right now
okay
um
it's been an exhausting day
where's my wine glass
Dr Nesbitt you're gonna have to uh rest
in the lounge for a second
um Dr Nesbit just went into the lounge
okay uh
where's my wine glass
I forgot
I'm gonna have a glass of wine
a lot of blueberry drink challenge
deserves a glass of wine
it's a dry wine
I am a doctor and I'm drinking my dry
wine I got from Napa Valley
hmm a very good one
can you afford this wine it's 67
000 for one tablespoon of it
because in our Winery our wine is
ancient and it's good
someone told me it's just all grapes
you got pretty pretty incredible you
guys all right just hang in there
all right
you guys this was day one
of the medical medium
wild blueberry drinks challenge please
get the Emergency Services over here for
Doc for uh tell the doctor get doctor
over here for uh Mrs Ferguson she fell
down the stairs she slipped
and she was holding a glass of wild
blueberry juice
and it went all over her
she's blue but she's she's okay
I'm gonna take one more shot
bartender give me another I'll see you
guys tomorrow for the second day sign up
if you can
download your grocery shopping list it's
free it's a free challenge it's the way
we like to do it
check out oh wait wait wait oh I hear
I'm sick I'm sick I'm sick out there
like I hear it from friends out there
everybody
cold and flu tool kit
download the free cold and flu toolkit
this thing is just so kick butt it's
amazing download this one it's free go
to medicalmedium.com also look for the
link keep an eye on the website I'm
constantly updating it to the
macromedion.com with lots of information
seriously though you know people out
there they're suffering with the flu
they're suffering with the cold and flu
they're sick everything make sure they
have their cold and flu tool kit you can
download it for free right check out the
medical meme podcast I did one on
swelling recently it is an eye opener
and quite a great episode so check it
out medical meme podcast at Apple
podcast telegram I'm doing exclusive
audio messages I'm gonna do another
round pretty soon probably after the
challenge is over tomorrow
and we're going to do more telegram
messages so those are exclusive messages
you guys so make sure you subscribe to
my Telegram
feed whatever you call it
and make sure you're on the medical
medium newsletter because you can get
the information you need know what's
going on and everything else and heck
free recipes and all kinds of cool stuff
and everything
you guys Jackie B says yay thank you I
love those TG messages
you guys I will see you tomorrow
can't wait it's all I can say I am going
to have
this drink right now
um
that's insane that's so good and this is
good too
sangria
um
my God these are so great did you guys
have your shots yet
no let me take your shot chicken he
didn't want it today for some reason
chickadee what do you say
bartender give me another