so welcome to another in my fields
with my amazing co-host noah cyrus
and the amazing uh new york number one
bestseller
anthony williams aka medical medium
it's an honor man it's an honor it's
incredible i'm glad i'm here
yeah thank you so much for coming on
we've both seen your work like
tons of times my favorite was whenever i
saw you give kanye
a reading yeah um but
which is not an everyday occurrence no
he's like i i can do all this
it's like he's so cool but yeah it was
so nice to meet you
um lou has also
told me that i should start drinking
celery juice as well
so yeah so i'm excited to do this
gotta get you on the celery juice gotta
get me yeah of course of course it's so
good for you my god you can't pass that
up
what is it about celery juice that
it goes to the brain is what it does
it's the the most powerful electrolyte
there is you know you know how the whole
electrolyte thing
it's electrolytes got to give my
electrolytes you know everybody wants
you know everything with that well
that's what it is
it's like beyond that it's beyond that's
a complete electrolysis throw out the
gatorade
yeah yeah yeah that's true can you
imagine
right you know celery i mean have you
spoken to the sports people about
celery juice and replacing cakes yeah
you know it's funny they'd have to be
juicing it fresh on the field there have
to be somebody there
to pump it out like that and that could
happen why not yeah
why not absolutely i should talk to hey
i should talk to some sports people
about it absolutely that's not about we
actually have a sports scientist coming
on
soon yeah we've got the works yeah
he's trying to get my mind right while
i'm doing work so
this is like his way of like getting me
healthy slash having a
absolutely see because we we're kind of
a wellness
podcast in a sense but kind of relating
it to you know creativity and everything
else
entertainment fields um and the presence
for this fit for this um podcast is
uh in my fields so you what you
all your thoughts feelings everything
created on the inside creates your
outside i have a lot of those
so i want to relate back to you know the
celery juice and
and you know the healthy eating and
stuff is is it equally as important to
have a healthy mind while consuming
the healthy foods does that can does
that have any
it matters it does help absolutely but
you know there's some miserable people
out there
right there's some miserable i mean just
the whole bit right
you know someone has to you know
everybody knows somebody that's totally
like either grumpy all the time
bad attitude miserable never positive
right negative
hold up sorry can we shut that door over
there thank you sorry
no no no worries drill going on yeah the
podcast
yeah so there's i mean so but if they're
eating good
they could feel good and still be
miserable yeah all right and still be
negative
and still be everything else their mind
could be total just crap i mean
literally
and you know whatever it is but if
they're really taking care of themselves
they're eating good and everything else
they're going to be healthy while being
you know miserable so it's kind of funny
but yeah you want your mind right
because you want to live you want to
live at your best i mean when your
mind's right you're just you're now
living at your best in every way you can
possibly be so you want us
you want to be healthy minded you know
spiritually connected anything you can
do i mean
just going on a hike i was talking to
somebody the other day they went on a
hike they came back they're like
i'm transformed yeah transformed from
that did they have the celery juice
before
they saw a hawk flying yeah exactly they
saw a hawk flying by yeah
right and they were just checking it out
they saw a deer they saw a hog fly by
everything and they're just like i'm
transformed just from that alone right
yeah because we get we get so in our
heads i mean look
i mean look at the work everybody's
doing everybody's working everybody's
working so hard on everything their
projects i mean noah's like probably
cranking out the music
it's like you know there's a lot going
on so getting getting that mind right is
yeah but i think even when i am like
doing a ton of music
and i'm working really hard lou knows
this as well like
i tend to actually get in my fields
and get depressed and get anxiety
but the one time that like right now i'm
feeling great because i'm
working out every day i'm doing my best
to like
you know eat really healthy i actually
made cake last night that doesn't count
but like like i do my best to like
because the only time i actually
feel right and feel like i can like
create well communicate well
is whenever i'm eating healthy and
exercising every day
like without going to the gym like i
wake up like so drowsy and like i
i don't know there's just something
about that that completely opens
your mind yeah you're moving your blood
you're circulating
toxins that are floating around in there
because what happens is those toxins
just build up
and they they build up they get into the
brain they sit inside the liver
then your liver gets stagnant and
sluggish and then you're eating things
you're not supposed to eat well well
whatever someone might think they're
supposed to eat things and then so
whatever but you're eating things that
may not be good for your liver
and then it's getting really sluggish
and then all of a sudden you're dragging
and you're just like dragging your butt
you wake up the morning you don't feel
clear you don't feel good you get
depressed
for no reason or and all that just
starts kicking in and really
it's about moving those toxins through
and everything celery cheese is a big
piece of it it's why
it's why spirit of compassion brought
celery juice to the world because
it it gets it helps people get all that
going it's just it's part of it
let's elaborate on that spirit of
compassion yeah yeah
so medical medium where does that come
from well it comes from my my
great-grandfather
uh named me the medical medium when i
was a child so that's when when i got to
receive the gift of hearing a voice
perfectly clear that tells me what's
going on with somebody's health so
anybody around me
yeah that's how it all started yeah so
then i dedicated my life doing this work
the whole time helping out thousands and
tens of thousands of people over the
decade
over the decades and then eventually
spirit of compassion said you have to
put this all
in in writing yeah so then i published
the books yeah and that's
what happened the books are out there
millions of people around the world have
them
they're moving their lives forward the
celery juice is one of the tools one of
those
those hidden tools and that that's just
no one ever
knew that this could really change the
lives of so many people
millions right now around the world are
healing from it yeah they're they're
they're healing
diseases illnesses symptoms they've they
couldn't it was unimaginable to get
rid of yeah celery juice is part of that
and spirit of compassion the voice i
hear because that's that's what the
voice told me it's the spirit of
compassion
yeah and um and that's what i've been
doing my whole life listening to that
voice
when you say you hear a voice right yeah
yeah does it come in
as like clear words to you like is it
your mind that you're hearing are you
hearing another
like male or female or how does that
come across you whenever you
hear spirit i think you're the first
person to ever
ask that question in that way in that
way like
is it something you hear in your head
yeah or is it something
else and it's out it's from out here so
it's like having like
you hear me now clear right i hear the
same way from the spirit of compassion
from the voice i hear clear like you
hear me right now
the same voice every time same voice
every time and it can be blocked a
little bit too because it's coming into
the right ear so i could take my hand
and just do this and kind of block it a
little bit because it's coming it's real
time it's in real time
right now anytime it's coming through
yeah and that's how it works so it's not
in my head it's not like i'm channeling
i'm not channeling anything
or it's not my intuition and i'm kind of
thinking what does my voice inside of me
say or what is that
what does that child voice in myself say
or what is no that's not it at all
it's a voice that's been basically
torturing me since i was four years old
so there you go so
you like be on a date and you say
something wrong and then the spirit of
compassion is like no
not that exactly always correcting me
always trying to keep me you know
making sure i say the right things all
of that because
what it is it's about i work for
everybody i work for everybody who's
chronically ill i work for people who
are struggling with anxiety crippling
anxiety and depression exactly all these
things and
let's work together after this interview
hey look we'd love to and aches and
pains and all the fatigue and all the
mystery fatigue do you know anybody
who's mystery
tired they're like more tired than just
tired parents
yeah absolutely i feel like i've been
slept since 2005.
so like yeah
we have to get strong we got to get that
energy back and so there's so many
people dealing with all these things
they're going around but we're all
supposed to pretend it's normal
we're all supposed to pretend that it's
a normal occurrence happening
yeah that we're supposed to be sick now
everybody's supposed to have a symptom
or something wrong with them that's how
we're that's kind of how we're go like
it's the new normal
oh what do you got you got a thyroid
problem oh whatever it actually is it's
scary yeah right yeah
and so but it's not supposed to be like
no and that's
it's like a constant complain of
illnesses exactly
i mean you know as complaints can be but
i mean i guess we're conditioned
to be negative as a race anyway yeah so
i mean if we were conditioned to be
positive then a negative negative
situation comes in we would kind of
brush it off because now we brush off
the positive situations as it's because
it doesn't feel right to us
because it's not the normal feeling of
it exactly um so celery juice
in terms of is it the placebo effect is
it the actual juice that's healing
people or is it people believing
that this or is it a mixture of both
well when did placebo fix
the world i don't get it wouldn't
everybody be better placebo worked
true think about this a placebo worked
yeah they would have ingeniously
you know science of research would have
placeboed everybody out to get to get
them better
they'd all be better everybody would be
better yeah because
all you need is any kind of placebo tell
somebody that this pill works if it
doesn't they should be better
yeah it's a placebo yeah but see so
placebo doesn't work
it never did yeah if it did i mean
i could hand you like a candy corn okay
a little piece of candy and say hey like
you know what i mean we can
it just you can't you you can't get
better on that yeah
i believed it and for a fact 100 it
would
well because in terms of how i live my
universe if i believe things for fact
yeah they shall appear well you know
what when you're when you're
when you're bedridden yeah and you can't
push out of bed
and your body your body's covered with
exomar psoriasis yeah and you're really
sick
and and there's no placebo that can fix
that yeah
it just isn't i don't care what doctor
whoever comes in and says
take this pill and it's a placebo yeah
you're going to get out of bed you're
going to be able to function you're
going to get rid of that brain fog and
no that brain fog stays no matter
what's happening that's the difference
when you're chronically sick
man it's a whole other story and i've
been batting for the chronically sick
that's the whole thing i'm the messenger
to
kind of have their back because they've
been swept under the carpet and
kind of pushed aside for the decades
it's been unbelievable right
what has happened and what's going on is
science and research
hasn't actually had the answers yet for
people who are sick on that level
but celery juice big difference what
goes on you know it's
it's it's hey there's people who tried
everything done everything
every diet every kind of lifestyle every
kind of supplement they tried all kinds
of modalities they tried everything
right
and they're still stuck but when they
bring celery juice in
they're getting better and those are
people that were like skeptical about it
yeah we're skeptical i mean i know
people are like that's not gonna work
celery juice i chew on celery i have it
in my tuna salad
celery's not gonna fix me and they're
drinking the celery juice for two days
and they're negative about it
and they're like oh my god my hip is
getting better what the hell is going on
here this is the freakiest thing ever
that's how it's working and it's
spreading it's spreading like wildfire
you gotta remember something you guys
there's no money behind it celery juice
isn't a trend because
it was like backed by tons of money to
make it trendy
yeah celery juice is trendy because the
stuff
works yeah it just does i think you've
single-handedly pushed the price of
celery up
in los angeles yeah yeah yeah yeah
no it's crazy it's been you should come
out with your own line of celery
your own farm of celery
is that is there a difference for you
between say organic celery and kind of
normal normal celery or celery or that
or organic fruits in general do you have
to juice it what if you just
eat a celery you can eat it it's good
for you it's not going to fix anything
better juice it yeah it's not going to
fix anything eating
squeeze the [ __ ] out of it drink it yeah
it never fixed anybody eating it it just
hasn't
it but it's the juicing has to be
juicing on an empty stomach
yeah that's you know 16 ounces minimum
on an empty stomach
32 ounces and you're moving forward i
mean you're moving forward that's a lot
of celery
64 ounces yeah if you really have
something that's major going on with
your health is that every day
gross does it taste gross sometimes it's
like sweet and salty
sometimes it's like just too astringent
and like bittersweet i'm asking because
i'm gonna go home and start chugging
celery juice
no joke i need it the celery's been
pretty good lately out here in la
like it's pretty good it hasn't been so
astringent it's been pretty good i think
you're gonna like it
all right i'm doing it the funniest
thing is i i've never eaten celery ever
me either i feel like it tastes like
[ __ ] i hate celery but if it's dipped in
ranch but noah
when you juice it it actually tastes
better than eating it really
or something to make it better it has
like a sweet taste to it when you drink
it
but yeah when i eat it like i have to
like dip it in hummus or do some other
[ __ ] to it but
me lives it in ranch yeah
exactly yeah i'm your worst nightmare
i'm like chicken fingers
like yeah pizza yeah i thought you were
gonna give me a reading be like i'm
sensing some chicken fingers
in here i actually have a question
okay so it says you're you
really discovered like that you had this
amazing gift when you were four
yeah that's when it started at age four
with your grandmother
right there and um you just had
you kept getting this feeling that she
was sick with
cancer well i couldn't avoid it because
the information came through all the
time
so spirit spirit of compassion would say
you know this is what she has going on
and you know you're four years old you
don't know what the words mean
so you're trying to pronounce my
grandfather died when i was four of lung
cancer so that's why
yeah so it's crazy so that's why i
wanted to ask you like
when you got that did you did they take
her to the doctor
yeah a few a few weeks later a few weeks
because she was fine she didn't have a
symptom
there was no symptoms she was perfectly
fine but it took about three weeks
later and took her in because i was
saying it too much
and so so someone spoke to you about
what your
your gran your man of compassion yeah
had
yeah i'm bringing spirit of compassion
was telling me oh my god you know
pronounce lung cancer did you name
spirit spirit of compassion or is that
that came from the voice
spirit of the comp spirit of compassion
when i asked so many questions are you
an
angel are you just someone are you a
ghost it's not a ghost
i'm not talking to you you know it's
amazing until this day
it's funny there's there's there's a
whole group of people in the world
that have healed from the medical medium
information that no
it's not a ghost they know what the
information is because
it's it's advanced medical information
ahead of science and research right
so what happens and doctors are using it
all across this country and
globally they're using it these books
are all over doctor's offices you know
all around the world
and but then there's a group of people
that thinks i'm the celery juice guy
that talks to a ghost
i mean i like that one too i think
that's cool that's cool and
but the bottom line is it's yeah spirit
of compassion i got that
um from spirit you know i've once in a
while i'll say spirit to make it short
but every time i make it short like that
then some people like oh you talked to a
ghost
yeah but spirit of compassion is like
you know i've always told you it's
spirit of compassion why are you saying
spirit you're cutting me short yeah you
know
yeah yeah absolutely so you were for how
was you feeling could you could you
remember your feelings at the time of
when you heard this voice oh yeah it was
it was just
it was shock yeah it was shock i mean i
always say
i always say the spirit of compassion i
always say like why me
because i'm not really the the most
spiritual guy i mean i know people
they're really spiritual connected
spiritually connected i mean they're
like on mountaintops
they're like they're like praying
they're like 40-day fasting
they're they're breathing air and that's
it you know like doing all kinds of
things right like you know
and you know and they're in retreats
around the globe and they're in the
amazon and they're just like they just
disappear and they come out and they're
just coming out they come out of the
amazon naked
after like two weeks of being bitten by
mosquitoes they're like
they're connected right naked vibes yeah
yeah they just do things like that right
me you know it's not like that and i
always say the spirit well how come me
and spirit said because
you can handle it because it's really
difficult
it's really difficult on a way because
you can't
you don't live a normal life whatsoever
yeah and i mean a normal life i mean
you're just that's it when it started
happening it was
it was like okay you know look i
couldn't pursue anything else couldn't
pursue a dream couldn't pursue anything
else couldn't do
anything it had to be this only there
was no way out
wow and it takes it takes a skin for
this yeah and i didn't know i have the
skin for it but
but apparently i i might have it because
i'm still
here and i didn't jump ship no so it's
yeah
does the spirit uh of compassion ever
talk to you about was it predetermined
you were supposed to was this pre-birth
or is it
of a spiritual nature or did they say
where they why they come to you where
they come from
what plane they live on i think it's the
strongest that that can handle the
strongest that survive it
yeah you know because when i when i
asked questions a lot of that it was
given to others but they didn't stay
here long
yeah because it wasn't easy
the teenage time is the hardest when
you're a teenager with it that's when
you lose it that's when you lose your
mind with this gift yeah
because you want to like just be normal
you want to do normal things you want to
have fun and you're hearing a voice
telling you that someone's got a brain
tumor you hear a voice
non-stop you go into a crowd and then
everybody in that crowd is being
assessed by spirit and
information is flying in coming in you
know if i get on if i get on a plane or
something like that
everybody on that plane i mean i was on
a plane one time
and uh you know my assistant was sitting
with me because i have to go with an
assistant because
it's just too much with the readings and
and all of that
and so so i'm i'm on the plane and
there's all this commotion going on all
this commotion from spirit
well actually well there's commotion
going on on a plane like stewardesses
are running around there's all this
stuff happening
and spirit tells me that somebody in the
back is seizuring
so they're seizuring in the back wow
it's like it's a guy back there at
seizuring and everything so
i tell my assistant so the finally
everything calms down after about 20
minutes half an hour or so
and then my assistant asked the
stewardess what's happening and she goes
there's a man back there seizuring
and it's it's always there and i can't
get away from it and when i was a
teenager
just think about that that's a difficult
time for everybody
when this is all you have to do or all
you you all you're supposed to do you
can't get out of it you can't get away
from it
you got to be strong yeah i mean there
was times like i'm not
i'm not going on yeah with this i'm i
might jump ship so
but you know what i hung in there and i
think that's what predetermined it
it's like okay picking you you can
probably handle it for some reason yeah
who knows what that reason is
yeah but yeah that's how it went i mean
obviously the reason is this
yeah spreads spread the knowledge of of
health so is it only the the medical
that
the the spirit of compassion speaks to
you about it's the most important so if
you was to say eat a pizza it'd be like
nah bro not today don't eat that
well you know what of course like small
talk like that
yeah you know it's always there with
spirit absolutely don't worry
spirit's never short for all that stuff
yeah without a doubt
but the medical is the most important
because if you don't feel good
yeah if you're if you can't like do your
work if you can't live your life
if you can't be happy in your
relationship because you're sick if
if you just got diagnosed with something
and and the doctor said well
hey your body's attacking itself because
you got an autoimmune disease
which actually is incorrect how it works
the body doesn't attack itself but the
point is when you're
driving from that doctor's office and
you've been told you got something yeah
you're miserable you're in misery it
takes over so many people are like oh my
god what is this now i got like thyroid
problems now
or what do i have i have this and and
it's hard so
medical is the most important and that's
the whole point it's your health it's
the most important thing yeah
i agree yeah yeah so in terms of say
for example um can can diet uh
make you know aid in anxiety and
depression
and all these type of aspects to the
human you know psyche
or uh does it have an adverse effect on
it should i say
well it has diet plays a role in getting
those things better
yeah but the problem is science of
research doesn't know
why or how someone can get better why
food does work
doesn't work we're still in those really
early stages of understanding it
what's the cause of anxiety unknown yeah
it's unknown right now right that's what
it is
well spirit of compassion knows the
cause of anxiety mystery anxiety
the cause i write it in the books i put
it in the books the information is there
people have been able to heal it because
they know the cause that's what i've
been able to do
is with this voice that comes to me i've
been able to bring that information
forward
and it's never happened before it's
never happened yeah there's an actual
cost to anxiety there's actual cause for
all these illnesses for aches and pains
tingles and numbness ringing in the ears
you know all of that you know everything
from restless leg syndrome to neuropathy
to headaches migraines they're they have
no causes for all yeah
why do your ears ring mind you that
sometimes
like am i is there something wrong with
me well
honestly if there is please don't tell
me because i'm a really big
hypochondriac
and i go to my cardiologist and have him
take blood all the time and he's always
like noah you've got to stop coming
because you're okay
yeah and so like i'm really crazy about
that stuff so
don't tell me if something's wrong but
how come that does happen
what is that it stops after a second
yeah but that's different that's like
just
little little earrings comes and goes
once in a while
no maybe that's your spirit of
compassion trying to get through
i have i do have to say like for me
i think we've talked about this before
my dad is very spiritual
and as am i so like i different from you
my whatever my like feelings that i get
or not like
so standing next to somebody and
somebody will tell me what's going on in
their lives but like i've definitely
always had like a more spiritual
connection where i've been able to like
with
being in my house or like things like
that or like i just have very strong
connection with my grandfather who i
know for a fact that i like get
these message from messages from you're
connected i'm very connected
my dad was very connected my whole life
and like i think that's where i
definitely get that from
yeah and like i don't know i think
that's always been like when i was a kid
i was actually like i would get kind of
freaked out
because like i lived in a very like
historical home in a historical part of
nashville where there was a battle of
franklin and
all the energy is so actually heavy i
know that's like
not your field of like vibes that you
get but i that's just something that
like i grew up with was like i would be
at home and i could like
feel like oh my grandfather is like
sending me like a message
what do you think about that do you
believe in that
oh absolutely absolutely i mean i could
use spirit for that i could use spirit
for those things
oh yeah i mean i can but it's it's never
the most important
when and i'm not saying that's not
important that's important 1 000
but when a mom can't get out of bed to
take care of her three children
and she loses her part-time job and
she's like
and she can't even barely walk or take a
shower because that chronic fatigue hits
her
and no one nowhere can help her 20
doctors 10 neurologists
10 cardiologists um everything
information on the internet can't help
her
yep and that's the most important so
that's what that's what the books have
done it's for millions that are in that
condition
and that's why i have to keep on using
that so if if i do take the time out
and and go the other direction
spiritually which i love to do don't get
me wrong i love to do
have you used spirit yeah absolutely
absolutely i have for for all those
different things exactly
but once again the need is unbelievable
there's a way there was a waiting list
to talk to me
back six years ago that was in the
millions that's how many
people are sick so i i i you know
i feel guilty if i do the more
fun spiritual connected stuff i feel
guilty literally because there's so many
children
that are oh my god so many children are
suffering and struggling yeah and they
have the worst conditions meaning
they're just
literally and their whole bodies are
covered with eczema and they can't even
put you you can't even put a t-shirt on
your son or your daughter because the
eczema is taking over and
you have to just live at home and you're
look going to doctor's offices every
single day like
these kinds of things like you know and
it's it's it's moms with like
with anxiety that's so crippling they
can't drive and it's all these things
that
that i had i have to like be focused on
and get that information so when people
tell me they go like you know like
you know talk to me talk to me about you
know the spiritual connection about this
and tell me what what's going on in the
universe
tell me to all of it i can i can tap in
without a doubt and ask spirit of
compassion questions but then
i feel like oh my god there's so there's
so
there's the weight the weight of the
suffering
yeah the struggling and you know when
you feel good like you guys feel good
you guys feel good
you know and and i feel good and you
know when you feel good
you just don't know what's out there
sometimes yeah until you run into a
friend or something you haven't talked
to the wall and you're like what
happened to you
yeah where what what are you doing what
do you mean you know and
and but so so that's why but i love the
spiritual connect
i love all of that like i love helping
someone
really get in touch with the people that
have passed over the
their loved ones in different ways or
what's happening in the moment like
is the ringing in their ear some some
something yeah a message coming through
what was that dream
you had the one that the one that like
had so much meaning to it
yeah i've totally had like dreams
exactly yeah
it's actually that's what i mentioned
like that's why i looked right at you
and said what is that dream
it's like that dream is i love going
into those dreams
and talking spirit of compassion and
being like what does her dream mean
because that is like that's there's
something there was it a past life
was it something in the future that we
don't know about was it something in the
moment where it's about to happen or is
it a direction where you're going to be
focused on soon because of a passion
inside of you is it
healing a wound that you have from a few
years ago from somebody
is the dream about a wound that's
healing because you had kind of a bad
a betrayal going on or something some
kind of trust was broken
and all of that that's powerful stuff i
love it
i want to dedicate time on it i can't
yeah
i can't that's how it is it's funny
because um
i had a dream recently and i beat myself
up
for not remembering the detail of it but
i i dreamed that i found the formula to
see the other side while still being
alive
yeah and i saw the formula on some paper
we were running all these weird tests
like using human blood and [ __ ] like
that and then all of a sudden you would
have that dream i would have that dream
right
and they would have that dream and then
literally
um we did all those tests and it went on
for ages and then
there was just this paper and it was
just believing you could see the other
side
but i couldn't remember what the formula
was for it
and i was like [ __ ] and it felt so real
yeah yeah and there's there's reasons
for that
one thing you get connected to you want
to get connected to is angels you want
to
always focus about angels and focused on
angels
you believe in god yeah i believe in god
absolutely but
hey high five for god but but but at the
same time if someone believes in the
universe and that's what they believe in
and they don't believe in god but it's
the universe i'm i'm i stand behind them
yeah if they believe in the light
and there's some kind of light if they
believe in the creator if they believe
in nothing that we're on this big rock
and it's just a ball it's just a ball of
gravel and it's floating through space
and then you live and you die and that's
what they believe in
look i'm okay with that i mean i believe
in god
but but everybody yeah you just you got
your choice of what you want to believe
in you got your choice on what you yeah
exactly
have you asked spirit about religion
like if
oh my god something is it's been my past
time my past
my pastime is asking spirit every
question of the sun that isn't health
related
i mean when i'm when i'm on my time so
i'm totally flat-lined i'm like
i'm like meaning i'm totally exhausted
just finished the last book
and i'm i'm laying down on the floor and
i'm just like what more do you want out
of me
spirit and then be like hey can i ask a
question
can i ask a question you know i want to
talk about it
yeah i want to talk about other planets
yeah i want to talk about life on other
planets yeah i want to talk about
you know like whatever it is you know
before the phone rings
yeah and or a text message comes through
or something there's some emergency
crisis over the years that if you know
people need people in need
people in need but yeah wow what do you
think about life on other planets
what do i think about it yeah what do
you think you think it's it
has to be true right there has to be
there has to be life on other planets
it is true come on cause some
controversy come on
it is true tell us what you know let's
get nasa up in here
no it is true without a doubt of course
there is wow yeah yeah
as we know it or as something else i
mean i mean seriously
yeah the bottom line is oh well no
there's there's yeah
there's there's life on other planets
and it's as we know it too yeah
is the spirit of compassion i mean do
you believe that one thousand percent
they can't handle the truth
i think somebody i forget who it was was
somebody was like if i get elected as
president
i will tell you if they're aliens but i
saw a
son what about everyone rushing uh
area 51. yeah that sounds scary
i think i'll just watch from tv i'm
gonna watch the live stream
it's not a fast rush i mean it's a lot
of miles before you get to it
yeah a lot of bottom line too yeah the
first fence is just the first fence and
you got what 300 miles so yeah
it's just yeah it's not a quick rush
what are your views on uh
marijuana ooh look that was actually
just my next question
no way yes sorry survived in my fields
you know the bottom line is with that
it's like it i always that's one of
those soul decisions
yeah okay because there's there's a few
things that are so soul decisions
it's in the person's soul and i don't
have a place to say
yay or nay or or where i stand on it
yeah because it's it's different than
what's the cause of
rheumatoid arthritis what's the cause of
um
multiple sclerosis i have a stand that's
my place
yeah what's the cause of lupus i have a
stand i have a place in that
spirit allows me to have that marijuana
totally up it's a sole decision of
somebody whether
they think they need it don't need it
use it
don't use it it's one of those it's kind
of like abortion it's a sole decision i
have no place
to say you you shouldn't get an abortion
or you should get one i mean there's
that's
that's this is one of those this is one
of those epic soul decision places
like vaccinations it's like what you
know
some people think it'll save the world
some people think it it kills the world
some people think you know what i mean
it's like
it's like marijuana is one of those it's
like the sole decision that i have no
place to decide or actually give you
even my opinion on it because that's
something that's like
that's that that's something that's
deeper within
that you just can't you can't touch and
you can't play with it
yeah yeah would that be the same for
alcohol or is that something completely
different
that's actually different yeah oh there
we go
i'm a marijuana smoker so and cbd and
all those type of product
products and i feel like yeah yeah i'm
just actually the newer generation now
especially someone like myself
you know i don't really take medication
i don't really do any of that type of
stuff yeah and you know i'm about to
have a
a daughter in october so congratulations
thank you so much
i'm the fairy god so vaccinations
what do we feel about those that's the
same thing same thing it's like the
marijuana yeah
okay it's because what happens is
there's people that
they think there's they they believe
that without it the world will end
yeah and and that's that's in the soul
of the person
yeah and then there's people that
believe no you stay away from it
it's the worst thing you could ever do
yeah and and
and it's not just the decision that
occurs it's more than that
it's like something that you can't
penetrate it's it's it's part of
who they are in a soul that decides that
you see what i mean so it's
yeah it's it's like that so i have no
pla i have no place there meaning
i i mean do you get vaccinations do i
yeah i mean
i mean he has no he had no choice well
like you can do follow-ups
i still get my flu shot you get a flu
shot
yeah because you know my dad who freak
out on me okay my dad's all like you
need a flu shot
all the time you know my dad he's like
terrified of getting sick well i haven't
thought about it i mean i haven't
thought about it haven't i
i've had no need for i haven't gotten
any so i i haven't thought about it
i mean but but if you if you're thinking
about it
yeah and you're really worried or
something that's when it clicks in that
soul decision clicks in you know where
where you you know you can you can
research both sides
you can then decide whatever lands in
that area you know
that kind of thing like i've never had
to worry about any health stuff because
it's spirit compassion so
i'm a different i'm the wrong person to
ask that question
do you partake in a little herb i i
don't
but i've i've got a nice glass of red i
i no i don't
oh wow neither neither no i love that
okay i know but but but that has nothing
to do with someone else you know no no
i'm intrigued there's there's people
there's people that if they don't have
that glass of red wine i mean they
they might have a stroke because of the
amount of stress they're under yeah that
glass of red wine
is the saving grace on the weekend yeah
you know has probably saved a few lives
yeah sure used the wrong way and it's
probably ended a few lives yeah
bottom line but the bottom line is so
you know it but i've never yeah i've
never had
had any use for that that's awesome
you're the coolest person i think i've
ever met
like you and lou come on
you're so cool can i can i ask you is
there anything you're reading right now
or is that an improper question any good
books in my reading i'm kidding
yeah exactly exactly and i mean look
information has come through with that
yeah i mean for everybody here
okay so do you want a reading noah yeah
i'm scared
well well well actually remember
he's a hyper kind you can do me then no
don't do that
you told me you're a hyper contractor no
no
let's not do noah i'm down are you sure
oh yeah i volunteer
are you sure yeah i'd love to if you do
it i'll do it
fine you sure yeah sure wait is it that
bad
no no we do a little fun thing but
usually what i don't do i don't do
here's this is this is fun this is good
yeah but i don't do big serious readings
meaning the reason why is because
there's millions of people waiting that
are really sick
absolutely yeah and so i you know so but
but this is fun this is just a little
stuff your adrenals
okay you have to get those better they
are they are weakened my what your
adrenals
okay okay that's one thing your adrenal
glands they sit on top of your kidneys
so you have to do some things for that
that the celery juice is important for
that all on its own so you should be
doing that that's going to improve your
adrenals automatically
okay but that's one focus we have to
kind of catch
now so that a few years down the road
they're not
like giving out a little bit on you and
then you're then you're really dragging
okay so so that's one thing what effects
i can't even pronounce the word what am
i doing wrong what what
is it is it diet is it what what well
you know
you know i mean here's the thing like
there's times where you don't eat
yeah and there's times where you do it
it's inconsistent with you
oh my god yeah it really is yeah it is
well spirit knows so that's
weird knows why yeah well that's part of
it because what's happening is when you
get inconsistent your adrenals are
flooding a lot
you run on adrenaline a lot more than
you should be
and that's what's happening you're over
using your adrenaline storage
because you're not eating consistently
wow
at consistent times so you're burning
out your adrenals
thank you spirit so that's the studio
the other thing is you got a little bit
of mercury
and in here oh i eat a lot of sushi well
you got a little bit of mercury in your
brain
i'm mercury poisoning you got some more
it's not really like a poisoning
poisoning or anything it's not like that
you just got a lot of traces and they're
building up
some is in your brain some is in the
liver so we
we should get the heavy metals out we
should get the mercury out because
that's going to start causing
brain fog it's going to start causing
little short circuits you're going to
start getting more anxiety
we got to kind of nip that in the butt
between the adrenals and the mercury
that's the two things with you
that's it that's it for today the fun
stuff yeah
so there
so celery juice
to help the kidneys yeah and that would
help the it'll help the adrenals
and then what's with what do i do to
help the mercury issues eating guys
i'm treating sushi gotta get on
spirulina oh yes
we have that right right you gotta get
on spirulina
you gotta get on barley grass juice
powder yeah you gotta get on that
cilantro you gotta get those in there
wild blueberries you could do the frozen
wild blueberries
is sushi bad for you yes so i should
stop eating sushi yes
oh my god okay your turn
that was easy your turn
oh man hopeless case today so no no no
just kidding yeah exactly no you look
good your liver
getting stagnant and sluggish it's
running hot yeah to get a hot liver
so that's one thing going on that we
have to be concerned about yep pancreas
for you
okay so it's another thing too so down
the road i'm worried about diabetes for
you
okay even though you eat pretty healthy
yeah but i'm worried about a little bit
of a
a1c rising type a type 2 diabetic
because like hypoglycemia you had years
ago so you had a little blood sugar
inconsistency
i did yeah yeah so absolutely did
somebody tell you you had that
yeah yeah someone what is it the my red
blood cells are thicker than
they should be or something like that so
you lin or whatever that's called
so you've you've been in that zone yeah
so that's one thing so i got to kind of
watch that so when i'm doing a read and
taking a look and then i'm actually
going partially blind right now good
thing i wore the shades today
okay because when i do the readings this
white light comes
and then i get snow blindness and now
i'm going to be you know tripping all
over the place for a little bit
in a little while but the bottom line is
i'm looking through your body
i don't see any diseases so to speak or
anything scary
i mean i don't see any anything that's
that's that's you know someone would be
afraid of yeah
but um future diabetes diabetes as far
as
pre-diabetes okay probably in about
seven eight years you'll probably get a
a1c going up
uh pre-pre-diabetes diagnosis and
and that's where you're going to be
sitting and you've got blood sugar and
inconsistencies absolutely
pancreas is is with you it's always been
a little weakened on and off you had
food poisoning years ago spirit said and
i'm trying to remember as far as spirit
told me about two minutes ago so i'm
asking against he had food poisoning
i think it was probably within the last
three to five years it was in his pocket
that weakened your pancreas so that's
that's why
i got to look out for you and noah
you're looking good don't worry i'm not
worried i'm
not worried about you why i'm good
you're making your doctor's appointment
for seven and eight years
i know what i have to do though like i'm
pretty healthy eater anyway
but i mean my diet can be inconsistent
so i'll eat
like healthy six days a week and then
eat [ __ ] i'm taking us to the cardio
the full day we're both getting our
blood work done
i actually have a medical on thursday so
i'm going with you yeah yeah
freya i'm freya the little baby i know
does anything come in sorry charles
does anything from spirit say anything
about
charles or the baby
the baby's healthy
exactly yeah he's healthy i'm so excited
for this baby it's
insane i know i'm glad you're healthy
freya
i'm excited for you thank you so much
really i am i mean seriously
yeah is she is charles is charles good
work we need work done there we go it's
probably the same as me
welcome to the club we'll figure it out
we'll work on it i love it so in it so
in terms of spirit compassion
i don't know if you've read like seth
speaks or abraham hicks or
any of these kind of kind of spirit
guide books is
are they part of the same teachings of
the spirit world
no this is different yeah this is
different okay
um and uh and i have tremendous respect
for that yeah
uh for sure i mean uh you know the
powerful work people have done in the
spiritual world
it's just it's been so helpful yeah it's
just been incredible
incredible help for people in so many
ways you know life-changing
life-changing
is entirely different this is this is
literally just
advanced medical information not
discovered by research and science yet
to save countless lives on the planet
and that's what's coming from wow it's
an entirely different thing yeah and i'm
just a messenger
i'm just the guy that's got to voice it
out
you know i love that well um you're
genuinely the coolest person i've ever
met
i wish no like genuinely like this has
been the coolest
mm-hmm welcome to my face i don't even
know what could top this
this is so cool i love it like i'm blown
away uh i recently did
you posted something on eggs yeah oh
yeah no and i got the
crap kicked out of me on that one you
know there's so many people that that
love their eggs we have an emotional
connection to them i mean we everybody
has emotional connection to them
it's like milk eggs and bread yeah it's
like these three things that you buy
consistently when you go to the store
and i wasn't trashing eggs i was just
saying
that look if if you feel good just eat
them what it is is that
here's what happened years ago years ago
decades and decades ago okay
there were viruses and bacteria raised
in labs
yep and in those labs they had to feed
the viruses and bacteria
yep okay and they did and eggs was the
food
they fed them yeah the chronic illness
of today is from
pathogens it's from pathogens yeah
that's what it's from
you get the lyme disease you've got the
multiple sclerosis you've got the you
know rheumatoid arthritis hashimoto's
thyroiditis you've got the lupus
the chronic fatigue syndrome
fibromyalgia that's all i try to do as
fast as i can you know i could ramble
off others
but those are from viruses
and so we walk around with these bugs in
us like epstein-barr
the epstein-barr virus and one that's
just that's one of 60 varieties of
epstein-barr
we walk around with that virus in us and
it creates fatigue
it creates problems and then we feed it
we feed it eggs it's not that i hate
eggs
they're delicious everybody loves them
we have connections to them
our parents make us eggs their mom makes
us eggs right who made you eggs
who who made did anybody make you eggs
um yeah
i mean me and the wife make eggs pretty
much on the weekends exactly right and
there's there's a feeling with that yeah
right i mean
what about you know it you don't like
them you know what it's
weird actually i like them kind of
but there's something about them that
kind of grosses me out at the same time
so like i'm very
indifferent it actually genuinely
depends on the day
like since it's 100 degrees outside
today
yeah there's no way you'd catch me
eating eggs in 100 degree weather
i don't know what it is but it has to do
with the weather i swear to you and
everyone makes fun of me
like my my best friend makes farming for
it all the time he'll like let's go get
breakfast and i'm like okay
but i can't eat eggs it's hot outside
and whenever it's hot outside
eggs extremely gross me out yeah but if
it's not hot and like i'm not
i don't know it's something i don't know
what it is but like
it just depends on the day with me and
eggs because like
i think i'm the same though i think that
makes sense it kind of grossed me out
my grandma used to have an obsession
with egg whites
but then she'd like burn them kind of
and they'd smell really bad and make the
kitchen smell bad for a while and i
think that really like
changed my mind on eggs for a second
yeah that's fine i'm indifferent about
them
yeah well you know well you're you're
rare because so many people love them
and then what happened was those viruses
somehow escaped the labs
they got into people over the last 70 80
years we have chronic illness because of
it
you know and and eggs are feeding it
so it's not that i'm against them or
anything i'm just saying look if if you
want a fighting chance
if you've got anything wrong with you
eczema anything psoriasis anything
like in sclerosis if you have rosacea
if you anything and eczema yeah well
that's that's actually toxic heavy
metals involved in that and then
with all of that you want to get rid of
the eggs you just do there's there's a
reason for this so the bottom line is
i took a lot of flak from that going
against eggs just actually just you know
there's torches picks pitchforks you
know i can imagine everything
what about the um what's your vibe on
dairy then
i mean dairy does something similar it
does feed bugs it does
but it's not the number one bug feeding
food if someone's worried about fungus
if they're worried about yeast if
they're worried about mold if they're
worried about bacteria if they're
worried about bad bacteria whatever it
is
don't eat an egg you're just going to
feed it yeah that's all i was just
delivering the message
kindly nicely it's kind of like the have
you read the the china study
i haven't read it but but i i hear
there's good information yeah
yeah and he's he basically says the same
thing he feeds like rats
and mice eggs and dairy and
feeds the other set of mice and rats on
plant-based foods
yeah and the ones who got fed the dairy
in eggs developed
more severe cancers and diets
prematurely than the ones who were i
think that's a plant i think that's a
plant-based book right yeah
see what happens is i'm neither nor
either more i'm not in the food world oh
it's actually no it's just a study
but there was a book after that from the
writer of the china study that had a
plant-based
i gotcha i got you know it's so funny
because i stay out of the food war you
got the vegans angry at the paleo people
you got the paleo anger the vegans
if you're a vegan i feel so bad for
vegans and plant-based people because
all you have to do is sneeze
and it's blamed on your diet yeah if
you're paleo if your keto animal protein
whatever
you can sneeze you can have an injury i
mean you could have anything you could
have bad health
you could have a problem you could be
sick no one blames your diet but if
you're plant-based it's your diet you
know what i mean so all these vegans are
like
they're falling from grace you know and
i feel bad for them because they get a
sniffle
and then they run back to animal protein
but the funny thing is animal protein
people are flipping too everybody's
flip-flopping
they're all going here some people vegan
some back here and what happens is
they're confused though they don't know
what causes illness they're playing with
food
they're playing guessing games with food
mostly i'm not trying to insult anybody
i'm just just trying to let everybody
know
i don't have a belief system i don't
have a belief system that plant-based is
going to save the world and i don't have
a belief system that
animal protein is the best way to eat
whatever it is
i don't have that but what i do have is
i will give you the cause of your
illness
and tell you what foods actually fix it
you choose what diet you want to sit on
that's fine and that's what a that's a
spirit of compassion there's no belief
systems here it's about providing
information
so everybody's not confused yeah because
it's a ball of confusion you know what
the thing is
all the keto people all the paleo people
all the vegans they're all still sick
yeah they're all still dealing with
their eczema their psoriasis their aches
and pains their fatigue their migraines
they're all still sick they're acne
acne is another one right there so you
know it's it's yeah
it's interesting wow man i love that
and go now oh i have a question
like because because i don't drink
milk since we were on the topic of milk
because it hurts my stomach
but i can like eat drink it right i
don't i don't
don't drink it i don't i drink almond
milk oat milk
does spirit tell you if i'm actually
lactose it's not about like lactose
intolerance
it's about creating inflammation so
everybody has bad bacteria in their gut
so that's just feeding any bad bacteria
in your gut
don't worry that's not unusual everybody
has it yeah they have bad bacteria it's
just that when you drink your milk
you're feeding that bad bacteria
yeah they came up with this whole thing
of lactose intolerance that's not what
it is it's you're
feeding the bugs and then the bugs are
creating inflammation
and then you get your ibs yeah don't
yeah don't drink milk i don't
it's not i used to my same thing with
eggs grosses me out a little bit but you
know i could say to people don't drink
milk milk's bad for you
milks milk will cause problems right i
won't get any flack when i say eggs i
mean
literally i had a you know i had to make
sure that
i left town fast there goes our eggs and
uh
dairy sponsorship for the podcast
no more ice cream yep no more ice cream
no more ice cream um ooh
what are your thoughts on cbd cbd it's
the same thing with the marijuana
it's it's really a true or dumb it's
it's it's a choice it's it's it's in the
soul
but do you think cbd does help
anxiety i know better things that help
anxiety
i'm not against cbd i'm not for it i'm
not against it i know better things that
help anxiety
yeah because i've seen thousands and
thousands of people heal their anxiety
with the information from spirit of
compassion so i know better things yeah
but but you know and that's the thing
but am i against it for it
either way it's whatever the person
wants to do because once again that's
something that's
it it's it's it's like diamond plated
inside your soul yeah have you met other
people
around the world that talk to
the spirit or your same spirit or not
same spirit or are there other people
yeah that have have you come in contact
with anybody
i haven't i mean maybe someone's out
there maybe they are i remember i did a
lecture many many years ago i think was
like i don't know 15 years ago maybe a
little longer and i did a lecture
and someone was out in the audience says
i hear the i hear spirit too the same
voice
i was so happy i was like get up here
yeah
get up here because this is it's like a
bumble bee finding another oh something
like
a like a bird finding another bird it's
like yeah i get up here
my god and they get up there and they're
like no i
i hear this i say your spirit too and
then spirit tells me all these i could
do
well let's get some people up here yeah
let's get it working
let me hear it and and in the end it was
just somebody that had a spiritual
connection and they heard a voice
periodically inside their head
yeah and i i have all respect for that
and i just
pat on the back like you know that's
great i'm really i'm really glad for
that but i was looking yeah
to find somebody that hears it all the
time
in real time no matter what and can read
people
on the spot see it doesn't matter if i'm
totally trashed i mean like exhausted
like no sleep
writing all night like last night i was
writing the book all night i had like
two hours of sleep last night so
and i'm and i'm tired but the point is
is that
it doesn't matter spirit's gonna talk to
me see how it goes
because psychics and mediums once
they're
wasted and totally tapped out they can't
they're the connection goes yeah they're
you know when they get burnt out
literally that's been one of the
problems with this is
i can be like i could be pushed to the
limit to the point of literally
practically dying because of it but
spirit will still talk because it's like
your best friend still talking to
did you ever have a friend where is it
she's your best friend or he's your best
friend
but you just can't hear it right now
yeah did you ever have
that where you're like no i'm tired i
and your friend wants to talk and wants
to talk in here well
guess what it's me when lou wants to
turn his phone off at 9pm
which i do so it always happens i've
never found
somebody with that yet and i've never
found someone that knows advanced
information
ahead of science of research that's
they're getting it from here
so no i i've never seen it but i'm
hoping it happens because you know what
i'm kind of i kind of want to
be done and retire i want somebody else
to take take it over
let them take it over let them put the
books out i'm um it's
such a unique position has any doctors
put a hit out on your head yet
no you're not friends i'm friends with a
lot of guys there's a lot of great
doctors out there one great doctor dr
alejandra younger
yeah he did the forward for the first
medical medium book he's he's a he's a
genius he's a great doctor he's a lot of
amazing doctors i know
over the years i've troubleshooted for
doctors that's how i
that's how i've been doing this all
these years doctors have been using me
they actually
look for the information because you
know why doctors got compassion
yeah they went into it originally
because they don't want to see people
suffer
so a lot of doctors they kind of like
break that ego thing
and they say i want to hear what he has
to say i want to know what he has to say
yep so there's a lot of great doctors
out there do
do you um do you teach nutrition because
i feel like whenever i go into like a
hospital or a doctor's surgery or
nutrition is so far removed from any of
the
the diagnosis of any illnesses ever i
mean that's just my interpretation of it
other people may be different but um i
feel like they don't have enough
knowledge in nutrition
well you you can use you could see it
like there's articles yeah there's
there's articles on me all the time out
there yeah they're like writing dozens
of articles out there and it's actually
really funny
because they write these articles they
never have any of the information right
about the medical medium which is funny
that always makes me laugh but that's
nice
then then a dietitian will come on which
i know some great dietitians
but a dietitian will come on and not
even realize celery
is an herb so they're sitting there
ripping apart the celery juice movement
saying it's placebo saying it doesn't
work right they're saying all these
things
and then they're calling it a vegetable
when it's an
actual herb and it's just like oh my god
you know and
they haven't dealt with the chronic
allele recovering from diseases using
celery juice so they're just complete
so yeah you know nutritionists
dietitians i have total respect for them
people in the health field movement all
the health professionals respect for
everybody
but realize there are some things that
are actually fixing people now yeah by
the millions celery is one of them so
amazing
amazing what um you said you're writing
a new book yeah writing one now i
haven't let any i haven't let anybody
know what it's about i just came out the
celery juice book medical medium
subjects people should
check that out i have hundreds of
conditions illnesses symptoms in there
and i talk about what causes it and how
celery juice helps it's a really great
book
but also i just did liver rescue so a
book called liver rescue i saw that
right before that yeah so i mean
back to back these books i'm finishing
up one right is that the one with the
beat on the cover
it's the one with the apple on the card
apple which is the one with the b yeah
no beat
no beat on the cover of my books hang on
which one did i see
it's funny because i had um we made some
beaten carrot juice
and i feel like i've been like urinating
it out for like three days
and as well as many other things is it
it
is beats same property as um celery in
terms of
the health it does for us well beets
don't do a lot for us
yeah oh wow there we go apart from turn
our stalls
red i mean they're
they're healthy yeah it's a healthy food
yeah
but it hasn't changed anybody's life
okay see okay lou the difference is
unbelievable and now i have to sit here
and i have to convince you
now i gotta convince you lou here's the
difference
okay everybody's juiced carrots before
everybody's juiced beets before
everybody's juiced
everything before no one's recovered
from literally death defying illnesses
because of it
what celery juice has okay this is an
entirely different thing this is
i'm so i mean we have it like full time
four five times a week
not quite 16 ounces though yeah you got
maybe half of that
you should be on 32 ounces jeez every
single day
you do that for 60 days and you will
never go off of it again
because when you go off of it you'll be
like oh my god what the hell was i doing
leave the beat bacon to me i'll make all
the i'll make the beets and you drink
your celery juice
and i'll drink my celery juice while i'm
in with london on the track making our
beads
the celery juice in your next video yeah
i'm gonna be singing lonely
and pressing celery into a juicer yeah
put a little tag at the bottom saying
medical medium done
we have to have you in a music video one
day give me some credit
give me a little credit i'll take it
because the spirit will love you for it
oh my god i love it wow well i mean
this has been incredible yeah thank you
i mean i want to thank
music studios you and
anthony medical medium obviously my
co-host noah and everyone here
this was [ __ ] awesome yeah thank you
so much i appreciate you and your time
thank you so much hey i'm honored
best day ever right now the best day
ever that's right the best thing ever
thank you