three different nut Butters it's going
to be really fun I'm really excited you
guys let's get going on it this is the
medical medium cooking show I'm excited
because I can't wait to make these
recipes I'm going to show you a few
things we got going on right here which
is really cool all right so I got some
mustard greens that's a leafy green that
I was really spicy by the way that I
want to show you how to use with hummus
which is really going to be cool I got
some kale right there which is exciting
and then what I have is arugula I got
parsley I got Sage right here I got
rosemary I love one Rosemary is just
like this would you actually pick it off
like that usually what I do is something
different but I want to show you the
whole thing and I'll talk about the
Rosemary a little later got the celery
got lemons you got a whole bunch of
different stuff here uh lots of stuff to
show you actually because we're going to
make four hummuses right so it's awesome
and then I got the nut Butters the
roasted nuts ready for the nut Butters
how cool is this right so I'm gonna get
started right now I'm just gonna prepare
a little garlic I just actually took off
the sheath of the garlic and now I'm
just chopping it up a little bit because
I'm making a chickpea garbanzo bean
chickpea right there can you see that
there you go perfect I'm making that
hummus first
now if you're wondering what other
hummus is I'm making I'm making a lentil
hummus I'm going to be making
cannellini bean hummus I'm going to make
a black bean hummus too so it's going to
be incredible so let's get going
so much to show you guys so much going
on here so I'm gonna move these check
that out right there so I want to see if
you can see that pretty clear
these are the garbanzo beans right there
now I don't like store-bought hummus I
was talking about that earlier I could
talk about that later too store-bought
hummus will have natural flavors in
there which is toxic it'll have citric
acid in there which is toxic they don't
have nutritional yeast in there which is
toxic so this is really healthy healthy
hummus and this is the hummus that I
make for friends and family and anyone
that's coming over or something or for
holidays which is exciting too so we
move that over
and I'm gonna get the mm 1500 over here
now so many so many of you guys have the
mm1500 you probably already make your
own hummus
so
I'm doing that here excited
so I'm going to start out with firing it
up let's make the garbanzo bean hummus
right off the running
this is awesome that's all I could say
so in this one it's going to be garbanzo
beans or chickpeas same thing
garlic lemon chili pepper flakes what
else cumin and sesame seeds now check
this out you guys I got sesame seeds
here
so I have sesame seeds right here and
let me get this off because this kind of
gets all noisy in the machine let me
take that out
so the sesame seeds I put into the
machine instead of like see because what
happens is hummus is really fattening
because it'll have a lot of different
oil in it or fat in it there's either a
lot of olive oil or canola oil when you
buy store-bought hummus it usually has
the canola oil in it so that's the big
thing with that so and I don't like that
it'll have a blend of canola and olive
oil in it so when you buy store-bought
or it'll have a really low-grade tahini
so what I like to do is just get the
sesame seeds
and when you get the sesame seeds you
can do it that way it's so much better
and you put it into the machine when you
make your own hummus
that's my favorite way of doing it
so let's drop some
let's drop some beans in here some
garbanzos
there we go
I like to drop some seeds in here too
now take a look at this right here which
is really incredible we'll do a close-up
on here as well let me cut a lemon
do you see how incredible it is you can
make a fat-free hummus
with no oil no tahini no anything and
it's the machine makes it in a way that
I've never seen a blender make it
I've never seen anything naked it's that
incredible you want to even think about
it so I'm gonna drop some more garbanzos
in I'm gonna squeeze a little bit of
lemon juice in here too
I'm gonna put some more sesame seeds
you know when I have people over during
the holidays and I make it in front of
them they're like you're always like
blown away they're like medical Medium
you're you're at it again you know like
you're doing the coolest thing so I'm
dropping some more sesame seeds in here
just like this
got to think about it how they're just
using a little bit of sesame seeds
you're not drowning it in oil and sesame
oil or anything like that it's so
incredible when you even think about
that
so
you're watching those garbanzos come
right out
now you can actually put a little bit of
salt if that's what you like right let
me get a little bit of salt
if you want a little pinch of salt in
here too get a little pinch of salt in
there
add some more garbanzos
these recipes are incredible for every
day it's not just holiday this is every
day you know that's how great these are
for people friends family children
so easy
so you're watching
how the garbanzos come out of the
machine which is so incredible I'm gonna
drop a little bit more in here this
I'm going to drop a few more sesame
seeds just think about
like you're just using the sesame seed
it's incredible a little bit more salt
and a little bit more lemon
it's amazing really it's actually
amazing
now I'm also going to add some spices
you can mix the spices in later
so I'm going to add a little bit of
chili pepper flakes
there we go
that's it you can make as much as you
want
saves you money it's less expensive than
buying it pre-made in the store
which is incredible all on its own so
there you go
no harmful additives
natural flavors are harmful
in all products
it's one of the greatest scams if you've
heard the medical medium podcast at
Apple podcast I talk about the natural
flavors
so there you go
we got some hummus
I mean you don't have to just do this
for the holidays you don't have to make
it for then you can make it for
at any time
then you just mix it you can put some
spices in there too
so what I'm going to add is a little bit
of chili pepper flakes right here pop a
few on
put in my hand and sprinkle a few in
there I like it spicy I Like It Hot I
don't know about you guys
I'm adding a little bit of cumin in here
too
cracking that in here
and
so
I'm gonna move these out of the way a
little bit this is some kale it's kind
of in the way here
there we go
so can you guys take a look at that
so I'm going to mix up those spices in
here
so what's incredible is this isn't a
hummus that's greasy that's loaded with
oil
that's loaded with
a really high fat because that's what
the hummuses are it doesn't have
nutritional yeast in it which is toxic I
know there's many of you guys that eat
new nutritional yeast and you don't know
about the medical medium information
about nutritional yeast just don't judge
me on that right now maybe like another
day kind of learn about it and be like
okay let's look into that with mm info
but either way and if look I'm not
judging you either about if you buy a
hummus and it's got nutritional yeast in
it or it's got natural flavors and
citric acid fine I'm not judging you at
all as a bad person you're a good person
you're just buying a hummus that
you may not know but isn't good for you
even though you think it could be good
for you and that's the really kind of
tricky thing all about it
now you can put fresh herbs on your
hummus so I just mixed it up like this
just to get everything in there a little
bit and then there you go there it is
now I'm going to put it in a little bit
of a bowl a little Bowl here
let me get a spoon I'm gonna scoop it
out I think I'm gonna put some fresh
parsley on top
to give it like a really nice look too
and a little extra parsley flavor
Laura Atkinson asked um over there on
Facebook what machine are you using for
that I'm using the mm-1500
here it is it's 25 off right now the
link is in the description
and what this machine does a lot I think
a lot of people a lot of you guys might
have this machine and you already know
but what it does
is it makes a lot of things you make
salsa hummuses nut Butters nut milks ice
cream but
something that's really important too is
it makes green juice and it makes celery
juice and it saves you money because it
squeezes the juice out we'll get I'll
actually make a little juice too
okay
so I'm going to pop a little parsley on
here if you guys don't mind
let's see
here we are
let me just chop some up maybe we can
take a look too I'll give you a close-up
on that as well
get our camera's working
there we go so we got our parsley
and the parsley I'm going to sprinkle it
right on top of here
okay now this is going to go
right in here
so I want to give you a close-up on that
you guys so on IG can you see that and
then here you go how does that look you
guys
so that's the hummus right there now
think about how incredible that hummus
is
because one reason it doesn't have all
that oil in there
so you know you're not bogging down your
liver with all that oil
and hummuses have cheap oil in them
store-bought too
so what that means is spoiled oil right
Rancid
it's bulk it's for you know big
purchases for the company to actually
just put it in you know each container
it's just you don't like that it's not a
good thing this is homemade this is
actually clean which is really
incredible
and it doesn't get any cleaner than that
okay so you can buy your chickpeas
garbanzo beans that's a really good
Focus right there it's fantastic
and you can actually make the cleanest
hummus you ever want it to make and you
still have that Sesame behind it because
I used the sesame seed and the sesame
seed was pulverized in here
so it's not like it's whole seeds now
that's what's incredible about the
machine
you're actually looking at pulverized
sesame seeds when they went through here
and that's the nice subtle flavor behind
there that's really nice too
so Mega juicers.com they're having the
biggest sale of the year right now just
so you know it only goes for a couple
more days this is the mm-1500
stick around because your mind is going
to be blown when I make nut Butters
because my mind is always blown when I
make nut Butters with the mm-1500 and
I'm also going to show you how to save
money with juices too because food costs
are up the mm-1500 all it does is pay
for itself over and over again pays for
itself and pays for itself so I'm like
pumped up about that all right
let's make another hummus which would be
really cool
that's next
now you might not be making four
different hummuses when you make a
hummus you might make one that day and
that's the one you make so we're right
now we're doing more than that so we're
gonna have some fun we're gonna do the
cannellini bean hummus
so get ready
because that is next
I'm excited
all right so the kandellini be hummus
here's what I'm gonna do I'm gonna do
some fresh herbs in this one so I just
like the way it looks with the fresh
herbs of cannellini beans I'm gonna use
some arugula I'm gonna use some lemon
some parsley what else uh sesame seeds
again and I'm gonna use some black
pepper
and a little pinch of salt in this one
so let me just get the black pepper just
ready for a little later which is really
cool I got salt the black pepper right
there and I got my herbs so on the herb
front this is going to be a fresh herb
one so I'm gonna add the arugula into it
as I'm making it so I'm going to chop up
a little bit of arugula now and just get
ready and prep for it real quick
so let's do that here's arugula
so I'm going to chop it up
you can mix it into it afterwards as
well which I like to do but I'm going to
add a little bit in there
I'll put those stems there I want to
save those I don't like tossing those
stems they're just so good
right
okay we got arugula ready what else am I
going to put in there besides arugula I
think that's it um
some parsley too
so let me chop up a little bit more
parsley how about that
foreign
okay all right
I think what's happening is that Jews
are strong stuff out of focus a little
bit all right let's see what we got
let's fire this up
let's make another hummus
I'm gonna drop some cannellini beans in
here
foreign
I'm going to squeeze a little bit of a
lemon
on down
right I'm going to drop some sesame
seeds in here too to get pulverized so
I'm excited about
you need when you're making a hummus if
you're just using a little bit of sesame
seeds like how awesome is that would
even think about it and it's so great
had a few more of these cannellini beans
so let's get this moving I'm going to
add a little bit of parsley in here
I'm gonna add a little bit of arugula in
here too
there we go
I'm gonna add some more cannellini beans
so I'm excited about this one
there we go I'm gonna add a little bit
more arugula a little bit more parsley a
little bit more lemon
nice I'm gonna add a little bit more
sesame seed
the fresh herbs
adds the medicine to it
so we're talking about adding medicine
into this really I mean that's what it's
about you're making a medicinal hummus
right there
some more cannellini beans
got a better one right here filled up
there we go
so you're talking about the medicinal
Factor when you're doing fresh herbs
like that
I'm gonna add some more fresh herb right
add some more lemon
a few more sesame seeds
people add even
a little bit of salt
so many of you guys like salt so I just
don't want to take that away from you
and you know company comes over they
want salt
they want salt
right that's when it's like okay you got
it I can throw a little salt at anything
you guys want
whatever your heart desires here
so just putting a little bit more of the
cannellini Bean down in there you guys
this is not like cool or what I mean
come on
that's actually so cool
there you go
and you can make as much as you want I'm
just making some small bowls of it
there you go
I'm sure the rest of it comes out
okay
all right I'm going to add a little bit
of pepper
I already put the salt in so I'm gonna
add a little bit of pepper to this one
so crack a little bit of that black
pepper on there
because a lot of people love black
pepper in their hummus so it gives it
that flavor
we are live right now you guys this is
not a pre-recorded episode or
pre-recorded whatever we're actually
live right now I get tons of questions
about the mm 1500 regarding the mm 1500
it's 25 percent off
I wanted this to be a medical medium
cooking show because people are also
asking me Hey where's the medical beam
cooking show where did it go so and
lately I've been using the machine to
actually cook so I figured look let me
bring it out
um that's 25 off it's on sale right now
just so you know now what we're doing
today is we're making four different
hummuses this is the cannellini bean
hummus
and we're making three nut Butters we're
making ice cream and we're gonna make a
green juice
which I'm really excited about too so
foreign
here we are
all right now that's the hummus right
there
so I want to just give you a little
window into this I'm going to put it in
this glass bowl if you guys don't mind
this is just an incredible hummus now
think about the medicine involved in
this one when you make your own hummus
there's a big difference you guys
you're putting in your fresh herbs this
isn't like the store-bought kind right
this is your fresh herbs in here it's an
entirely different situation so what I'm
going to do is move this over
foreign
give you a little window how does that
look right there
so there you go
so that's your beautiful herb cannellini
bean hummus right there
okay let's get that inside
here there you go
take a look at this
that was the second hummus made right
there with the mm-1500
what do you guys think
wow take a look at that right there with
the crew today nice focus on that
incredible
there it is that's your cannellini Bean
one
think about how you're not
eating toxic stuff
so people who love hummus
they love it but they don't realize
there's toxic stuff in it I'm not trying
to be a downer about it it's just real
you know a lot of people say oh there he
goes but I'm actually just trying to be
real about it
when I go through the store or
somebody I know goes to the store
and they're just like hey let me ask aw
and they're asking me I'm like whoa that
one's got citric acid in it that one's
got
toxic stuff in it that one's got
nutritional yeast in it which you guys
know is the MSG Factor plus other things
that's got natural flavors and all kinds
of stuff and that's got the bad rancid
oils
you're looking at the cleanest hummus
right there homemade right there with
the machine with your fresh herbs you're
using your sesame seeds and I have
tahini here so I'll show you one with
tahini in a little bit too all right
let's make another
which I'm excited about big time here
very excited about all right
now this one is going to be
a black bean hummus that's next on the
list
let's go
so I got the black beans right here now
in this one okay this is gonna be cool
we're gonna have lemon we'll have a
little it's Pulte uh seasoning right
powder we'll have a little cumin we'll
have a little bit of chili flakes we're
gonna make this one hot and spicy that's
what we're gonna do with this one sesame
seeds and garlic so we're going to pop
that garlic in there too
all right
let's fire it up get started
that's why I love you
love me so there's gonna be a little
left over of the cannellini you can just
take that aside put it somewhere else
when it comes out but there it goes
there's the black beans
okay I'm gonna squeeze a little lemon in
here
I'm gonna put a little bit of garlic in
this one
we got our garlic in there I'm gonna put
some sesame seeds in this one too
here we go pulverize those
get some more black beans it's just
basically doing it itself right there
it's all coming out
so this one's really spicy it's got the
the
spicy
hot pepper I'm putting more garlic in
I'm putting a little bit more lemon so
I'm making the black bean hummus right
now you guys just got here watch this
replay we're live right now but watch
the replay after
we're still going to make three nut
Butters we got a lot to do it's gonna be
pretty crazy here
so I'm just gently pushing this down
doesn't really take anything at all
letting it do its thing pop some more
garlic in there let me put some more
black beans in here too so this is our
third hummus the black bean hummus right
here
how do you like that or sesame seeds
now you can add a little salt to this
one if you want too you can have them
salt free you can you can you have your
own free will you can determine what you
want
foreign
Jan says sick machine oh no it's an
insane machine but you know what the
sickest part of this machine is
right it's not just the like healthy
hummuses and nut Butters and nut milks
and banana ice cream and everything else
and ice creams and sorbets
and Salsas it's not just that it makes
what's really sick about it
is that when you juice your celery and
your greens
you really do save money in a machine
pays for itself that's the sick part
about it that's like the part that just
blows me away okay I'm just telling you
like that's the part that blows me away
so I'm going to add a little bit more
lemon in here
because I want to make a little bit more
black bean hummus
and I'm going to add some more black
beans you guys it's 25 off the machine
check out the link is in the description
it's your biggest sale of the year and
it's only like on sale for two more days
squeeze a little lemon in there and a
little bit more garlic boom
it's just going through on its own I'm
not even pushing it through right now
just going down so
there you go amazing
insane
smooth
right
you can't do that in a blender by the
way
you can't you have to add like all that
oil in the blender you just can't put
like dry beans in there in the blender
and make a hummus it just doesn't happen
but
the blender heats up everything too it
just burns it all in there like the
friction this is different
this is like a cold pressed masticating
juicer but it has attachments so you can
do this which is is really a blessing
Mary Murphy says I have this juicer and
I have only used it for celery so far I
can't wait to experiment more and that's
one of the reasons why I'm doing this
today because I never get a chance to
show you guys what the mm-1500 does I'm
always showing you guys you know how
food costs are going up and produce
costs money and everything costs money
I always just worry about that all the
time so I'm just being real about this
I'm always worried about how do I get
people with chronic illness to save
money how do I get people to save money
and saving money it's the only juicer
that has such a compression where it
actually squeezes out all the juice
and so you buy less celery less greens
less things you want to juice right so
it saves you money and it pays for
itself that's that's what I'm always
screaming about
but the thing is is that when I'm always
doing that I don't get a chance to show
you like what it does like it is a sick
juicer like it's insane actually so I
just made some black bean hummus now I
want to add some spices and everything
to it
which I'm excited about okay
for those who are asking yes I'm using
canned or boxed beans today I am
um you can look at medicalmedium.com and
you can check out my directory and you
can see which ones I have and everything
there so here is the black bean hummus
all set
now I'm going to put some spices in here
so I'm showing you right here this is
just so awesome really let's get the hot
spices into it so
Chipotle powder let's use that power in
says
this looks so cool actually this juicer
is revolutional with all these different
things it does and it's really
incredible you guys know I'm always just
doing this thing where I'm putting some
really heat in here I'm putting some
serious hot heat in here I can't help it
I like the hot the hot right spicy I'm
gonna put some red chili flakes in this
one too this black bean hummus is gonna
be yeah
it's gonna be real hot
nice
so
all right let's see if I got everything
let's put cumin in here
cumin gives it that real hummus that's
that real hummus
flavor I'm gonna pop a whole bunch of
cumin in here I'm gonna hit this one
hard boom real spicy real nice
everything else is in here too so we're
all set let's mix it up
okay let's even get this in folks ready
take a look at that okay now I'm just
mixing it with a fork just so you know
I'm mixing the spices in with a fork
right you guys can see there we go this
is the black bean hummus now what's your
what you notice here this is an oil this
isn't Grease
this isn't just all that oil like I just
put sesame seeds that were pulverized in
here that's all it was all right so
there you go let's get this in a
new bowl
right here
we go
incredible
amazing there you go let me get get up
close up on that right there can you
guys see that
there it is
that is the black bean hummus you guys
see
get a good Focus right there I think
so the chili pit you can put chili
flakes on top a few just like this
just to get it to look a certain way you
can put a little bit more
um heat on top as well so I'm going to
drop a little bit more Chipotle
right there
if you guys can see can you eat uh
probably a little bit there you go nice
close-up nice focus on that now watch
this
I am going to trade out my last hummus
I'm gonna put this in the crudite
and I'm going to bring the crudite back
if you guys don't mind
boom take a good close-up on that
there you go that's the black bean
hummus right there
and
incredible so what did we just make
three hummuses with the mm-1500 like
what
does that make any sense the mm-1500 I
thought the mm-1500 only Juiced celery
apparently not
it does more than that it really does
let's do a little bit of
let's just have a little taste now I'm
going to have some a little later but
we'll get a let's see maybe a red bell
pepper in here and maybe we'll scoop
some out okay
there we go you guys see that
all right I'm not gonna go crazy eating
right now though okay
I'm not gonna go nuts eating let's get
moving we got a lentil hummus to do
let's go
all right check this out you guys
no
people always say
does aw does aw tell you everything he
does in his life is he talking about his
life like what is he doing everything
let me tell you something that you guys
don't know
one of my favorite hummuses of all
to make for family friends whatever that
I like to is lentil hummus by far one of
my favorites so I'm going to show you a
close-up on the lentils right there
these are cooked lentils okay it's a
brown lentil
and we're gonna make a hummus so what's
going to be in here this is going to be
lentils Sage fresh Sage how cool is that
lemon a little bit of salt Rosemary
and sesame seeds and what else what else
what else was hot pepper chili flakes
all right let's go
nice
fire it up
oh
let's go
foreign
that's a little bit of the black bean
hummus left you can always just clear
that out and put that in the hummus that
you just previously made there's nothing
wrong with that pop some lemon in there
fresh Sage you're going down Sage there
you go you're going in there you're
going in the
little tube there
incredible
all right let's get these levels down
I like this whole fresh sage in here
let's do fresh Rosemary in here too
whoa
we got a little Rosemary in here as well
let's get some more lentils
[Music]
incredible
there we go
more lentils let's put some Rosemary
let's squeeze a little bit more lemon
nice
let's get sesame seeds in here
boom
we're making lentil hummus
real and you know what for you guys like
for the ones that are like protein
fiends like you can't get rid of the
protein law
you're just you're stuck with protein in
your head where am I gonna get my
protein where's my protein you know like
you know how there's people out there
they're just freaking out where am I
gonna get my protein lentils are so high
in protein it is absurd
it's not why I eat them
but they're so high in protein it's
insane so I'm just letting you know
right now okay
so
this is a lentil Sage
Rosemary
hummus right here
you can do what you want be you do you
make the hummus you want with all the
ingredients and spices you want to make
I'm showing you four different kind of
hummuses that I make I'm adding a little
bit more
here we go let's put a little bit more
sesame seed in here do you realize how
very little tahini was used with just
some sesame seeds I made all these
hummuses and that's like this saves you
money I can't even tell you how much
money all around to get flavorable food
like if anything
and I I told you guys the other day
the the mm-1500 900 came about because
how can I get medicine in people who are
chronically ill and save them money
that was all it was about is how do I
have people save money so that it pays
for itself because I couldn't find that
out there with all the juicers I would
purchase all these years
I couldn't find a juicer that paid for
itself it just seemed
master that was costing money and
people don't realize that it was like it
never paid for itself and so the mm 1500
900 was
designed to make it so the consumer
was not only getting medicine because
that's what I wanted I wanted medicine
and people the other thing I wanted it
to pay for itself
people were always saying well they have
problems with like resources and stuff
like that because they don't have any
money or resources and how are they
going to heal if they don't have things
a little that's what it's about it's
about finding other options
creating other options you know
and that's what it's really about it's
about saving money where you can
it's about saving money I mean I worked
with so many people for so many years
and
and it's like not everybody is Rich out
there
I know the other juicer companies think
that everybody's rich
but they're not not everybody's Rich out
there okay so how can we heal and do it
in a way that we can save money and
everything and that's what it was really
about it's a cold pressed masticating
juicer it does so many things
anyway
so let's actually do this now
this is the lentil hummus now with the
lentil hummus I'm going to add a little
bit of salt in there too
okay for the people that love salt now
I'm going to put some dried hot pepper
in here
this is a sage lentil hummus sage and
rosemary one I'm adding some red hot
pepper flakes
yeah
there we go
just mixing it up a little bit
and in a bowl it goes
excited
this is the lentil hummus so I just made
you guys four hummuses
or I made myself here for hummuses what
am I going to do with all this I know
what I'm going to do with all of it
okay
give you a little window into this there
it is it's a beautiful lentil hummus
that's it right there incredible
seriously ready
here we go
back onto the crudite display right now
here we are
see what you're looking at right now is
a lentil hummus
right there in the crew today I'm gonna
grab radish real quick do you guys mind
and I'm gonna taste the left mental
hummus
yeah
boom so good
insane
that's good incredible love it I'll show
you real quick these four different
hummuses
let's get them all out
all right got the black bean one right
there
cannellini Bean one right there
garbanzo bean chickpea one right there
lentil one right there
all four
right there incredible
see guys I'm gonna just do a little
cleaning up in front of you here and
we're gonna make nut Butters
three nut Butters
I got the nuts toasted
and we're ready for some roasted toasted
nut butter from the mm-1500
so let's do it I'm gonna move some stuff
out of the way
you don't mind
so
we'll do a quick little cleanup as well
okay
got a question right there difference
between a 900 and 1500 the 900
you can juice your celery
and you save money because it's pushing
out so much juice and the pulp's coming
out that dry bulb right that's the
mm-900 you can put greens you can do
green juices
you can do your celery juice
and that machine can take a beaten
that's something that people don't
realize
people who juice
they'll have a juicer for like five
years they only use it once a month
maybe they use it for three months in a
row and then never use it again
and so it sits there right the medical
medium community and like me I juice
every day I'll juice multiple times a
day
I juice every single day seven days a
week every year and so what I love about
the mm900 and 1500 the engine
the engine supersedes anything I've seen
out there
so it's the power of the engine and how
it's well built right because what
happens is you may get a worn out part
but then just what call the company get
a new part right you may get a worn out
part but the juicer has paid for itself
over and over again
you have saved money and saved money and
money can you're using the heck out of
your juicers you try using the heck out
of some of the other juicers out there
they break down and the whole engine
just breaks everything breaks about it
these are made to get the crap kicked
out of them they're made for juicing
every day every day and that's what I do
and they save money so the 900 is for
like the green juices and for the celery
juice
okay which is incredible the mm-1500 I'm
showing you all the other stuff
which is amazing all on its own
all right so I'm just doing a quick
little cleanup right here
if you guys don't mind
these are my personal recipes I work I'm
getting them uh if you like look these
are my personal recipes that I do
go to medicalmedium.com you can get the
recipes there
oh hold on here
so I'm just gonna need a little more
cleaning
I will work on getting them at
medicalmedium.com that's what I meant
here all right so I'm going to remove
this just for easiness
you can clean this really quick but I
don't want to waste your time giving
that a quick clean
so let's make some
nut Butters
right here
now if you guys just got on here I'm I
just made four hummuses but what I'm
gonna do too is I'm gonna make Nut
Butter I'm gonna make banana ice cream
and then I'm also going to make some
celery juice too some green juice
and I want to show you what I do with
wheat greens because
they're not Incorporated enough in
people's diets I don't care how clean
they eat they're not doing enough leafy
greens
so let's see here's a question from
mocha so is the 1500 more powerful no
they're just as powerful
it's just that the 1500 offers all these
other things like you can make the
sauces the hummus is the nut Butters the
nut milks
you can make like all these different
things to sorbets the ice creams right
and then you can do your green juices
too but the 900 you can do your green
juices and your celery juice is still
just as powerful they're powerful
machines
they're okay get ready for this
we're gonna make the first
nut butter and let's see which one we're
going to start with right here we're
going to start with
cashew butter take a look at the cashews
let's get a quick look on that
I just toasted these can you take a look
at them
so these are toasted
you can kind of see it too
they're a little toasty looking
if that actually if you know what I'm
saying right okay
now
before we go into making this I want to
show you something
this is going to be an education for a
second you guys you gotta check this out
Brenda says can a normal juicer make
these things no they can't a normal
juicer cannot make these things it's the
mm-1500
and a normal juicer cannot save you
money when you're juicing or save you
money in foods this is to battle the
rising food costs that were starting to
happen in 2019.
so in 2019 food costs were Rising
and I was worried about people with
chronic illness
being able to heal themselves and save
money
that's how these were created
there was a real mission
and real love behind it
or I would have been the juicer guy for
the last 30 years if it was just me to
be a juicer guy like hey aw is now a
juicer guy I would have done that for
the last 30 years if it was just about
that
but it wasn't in 2019
the mission was oh my God
food costs are going up
and up and up
how do we do this
like how do we heal people
and so a juicer is a medicine maker and
then when it's done right like this and
it's squeezing out everything including
those nutrients everything gets squeezed
out when you make your medicine it has
to be good and it has to save you money
people were struggling to buy celery
because there's juicers who are wasting
the money
so people were struggling they'd have to
buy so much celery
but they needed the celery juice to heal
their conditions and symptoms do you see
the problem we had
it was like spirit and compassion and I
were like okay they need their herbal
medicine which is the celery juice it's
already saved so many lives out there
but let's let's do something to actually
help people because to see I saw people
going into the store and buying a lot of
celery and then running all that celery
through all their juicers including the
fancy ones that have that are out there
now that you see every day right now
with ads and influencers
and it was just running all that through
yeah they'd have some juice a pile of
juice but they were spending this this
much more money right and so what
happened was it was like how can we do
this how can we get medicine herbal
medicine in people have them save money
have the machine pay for itself and for
them to heal
and now we have the brain shot therapy
which you need a juicer and the brain
shot therapy is incredible because it's
there to help people heal you know it's
in the brain saver books and so you need
a juicer that's saving you money and
allowing you to heal yourself
that was the mission
it was about getting all the juice out
of the wild foods and herbs out of the
herbs so you have medicine in extraction
so these were the medicine extractors
and so the goal was how do we do it
where it's incredible where the metal
isn't touching itself I saw somebody
make a comment a while back after I did
talked about the mm-1500 and they said
oh yeah you're just a Salesman
and they were like yeah metal touching
metal whatever oh yeah the juicers out
there either have the
they just get all dull where do you
think all that metal goes when that
centrifuge is doing this
what do you think all the metal goes
when the parts are rubbing each other it
goes in you in the medical mean
Community they use juicers every day to
heal themselves
so I didn't want that metal involved
it's like there's a lot of thought that
goes into all of it is what I'm saying
but we have a lot to make right here and
also the mm-1500 is quiet and the mm-900
is quiet and they're easy to clean and
and when you make sauces it's easy to
clean when you make nut Butters it's
easy to clean and when you make nut
milks it's easy to clean like it's it's
insane how easy to clean it is
so I just want to be real with you guys
like what is this about I could have
started a Juicer Company 20 years ago
and been known as the juicer guy and
sold a trillion juicers in the last 20.
I didn't want to do that it's specific
it's for people who are trying to heal
themselves who need the medicine who are
chronically ill who may not have a lot
of money they're not rich
and we got to get the medicine in them
you know and so
and I didn't even start my own juicer
so I don't have a medical medium juicer
I could have started a medical medium
juicer you guys do you know this
where it was a instead
I'm helping Omega
like get their juicer out there that
they created like I'm actually helping
them to get it out there for people then
they create created it in the light that
I was hoping to help people to say bunny
and everything
anyway
blah blah blah I want to show you
something that'll blow your mind
what are you looking at
can anybody tell me I took the label off
but it's like this with every nut bugger
it's not the specific one I have right
here
but you see
the label off I'll get a close-up on
this right
see the label off but what do you see
now
you see oil sitting at the top so let's
get a close-up of that do you know what
do you know what you're looking at some
of you guys
see
now your yours may not look like that
yet because it didn't sit long enough
because it was still mixed the oil
and the nuts or seeds were still mixed
but this is what happens if you let it
sit for a long time it'll show you the
scam
what you're looking at is a scam
right here
if you want to be educated about this
it's going to blow your freaking mind
okay I'm not trying to be a downer I'm
just trying to tell you I'm gonna give
you this skinny
on the nut butter seeds
Sesame tahini world I'm going to give
you the in just like medical medium has
always done this with podcasts and books
always gave you the in the no
okay you ready
you're looking at a nut butter
happens to be almond butter
you're looking at that much oil
that's oil
is not from those nuts
did you guys hear me
welcome to the world of screw everybody
over
this is why I will only make my own nut
butter
right there
and if you can't make your own nut
butter then I'll recommend the best Nut
Butter I possibly can or whatever out
there I'll try to recommend something
says OMG what
I'm trying to tell you guys something
we're gonna make three nut Butters I
have toasted roasted nuts we're gonna
make three nut Butters
Kim Marietta says you're saying the oil
is not from
the nut in the jar correct
correct
The Nut Butter companies and the seed
butter companies and the peanut butter
companies
mix in an oil
and then if it's freshly mixed in they
just did it and they got on the Shelf
you won't see it do this yet
but it's still all the same
so the question is right there I see a
question down there the question is what
kind Alexis says what kind of oil are
they adding
they are adding a bulk rendition of the
same oil you ready
they did the almonds but the oil they're
adding is not from those almonds it's
from other almonds from some other part
of the world that they had to purchase
in bulk
a lesser even quality
that could even be rancid and then they
put it into the mix
and spirit of compassion says it's time
they knew
I'm going to show you what a real Nut
Butter looks like
without adding oil to it so if you're
feeding your children nut Butters I'm
going to show you the best Nut Butter
you can ever make anywhere anyhow
anyway
all right
and just just so you know it's every
single nut and Seed butter
they add the oil oh oh I forgot I forgot
they had the oil because they can use
less nuts
hmm
we're gonna charge you 16 for that
almond butter jar 18 food costs are
going up we're gonna charge you twenty
four dollars for that organic almond
butter
but we're not going to give you that
many almonds you see what we're going to
do suckers is we're going to just give
you less almonds jack up the price and
add a whole bunch of oil in there that's
cheaper they buy the oil cheaper
in bulk and then they can supplement the
oil into all of the nut and Seed Butters
all the companies and then you get less
almonds and less nuts you guys
the vegans don't know this the vegan
doctors don't know this
the vegan experts don't know this the
vegan authorities don't know this the
keto authorities don't know this the
keto trainers don't know this none of
them know this another original and
unique piece of information which also
gets me in trouble because when I go and
do this stuff and say this stuff
I get a whole bunch of for it
and so but I always say this
you tell The Chronic Leo the truth it
outweighs the big kick in the ass that
you get
you know like you got to tell them the
truth because you have to get them
better you have they have to know how it
works in the world
and then you can take the kick you know
the kick and the stab in the back and
the kick in the butt
anyway let's go let's do it
I mean you know people say well he's not
transparent sometimes people will say
that I see that out there it's like how
transparent do you want me to be I'm out
here in front of you guys live all the
time I say all kinds of crap I don't
know how it's more transparent I can be
so let's go into it let's make this I'm
gonna get some jars
I have a jar
and into HR we're going to catch some
nut fire let's go
[Music]
maybe I'll just go with a bowl first
really quick I got one so I'm gonna grab
it right now you guys
yep
let's go
so let's get some nut Butters going
and then we're gonna put it in that jar
that's actually going to be really fun
all right
[Music]
now these are roasted
you know what you're looking out there
that's coming out take a look at this
I want to show you this
I'm going to shut off the machine
that's pure cashew butter
but where is
the tons of oil that they add
it's not there
that's your real cashew butter for
children I'm just saying if your
children loves nuts or seeds or your
friends or your family that's real Nut
Butter coming out of this machine
foreign
nuts yes you can I'm just doing toasted
because family my family loves toast if
they'll come over they'll actually be
like hey is it roasted I'm like yeah
you can use raw you can use raw nuts raw
almonds you can make raw Nut Butter heck
yeah why not
no one can stop you
you can do it it's your life you got
your free will
machine does it it's incredible
that's what I'm talking about right
yes it's okay to roast your nuts I did I
just saw a question is it okay to roast
your nuts yeah I did Annabeth says
that's a great machine it is for so many
reasons I don't even have time enough to
actually tell you all the reasons
it's that incredible I'm just being
honest
I'm making cashew butter
take a look at this right here
do another close-up on that
do you guys see that right there
is that sick
that's insane
guess what's missing
you know what's missing
all that oil they add
they take away your nuts they charge you
a ton of money then I tell you the
mm-1500 saves you money I'm not kidding
and they add all that rancid oil that
comes from a cashew that's an entirely
different place in the world
it's bulk
it's low quality
I am Christina says does the oil
separation still occur when you make
your own no it doesn't
because the oil separation isn't the oil
from the original nuts
you guys I'm trying to drop a big bomb
on you right now everybody's being
scammed I don't even know what to say
uh pyron says these look different like
night and day on YouTube
incredible
okay so I just made cashew then I told
you guys
um yeah Billy
Billy Rin yeah
I'm gonna make a little bit more if you
guys don't mind
roasted toasted cashew butter coming on
out amazing amazing amazing I'm gonna
let it run out now because I want to
make you guys other nut Butters Rita
LaFleur says I am blown away God bless
you
but you know now what you guys should be
Blown Away about
no you should be Blown Away about
how much money you save when you're
doing your medicinal celery juices and
your medicinal green juices like oh my
God
when you use the celery attachment it's
just mind-blowing I don't even know what
to say and this saves you bunny too okay
so I'm giving you guys an incredible
lesson on nut Butters
Kate Ingram says they can say just
cashews on the label yes true and not
mention the other oils correct because
in the food world because I know the
food world and how it works they don't
have to as long as the oil they're
adding is a cashew oil
correct
wow
all right
okay are you guys ready to be blown away
still
I am going to put this in here I'm going
to get a Jar full of this incredible
cashew butter
and I'm gonna pack it down in the jar
and it can sit in your refrigerator for
a long time and it's just pure and
incredible I'm just doing a little jar
of it right here you can make a big jar
of it right here
Kim says does that machine have
different attachments yeah yes it does
it has the attachments for the celery
juice attachments for the sorbet I'm
going to make it a little bit long haul
19 Real Talk says how long can you store
it a long time you can have it in your
fridge for a very long time
it's as long as you want to store any
nut butter
the thing you know what the difference
is it's real Nut Butter that's the
difference
and I'm giving it like I'm putting it in
nice little incredible Storage R here
like to store it
there we go and then you can pop the lid
on it and you're all set
I'll put a little bit more and you can
put it in a bigger jar I just have these
cute little jars right you guys and I'm
just putting in here and packing it in
there and that's the nut butter right
there
there you go
and you feel you feel it you feel it's
Nut Butter like you feel that okay
all right you guys I just made pure
cashew butter
let's take a look here
whoa what's this I promise you that oil
that's even mixed into your nut Butters
before you it actually settles to the
top is not going to be in here this is
pure cashew butter pure Nut Butter this
I told you watch this from the beginning
on how it works with all the nut Butters
and Seed Butters out there I don't have
time to probably go over it all over
again but let's do some more
let's spend some time having some fun
what's next on the list we are going to
do a walnut butter OMG I'm excited about
Walnut butter and I can't wait I have my
toasted walnuts you could do raw walnuts
that's perfectly fine
there's nothing wrong with that at all
you could easily do that okay get ready
fire it up
Let's Roll
you know when you're proud of something
feels good
like
I knew when
when these machines
were done and I knew like when you save
people money and you give them something
like would you give them options for
Pure Food it just it feels really good
you know because it's like
I gotta put myself in
there always
you have to okay so what you're noticing
right here I'm gonna shut this off
check this out you guys
that's pure Walnut butter right there
without all the rancid additional walnut
oil they add into the jar that doesn't
belong to those walnuts
keep that in mind
that's your pure nut butter
[Music]
you can do raw you can de-toast it
choose which one you like
here's a question from Leah Leah I'm
never buying nut Butters again Dan
neither am I
okay
Robin Hansen says does it need to be
refrigerated is it soft spread yes you
can refrigerate it
now when it's cold it doesn't spread so
easy right when it's out of the
refrigerator just leave it out overnight
it'll spread much easier
okay now that is Walnut butter pure
Walnut butter let me show you guys
yep pure Walnut butter right there and
it's soft and you feel it see how it's
soft Watch What Happens ready see how
it's turning into like that butter
without all that oil rancid oil they put
into every single Nut Butter it's a
major scam going on with the nut Butters
out there and Seed Butters I don't care
what company I'm just saying this is
important to know if you're somebody who
cares about what you put inside your
body because that's really what it comes
down to too it's like you need to know
what's up you're going to put stuff in
your body so
all right
so what I'm going to do is get a spoon
here
and I'm going to get the nut butter in
my jar
guys stick around because we ain't done
today we got a lot of like good stuff
we're gonna do
we are not done we made four hummuses
so pumped up about that
so what I'm doing is I'm putting my
Walnut butter in here
packing it down
right
incredible let's put a little bit more
there you go
foreign
oil
here we are
let me spread a little bit of Walnut
butter on a cracker
I have a cracker in front of me right
here
I am going to get a butter knife
if you don't mind
I am going to take some of this Walnut
butter right and I'm going to spread it
on this cracker
there you go
I'm going to spread one more on a
cracker too
right I'm gonna grab some of this Walnut
butter here we go
take a look
take a look you guys
there it is
got Walnut butter that was a walnut that
wasn't toasted
it's roasted toasted walnuts
there's your nut Butters Mickey's in
this is the medical medium cooking show
I just want to tell you I'll give you a
little half time announcement
announcement
you have just entered the medical medium
cooking show we have a lot going on
where we just made four hummuses we're
making three nut Butters and we got a
lot more to do I'm excited jenjo says on
YouTube I love your shows I am
completely honored I promise you I truly
am I'm honored greatly indeed and I am
at your service the medical medium
cooking show
pretty cool someone asked love life
design asked what machine is this the
mm-1500 link is in the description link
is in the profile the sale is only on
for a couple more days it's 25 off it
even comes with a cleanse the heel book
don't miss out why you can and I promise
you this you will save money whether you
know it or not that means you'll be
juicing and not even know and you're
saving money because it saves you money
instead of the other juicers don't I'm
not trying to harp on the other juicers
it's just that the other juicers and
influencers with the other juicers are
trying to basically get into the medical
medium community and they're just trying
to sell these other juicers and then
everybody
spends all this money
on not only the juicer but all the
produce and everything and it's going to
be one costly Venture the idea is to
save money and that's what these do I
will repeat things for new people
because I'm I'm trying to be
patient and I want people to actually
have that opportunity so new people
coming here if you notice
some people will say how come he repeats
himself
well I repeat myself because new people
come in here and they don't know what's
going on and they have questions and I
want to be nice and answer them okay you
guys
let's make another nut butter
It's Not Butter on the list
no
I got some almonds here they're roasty
they're toasty they're ready to go we're
making our third Nut Butter I'm excited
about that
before I click on the machine though
um so yeah you guys
Walnut Butter sounds lovely Ruth said
incredible we're always live these are
not pre-recorded and people come on
asking questions and that's why I repeat
myself and so then I'm guilty of the
crime of repeating myself and then
you'll hear in reviews and comments how
he always repeats himself it's like dude
99 of my stuff is live and people are
coming on and I'm just trying to be
helpful
I want to be helpful to new people
and um and I know that some people are
very disrespectful when they say he's
repeating himself you shouldn't watch
them it's like dude don't be
disrespectful to people that are sick
and that are chronically ill and they
want help and questions answered right
doing the best we can now almonds
roasted almonds really tough so what
you'll notice if you throw in a whole
bunch at the same time
you could get like a jam and what you do
is you do the reverse on there and there
you go
I want to show you guys
every time I do the almonds
can you put too many at once so just
give it a second here
all right here we go
hold on
raw almonds will never do that but
you're all set
when you do almonds though in here right
don't drop a whole ton down like I just
did do it this way
feed them in slower because roasted
toasted almonds are so tough
you have to actually you know work with
it a little more finesse look at this I
want to show you something guys
this is just incredible
now I love making roasted almond butter
with this machine
watch this
this is pure almond butter coming out
right here Cold Light spring I've
noticed the people who always criticize
They Don't Really follow mm correct they
don't know the books they don't have the
brain saver books or any books
guys take a close-up on this I mean see
a close-up on this you guys look what do
you think that's straight roasted almond
butter the pure stuff it's coming right
through see if I can get a little bit of
a focus on there
there you go look at that incredible
Wendy says your patience is incredible
that's how we learn we need to hear it
more times thank you aw
you're welcome
someone said what kind of cracker check
out medicalmeem.com look at the
directory and you can find like a
cracker or anything else you need
so what I'm doing here is
you can see you've got to feed the
almonds in slower when they're roasted
almonds are really they become like rock
hard you know how it goes with almonds
and you just gotta feed them like this
and take a look the almond butter is
coming out
look at that
it's just amazing
that's your almond butter
I want to show you the difference
between our almond butter that we're
making right now and the almond butter
you got to just drop these in like this
take a look
I love the purple lights
got some purple lights in the back yeah
I love them too
Loop is free with celery three through
three yes I saw an article a
nutritionist wrote criticizing medical
medium and she did not even read the
books too bad she she deters others from
reading them too yes she does
this is how it works right
this is how dark this works you know in
the alternative field of medicine they
write articles when they don't even know
anything about celery juice or medical
medium or the books in hopes that a
thousand people will read the article
and never do medical needing
that's what they do
and it happens everywhere and then an
influencer will do it and then a news
station will do it and then a media
Source will do it and then
another media Source will do it and
they'll do it over and over again until
people get turned off from even thinking
about using medical medium right
but
what are you gonna do
you just put out the best books ever in
health and you pray that angels for some
Divine source or God
or a friend or anybody tell somebody
about that opportunity
Kim says hearing the crunch is
satisfying haha yes it actually is so
we're doing some almond butter
I love it
we're making some nice almond butter
right here we're going to fill a jar
there we go
boom
okay guys we have made almond butter
roasted almond butter and we are going
to put it into a jar
I have a jar right here
so first of all I want to show you give
you a close-up right there see if we can
get a focus on it
there it is that's your almond butter
right there
roasted almond butter I'm gonna get it
into the jar
like this
and I'm going to press it down in with
my fingers just to get the air out
you can store this forever in your
refrigerator I mean not forever but but
okay try not to store it in your fridge
for 10 years
okay
but I've had one in my fridge for two
years then I took it out and used it so
I'm just saying like use your own
discretion in the sense of like how long
you think you can have it in your fridge
but
I kept mine in there for a long long
time do you think you'll get enough
consumed in a few years like out of one
jar here's a little jar I'm just
actually topping it off right there
there you go
all right
what you see is some almond butter right
there
wait
which one do you want
do you want that one
or do you want the store-bought one
that adds the extra oil from almonds
from a different place bulk
you don't want an almond butter that has
50 different almond oils
that were stored for God knows how long
in factories and warehouses and were
used to actually
fulfill a need to lessen the other stuff
I mean it goes rancid so what you're
looking at is rancid oil that's added to
all the nut Butters and Seed Butters out
there so personally I would like real
nut butter
and I would rather have that instead of
the rancid stuff that's added
so I got my nut Butters here I have
three nut Butters let's do a last little
work on that before we move on
foreign
[Applause]
got him right here
all right so the next thing we're doing
is
you guys don't mind if I make a little
celery juice I didn't have any yet today
didn't have any celery juice yet today
so
so that's next let's make some celery
juice I might even throw
something else there and there
okay
this is a major project here I've got a
lot going on
Joel says what's up Anthony signed up
for the late blast yesterday and I'm
super excited yay incredible
Courtney M.A says aw your skin is
gorgeous thank you very much
okay
Cornelia says these nut Butters could be
a nice Christmas gift yes indeed you can
make them throw a lid on them
and boom you have a nice Christmas gift
mostly crunchy Wendy says I'm making my
celery juice right now as well cheers
okay are you beating me to it oh no no
I think you're beating me to it come on
you're making it right now
no I have to hurry up
let's make some celery juice
I'm excited
all right why have the mm-1500 make your
celery juice
because you're gonna use less celery
this is a medicine maker this is an
herbal it's extraction you're witnessing
you're witnessing me making an herbal
extraction
what that means is
celery is an herbal
medicine
when you eat it you do not get enough of
it you need the juice separated
that's the attraction
you have to juice it in order to get
enough of it the medicine out of it
so when a registered dietitian which you
know there's some good registered
dietitians out there that do medical
medium protocols but when a registered
dietitian that doesn't know medical
medium information or the books
does a hit piece and a media Outlet
allows them to do a hit piece without
hearing my side
or the or the stories of people who have
feel your skin and their body and healed
from excellent psoriasis and healed from
lupus when they don't allow those people
into the article
thank you then they're doing evil
they're doing evil bidding
they are dark
what a media Source in alternative
medicine chooses not to call up medical
medium and say look I'm gonna have some
registered dietitians on there to rip
apart
celery
would you like to at least
have it equal where you can talk about
what it has done you know anybody who
has healed from celery juice
they don't do that the alternative
source
that posts an article
They Don't Care About The Chronic Leo
but yet they act like they do because
they're an alternative like website
putting out articles right they act like
they care about people they don't
so they have a registered dietitian or a
nutritionist on there saying how
cellular juice is worthless and science
and research has not found you know
found anything
science of research hasn't even studied
celery juice
the stupidity is so great
loving healing says anyone that picks up
your books knows deep down the info in
them is truth I think haters are afraid
to read them
you know that's really true and another
thing too haters don't read the books
poachers
feel at
m in the health Realm
but yeah the haters they
and they don't cite it whatever I study
nutrition medical medium gave me answers
nutrition couldn't that's from fsog
now I'm just making celery juice if you
want to make a celery kale juice you
could if you want to make a celery
parsley juice you could can you make
almond milk with the machine yes you can
make nut milks in fact it's mind-blowing
and now here's the funny thing I was
going to make nut milk in this in this
video this episode even though we're
live right now all right
but there's so much there's so many
things I want to show you
live is free with celery says someone
contacted me to ask how I got a job
promoting you I spread your info because
it saved my life see that's
that's how it works it's like
there's so much Darkness out there you
guys
if you spent the day with me
and saw what I saw
you wouldn't believe it
it's like there's a hit piece on me
every other day
there's hip thesis out there that I
don't even see
it's just unbelievable it's private hate
groups you name it
but I can tell you this
um
they're not used to people promoting
something without getting paid
that's why so they'll just say oh you
must be getting paid
so what they'll do is a media Source an
alternative or conventional but an
alternative media Source just really a
rag of a source
literally did an article on celery juice
smeared my name in it
and had some nutritionist or Rd on there
saying how it's celery juice is
worthless right when you think about how
awful that is right and why does it
bother me because someone's going to
read that and never drink celery juice
and never heal
they're never gonna heal because
they're not going to think they should
drink celery juice ever
so they're losing a healing tool right
so that's what it comes down to they
lose a healing tool so I'm going to grab
a little glass here
now what's really cool about the mm1500
for so many things
so I got some celery juice right here
[Music]
it's a lot of celery juice okay you can
do a close-up on the celery juice too
there you go
and then the pulp right here now what
the mm-1500 does
is it actually gives you drier pulp than
the other juicers and what that does is
it gives you more celery juice so that's
where you're saving money and that's an
incredible part about it and that's what
I love we got more to do you guys so I
got to make some banana ice cream am I
going to get that ready
Michael Moeller says Susan Craig are
really much impressed by your
I don't know why they gotta fly up there
like that but
most all Health info and people in
health have organizations and programs
that people pay
into right
and then it to promote things and get
paid and promotion all that or affiliate
programs it's not because it really
works and what medical medium
information is it's like people who heal
and they tell somebody else or they post
about it
and it's just so heartwarming because
it's like I'm healing or I healed and I
want to spread the message and they're
not used to that out there
out there because
influencers and everybody they're being
paid to actually say this this product
is this or this thing does that or this
thing does that and so no one's used to
a community that's out there talking
about how they healed
and they weren't paid to do it like that
doesn't exist it's Grassroots the
medical mean communities like Grassroots
community
that cares about people getting answers
and stuff
foreign
all right
see you guys
it's time to make some banana ice cream
so let's do it
so I got some frozen bananas here
now I love making banana ice cream I'm
just gonna be honest okay it's one of my
favorite things to make
foreign
bananas here
we're ready to make it
now what you want to do if you get your
frozen bananas out of the freezer if
they're too Frozen you might want to let
them kind of like sit for a couple of
minutes
that's usually like
you know a good option depending on how
Frozen these are these are pretty darn
Frozen Let's just give it a run
[Music]
I love banana ice cream personally
it's one of my favorites I know it's a
crack pleaser for not just holidays or
anything but it's just a crowd pleaser
in general
who doesn't love banana ice cream who
doesn't love ice cream
but
to think that the MN 1500 can make
banana ice creams it's like okay what
else can it do
good like is this insane
have I lost my mind
please somebody tell me
do I need a psychiatrist
foreign
yeah I like to make my banana ice cream
tell me
Anthony William
what's your favorite thing to do well
doctor
I like to make banana ice cream
I can make it all day
is there something wrong with that
I'm gonna make it in a smaller one right
now
here we go
where's my small
okay
that's just perfect
[Music]
so I'm making a smaller one now I just
froze these
so they may not have been like perfectly
Frozen
but they
have much
these were pretty ripe too whatever
Lana says we've eaten many banana ice
creams made by the m1500 it's absolutely
Divine yeah I love it
that's so great
all right you guys something's out of
control here this machine's sending it
all out I got to get it back on here oh
wow okay
lots of ice cream coming out
okay there we go now understand that
this actually these are Frozen but not
solid frozen like
they're just a little less but I still
like it though
still amazing so here's my little spoon
here incredible right there
and I got this one right there too you
want to take a close-up on that too it
just looks really great but anyway guys
there it is banana ice cream it's a
little melty
I'm guilty of not freezing it long
enough but I do have some bananas in
there that are really Frozen I should
have probably pulled those out
sprinkles on top it's really good
so good
I love it
I hope the show helps
for anybody who has the mm-1500
I want you to know how many options you
have you might be thinking that you only
can juice celery
and I wanted you to know that you know
and the ice creams come out amazing just
so you know this one maybe maybe not as
Frozen is enough but they come out so
incredible
I want you to see how you can make nut
Butters and hummus
so good
let me move some stuff around here
so this is the mm-1500
it's on sale a couple more days
you guys don't mind I'm gonna have a
little bit of this ice cream
cold
brain freeze
if you're looking to get one of these
now it's the biggest sale of the year
the mm 1500 25 off you get a free
cleansing heel book
if you want to get one now it's the
biggest sale right now so
let me get some of this food out
we got hummus's Galore
incredible
we got four different kind of hummuses
this is insane
we got nut Butters
true
it's incredible
um you guys don't mind I might actually
take one of these
so where's my seller just
where's my nut Butters
what's going on
I lost everything
come on guys
got some nut Butters here too
cashew butter Walnut butter almond
butter the real deal
come on
got a party going on got some crackers
here
crackers as well
put these hummuses here that's the
lentil hummus right there
it's a black bean one
wait a minute no it's cannellini bean
hummus which one's what
I don't know
messing up here 's one right here
oh good
really delicious if you take one of
these cherry tomatoes
I'm gonna dip it right in here
incredible
Leah says what kind of crackers go to
medicalmedium.com check out the
directory
Centaur says oh my God I missed so much
yeah we did a lot today
amazing
oh wait that's what I want to show you
guys I forgot
hmm
what I love to do is to take a piece of
kale
I can't believe I forgot this
I like to take a piece of kale here
right and I like to put some hummus
in the kale leaf because it's about
getting those leafy greens that's what
you have to think it's always about
getting the leafy greens right
so if you're going to make your hummus
make sure you make your little hummus
boat and you use your kale or your you
know a mustard green or something and
that's really important to do oh
watch this so
these are mustard greens right here
they're really spicy
set some mustard green I'm going to take
two of these mustard greens like that
put them together
and then you can put a hummus
put this spicy black bean one right in
the mustard green
you can also take I got some arugula in
here
so I got some arugula in here too and
this is how you can do the leafy greens
with your hummus you're adding in your
arugula and you're having your mustard
greens
by the way this is amazing with the
holidays party these are party Pleasers
all of this
for family ready and then you got your
here's the leafy green way to do things
right
and that's what I've always done if I
was going to have hummus or anything
like that it's not about a chip
in hummus
it's about how do you get your leafy
greens in you with almost everything you
do
it
that's the way to do it right there hold
on
so good
hmm
that is red hot right now that black
bean
I put way too much hot spice on it
lay Barton says hello aw followed
medical medium since August whoa
the protocols helped
my overactive bladder numbness on my arm
and legs and my canker sores miss your
light blast today hope I can catch it
next time
you are the best aw
I'm honored you're here
thing is you guys I'm honored all of you
guys are here
because
the opposition is so intense
with all the hip pieces and everything
constantly
it's amazing
that's why I always say the medical
meeting community
is by far the most spiritual
by far the most spiritual and the most
grounded
and the most compassionate
there's no code necessary for the
mm-1500
Robin Hansen says is there a code for
the purchase of the juicer no there is
not you're on Facebook there
nope check it out the mm-1500 no code
needed I am going to grab this piece of
kale
and I'm gonna actually put maybe a
little bit more in here
guys I'm gonna try
the lentil hummus back here
yep it's red hot Sarah bear it's red hot
incredible
foreign
says light blast today no
the registration was yesterday
it got all filled up
20 000 people signed up in an hour
I wish I could leave that registration
open until the light last
so you know there'll be whatever a few
hundred thousand people signed up or
you know 500 000 people whatever but I
can't
the system
that
we're using in everything we're doing I
Can Only Hold 20 000 this time
Donna JD says Anthony I want you to know
that you have literally saved my life if
it weren't for the medical medium
protocols yeah dot dot
on YouTube
by the way guys on YouTube hit the like
or whatever it is if you like the video
yep
Elizabeth Fisher says you saved my life
I'm honored
truly
check out the body swelling podcast you
guys medical meme podcast at Apple
podcast
I know it sounds like I'm repeating
myself again but if I don't tell the new
people about the podcast what am I going
to do never talk about it again
oh I'm never gonna mention the podcast
again because I don't want anybody to
think I repeat it myself
anyway remember me a podcast at Apple
podcast
the swelling fluid retention
lymphedema podcast you can't miss get on
the newsletter medicalmedium.com
so you can get notified and get the
emails and the free recipes and all the
other stuff so you don't miss the
possibility of another light blast event
in the future or whatever it is make
sure you sign up the medical medium.com
to the newsletter
make sure you listen to the podcast
episodes
and sign up to Twitter if you can okay
that would be incredible because
um no one on Twitter out of my hundred
and something thousand followers ever
got a notification in the past so just
so you know
our Twitter was non-existent and
unusable for 10 years
to saying
so let's hope we can use it again
all right because what I want to do is
put exclusive content that I do nowhere
else on Twitter
I want to do exclusive content big time
including things I say
including videos but I want to put a lot
of exclusive content on Twitter
because somebody might see it again
because my Twitter has been kind of on
hold for 10 years
anyway
exclusive content and oh by the way
telegram I do exclusive audio
messages
on Telegram
so I want to let you guys know about
that pretty cool
so much good stuff
follow me on me we too
so on me we
that's another place to follow me
which would be amazing
because I'm going to do a lot of
different material different exclusive
stuff all of that and if you guys can
leave some reviews on the books so brain
saver
have you guys read this yet
If You Think You're Gonna read it in one
night all I can say is good luck
and it is impossible
you will not be able to read
these two Bibles and so people call them
Bibles in one night
Courtney M.A says the body swelling
episode was
is mind-blowing
my blood
anyway check out brain saver brain saver
protocol
does anybody need one for Christmas
great Christmas present go to amazon.com
U.S 40 off brain saver brain saver
protocols or go to the library
I know somebody that went to the library
they got it out for free
and they gave it to a loved one for
Christmas Even though the loved one was
gonna have to give it back to the
library eventually
still was really thoughtful and really
amazing okay it oh wait how do you clean
your books
remember
take a towel
whatever paper towel or a towel right
dishcloth just have it moist not soaking
wet just a little damp if you want a
little touch of soap or something or you
can use a hand sanitizer or something
and you could just clean off your covers
because they come dirty because of
Amazon's conveyor belt
the publisher ships pristine copies
right off the press
to Amazon
and other places
and then the person receives it in the
mail
and it's got smudge and dirt and grime
all over it that's from the conveyor
belts
the grease tickier thing your little
doll and you just wipe off you clean it
up nice and nice and good
it comes out great
Uma pretty funny right
foreign
yep
If he if he says I hope you can say
something about exercise I used to
exercise very vigorously 10 hours a week
whoa now on medical medium protocols
it's less than two hours per week yet
I'm more lean more defined and more
stronger because that's what happens
medical medium information makes it and
protocols makes it so you can actually
become a stronger healthier person and
if you wanted to exercise less you're
welcome to do so and you'll still be
healthier than you were before medical
medium when you're exercising more
that's how it works
in a nutshell maybe I'll do a podcast
all about that you guys I love you and
I'm gonna have like a total feast and
pig out is what I'm gonna do
um and I got some people coming over
some family so hopefully uh everybody
likes all the good stuff love you guys
and I'll see you soon