[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week we talk about the
most advanced healing information most
advanced health information that's out
there anywhere and decades ahead of
what's out there now as far as research
and Science and everything else and
that's how you get people better just
like the 16 ounces of celery juice on an
empty stomach every single morning is R
literally changing the world right now
and that's the medical medium
information The Source spirit and it's
changing the world right now and it's
helping to clean up people's blood
because people have toxic blood today's
talk is on is your blood toxic is your
blood toxic this is really an important
show all the way around from for so many
reasons and advanced information is how
you get people better that's how they
get better it's how I've gotten people
better for decades and decades and
decades and and it matters that much to
have even the smallest piece of
information that's never been out there
before which is straight celery juice
that's an example because that's
actually good for your blood good for
getting your blood not to be toxic
that's why I'm even bringing it up right
now but it's a prime example how one one
little gem one little gem can be that
lifechanging can you imagine all the
other gems that are in Liver Rescue can
you imagine all the other gems that are
in the other medical medium series books
that Spirit has delivered and that's the
whole point so everyone starts to turn
their life around and it matters you're
worth it you're absolutely worth it
you're worth doing the things you need
to do you're worth seeking out the right
information you're worth staying away
from misinformation you're worth it all
and you're worth staying away from the
trend
someone said to me hey the celery juice
it's a trend now no actually the celery
juice is the PowerHouse and then the
trend is trying to destroy it now
they're trying to destroy it they're
saying oh wait a minute you shouldn't do
all straight celery juice Oh that's oh
wait a minute you should do this put
this put pre P protein in with it do
this the trend is out there to try to
actually break it down and ruin it
actually that's what trends do so no
it's not a trend it's a truth celery
juice is a truth and I'm talking about
it a little bit because we're talking
about toxic blood what are we talking
about talking about dark circles under
the eyes varicose veins we're talking
about reenal syndrome you know the
discoloration and all the symptoms when
you get the the purple blotches and
you're you're you're feel like the
circulation isn't there and your
extremities and everything else we're
going to talk about that a little bit um
I mean list goes on we can talk about a
lot of things gout we can talk about
everything that has something to do with
dirty blood and you think that those
don't apply to you you think that gout
or Renault syndrome or anything else
doesn't apply to you you're wrong
because it's more than that toxic blood
causes problems everywhere it causes
every problem you can possibly imagine
when your blood's toxic with certain
things in it you get the brain fog when
your blood's toxic with certain stuff in
it you get all kinds of symptoms you get
the fatigue you get everything that
that's the whole point is your blood
toxic and we're going to go deep into
this deep into this indeed because it
needs to be done you know I can't I
can't just sit around and wait and wait
and wait hoping that chronic illness is
going to slow down out there it's not
unless the information gets in your
hands unless you become the expert I
want you to become the expert I really
do so here's the deal here's a deal is
your blood toxic how does this work
first of all I'm going to start off
right here right now with this there are
so many things in our blood so many
different toxins in our blood that
science and research in the medical
industry can't even do an analysis on
they can't even analyze it blood Labs
don't even have the ability to see
what's inside our blood they don't it's
limited it's absolutely limited they
can't see the petrochemicals inside your
blood can they can they see the
petrochemicals that are inside your
blood you tell me can they see all the
solvents that are inside your blood you
you tell me can they all those
detergents and spray cleaners and
everything else that have all these
petrochemicals and solvents can they see
all that in your bloodstream when they
draw blood do you hear that come back
from the doctor's office no no of course
not do they see any viral material in
the in the blood no they don't see
byproduct in the blood they never do
they never see byproduct they never see
viral stuff they never see all that
discharge from all the bugs they never
see all that either in the blood do they
see heavy metals in the blood
no no now unless you literally unless
honestly you stepped into a mine of lead
a Lead Mine somewhere you know what I
mean and you were bathing in lead water
and they could be like yeah you got lead
poisoning they do blood they could
actually they could find the lead sure
that's different but I'm talking about
traces that that torment people's lives
on a daily basis that are just floating
around the bloodstream you go to the
doctor doctor's office you come back you
can't they can't see all this stuff it's
not possible and what about other things
too what about all the other things too
what about domestic the domestic
Invasion the domestic Invasion that's
means household products that we're
using every day um plug-in fresheners
we're using plug-in fresheners we're
using uh aerosols we're using yeah you
know whatever air fresheners everywhere
what about that the assault on that what
about when you walk into stores and all
that candles and all those perfumes and
all the cologne you smell everywhere
that's in the bloodstream do you think
it just just magically disappears do you
think we don't need to take care of our
blood and our liver do you think we
don't need to take I mean seriously what
about going to the gasoline station go
in gasoline station gra just pump your
own gas oh fumees coming out breathe it
right in oh that doesn't go into our
bloodstream no that's not going to sit
there for a whole day or two or three
days just floating around in our
bloodstream no and science of research
can't can't can't showcase that I me
they can't pull blood out and say were
you at the gas pump the other day
inhaling somebody's gas fumes that was
spewing out of their car and and the
wind was taking it right to you and
you're breathing in straight gasoline
where you know with all those
petrochemicals going in there going
right into your lungs right into your
bloodstream and once a week you're at
the gas station filling up we you know
they're not the doctor's not going to
say that the blood lab's not going to
say that they're not going to say are
you know where were you they're not it
doesn't work like that it doesn't when
you're working on your when you're doing
your gas grill or your gas stove and
you're breathing in all burning gas
fumes or whatever it is and it's just
you know you're cooking every day and
you're breathing in all those gas fumes
I'm not trying to tell you that you got
to hide I'm telling you we got to clean
up the blood we got to protect you we
have to make sure your blood doesn't get
too toxic that's just some of the stuff
that could be in the bloodstream that's
not even the natural toxins that the
body produces see the body is under such
a load it's unbelievable every single
day it's under such a load it's under
adrenaline adrenaline is so darn toxic
it's it's not even funny it is literally
so darn toxic you could not believe how
destructive it is it's it's that
destructive even healthy adrenaline like
just just something that gets you high
something that's gets you high and it
seems like it's a good thing like
anything like hey I'm going to go skiing
and whoa I'm going down a more of a
dangerous slope who I never took that
way before and wow my adrenaline's
pumping I made it down and you're all
you're all psyched and happy and that
adrenaline right there is doing 101
damage damage to the liver damage to
everything and I'm not saying you can't
do that because you still there were
still things that you got out of that
was that was really amazing but the
point is is that the blood gets toxic
that's why we don't live forever that's
a whole another reason why we don't live
forever I mean you could you'd be
surprised yeah I there's people out
there is like oh my God I can't believe
what happened to that guy oh no what
happened to that girl I don't get it
what happened to that girl she was she
was doing this she was skiing she was
snowboarding everything was going great
she just went to school did this did
that and all of a sudden what she's
bedan with Lyme disease oh what she's
got this oh wait a minute what happened
oh this person died this person's gone
now who where what happened we got to
keep our blood from being toxic it is so
important because no matter what it
plays a role in every single thing we do
in our life and in our health you know
and I am so sick so sick to death of all
the like misinformation detox programs
and all that out there I am so sick to
death of it all I got to be honest I
can't even tell you because first of all
no one even knows what's in people's
bloodstreams second of all they don't
even know how the liver detoxes I'm
sorry I'm going to say it over again if
you don't like it I'm sorry I don't know
what else to do it's either give you the
truth it's either give you the
information or just be like yeah yeah um
oh yeah no sure that's fine too yeah no
I guess yeah no you're tired toxic you
got to detox yeah you're detoxing right
now that's really what it is here just
keep on doing all this all that just
keep on doing that shake every single
day oh keep on doing keep on doing that
cleanse yep yep go keep on doing that oh
that protocol somebody's protocol sure
sure you're detoxing that's why no you
know what I'm not going to play the game
you got to know how your liver Works how
it cleanses how your blood gets toxic
how it affects your heart how it affects
your brain what's in there how to heal
what to do to protect yourself what to
do to protect your families you got to
know all of that and you got to become
the expert because other than that it's
a wild west I swear to God out there in
Alternative Health still to this day
it's the Wild West it's infiltrated with
so much misinformation many of it coming
from garbage studies garbage studies
that still get no one better
unbelievable sending people off the
track all the time for example you'll
hear out there ELC carnitine El
carnitine is good elar cartin El cartine
did you know something did you know what
feeds every virus there is I talk about
that in medical meeting book one it
feeds every virus there is it can make
you sick and take you down and you know
and that's out there everywhere El
carnitine elar carnitine and what about
collagen and stuff like that collag
everybody's on to college and college
and College college has nothing to do
with people are sick and if they got to
get better it's unbelievable and you
know people go I got to put my college
in my shakes got to put my college in my
shakes it's unbelievable the
misinformation oil oh you got to be on
your fish oil the whole bit yeah it's
methyl mercury in the fish oil doesn't
matter what company makes it that's
different than eating a piece of fish
you get more Mercury from a Mercury free
fish oil capsule so-called Mercury free
fish oil capsule you'll get more Mercury
from that than a can a tuna because it's
it's basically homeopathic I talk about
in the books too it's homeopathic what
it is is when they extract when they
pull Mercury out of something it gets
stronger believe it or not and sure if
Mercury's in it it it's also strong too
but when you keep on pulling it out when
you centrifuge it out and you give out
fish oil it's actually has the memory of
mercury which is which causes more
effects more effects on the health can
you can possibly imagine and so what
happens is because it's so so hyper when
you pull it out and pull it out it
becomes hyper it's a homeopathic option
it's really bad so what it is
everybody's on the fish oil it's highly
inflammatory fish oil they're all on the
fish oil
unbelievable
unbelievable same thing with apple CID
of vinegar you want to hurt your liver
keep on drinking that Apple CID of
vinegar keep on it's the best vinegar
there is if you're going to have vinegar
do apple cided vinegar absolutely if
you're going to have vinegar and I can't
stop you if you're going to have vinegar
and there's nothing I can do about it
let it be apple cider vinegar because
it's the best one there is of course
it's from apples it's from apples for
God's sake it is it's amazing it's
amazing stay away from fruit everybody
says which you don't want to do you want
to make sure you're eating plenty of
fruit stay away from fruit but do apple
cider vinegar stay away from apples oh
those apples are too sweet you better
eat a green apple oh my God the
misinformation you guys are so thick
it's unbelievable if you've been
affected by it if you've been infected
by it uninfect yourself if that's even a
word disinfect
yourself disinfect yourself from the
misinformation that's how you will get
more years on your life in this lifetime
for yourself I always tell people okay
people say well yeah my my uh my
grandfather died at 80 he well he would
have died at
95 if he did this and this and this and
this and
this that's right oh you know this
person died at 70 it would have died at
80 do you want 10 it's 10 more years
even worth having it is worth having 10
more years is worth having 10 more years
there's people that die at 50 they could
have could have made it to 75 they were
doing just some of the right things in
their life life with their health as
people who die at 90 they could have
lived to be 115 120 you know it's
amazing how it works the point is does
it even matter yes it does it matters
cuz it's not just about how long you can
live regardless it's the quality of your
life no matter what it's the quality of
your life during when you're living and
the whole bit and that matters and so
many people and I understand you'll lose
the quality of your life because our
blood is toxic cuz we don't know what's
going on we got all these different
things going on back to Apple CID of
vinegar cuz I probably angered a whole
bunch of you guys like crazy I know it I
know it like bees like bees I get it
because you're into the apple cider
vinegar I totally get it but it pickles
the liver you don't know what your liver
likes it's unbelievable what we like and
what we put in our mouth has nothing to
do what what with what the liver likes
and that's another thing too in Liver
Rescue I talk about that I have a
cleanse in there a cleanse that you
don't have to spend $5,000 to do okay I
got a cleanse a simple cleanse in there
to protect your liver you can do the
cleanse periodically and bring your
liver back and get your blood to to not
be toxic that's what we need to do and
that's the power of healing because it's
not about having to go and and do this
massive you know oh my God I got to do
this I got to do that and got to do this
it's not about that it's about just
doing a few of the right things and it
matters it really does so with apple
cider vinegar what it does is it pickles
the liver there's sodium in our blood
there's sodium inside our blood okay and
naturally inside our blood our liver
harb a larger amount of sodium because
our liver is the filter the filter for
poor sodium bad sodium that we get in
our life all through our life you don't
think you you think the salt that you
ate on that hot dog or whatever it was
in that hot dog 5 years ago you don't
think the salt still traces of it aren't
still in you somewhere you don't think
the salt that you've eaten all these
years and all those treats and all that
garbage and everything else and I'm not
blaming you for that I get it I mean
what everybody I I get when why we eat
the way we eat and that's not about what
the show is about we can do a
compassionate show about why we end up
eating like we're eating how we're not
educated how it's emotional to I I
understand all that I talk about that in
Liver Rescue in the book Liver Rescue I
talk about that in there but I'm talking
about you don't think that sodium that
sodium that road salt isn't in your body
it is it's stored in the liver it's
stored in the liver to protect you it's
sitting inside the liver the liver
actually stores it and then tries to get
rid of it and discard it over the years
we've compiled so much salt on our in
our bodies to and it makes our blood
toxic cuz it's not the right kind of
sodium like celery juice which makes
your blood not toxic it cleans your
blood celery juice cleans your blood
straight celery juice so what happens is
it it actually
dismembers dismembers if that's a if
that's an okay word to use it it
completely dissolves and breaks down and
dismembers other salts that have been
that won't leave the organs we get
salted throughout our life this isn't an
anti- salt campaign this isn't a anti
salt show you can do a little Himalayan
sea salt if you really want here and
there for a fun treat you can do a
little bit of Celtic Sea salt or
something if you you're making a recipe
if you really love salt but we've had a
lot more salt than that in our lives
early on early on from the beginning all
the way to now and even though the salt
might diminish in the bloodstream it get
collects in the organs and it cakes in
the organs it cakes pockets of sodium
pockets of salt end up in the liver and
in other organs and this starts also the
process of really dirty blood dirty
blood in and toxic blood so when you do
vinegars any kind of vinegars whether
whatever kind of vinegars all the other
vinegars are bad they're way bad and
apple cider vinegar is better but you do
apple cider vinegar and you're doing a
lot of it every day a few tablespoons a
day or you're putting it in your food
every single day or you're told you
should be just drinking it every day or
whatever it is because it's good for
this good for that you know someone says
oh it fixed my acid reflux can I tell
you how many cases of acid reflux it
caused how about that you there there's
a percentage of people that fix their
acid reflux do you know there's a larger
percentage that it caused acid reflux
did you know there's a tiny small
percentage of people it helped their
bloating did you know there's a massive
large percentage that it causes bloating
how about that okay 10 people it gets
their bloating better or they think they
got their bloating better from the apple
cider vinegar 90 people bloat the hell
up like you can't believe from it it's
unbelievable
unbelievable okay 10 people get to get
their acid reflux a little better by
actually using Apple set of vinegar even
though they changed their diet and did
other things too along with it and then
90 people get the worst acid reflux ever
imaginable from from apple cider vinegar
I've seen it over and over and hear
about it over and over and over again
it's not apple cider vinegar attack it's
is your blood toxic and I'm talking
about what's going on when you're doing
the vinegar what it does is it gets it
mixes with the Sodium piles from your
old sodium storage is from Bad salts all
this time it mixes with it in organs
such as the liver and it pickles the
liver it literally pickles it and that's
what happens it causes a
pickling literally and you have to
understand what that does it prunes up
the organ it puts it under stress
massive stress makes the organ more
toxic so apple cider vinegar isn't for a
cleanse it's not cleansing you it's
making your blood more toxic is your
blood toxic yes it is Apple CID V will
make your blood more toxic I don't care
if there's pitchforks torches you know
what I mean the whole bit at the house
you know I don't care or at my office
and they're all sitting with pitchforks
now cuz of apple cider vinegar I don't
care and I don't care about the trolls
which which I call clones I don't care
about the Clones either I call them
clones cuz it's like gen genetically
modified people that that are heartless
and they all talk the same bling
language so it's unbelievable so and
troll I like the word troll because I
think it's a good word so I don't know
why we have to call you know we have to
call everybody trolls out there I call
them clones so I don't care if the
Clones are upset about Apple CID of
vinegar and I don't care what it does
for Apple CID of vinegar sales out there
CU I don't sell anything I don't sell
anything I don't sell any products I
don't sell nothing I don't sell anything
in the thing and you want my book get it
from the library you can't buy my book
get it from the library I don't sell
anything in the end you can get all my
information from free you got 150 radio
shows you can get for free on Soundcloud
right here you got all the information
all the articles for free you can get
every single thing for for free and
that's the way I've always worked and I
don't care what industry I kind of harm
it's just the what it is I don't care
what Empire that starts to break down
because of because my information gets
out there and then some Empire breaks
down because Apple C of vagram Empire
starts breaking down oh the lectin
Empire starts breaking down oh some
other bogus Trend breaks down you know
breaks down it's about your life it's
about your health it's about you it's
about your loved ones it's about getting
you extra years it's about making sure
you heal it's about making sure you're
not lost and you're not lost with
information everybody else they're
trying to sell something so how can you
even trust if the damn information is
even right they're trying to push
agendas all the time you're getting this
for free there's a reason for it and you
can heal so blood being toxic happens to
all of us naturally even naturally our
body's already under a load trying to
process so much we're trying to get
ammonia out our digestive systems don't
work good our livers are broken down the
bile is not strong enough to break down
the fats and disperse the fats okay our
hydrochloric acid is not good enough to
break down proteins everybody's HCL is
down that's why celery juice is so
critical important to get you better
think about that think about that so
what happens is when food starts rotting
you get gut rot you get get food rot
everybody gets his food rot and they're
dropping proteins in and everything else
and their food's rotting and ammonia is
being produced all that ammonia is in
the blood causing toxic blood and in the
end it's going to cause cellulite down
the road if you think you're cellulite
free and you're never going to get it
try try again you think you're never
going to get cellulite because you're 28
years old and you're you know in shape
and you're running in the gym and you're
doing good but you're eating your
protein and you think you're drinking
the appleid of vinegar and you whatever
you're doing you think you're not going
to get cellulite when you're 42 try try
again you could void all those things
and that's just one thing I'm talking
about skin problems I'm talking about
all kinds of different health problems
I'm talking about strokes and heart
attacks I'm talking about everything no
one's immune but we can protect
ourselves more than you could ever
imagine in any way
possible what happens is HCl lowers no
matter what kind of shape you think
you're in no matter what you're doing
you could be running every day you could
be running five 10 m a day you could be
in your you know your sports gear
running 10 miles a day you could be on
your bike you riding your bike and your
food can still rot and pneumonia could
be pouring out of your pores and into
your
blood and it could be literally
weakening things in your body and that's
how the blood gets toxic and that's just
somebody like that what about somebody
who's viral what about somebody who's
got the Epstein bar chronic fatigue
syndrome fibromyalgia they got
hashimotos thyroiditis they got all
these other things they got you know all
tingles and numbness raining in the ears
tonight's vertigo balance issues aches
and pains um headaches rashes ecos soras
um you name
all these different things Tremors
shakes um Twitches insomnia all these
different problems that we can have
floaters in the eyes spots in the eyes
what about all that's that's toxic blood
too but that's viral blood that's what
happens when viruses they release
neurotoxins and dermat toxins with
examon orasis it's dermato toxins
floating to the surface of the skin
released by The Epstein bar virus
feeding off of copper this is I'm going
really quick cuz there's so much
information to deliver so make sure you
listen to the show more than once so you
don't miss this exos psoriasis and what
it is and that's the that's a virus
inside the liver feeding off of copper
creating dirty blood creating toxic
Blood by releasing poisons inside the
bloodstream called dermato toxins that
will surface to the skin and cause
rashes like eoris rosace and so forth
that's what that is but that's toxic
blood once again so the thing is with
Liver Rescue whether it's anything
that's viral or not viral and it's just
toxic blood in general dirty blood we
have to address it we have to address it
it's important and anybody with chronic
fatigue syndrome hashimotos thyroiditis
any kind of other things going on you
know any kind of thing happening lupus
um they're getting diagnosed with lime
which oh my God if you want to know the
truth about lime get medical medium book
one take take a minute out to order the
book take a minute out just go to Amazon
order the book medical medium just get
the book first book medical medium
Secrets just get that book and and if
you can't can't afford it I don't know
what it is I don't know if it's $10 or
$12 but if you can't afford it go to the
library get just get it for free because
you need to know what's going on with
lime disease so you can get better so
you can heal so you can move forward so
you can do what you need to do the truth
about it it's still it's still
unbelievable I put that book out a few
years ago whatever it is and still to
this day I mean the lime the lime like
control over people's minds and the labs
and what they do to people and nobody
knows the truth it's unbel it's so sad
so anyway with 30 blood and toxic blood
it's not just about detox detox detox
detox and it's not just about Talking
Heads out there and the so-called
experts in the detox world they're like
oh you got to detox oh you got to detox
it's more than that it's all these
things I'm telling you no one knows
about the salt that's compiled inside
the liver that's been there for years
and years and years from hot dogs you've
eaten a long time ago and everything
else that you've eaten and whatever I
mean you could just damn it Pizza what
everything it has all that bad salt do
you think that salt just disappeared it
disappeared out of the bloodstream
it did but it stayed compacted in the
organs and then when you do like
vinegars of any kinds you actually
pickle organs and you age rapidly you
actually age rapidly and that's what
happens but you can get those toxic
salts out by using celery juice and
things of anything with skin problems
anything like exam psoriasis hives any
kind of thing that happens with the skin
too peeling in the hands peeling in the
feet all kinds of skin issues you can
celery juice literally can help by
actually removing dermat toxins and tox
and viral toxins out of the blood to try
to get you better the blood is filled
with so many things that's not seen by
research and science they can't see
anything in the blood you know what's
really annoying you guys is they will
take so much blood from you do you know
how much blood they throw away you
wouldn't believe it when they pull vials
I run into this all the time the blood
labs are they're literally criminal in
my opinion because they they they demand
so much blood I've seen people get
sicker because they had 15 vials of
blood taken out you know people with
chronic fatigue syndrome what happens is
when you get all that blood removed it
removes your immune system and then how
it doesn't remove the viruses that are
that are hurting people so you got the
worst CFS M you got chronic fatigue
syndrome you got fibromyalgia whatever
it is you got fatigue you got you you
know aches and pains you're your body's
burning up you got all kinds of
different burning on your body you got
rashes you got whatever it is you're
dealing with you got you can't think you
got the worst brain fog possible you got
so-called Lyme disease or whatever it is
that's going on or whatever you're
diagnosed with multiple sclerosis and
what do they do I'm talking so fast my
voice is getting dry what do they do
they they extract too much blood from
people that are sick I see it happen all
the time what I've always told clients
no no no no no you give them four five
five vials at a time you give them three
vials it's it's their problem they're
Throwing It All Away they throw it all
away they throw it all away they remove
your immune system they literally remove
your immune system you'll never hear
this anywhere that's the whole point
you'll never hear it anywhere else
you'll never hear the truth about things
anywhere else and listen I know a lot of
Physicians and I know a lot of experts I
know a lot of science people I know a
lot of people in science I know
geneticists I know so many people in the
field of medicine and people say to me
they say like things like it's amazing
what they say to me they'll say how do
you know what how it works how do you
know which way work you don't know any
doctors or anything are you kidding me
are are you kidding me I mean just I
mean it's unbelievable and and yeah I do
and the thing is is this is that is that
I know a lot of people in the field that
are even above the regular thing that's
going on so when you go to your doctor I
know people that are that are actually
in the system of the medical field that
tell me and they say you know what
you're 100% right about how the blood
Labs work this is what they do this is
what they do they they take all this
blood they use a Speck of it and they
literally throw away your blood they
throw away your blood it's unbelievable
and when they screen blood it's it's the
system is so flawed the way they screen
it and how much they waste and what
happens is when they pull it out like
that you get more toxic so when you're
sick they're actually killing you slowly
that's the irony because you get more
toxic and more viral because what they
do is when they pull that much blood out
they're pulling out your immune system
your white count they're just ripping it
out it's in your blood it's hard for
people to produce that when they're sick
when they're that sick and they're that
Viral with lupus Lyme disease multiple
sclerosis Hashimoto fatigue cry fatigue
fibromyalgia scaros all these different
things whatever they're dealing with all
these different illnesses and different
situations and they're going to the
doctor and they're getting all pulled
out of them and then you go to these
functional medicine doctors which I
still love too but you go to these
functional medicine doctors and they're
pulling out 25 vials 20 vials it's all
being thrown away cuz the labs are
throwing it away and then what's
happening your whole blood your all your
white count is being removed and then
and what's happening the viruses aren't
being removed and then there's less
white count to stop your viruses and
people get sicker and sicker and sicker
with Lyme disease and their lime doctors
are pulling all this blood out of them
they're getting sicker and sicker and
sicker that's how it works and then they
get thrown antibiotics in them even
though they get thrown also herbs and
even though they get thrown natural
stuff and diet they also get throwing
antibiotics in them and then that makes
them sicker and sicker and their blood
more toxic I've seen this over and over
again that's just lime I'm talking about
all kinds of different things and so
what happens is when you're sick your
blood can even get more toxic when
you're not sick your blood's still toxic
and science and research doesn't have a
clue as to far as far as what kind of
petrochemicals are floating in the blood
all day long what kind of diesel fumes
you just breathe in when you were on
your bicycle on the road you know like
riding your bicycle and somebody drove
by and all that petrochemical went
inside your bloodstream and it's sits in
there for 2 weeks and then goes inside
your liver no one talks about that or
how about that when you're in college
and you paint at your dorm room and and
and you Splash pain on yourself and
everything and it's all sitting inside
the liver and it still keeps your blood
toxic every single day as you're getting
older and you age faster then you get
the hot flashes then you get the viral
issues and the hot flashes and the
weight gain and nobody knows why you're
getting the weight gain and your blood's
toxic they can draw blood they can't see
the toxins it doesn't you know it's
unbelievable that's how flawed the whole
system is and that's how behind we are
with health even the most advanced Al
Alternative Health is dogging it's so
bad it's painful when it comes down to
chronic illness but yes science and
research can send some amazing rocket
ships in in their sending rocket ships
in space even though they're antiques
compared to what's coming in the future
but still they can send them into space
they can remove aneurysms out of
people's brains they got robots now I I
know a neurosurgeon that actually uses
he uses a mechanism he controls a
mechanism to carefully carefully pull
out like remove an aneurysm it's it's
unbelievable and that's science and
research in a good way life-saving
medicine stuff like that sure but in
chronic illness it's absolutely
disastrous and toxic blood not being
recognized like toxic blood not being
recognized dirty blood not being
recognized is one of the big mistakes
and in throwing blood away in all the
patience is another terrible mistake
when will that get fixed probably not in
my lifetime not in my lifetime that's
never going to get fixed but I tell
clients you give them three to five
vials the most
at a time you go back and you have them
do different tests then and do another
three vials and let them throw away your
blood carefully let them throw it away
carefully so your white blood count
doesn't diminish to such a degree that
you get more viral and more sick and
your strep comes out and and annihilates
you and your the Epstein bar comes out
and your hhv6 comes out and your simplex
one comes out and starts screwing you up
and getting into your nervous system
causing more problems with your nerves
and so it's important it's really
important to know that you can protect
yourself because your blood could get
more toxic when you're sick just from
regular standard medical practices it's
just a little tidbit to try to help you
along with this
so how do we allow toxins that are in
our blood all the different things I
said that are in our blood from you know
cooking on a gas grill from being at a
bombfire one day with all that treat at
wood being burned and going into your
lungs you know all of that all of that
or being you know Somewhere over the
summer and there's just a pile of wood
burning a massive pile of wood burning
and you're you're out there and you're
just you know you're partying or
something like that and it's just like
you're breathing in so much of this
stuff and and you know what I mean and I
don't like that whole thing ah you can't
live forever hey your immune system has
to deal with it you said The more stuff
you throw at yourself the more it builds
you up it makes you stronger it doesn't
work like that that's the biggest croc
that's the biggest pile of of you know
what I've ever heard it doesn't work
like that you age faster stuff happens
in your life organs start you know you
start oh wait a minute what my I have
kidney problems you next thing know
you're 38 years old what do you mean
doctor I actually have kidney problems
is that what this is It's I have to go
on dialysis it's like it's like it's
like there's reasons for all of this we
have to keep our blood clean and we have
to protect our livers and get them
clean and so and and clean up our
viruses clean up all the other things
that's inside our body the irony is
people don't even know they're viral
they just have symptoms and they're like
well I don't know I just have I have
these symptoms they don't even know
they're viral like well I have these I
have this vertigo I had it and I went to
my chiropractor and my chiropractor
didn't know what it was and it's viral
any kind any kind of vertigo is that's
what it is 100% viral and so it's it's
one of these things where you know
people don't even know they're walking
around oh I'm tired I'm fatigued yeah
it's viral and know they don't even know
these things it's amazing how it works
but it's it's important to know what's
going on with you so back to toxic blood
back to the whole thing about how we
don't know how toxic it is our bile
coming out of our liver is filled with
poison filled with poison so if we don't
take care of our livers and clean them
up the bile itself is filled with poison
and it goes into the Gove ladder and
that's how stones are produced they're
produced because of the amount of poison
that we have that our liers collecting
all the time someone said to me how does
a gall stone start it starts with you
being having toxic blood for many years
eating the wrong things getting exposure
to all the wrong things and then the
liver having to process all this and try
to get it out in some way and detox it
out sends it up the bile duct into your
gallbladder and it forms stones and it
also goes into your digestive tract all
the time into your digestive tract the
poison goes in there all the all the
different stuff all the different stuff
and if it's poison if it's poison such
as like dermatoxin from an Epstein bar
and having copper in the liver then it
becomes
rosacea see that's how it works science
of research has no idea how what rosacea
even is they they don't even know what
causes it what's going on they're just
right now they're they're in the mode of
blaming everything on their safe fault
it's the safe fault is which is bait and
switch or safe fault whatever you want
to say it's it's your body attacking
itself it's your fault and science and
research is going to figure out ways of
trying to stop your body from attacking
itself and we're going to study more
genes because it must be your genes too
these are the two things you're holding
on to so that people with chronic
illness get sicker and sicker and sicker
and sicker instead of getting down to
the bottom of everything and what's
really happening instead of getting down
to the bottom of what's really going on
and what you need to do so we live our
life we eat all the wrong Foods our
liver gets totally filled up with so
much poison and toxin completely filled
up with so much poison and toxin that's
what our liver does so that's all
happening so we're aging faster okay and
then we get the viral issues that we all
have the viruses that get into everybody
in so many different ways and the
bacteria that gets in UTI UTI is a strep
that means you have strep in your system
sibo that's strep in your system I talk
all about this in Liver Rescue if these
are just Prime examples in 10 years
every single person young adults mostly
women young women are going to be all
diagnosed with sibo all diagnosed with
sibo in the next coming 10 years all of
them they're all going to be going to
the doctors they're all going to be
going to even conventional doctors they
be diagnosed with with a small
intestinal overgrowth back bacterial
overgrowth and they're going to be
diagnosed with sibo that's all strep in
the gut still to this day science
research doesn't know it's strep but
it's actually strep and so we have all
these things they're producing toxins we
have old salts inside of us caked in
there we got other poisons
petrochemicals we got Plastics that are
inside of us we got Pharmaceuticals
inside our liver inside our brain inside
our body in different places it builds
up it builds up it builds up and then
then in many women in most women it's
blamed on menopause all the symptoms
when it's not menopause all the symptoms
that's toxic blood that's occurring
that's the liver being toxic with
viruses such as Epstein bar toxins and
poisons that built up for years decades
from Bad suntan lotions okay from Bad
perfumes from Bad lotions from bad colog
from from anything from Hairspray
whatever it is built up over the years
and and that's just some things that's
not even the foods and the chemicals
that are in foods and preservatives it's
all in the liver it's all in the blood
the blood gets toxic and then you start
getting around 35 38 years old and many
women it's a lot earlier now they're all
Expos they're all experiencing menopause
symptoms like just earlier it's not
menopause it's the hot flashes it's the
liver being toxic it's the it's all of
that heart palpitations the liver being
toxic with viruses releasing poison
going into the heart and creating heart
palpitations that's how it works but
toxic blood is the heart palpitations
the toxic blood it's it's all of that I
mean that's how that's how the hot
flashes and it's blamed on hormones so
then they're given steroids which are
hormones they give steroids to try to
calm the symptoms down and make
everybody happy it's unbelievable where
we're at we're so behind it is
unbelievable you want to know more about
any of this just get the medical medium
series get the books get the books and
like I say I say it over and over again
just go to the library cuz I don't care
I don't care if someone buys the book or
not I care about them having the book
it's all that I care about and I need
you to have the book you know and so
because you have to know how to help
yourself what's the point otherwise wise
I mean you're worth it you're worth
knowing what to do and so this toxic
blood carries us out through our
lifetime through our lifetime and if
we're more viral then we get sick early
and toxic blood happening like all of it
together compiled together and the liver
gets overloaded with viruses overloaded
with toxins and metals so what do we do
what are some things to help get rid of
toxic blood one is is the heavy metal
detox smoothie so the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie you can go to
my blog you can go there you can find it
you go into the books Liver Rescue has
it in there the heavy metal detox
smoothie very important thing to use
okay so it's got the spirulina in it
it's got the vmer barley grass juice
powder in there it's got that it's got
It's got the the cilantro in there it's
got the Frozen wild blueberries and it's
got a little bit of this the Atlantic
Sea Coast vegetables so Atlantic Sea
Coast sea vegetables meaning the douls
in there a little bit of Dolson you'll
find the recipe so the heavy metal detox
smoothie pull Metals out of the blood
everybody's loaded with metals from all
the exposure of plastics which have
metal in all the exposure of
pharmaceuticals which have metal in it
all the exposures of petrochemicals that
you're Brea in every day that have metal
in it and metals falling out of the sky
use the heavy metal detox smoothie to
start cleaning up your liver and blood
that's one thing another thing you can
do is a celery juice 16 ounces I I I
would do 32 ounces if you could if you
can't do any do a little bit do a little
bit the one thing I see all the time on
the internet I see people saying I can't
do 4 o of accelery juice and I I got
respect for you I completely understand
it I I get it and you know people be
like I can't do 2 oz it just bothers me
meanwhile I have on my Instagram feed
there's babies that are drinking a whole
glass of celery juice like they're 6
months old and they're holding and
they're holding a glass of celery juice
and they're gobbling it down and
drinking it down and they're smiling and
laughing and they're they're actually
getting celery juice in in them so when
I hear when I hear adults that are 40 50
years old and they're like they they
they they they don't like the taste and
they go I just can't drink this I can't
drink The Taste and these are little
babies there's one-year-olds drinking
celery juice every day but that's that's
not all all across the country and
around the globe and the people that
have the medical medium book series
they're they're they're little kids
they're one-year-old they're 2-year-olds
are drinking celery juice and they're
all drinking celery juice and and so I
got these 40 and 50y olds that they're
like I I can't drink the 2 ounces it
make kind of makes me doesn't feel good
and like it's like come on get get it in
you and just get it in you it's amazing
how the mind works get it in you and
work on healing really unless unless you
just have an inversion to it it's a
horrible inversion to it where you're
some kind of like you going into
athlectic shock or something I mean
something like you know something
happens like that if you're if your
doctor tells you you're allergic to
celery then don't then yeah I don't I
mean like a real allergic reaction not
not like going to get like a going to
like getting you know the whole thing
with your mapping out your food and
you're doing food elimination things and
you're doing food uh food sensitivity
food sensitivity testing and celeries on
the list but it it doesn't bother you
but it's on the list don't get fooled by
that that that's all a mess that's all a
hot mess that whole food sensitivity
thing make sure you're doing celery and
with celery juice so that's another
thing celery juice will go into the
liver start to loosen up old old
compacted cake salt so that if you do
have apple cider vinegar you won't cook
your liver you won't salt you won't
pickle your liver and prune it up and
damage it I'm not saying do the apple
cider vinegar I'm just saying so you
want to do the celery juice you want to
clean that up and you want to clean up
the blood cucumber juice if you really
can't do celery juice do cucumber juice
that will help also with the blood it
helped actually helps to get the blood
less toxic cleans up the blood lemon
water every single morning lemon water
every single morning okay that's why we
put it on the map people did lemon water
I I'm not the I'm not the beginner I'm
not the beginning source of lemon water
I'm going to tell you right now I'm the
beginning source of celery juice
straight celery juice I'm not the
beginning source of lemon water but
we've definitely mov the needle on Lemon
Water people are doing it it's a
definitely become a main staple out
there which is incredible make sure
you're doing the lemon water that's
absolutely the that's what you do I mean
I've been doing lemon water since I was
four years old but you know it's a long
time ago but it's been around it's been
around for a long time and they were
doing lemon water in Italy long long ago
squeezing lemon and water adding a
little honey if you want to add a little
honey if that's what you want to do
that's the only way you can get that
lemon water in you then add a little
honey I'm okay with that and so the
whole deal is is that it's about getting
the blood less toxic so you want the
lemon water every morning you want your
celery juice you want your heavy metal
detox smoothie if that's all you can do
and the rest is whatever you're doing
the rest is whatever not so good food
choices or not so good whatever then
that's all you can do I'm totally on
board with that but but it's going to
help so you don't get dark circles under
your eyes so you don't get varicose
veins and spider veins on your body so
you don't get cellulite on your body so
you don't get weight gain because your
liver getting so tired and so inflamed
and from so many poisons and and toxins
in your liver that are never being
cleansed or cleaned out and viruses and
bacteria so the weight gain happens it
hits everybody and their weight starts
coming on their weight just starts
pouring on it hits everybody it's so you
don't get any of that too so you stay
away from all that weight gain that's
another thing too getting your toxic
blood cleaned up gets weight problems
behind you it gets you in a better place
so you can lose weight and start healing
because viruses won't be able to pollute
your liver so much they won't be able to
affect you so much and in Liver Rescue I
talk about all the different supplements
and things you can do for viruses and
all the different conditions you know
that people have but the thing is is you
this is the big start of getting your
blood less toxic the other big start is
lower your fats lower your fats and do
not listen to the trend out there when
they tell you when they tell you protein
protein protein they're telling you fat
fat fat fat fat that's what they're
telling you so be careful so if you're
totally into animal protein reduce it
I'm not saying get rid of it if you
don't want to get rid of it fine I'm not
I'm not against it I'm not against
animal protein you but reduce it if
you're if you're if you're plant-based
or you call yourself vegan or whatever
it is you're plant-based
then reduce your nuts and seeds lower
the fats reduce any oils reduce nuts and
seeds cut your avocado down to size a
little bit cut your tahini down a little
bit cut your cashews down cut them down
so you can lower your fat because what
happens is the higher the fat levels you
have in your bloodstream the more toxic
your blood stays remember that your
blood will stay toxic so much
longer so much longer the fat suspends
the toxins it suspends it it doesn't
even let it leave the kidneys it doesn't
even let it leave the body and these
high protein diets whether they're vegan
high protein whether they're animal you
know high protein paleo high protein
they're high fat for God's sakes and you
know what happens in the end heart
disease cardiovascular disease down the
road problems everywhere even if it's
healthy fats you get problems too much
fat harms the liver causes it to get
congested causes the heart to have to
work harder the more fat in your
bloodstream the harder your part heart
has to work to draw that blood through
it tires it out for down the road and I
don't care if you're exercising every
day and you're taking care of yourself
on that level and you're in shape and
you're fit you don't think people die of
heart attacks like that I see it every
day I see it happen all the time it's
like wait a minute how did that
38-year-old guy die of a heart attack he
was in the gym every day did you see how
cut he was how come he's how how come
he's dead how come he's gone I mean it's
unbelievable
because because you you're still putting
in all that high fat in every single day
which is under the Guist of high protein
and then viruses can accumulate and then
you can have a stroke viruses can
accumulate because it's hiding viruses
love to hide in the liver and hide under
all that fat you can have a fatty liver
but not have a scrap of fat on your skin
on your body yet and have a fatty liver
and not even get diagnosed by the doctor
of having a fatty liver because they'll
see you and be like whoo you're in good
shape and you walk out so it getting the
toxins out is also part of lowering the
fats so what does that mean if you're
doing grass-fed beef once a day I mean
if you're doing it twice a day once a
day if you're doing chicken at dinner
grass-fed beef for lunch grassfed beef
for dinner chicken for lunch get rid of
the chicken do it once a day we do it
once every other day get rid of eggs get
rid of cheese milk butter I don't care
if it's free range I don't care what it
is get rid of eggs dairy all dairy
products it's all high in fat all it
does it stops you from being able to
detox and get rid of the toxic blood it
stops you from being able to protect
yourself from all the different
autoimmune diseases which aren't the
body attacking itself but viruses
attacking the body all the different
autoimmune diseases that everybody's
coming down with out there you want the
blood less fatty so we can get the
toxins out because everybody's blood is
toxic I've seen people's blood so
dehydrated and so toxic that when
they've gone to get even blood work it's
literally like it was it was like hard
for them to draw blood out of them hard
for the for the practitioners to draw
blood out of their body and the
practitioners didn't know why it's
because you also get dehydrated with
dirty blood you get chronically
chronically dehydrated that's why I'm
saying do the celery juice in the
morning or cucumber juice if you really
have to do the do the um do the lemon
water in the morning do the heavy metal
detox smoothie have a salad for lunch
maybe a little bit of avocado in the
salad how about that have tomatoes on
there don't be afraid of tomatoes God
for a bid they're life-saving you have
tomatoes on there cucumbers on your
salad lettuce is spinach okay and then
you know and and put a little avocado on
there if you really want you can do that
squeeze some orange juice on there
squeeze some oranges on there put some
dates on there you know you can just you
don't want your fats too high so you can
put a little avocado in that one if you
don't have avocado you can put some hemp
seeds on there but you don't want it too
high I mean that's that's if you're
plant-based you know you're doing that
and if you're not plant-based and you
want to have chicken don't have you know
6 oz have have have 3 oz of chicken on
your salad and don't have it again at
night you had your chicken at night have
some sweet potatoes at night even have a
potato nothing wrong with a potato and
if you're at all raw person and you're
totally all raw do another salad with
fruit lots of fruit do fruit for lunch
you can do smoothies all day the point
is there's a lot of ways of making sure
we can lower your fats whether you're
high protein you know animal paleo
whatever it is or or you're in the in
the vegan area or you're in the
plant-based area you can you can totally
totally lower fats bring in more fruits
and vegetables
and and and make a huge difference and
impact on how toxic your blood is to
reverse so many different conditions
like with reenal syndrome what Happ what
that is what rain out what that is
that's all these poisons and toxins from
Epstein bar virus that go to the
extremities that's what that is with
heavy metals with a high heavy metal
rate so they go to the extremities
that's toxic blood yeah we want to get
rid of the viral debris and all that but
you have to at least start cleaning up
your blood and start getting yourself
better and start rebuilding and
cleansing your liver and the whole bit
so is everybody's blood toxic out there
100% yes it is different levels
everybody's at a different phase
everybody's at a different stage and
don't get fooled by if you hear
something out there I did the medical
medium program protocol didn't really
help I don't have a protocol I have
Timeless classic Timeless information to
help anyone heal in all the books the
information is there for wherever you
are in your life and in your journey
that means if you're really really
Advanced you could even take your
journey further if you're extremely
Advanced then you can take advantage of
the supplement the supplements that I
talk about in there and how to take them
you can even you use the foods the
cleanses and you can keep on going all
the way with the cleanses you can push
it to the limit even if you're 100%
super Advanced super just just eating
really really clean no matter what side
of the aisle you're on it's there and
it's about information to why people are
sick it's not about oh I did the medical
medium protocol that's somebody who
tried what celery juice for 2 weeks
they're like I tried that there is no
medical medium protocol instead there's
information from my source that's in
there to help you with your journey no
matter where it is and how you've come
along no matter how bad off or how good
you're doing or how advanced you are
it's to take you to that next level and
educate you on what's going on in the
body so you become that expert and you
can take your healing even further it's
classic information is what it is it's
going to stand the test of time and it
already has because science and research
are trying to actually pick up and speed
up up they're trying to catch up to the
information I put out just years ago and
they're just starting to actually come
out with stuff now that I've actually
have documented before they even even
were looking into it so it's there for
you and your family to get you better to
move on let's get our blood less toxic
let's get ourselves better and let's
move forward together that's what we
need to do move forward together so
we're talking about cleaning up the
blood and I'm just talking about using
foods to do it you want to do a much
more advanced way of cleaning up the
blood get Liver Rescue get Liver Rescue
and do the
369 Liver Rescue cleanse do the 369
Liver Rescue cleanse and read it read it
and get and and do the cleanse read it
and do the cleanse really important this
way you can work on healing and you can
actually really also clean things up but
if you want to start doing something
right now do the lemon water you got it
do the Cy juice you got to do the heavy
metal detox smoothie do a salad with low
fat keep the fats low try not to get
hung up on the words protein you're
going to get yourself in trouble you're
going to get yourself in trouble over
the years until you age and your skin
gets wrinkly and you get sick because
you're so focused on the protein bull
crap that that's been going around for
years it's all about protein all about
protein oh you're you need that you're
sick cuz you need more protein oh you're
just yeah okay sure should you kill your
kidneys with tooo much protein whether
you're a vegan or you're or you're
somebody in the Paleo movement or
whatever it is you kill your kidneys
literally instead the keto thing you
just kill your kidneys with all that
high fat and the protein they'll be
bringing more fruits more vegetables
more leafy greens every day bring the
juices in and then if you are into
animal protein have a little bit if you
are into if you are into the plant
plant-based have a little bit of avocado
but you got to and a few nuts or
something here and there but you got to
be careful get your blood cleaned up and
we could do it really advanced really
Advanced like in live a rescue and easy
cuz it's easy to do in there or we can
do it just gentle baby steps it's about
wherever you are and everybody's in a
different spot that's why there is no
medical medium protocol it's more than
that it's bigger than that it's bigger
than that that's the whole point where
are you right now in your healing
process where are you right now in your
healing process are you just starting or
just if you haven't even done anything
just you're starting here then do that
celery juice are you really Advanced
where you've been cleansing your whole
life and doing this and eating hardly
anything and eating mono then you need
to do this too the information's in
there for everybody that's the whole
point and it's always been like that
take advantage of me take advantage of
me that's what everybody needs to do
while I'm still here just take advantage
of me that's what you need to do I love
you guys dearly you know that every
waking minute every morning I wake up
and I say what can I do what can I do
for you guys in any way possible can I
do and that's what I
believe I believe that I can do more and
so I say what can I do and I ask Spirit
what can I do I love you guys dearly I
believe in you take one day at a time
take care and I'll talk to you on the
next show I can't wait listen to the
show again all right I love you bye