chemtrails in the air all the time. We
breathe them in every single day we step
outside. They seep in during the night
and during the daytime in our own homes.
Dangerous toxic chemicals have been
dumped on everybody since the 1960s.
Planes filled up with tanks inside of
them. No passengers on there, just a
couple of pilots. and dangerous and
deadly toxic chemicals, toxic waste
being released out of these jet planes
into the atmosphere, dumped on us day in
and day out. And these chemicals are
cocktails, highly toxic cocktails,
mercury, lead, aluminum, copper,
petroleum byproducts, acids, barerium,
solvents, herbicides, mosquito killers,
thousands of different kinds of
byproducts from worldwide industrial
chemical industries. chemicals from old
storage bins from World War I, World War
II, Agent Orange, DDT. They don't care
who breathes in what. They don't care
what's dumped on everybody's food, the
gardens, the farm fields, and they don't
care about little children with
asthmatic conditions, and they don't
care about the chronically ill. They
don't care about people with different
kinds of symptoms and conditions that
are hyper sensitive. What they care
about, they the evildoers, the people
that run this planet way above public
authorities.
What they do care about is if you know
it's a chemtrail, is that you know the
truth that they're dumping stuff on you.
They don't want the chemtrails to stop,
the classified programs to stop. They
want to keep on dumping what they want
onto people and they want everybody to
believe the ultimate con.
[Music]