oh my God
medical medium brain shot challenge this
week I kid you not it's Thursday October
20th don't miss it here's what you have
to do you have to go to
medicalmedium.com and you have to sign
up to the brain challenge it's right on
the home page that's how you find it
check this out you download when you get
there and you sign up to the brain
Challenge on medicalmedium.com you
download the free pdf the PDF the whole
thing's free you download the PDF and
you get your grocery shopping list you
get the tools the whole thing of what
you need to get for the challenge I'm
just letting you guys know okay get
ready it's a 10 day challenge
10 days we're doing one of these
incredible
incredible legendary brain shots each
day all right so each day for 10
straight days if you guys just came on
here watch this from the beginning
please so you have the details it's
gonna be incredible do you guys have the
ring the brain saver books because
seriously I'm not kidding for real go to
medicalmedium.com when you get a chance
after this sign up to the free brain
shot challenge it's gonna be with me 10
straight days it's starting Thursday if
you don't have a brain saver book yet
you can still do it sign up and do it
because I'm going to make sure you have
all the information you're gonna have
your grocery shopping list you you when
you get to medicaleame.com and you sign
up with the brain challenge you have to
download your PDF
with the information in that PDF like
your grocery shopping list I'm gonna say
this over and over again oh my God oh my
God
I am excited you guys seriously
this is gonna be incredible so I want
you to know if you don't have the brain
saver books get one when you can they're
legendary powerful healing books with
information that will blow you out of
the water blow your mind I'm serious
these books have lightened them you feel
it when you get them they are very
special
hands down the greatest books of all
time the greatest Health books of all
time the greatest medical books of all
time the greatest healing books of all
time I'm letting you know that's what
these are and you'll know it when you
see them and you get into them the
information in here is unbelievable so
back to this you guys I just came on
here to tell you that if you go to
medicalmedium.com you can sign up it's
right on the home page to the brain
saver challenge it's free when you sign
up to the brain saver challenge you will
see that you can download a PDF it's all
free the PDF will have information on
your grocery shopping list because we're
doing a 10 day challenge
each day we're doing one of these
unbelievable incredible life-changing
brain shot therapies each day out of the
10 days it's going to be mind blowing
I'm letting you know
okay so this is going to be really
really fun okay hope says can you make
several shots hope check it out when you
get there when you get to
medicalmedium.com and you and you
actually download the PDF you sign up to
the brain saver challenge you'll get
like those answers will come they'll be
there for any questions it's going to be
incredible you guys
seriously so
I got the brain saver books in front of
me do you have your brain saver books
and thanks for asking by the do you have
the brain saver books because
the books are just that unbelievable
people are having
experiences with the shots they're
having experiences right so here's what
it is brain shot there but if you just
got on here like what is he even talking
about you got to make sure you get your
brain saver books but there it is
medical medium brain shot therapy okay
medical medium brain shot therapy offers
instant relief while you're working to
fix deeper problems and levels with the
brain and that's what's incredible about
these because these help you get there
that's the whole point your brain and
body have a quick response to medicinals
delivered in liquid form what I call a
shot
designed to be highly absorbable in the
mouth but it's more than that
these brain shots the valuable healing
components can reach the brain fast it
can reach the brain really quick this is
why you get that relief this is why the
brain shots are unbelievable
okay so be specially formulated shots
have the ability to reset and rewire the
brain they do you will experience it I
promise you this that you will
experience a rewiring of the brain when
you do these medical medium brain shot
Therapies
and here's another thing that's
incredible it shocks you out of patterns
while at the same time reducing triggers
reducing triggers that's part of the
power they have that is power that's
part of the power so
I got a public service announcement
right here Public Service Announcement
right here if you go to
medicalmedium.com
medicalmedium.com go to my home page
Boom the home page okay
and listen in Kate like this is in case
okay here's how you here's what you need
to do you got a couple things go to
medicalme.com right to the home page
and you'll see the brain saver challenge
click the link
get in there sign up sign up and you can
download the PDF the whole bit you guys
so in this case go to the link in the
description right here too the link in
the profile or description
all right of this live stream and you
can go to the menu on medicalmedium.com
and go to brainshot therapy option you
will find the sign up or the follow Link
in description or Link in the bio on
Instagram just letting you guys know
watch this from the beginning so you'll
have all the details
I'm really excited about this you guys
I notice is the light infusion
meditation is everything the light
infusion meditation inside the brain
saver books is that incredible all on
its own it really is
you guys click the link right here in
the description
on the bottom you can do it that way too
I've done four different brain shots so
far
just did the anger shot and this one is
so instant sends send you so much peace
in the mind and that's the thing so
let's go over the couple of the shots
right here and see what we got
negative exposure shot we're going to be
doing that one in the 10 day brain
shot challenge plunge we're gonna do
it's not to cleanse the brain shot
challenge so here's what it is negative
energy exposure shot I can't wait to do
that one mold exposure shot I can't wait
to do that one
that's really going to be incredible so
many people are exposed to molder EMF
and 5G exposure shot that's going to be
in the 10 day
brain shot challenge
let's keep let's keep it going this is
going to be incredible
obsessive thoughts shifter
that's also going to be in the 10-day
brain shot challenge
let's keep them coming anger shifter
there it is the anchor shifter
that's incredible that's going to be in
there as well in the 10 day brain shot
challenge guilt and shame shifter
how about that that's going to be
incredible I can't wait for you guys to
try these
my God
my friends my family that are using
these they're just blown off their seat
we're gonna be doing a dream shifter
that's going to be really exciting
I can't wait for that one we're gonna be
doing the adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer
foreign
we're going to be doing the burnout
stabilizer
amazing
we're going to be doing we're going to
be doing the Betrayal
and broken trust stabilizer betrayal and
broken truss stabilizer when you guys do
this 10-day brain shot challenge tell
people tell everybody if you can
just look out life-changing results from
this I'm excited it's free go to
medicalmedium.com
so go to medicalmedium.com
you guys
really excited
the link is in the description link is
in profile in the description so look
for the link in the description and the
profile so check it out find the link
there hit that link and get there
that would be incredible
so you guys
just a reminder I'm going to take you
right back to the beginning really quick
also watch this from the beginning I
want you to have the details
the medical medium brain shot challenge
starts October 20th Thursday it's a free
challenge we're going to be doing 10
days and we're going to be doing 10
different shots chosen from above so in
this brain shot challenge these shots
were chosen from above for the brain
shot challenge
so this is going to be an exciting
moment an exciting time make sure you
have your brain saver books get a hold
of a brain saver book
when you get a chance if you don't have
it yet where you know you have and just
so you know I mean there's 30 shots in
the brain saver books
there's brain shot therapy cleanses the
whole bit we're doing a 10 day
brain shot therapy challenge just
letting you know
Michaela says can I do this challenge
with you while on 369 cleanse yes you
can indeed you can you could do it while
you're on the mono cleanse you could do
it while you're on the 369 you can do it
while you're on the medical meme 369
Advanced you can do it while you're on
the anti-bug cleanse you could do it
while you're on the heavy metal detox
cleanses any of them you can do this
while you're on any of the medical
medium incredible cleanses that are
helping people around the world and yes
you can perfectly fine you just signed
up
awesome I'm excited for you I can't even
wait seriously it's a free brain
challenge cleanse I mean brain challenge
that starts Thursday October 20th
and I'm pumped up about it I really am
so
when it comes down to the monoclines
depends upon you know what's going on
with the person too if they're doing the
monocleanse for all kinds of reasons
they could you know pass on it if they
like but anybody's welcome to do it I'm
excited truly am you're tempted to try
this
I hope so I really do
that's incredible Anna says I will sign
up will you have Replay for when I can't
be there yes we will have replay I can
answer that question
for sure
you guys the link is in the description
link is in the profile just letting you
know
Tracy Brown says which book is 369 and
it didn't cleanse the heel which is
kicking around back here somewhere
see you guys
just want to give you a little heads up
we're doing 10 days
each day is going to be one of these
incredible brain shot Therapies
it's going to be either the negative
like each day the negative energy
exposure shot the Betrayal and broken
trust stabilizer the obsessive thoughts
shifter the EMF and 5G exposure the mold
exposure guilt and shame ex shifter the
dream shifter like seriously this is
going to be absolutely incredible
I can't even tell you anymore like
that's how amazing what's the brain
challenge someone just asked amazing
question I'm here at your service here
at your service
at AWS Bar and Grill I'm here anyway you
guys
the answer to that question is first of
all
you're looking at two incredible books
that I promise you when you get them in
your hands you will be blown off your
seat
the information no one's ever heard
before
the the
incredible
light that comes out of these books
they're living when you and you think
that might not be possible you hold the
books you read the books
and you look into it you will see it is
unbelievable what's in these books the
answer to the question what is the brain
shots the brain shots are in these books
there's 30 brain shot therapies there's
seven brain shot therapy cleanses we're
doing a brain shot therapy challenge
it's a 10-day challenge it's coming up
October 20th it's coming up this week
Thursday
and seriously I'm excited negative
energy exposure shot patrolling broken
trust um shot 5G EMF shot like guilt and
shame shifter shot dream shifter shot
just a whole bunch of adrenal stabilizer
like seriously this is gonna be
incredible I'm talking so fast
I'm talking so fast I'm just
seriously if you can't find ingredients
to all the brain shots you can pick the
ones you can find ingredients for from
the book or challenge that you're going
to be doing each day with us
as you're doing it along with us Emily
says so much validation in these books
I mean right these books a lot of
information you take it a little bit at
a time PK I know it's pretty funny to
get a little bit at a time because
there's so much each line is powerful
each line has information in it that is
life-changing that you want in your
consciousness
question which juicer is the best
there's three on the Omega website okay
what to choose for mm-1500
I work with Omega on two of their
juicers mm-1500 that one right there
mm-900 those are the two that I love the
reason why just hear me out because you
save money when you're juicing and I
don't see that with other juicers I just
don't
I've used them all out there I've tried
every one for the most incredible ones
to big big ones to the most commercial
ones I've tried them all
and all they do is throw away money and
what happens is that the the mm-1500 the
mm-900
they're built so that you actually
squeeze more juice out of it so it's
incredible so I love that they pay for
themselves I'm just letting you know so
that question is on there if you need an
option the Omega 1500 900 are 20 off in
case you do need a juicer so this week
right now the Omega 15 mm 1500 mm900 is
20 off if you need an option if you have
a juicer fine use your juicer
if you need a juicer it's 20 off
so and it's free shipping in the United
States so it's free shipping in the
United States 20 off of the mm 1500 a
mega juicer incredible juicers they
squeeze so much out of them
Envy Doom
oaw important question do we need to
pass the brain shots through a strainer
same as with CJ
you can't you know look you can pass it
through a strainer you can kind of rub
it through a strainer that's fine if you
don't have a strainer and you can't use
a strainer you can you can try it
without the strainer but I like the
strainer and you kind of just you know
shake it through or rub it through
that's fine
I'm really excited about this I can't
even tell you my books are due to come
in about a week Lisa I am excited for
you seriously Olivia says wow thank you
for letting us know about the juicer
sale Olivia
it's incredible 20 off the mm 1500 by
the way the mm 1500 is just an
incredible juicer it's everybody I know
that has that juicer is is just like oh
my God and the 902 the mm-900 those are
the two that have like a compression
where they where the compressions really
high so they squeeze out all the juice
I'll be answering questions during the
challenge by the way news flash
news flash I'll be answering all
questions during the challenge
yep
exactly
it's gonna be really exciting I can't
even say it enough
listen to me
I'm like jacked up about it seriously I
am pumped up about it so you guys
I go everywhere with these literally go
every I just literally I walk around my
house with them I walk around everywhere
I go out with them I go if I go visit a
friend I'm taking them if I go do
whatever it's just like I'm literally
holding on to these and I go everywhere
with them it's like I can't help it and
it's the craziest thing because the
information is that incredible you have
to know something this is really
important right I was telling a friend
of mine and my my friend was like aren't
you sick of these you you wrote them you
like why would you hold on to them and
read them all the time I'm like
I got the information from above I had
to learn it all the same just like
everybody else I have to hear the
information learn it become an expert at
it I have to read it constantly I'm a
human being I have to learn the
information every day just like
everybody else who gets the books I love
the books I could feel the energy and
the power and the light in them I can
feel how blessed they are I can feel the
power they have and the information is
so mind-blowing and you don't just want
one you want to get both because it was
one huge Buck the brain saver books are
40 percent off on amazon.com us right
now 40 off you guys there's 12 books in
these there's 12 books in these
literally 12 books I'm not kidding it's
like one book right there of information
two books in there three books four
books five books a whole recipe book in
here six books right there of
information Nation ready same thing over
1200 pages right one book two book three
book four book five book six books you
guys probably seven books in here
there's probably a total of like I mean
a lot of books like 14 books in these
books
and it's forty percent off and the
information is already legendary in the
sense where it's changing lives I'm just
saying it's unbelievable the brain saver
book so I go everywhere with them the
only thing is they're heavy because
they're so packed you got like 12 14
books in the book so it's just packed
anyway
let's give you guys a quick rundown last
run down last news flash
Jackie says the amount of your love for
the books radiates from them both I love
the books so much I don't even know what
to say I was talking to an author friend
and the author friend who has the book
and the author friend doesn't love his
book he's just like I did the book had
some cool Concepts I took it online the
info I added a little twist of what I
thought
but your books are coming from above
filled with information I love them
Erica says that's your baby that is true
there's two babies right here
two babies right here two really really
big babies I mean seriously like for
real anyway you guys love my books walk
around with them all the time I know
what's in them and I say to these books
you're gonna heal a lot of people you're
gonna help a lot of people get their
lives back you're gonna reverse a lot of
anxiety depression to personalization
bipolar you're gonna take away people
schizophrenia yeah a bunch of people
have that you're gonna do all kinds of
stuff chronic illness fatigue everything
else you guys are going to be changed
these books are gonna be turning
people's lives around
Uma Cali scripture
Uma scripture
yep
brain shot therapy challenge
coming up October 20th Thursday
I'm gonna be there
10 days straight I'm gonna be on here
doing the shots with you negative energy
exposure shot betrayal and broken trust
Adrenalize adrenaline stabilizer guilt
and shame shifter dreams shifter mold
exposure uh EMF and 5G exposure shot
I might have forgot one or two
the brain shot therapy challenge sign up
the link is in the description please
and then download your grocery list and
information and details to prepare you
because it's free and it's for 10 days
it's for 10 days and it's free
I'm just excited because when you really
think about quick Heart to Heart
a quick Heart to Heart
I'm really excited because it's like
this
I killed myself getting this
information
in the books
and which is fine which is fine that's
what I do right it's what my job is to
to do right it's a messenger
but I know what's in here I know what it
can do
I know how it's going to help people it
already is
and it's more than that
it's going to help them for generations
and generations
I know how special of a time this is I
know these are the greatest books of all
time in health history and I know
they've hands down will always be and
you know when you know all that you feel
this feeling of like people are gonna
get you know they're gonna get the
benefits moved forward
reclaimers of Health books are unreal
amazing of honored truly I'm honored
I really am
and
you know what they're going to do for
people
I know what's going to happen
and I just I just I could feel
I could feel the power in these books
a good event at night
I got the books by my bedside
I fall asleep with the books on my bed
people are experiencing groundbreaking
results with the medical medium brain
shot therapy and and that's just the
medical medium brain shot therapy I'm
not talking about
the the seven heavy metal detox cleanses
including the advanced and the extractor
I'm not even talking about that
unbelievable
claimers of Health says books are unreal
you guys
you won't be disappointed
tell everybody about these books tell
them and they're 40 off amazon.com us
right now 40 off
you guys they're 300 400 books
and they're
26.29 dollars
they're 300 400 books easy with the
printing the full color the recipes in
it everything else the massive size of
these books
and the information that's in them
is priceless
and they're for 26
29 or something
which blows my mind anyway you guys all
right link is in the description tell
everybody about the link if you can to
whoever it is that you can tell let's
get to that free brain shot therapy
Challenge on Thursday get your
information
[Music]
textbook textbooks in school cost two
three hundred dollars a book right now
literally that's what's like people are
like oh well I'm going to school I need
all my textbooks and stuff like that
it's like
for a book this size it's like okay you
know it's a thousand dollars in books
they're like I need about two thousand
dollars in books
these are twenty six dollars they're
medical textbooks from above medical
medium science from above powerful
information from above to move you
forward I love you guys not gonna do the
robot
not gonna do the robot
not gonna do it I'm gonna do it though
Thursday
with the brain shot challenge I'm gonna
do the robot times 10 I'm gonna do like
I'm even gonna put the robot costume on
I'm gonna put the robot costume on I'm
gonna dust it off I'm gonna get it out
out of the closet
I'll even do that one but you know what
the last time I did that one you
remember what happened that was crazy do
you guys remember if many of you guys
were around at the time when I put the
robot costume on and I did the robot
costume that day remember what happened
that was crazy that was like bad
Ronaldo says yeah and those textbooks
expire within a year yours will be
forever because it's Advanced
information
that never gets proven wrong only proven
right over and over and over and over
again all right I love you guys
all right