right here gonna juice some celery for
you guys did you check
out the caffeine episode medical medium
podcast at apple podcast did you check
that one out
it's all about caffeine that's a mind
blower it's about coffee
matcha chocolate and you know what i was
thinking i was like
hey you know what if someone does want
to get off their caffeine because many
have
they did it with the celery juice so i
wanted to juice some celery just in case
you guys want to get off of some
caffeine or something because a lot of
people
you know they want to get off but they
they feel like they have to do it to
like get through their day to function
hey everybody and you know when it's
hard to push through
when you're like when you're not feeling
good you got a little bit of brain fog
or you don't feel good
and you're pushing through every day on
your caffeine you're like doing your
coffee drinks
doing your matcha drinks you're doing
your chocolate a lot of people do it
multiple times a day
and look i'm cool with that i mean you
guys can do that i totally want you to
do if that's what you want to do
but if you want to get off the caffeine
as i talked about in the episode so
check that episode out okay
it's episode 7 all right from the
medical medium podcast do not miss
that episode it is a mind blower did you
guys
listen to it did you hear that episode
it really is
it's about coffee about matcha it's
about chocolate
and it's about secrets of the the whole
thing about it all like all kinds of
things like that you don't know about
caffeine secrets about what people go
through with caffeine and nobody knows
about all of that so the link is in the
description
so you know just so you know the link of
the medical medium podcast episode
caffeine coffee matcha chocolate is in
the description
so make sure you check that out i'm
really excited if you guys hear it
are you doing the meditations to the
moon meditation keep the moon meditation
going if you want to do that healing
healing your soul
the brain meditation share it with
others share
the coffee matcha chocolate episode okay
the medical medium
podcast if you if you if you feel
inclined you want somebody else to hear
that episode
it's a mind blower so i'm going to juice
some celery because
then i thought about it because the
thing is most of the people that i know
that got off of caffeine so most of the
people that i know
they used celery juice to get off of it
and
would be like well how's that how's that
going to work it
does it has that kind of power because
what the celery juice does is it
it's a complete electrolyte and when
that complete electrolyte
goes to the brain that's when you can do
the switch off
then i talked about that so in the
episode you got to check this out okay
in the episode you got to hear how that
works by the way this juice right here
uh 20 off on this omega juicer my
favorite juicer which is incredible so
it's 20 off right now i think it's
running for a couple days so make sure
you check that out
and um which is incredible and this
juicer is my favorite you guys know that
i licensed
my name to this company here i said yeah
just use my name if you want it's my
favorite juicer go ahead use the name i
licensed my name
you guys know that and but this is my
favorite juicer
and it squeezes every last drop and
that's what i love about it it squeezes
every last drop out of it
that's what i dig about it but so back
to this whole thing with the caffeine
episode it's like it's like well okay
there's a heat
i put healing tools in that episode
powerful healing tools
so you can get off the caffeine if you
want all right and i talk about like
what caffeine does
to our adrenals what it does to the to
the emotional center of the brain how we
get dependent on it
and how it kind of sucks the life out of
us
it's not an even trade-off and i talk
about that about caffeine how caffeine
is not an even trade-off you guys it's
not i'm about to juice some celery juice
if you just got on here some celery
so but the even trade-off i'm talking
about is what
that caffeine does it's a powerful
diuretic
and it sucks out your trace minerals
trace minerals that are in here
so it draws out those trace minerals out
of your cells
that's what caffeine does it acts like
that powerful diuretic that just sucks
the life out of you it's like the
vampire
is what it is you have your cup of
vampire that's what you do
it's like i'm gonna have my cup of
vampire right now and
so because it will suck the trace
minerals and nutrients out of you
just draw it out of you and then what's
replacing it that's what i want to know
like where are you replacing all those
nutrients where are you replacing those
trace minerals like where is it coming
from
like where and how so i was like well
look
let me just juice some celery for you
guys so you guys know like how
many of the people i know got off of
caffeine like coffee
even matches like you know hey like if
you want i mean
if you don't want to get off your matcha
or coffee or chocolate yeah i mean i get
it
but at least you know there's options
and at least you know there's a way
right here celery juice powerful way of
doing that so i just want you guys
to just see it witness it i'm gonna have
some i'm gonna drink some did you have
yours this morning
did you have yours when you were
listening to the medical medium podcast
to that into that caffeine episode
and a reminder the moon meditation the
brain meditation
the air freshener show the egg show egg
eaters lose all
chemtrails show all the different shows
on there you should check it out
it's cool fruit fear um but hey so i'm
going to juice a little celery cheese
fruit and celery for you guys right now
that's what we're going to do
and um it's making some noise so just
bear with
it
so what i like about this model is
i mean in my opinion i've used every
machine every machine i mean i've
purchased
every machine when i purchased this
machine
any of the mega machines over the years
it's like well why is that
better how come it's always a better
experience for me
and that's why i like the omega machines
so it's like why is it a better
experience experience
for me and everybody's asked me for
years i hardly talk about they always
ask
what do you do like you sell it so i
said
no what do you do and i'm like what do
you mean what do i do
i told you i choose celery every day for
well
over 35 years or more and it's like well
you know like what machine what tools
they're like
the mega just that's the one and this
one's the uh
mm-900 hds just so you know
so you can check that out but
the key about this what i like about
this machine is this stuff comes out so
dry it's ridiculous
so you save money at the end of the year
that's how i experience it
like my experience is i actually
save because i'm juicing less
celery and when i'm juicing less celery
then boom it's like okay well i'm buying
less celery
that's what i love about this model it's
like i'm buying
less celery because i'm juicing less
and i'm getting more juice per stock and
everybody's got their opinion on what
juice do they like if you guys
if you have a juicer use that juicer you
guys got a juicer that you like a
favorite juicer you like just
keep using that juicer you know i tell
people if
if you love doing it with a blender do
it with a blender
i've been saying that for years i always
tell people would you have a blender
because if you got a blender just just
um strain it through a cheesecloth a nut
cloth
a nut bag or a cheesecloth that's what
you do because you want to strain it you
want to strain your celery
juice is what you want to do so um
but anyway but if you're interested in
if you don't have a machine or something
that you like and you're looking for a
machine
this is my favorite right here the
mm-900 hdf
link is in the description so
and it's 20 off which is insane right
now which is really cool because it's
helpful because
you know yeah it's helpful for a lot of
people right now and that's that's what
you know people need
but um i want to tell you guys did you
see the brain meditation did you do the
moon meditation
the medical medium podcast at apple
podcast
that's the platform i launched the
official platform of the medical meeting
podcast it's apple podcast the link is
in the description
it's the official one official platform
i launched it on because
i'm confident it's not censored i'm
confident that you're hearing the
complete episode
i'm confident that you're going to be
getting the information it's not getting
clip snipped or
diced or uploaded wrong
like i'm really confident about all of
that so
uh you know medical meeting podcast at
apple podcast
just so you know i'm going to do a
little bit more right here
and
shut it off here so got some celery
juice right there
which is great i mean honestly i didn't
count the stalks you can you know
like count them or something if you want
but this is really dry to the bone
i love it it's light and fluffy and
that's not my experience with other
juicers you know so that's why so
everybody's always like
you know and i'm like well i showed you
what juicer i use and like no
show me again show me again i want to
see it i want to see it i want to see it
so i think well
if you want to get off caffeine celery
juice is a way to do it
you know and look that's what you want
to do it's like
you know if you want to get off caffeine
if you want to do it that way
boom you could do you know celery juice
and that's a great way of doing it
so um did you catch the episode i want
to remind everybody
so the episode it's kate it's it's about
all about caffeine medical medium
podcast at apple podcast
check it out you know it's really a
powerful episode
jammed packed jam packed and
look if you're do this machine 20 off
you're saving 60 bucks
like 60 bucks on this machine um 20
off check it out i mean the sales in the
us from when i saw so the sale is the
sale that is in the us
and 60 you can save off this machine
right now which is really cool but if
you're somebody that wants to get off
caffeine
because they know a lot of people do
they're like dying to get off of it
it's this is a great tool now why is
celery juice a great tool it's a
complete electrolyte
because what we do is we try to gather
electrolytes all through our life we're
always trying to gather an electrolyte
every food we eat
it's like electrolyte electrolyte we're
trying to get little pieces but the
celery juice is a complete electrolyte
the power of that is incredible so when
it's a complete electrolyte
changes the game big time because what
happens is caffeine goes into the
emotional center of the brain it goes
into all the neurons in the brain
it triggers off adrenaline so adrenaline
floods your brain
and that can wear you down over time
burn out the neurotransmitters
burn out the neurons but yeah it gives
you a rush it gets you through your day
it can help push you through your day
and i totally get it so many people need
that
because without it they can't function
but what i like doing is restoring
the like fixing the problem and
restoring
what's missing so that's what i like to
do so the celery juice
the health benefits that i like and talk
about in the medical medium books is
like
is it's about that complete electric
going to your
neurons you know helping those
electrical impulses fire up
like rehydrating and restoring
neurotransmitters you've got to have
those neurotransmitters working
they've got to be working so that's a
big deal right there you're drinking
celery now sarah
and you're doing your jelly juice now
incredible you guys are amazing
so so um so the reason why
there's there's no trade-off that's
actually good with
caffeine got to remember that it's not
an equal trade-off it's like the vampire
it just sucks the life out of us over
time i talk about in the episode as far
as it
aging us so i know you'll hear all the
time
anti-aging anti-aging anti-aging no
actually
you know caffeine anything with caffeine
in it's
not anti-aging it's the opposite
overtime caffeine is the boy who cried
wolf with the adrenals where it's fight
or flight fight or flight all the time
so what i like about the celery juice is
it's like restoring
what has been taken from you all that
adrenaline that's been pumping out of
your adrenals
every year while you're doing your
caffeine right and
who's doing that who's restoring your
adrenals like who's doing that you guys
who's restoring the adrenals
who's restoring you know the
neurotransmitters
and that's what i love about the celery
juice so it's like it's one thing
you know and what i like about this
juicer
way better than any juicer i've used if
you have a juicer you like just use that
one if you have a blender you like use
that one but this is the juicer that i
like
it's it the the pulp is light as air
it's fluffy and light i mean hardly
juiced
anything like anything there's barely
any pulp in this right here
and i got a full container right now of
celery juice i'm just going to show you
right now
and i didn't even scratch the surface
which how much i washed a lot of celery
right here
and i mean i washed a lot of it and
didn't even burn through i still got a
pile right here didn't even burn through
like hardly any of it right there and
that's what i like about this juicer
and someone said to me the other day
well you like your juicer but that means
you've only used that juicer
company probably that juicer brand i'm
like uh no i've tried every
single juicer that was available
over the years every one i'd be like
okay i'm gonna try that one and be like
whoa that's a hassle
cleaning that or hey let me try this one
no that's not giving me that much juice
or
let me try this one that's not so great
and that's
my experience you know you might have a
better experience you might have a
better experience with
your juicer you might have a better
experience with your blender
you might have a better experience with
something whatever you guys do but i
love this one it's twenty percent off
which is so cool
save sixty dollars off this machine but
what i like about for me
i have too much going on i'm like really
busy i'm writing
books i got a book right now i'm writing
for you guys
and i got a lot going on got the medical
medium podcast where i'm
um you know throwing out those those
killer episodes you know like
the power packed episodes i hope you're
getting into them i'm hoping you're
doing the brain meditation i hope you're
doing the moon meditation
hope you're doing hope you're listening
to that caffeine episode you guys can't
miss the caffeine episode you can't and
i mean seriously you'll be blown off
your seat when you hear that episode
so medical media podcasted apple podcast
but i got a lot going on
so i can't be cleaning a juicer all day
long you know i can't be
cleaning a juicer i i use celery juice
twice a day
a lot of days it's twice a day or i'll
do a big
load of it in the morning right and i
just don't want to sit there cleaning a
juicer all morning long so this is why i
like this juicer
i like it because for me for some reason
it's just so much
easier and i've tried a lot of them like
oh my god what do i got to scrub and do
and this one's less of all that
my opinion um people ask me what my
favorite juicer is
so i thought i'd show you guys you know
i thought i'd show you guys i've showed
you before
but everybody forgets or something you
know they don't forget and then
they start bombarding me with what's
your favorite juicer over and over again
until it finally gets to a point where
it's like oh my god i have to i have to
do this but the perfect thing is
it's like wait a minute i you know if
you really need to get off caffeine like
if you're somebody that wants to get off
the caffeine and you're someone that's
trying to get off the caffeine
or anything like that that you got an
option it's like the celery juice is
that way to break withdrawal
and i talk about that in the caffeine
episode so you know
check that out the coffee matcha
chocolate episode
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
if you hear that
episode somewhere else on another
platform or something like that
it's not going to be the full episode
most likely definitely i don't have any
faith in that apple podcast is
i have a lot more faith that it's going
to be it actually that it is uncensored
there and that's where it's uncensored
it's really cool
so you got to check it out um
you know jennifer says uh got podcasts
24 7 going my dog knows the episodes
that's incredible thank you for
listening to those and i hope you guys
are sharing them i
please share if you can that would be
amazing if you guys share the brain
meditation the moon meditation if you
share all the different episodes if you
share this caffeine
episode and that would be really
incredible it really would
i would love that i would love that
because then i know
you're helping other people i'm helping
other people through you guys because
that's what it's about
and it's incredible so the link is in
the description for the juicer
um if you want to check it out it's 20
off and
the the podcast link is in the
descriptions the medical medium podcast
at apple podcast the link is in the
description you guys got to check it out
you really do you really do and i mean
you can't miss those episodes try the
moon meditation try the brain meditation
they're really a powerhouse for healing
people
you know i used i coveted the brain
meditation over the years where it was
just for family and friends and i was
like why am i doing this
i no one knows about this one and then
the moon meditation
i never did a guided version like this
for anyone so you guys got to hear
you're doing the beatrice says yes doing
the meditation every day
incredible and credible that's amazing
it's amazing
so um this is the mm-900 hds
that's the one so i mean if you if you
get another model from omega it's not
going to be this one this is their
celery juicing model but you can use it
for other things too but
this is the one that's really you know
the key
but yeah you guys i'm just proud of you
for all that you're doing i hope you're
taking care of yourself
so check that out medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast check out the
caffeine episode
all right coffee matcha um chocolate
check that out if you can
margaret says she loves being off a
coffee are you doing your celery juice
did you use it to get off your coffee
because so many people
thousands and thousands of people used
celery juice to get off of their coffee
they use celery juice to get off of
everything
so um you know to get off anything they
wanted to get off of whether it was like
a chocolate addiction coffee addiction
whether it was matcha
whatever it was the caffeine addiction
and
but what happens is caffeine can rob you
of your youth is what it does over the
years
and no one talks about that i talk about
that in the episode how that works
because it can rob you of your youth
and it's really important to know and so
it's like what are you doing to
put back in how about this if you don't
want to get off your caffeine
if you don't want to get off your
caffeine how about if you're doing your
celery juice to put back in what's
coming out
at least try that where you're putting
back in what you're
losing so what caffeine is sucking out
of you because
if you just got on here caffeine sucks
out the trace minerals
sucks out antioxidants so it's like hey
um you know my
my caffeine choice has antioxidants in
it chocolate
matcha's got antioxidants in it coffee's
got antioxidants well those antioxidants
are just being sucked right out with
that caffeine
not only those but other antioxidants
that you're getting anywhere else are
getting sucked out
so what are you doing to put it back in
that's what i want to know so
i'm not saying you guys have to i'm not
saying you guys have to uh
um get off your your caffeine that's not
if you want to stay with it i'm just
saying what are you guys putting back in
so that yeah you know what's going back
in the till
so you guys can restore those
neurotransmitters
electrical impulses get them stronger
all of that like what's going on there
what are you guys doing because it
matters
and so check out the medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast the link is in
the description
check out this juicer too if you want
links in the description cmm 900
hds um i told you i licensed my name to
the company because you're like well
you've been using
omega for how many years uh since the
beginning and i tried every juicer
and like well can we use your name and
and yeah for sure of course
let's let's do something let's do
something together and so
the key is is that well listen if you
guys got a juicer you like
keep with it okay if you guys got a
blender you like keep with it you could
strain
you guys could blend it strain it
through a nut bag or a cheesecloth okay
totally and it only takes a few minutes
to make juice with this it's incredible
only takes a few minutes and it saves so
much time
so that's what i love about it it's like
i look i told you
this saves you money with how much juice
you get
out of a stock that's the difference i
barely used any celery
i got a pile here i haven't even touched
you see the pile
haven't even scratched the surface of
that pile and it's saving me money every
year my experience
is i save lots of money on salary every
single year with this model so it's like
okay what's the trade-off
well it's 20 off right now get a deal on
it number one and then whatever it costs
you actually make back by the end of the
year plus some
so i like a machine that pays for itself
that's my whole thing and it's quiet
it's quiet in the morning in case you
got you know family or something you
don't want to wake up and you don't want
to run a loud machine this one's really
quiet
but my deal is like i like i like
knowing i have a machine that's
paying for itself and that's what i like
knowing so it's like what you're paying
for yourself
that's pretty awesome and this machine
for me has already paid for itself
over and over and over again but you
know
the celery juice is a big part of how to
break the caffeine addiction
thousands of people are breaking their
caffeine addiction
using celery juice any other tools in
the episode
check out the medical meeting podcast at
apple podcast check out that episode so
you can learn
how to break your caffeine addiction
because
this is one tool right here i give you a
whole bunch of tools because you might
be somebody like well i need more or i
need another type of tool give you a
whole bunch of tools in that episode so
um and you know what you can pre-wash
your celery that's what's incredible
you can pre-wash it that's what i do i
pre-wash a bunch of it
so i knock it out i put it in the fridge
keep it nice and cool so it sits in the
fridge nice and cool
pre-wash it how awesome is that right
take it out when needed
it's it's so great i mean it's just it's
really awesome
and then boom run it through the juicer
and then
got my celery juice and look i'm not
even going into the benefits of celery
juice
on a whole like i talk about the medical
medium books
like the cleanse of heal book whatever
and in other books it's like
yeah it has that much power of helping
us heal
in many different ways i talk about that
how it can help us in so many ways but
look
if you want to get off your caffeine and
you need some kind of
anchor you need something to do it
that's
that's the celery juice so it's one of
those healing tools really
a valerie says valerie reward says
amazing podcast thank you so much aw and
soc
did you did you really love the podcast
did you check out the caffeine one
the the coffee matcha chocolate episode
that one's mine mind blowing all the
episodes are mind-blowing and the
meditative
the meditations moon meditation actually
helps to heal the soul
you guys probably know that you tried it
did you did you share it
and the brain meditation helps to get
fear out
of the soul out of the body how about
that make the connection with the bridge
the brain meditation caffeine episode i
mean the thing is with that episode
is it blows my mind because i i listen
to it again
myself and when i listen to it and i
hear the information not just
speak it but when i hear it back and i'm
like it's just unbelievable really
it's unbelievable it's just so much
nobody knows out there about
and there's so much a lot of nobody
knows about caffeine and
what what the drawbacks are if there are
any pros or
whatever it is so it's so important um
so yeah so you guys i'm really proud of
elizabeth said where do you get the
meditations the link
of the podcast is in the description
check it out
share these they're so powerful share
them with family friends
the link is in the description you'll
see the caffeine
uh link okay so the caffeine episode but
you can check out all the episodes the
brain meditation okay just like
right the moon meditation those are
really powerful people are falling
asleep to them
they're healing and all of that so
really i mean you guys got to check out
the medical medium podcast at apple
podcast now remember
okay it's that apple podcast if you if
you have an android
you have a different device and you
can't you know have an apple device then
go to medicalmedium.com
medicalmedium.com and there you go you
go to the menu and you see the podcast
on the menu whatever you hit podcast on
the menu and you download the link
um mm-900 hds that's the model that
people are always asking me which one do
you use
which one do you like this is the one i
like everybody's always
like what are you doing like what are
you using and i'm just juicing celery's
but
people want to know so i gotta respect
that i want you guys to know what's up
and you can use any juicer you got just
get the celery juice
in you if you if you want to just work
on your healing process or break
caffeine 20 off you save 60 bucks the
link is in the description by the way
and but remember this when you're
listening to the medical media podcast
just know this when you're listening to
that podcast know this before you listen
if you haven't listened already your
mind's going to get blown
the information is jarring
inspirational mind-blowing so just look
out you're going to go for a ride
and then you're going to learn a lot
you're going to learn
a lot those neurons are going to be just
with all that information it's going to
be pretty off the charts
letting you know and michelle says link
is in the description
for the juicer yep totally totally there
lorraine l
hey lorraine you're the best you know i
see your comments out there too michelle
too you guys are like
you guys like no information you guys
know a lot of information
um thank you for all you're doing out
there you know teaching people how to
heal obviously you're seasoned
and you're seasoned on what doesn't work
out there you're seasoned on what does
really incredible uh gloria says i
wasn't planning to get off of coffee
after two days of having celery juice i
found myself with so much energy
that i stopped having coffee by day
three gloria
incredible that's the whole thing you
know if you check out that caffeine
episode coffee matcha and chocolate and
you listen to that information that
information
in that episode mind-blowing the link is
in the description for the medical
meeting podcast
but now you're like well hey now you
know why you need to be off your coffee
like right you need to be off of it
unless you're somebody that doesn't want
to get off of it i understand
but then you know you've got a tool
you've got a healing
healing tool to get yourself off of it
how cool is that
uh sabine says how do you store the
celery when you pre-washed it
you know what i do i take i take a like
a dish washing cloth
like a dry clean one and after i wash
the celery i kind of just wrap it in it
and just wrap it in it i got one right
here you guys
that's the cloth right here so what i do
is i pre-wash it
and i wrap it in there like that and you
know put a big hunk of it
just like you see all the celery right
here and i put it in the fridge and i
just have it sitting there it's going to
be in there for a day
or two right that's one way to do it
there's other ways you guys can come up
with your own way of doing it too
i mean there's other ways you can also
do you have a damp cloth wrapped around
it which is a great way of doing it too
there's nothing wrong with that at all
so yeah so
um anyway so the bottom line okay
medical media podcast did you check out
the caffeine
episode link is in the description have
you done the meditations
and have you shared them have you shared
them
um lorraine l says brain meditation is
otherworldly
that's the greatest compliment like i
could
get because you know i don't know if you
guys know but i'm discriminated against
because of
my source of spirit of compassion since
i was age four
and when i was age four and spirit of
compassion started speaking to me which
people are like well
wait a minute what is that how does that
work and the millions have actually
healed around the world because of the
medical medium information
and and when you when like lorraine when
you know that it's otherworldly because
it's not man-made like
i'm not me i can't make a meditation
like that
like i can't and it comes from above
so it works it's not hit or miss it it
works
and it's a powerhouse and that one i
feel kind of guilty
lorraine i feel kind of guilty that i
coveted that one when i was younger a
little bit i just had it for family and
friends
and then i realized with everything
going on why doesn't everybody have the
brain meditation
and i need you guys to have that so
medical meeting podcast
check that out and lorraine thanks for
for everything um
j m caffeine episode was mind blowing
thank you for telling us
did you learn new information about
caffeine that doesn't exist anywhere
else in that episode
because that episode is packed
jammed from front to back line for a
line
in his jammed pack the zil says moon
meditation is amazing as soon
as i see the colors and see the yellow
in particular
i fall asleep i don't remember the rest
that yellow is the hurt coming out the
magnetic pull of the moon
is helping to pull that out and i'm
guiding you through the meditation
that's the meditation at medical medium
podcast at apple podcast you guys link
is in the description
and that moon just the gravitational
pull once you connect to that
and you actually connect and know why
you're doing it and
it starts to expose that yellow color
and you're pulling that out you're just
going to find peace
you're going to get those wounds out and
you're going to fall asleep many people
do
incredible um stephana stefani you got
the cleanse to heal so you see it back
there
the the most the most comprehensive
medical textbook there is with advanced
information
that's saving lives around the world
like other medical medium books check
out cleanse the heal i know you can't
really see it you probably can't see it
back there but there it is
right through there um the podcasts are
mind-blowing
right and um so yeah you guys i mean
look it's like this it's one thing to
talk to talk like
hey get off your caffeine maybe you
shouldn't be on your caffeine
it's not good for you that's just not
really
like that's not helping really anybody
but it's another
to say here's why you should probably
get off your caffeine
listen to the episode so you can just
your mind just blow like
bro like right that information comes in
and you know like okay here's what's
going on well what can i do
what can i do now you know aw you told
me what's going on with caffeine what
can i do
well then tools to restore
and that caffeine sits in that emotional
center of the brain
it attaches itself to all kinds of
neurotransmitters attaches itself
to neurons sits in there a long time
just causes a lot of trouble
withdrawal becomes impossible for most
people do something about it if you want
that's the whole point
sharon says celery juice kills my
stomach just a tiny little tiny little
bit
tiny a little bit if you want talk to
your doctor about it if you're concerned
or anything we could do a tiny little
tiny little bit of it and because what
that celery juice does it's so
healing in so many ways it kills off
bacteria in people's guts bad bacteria
kills off pathogens and viruses so you
know so that's the whole thing
and that's what's so powerful about it
you can also you know you can also just
do a little tiny bit if you're worried
you know um but i love those questions
when they come up once in a while
because i want you to have a chance to
heal you could always
ask your doctor like can i do a little
bit of this lini says
it totally healed my psoriasis
incredible
so the celery juice totally healed your
psoriasis you know
you know people don't know like who
don't have psoriasis
and people or don't have symptoms and
conditions and i know a lot of you guys
have them so you get it
a lot of people out there who don't have
any kind of real
impeding symptom they don't know what
that means like
it totally healed my psoriasis
and what that means um paula bennett hey
paula
the coffee episode was unbelievably
amazing
paul share it with your friends share
with your family if you can
if not just please listen to it again
because
i had to listen to it again and i'm the
one that did it
and i listened to it again because i'm
like oh yeah and oh yeah you know yeah
it's
packed with information it's packed with
information
and and i'm honored you're listening um
so vegan sabina says coffee is a drug
it's pretty intense stuff i mean
it's print caffeine is pretty intense
stuff and
we get trapped in it and stuck to it
and married to it and attached to it
so it's really tricky you know it's
really tricky and getting off of it
it's another story but i got the mm-900
hds right here so this is the model that
i use
my favorite model my favorite company
but this is the one that squeezes every
last bit of juice
out of those stocks i personally save
money
from using this machine it's paid for
itself over and over again
you know and because when people say
well juicers are expensive well this one
it really isn't that expensive at all
compared to some of the juicers out
there oh my god they're off the charts
and this one pays for itself and it's 60
off right now 20 off like it's it's
crazy
so but this is the one that i like to
use because i save money
but i know i'm saving money by the end
of the year i juice a lot of celery
and i know i'm saving money at the end
of the year it's so important
so the brain meditation is good you got
to keep the brain meditation going
because
that brain meditation wilma is powerful
and it will just keep on healing every
time
and every time you've done the moon
meditation a few times too so proud of
you
you're asleep before it finishes lovely
amazing amazing
so brain meditation moon meditation
medical medium podcast
at apple podcast the link is in the
description
share with others that's the uncensored
platform in which i launched
the medical medium podcast all the other
platforms little pits and bits and
pieces
will be kind of taken out and everything
and you know it's going to be
just you know not going to be what it is
so you want to
want to listen to that apple podcast
margaret valentine how is that different
from the other omega juicers
this one's specific for celery juice you
can use it for other things too
but it's specific for celery juice so it
actually has in this control
right here it actually has a tool in
here
okay that allows you to squeeze
every last drop practically out of there
i mean it's
amazing just amazing as far as like dry
to the bone
and you use less celery because of it
and
i haven't found that experience and i've
i've purchased
every juicer that's in this realm and
even above
meaning price wise to be like okay i
just i'm biting i'm biting let me do it
they're trying you know you go in there
you look for different juicers like
what's this company do and they're
selling some juicer let me get it
and then you're like what i'm killing
myself to clean it
and then at the top not this juicer but
trying other juicers and killing myself
to clean them
and then it's not squeezing all the
juice out of them and then i'm like
it's costing me money to juice celery
it's like what this makes no sense this
is the one i believe in
but just use the juicer you love it's
it's perfectly fine you guys know that
um sandra says it produces more juice
than some of the others i've noticed yes
sandra it does
it does it's that's what i love about it
i love about it so
and you know it's like everybody's
always asking me what juicer i use
but i'm like okay well you use sour
juice to get off caffeine let's just
like
juice some celery so everybody has like
they can see like wait a minute i can
get off caffeine
i can do this susan darling hey how are
you after juicing celery juice for a
week
i could not tolerate caffeine so celery
juice made me want to come off caffeine
i'll tell you why that's really cool
i'll tell you why
because it's a complete electrolyte so
the trace mineral salts the subgroup of
sodium that it has okay
sodium cluster salts i talk about in the
medical medium books
go to the brain to where you're caffeine
dependent
so we get caffeine dependent in the
brain
that's what happens we get cathy
dependent and we get caffeine dependent
in the emotional center of the brain and
then
we're like oh my god we're in trouble
when you get off that caffeine we're
like withdrawal
we just we get emotional we start losing
it
we all of that and so what the celery
just does it's trading off
it's also putting something back into
you that caffeine
sucking out of you and it's really an
amazing thing so
you know um kathy king celery juice has
been a lifesaver for me over the last
four years
it has healed uh my shingles it's
incredible so proud of you
i really am and um but guys you know
the moon meditation the brain meditation
have you done those
those are mind-blowing meditations did
you check out the caffeine episode
if you haven't checked out the medical
medium podcast the official launch that
i just did the official episodes there
the new ones that i just put out there
it's the first time launching a podcast
for medical medium the other old shows
were old radio shows
and and this is an entirely different
story this is an uncensored version
of packed with information so really
powerful did you check them out
um but yeah so much so much so tammy hey
tammy i have a hard time getting organic
celery
is the regular celery going to work the
same
wash it good wash it good okay i used a
little bit of natural dish soap a little
bit of natural dish
dish soap if i have conventional and i
wash it good
because you have to do this no matter
what your celery and you can't
there's nothing that's going to clean
your celery any better than when you
take your
thumb and you actually do this when
you're under water and you take your
thumb
and you're rubbing that okay and you're
just getting you know really good i use
warm water so and that's what i do i
have the sink running it's
warm waters coming through and i rub my
fingers in the stalks in between right
here you see that right there
and right here and i get the dirt out
and any kind of film that's in here i
get it out so if you've got conventional
celery just get all that
out give it a little good wash and just
juice it absolutely it's okay what about
for eczema
ava says so that will there's thousands
of stories out there
of medical medium tools like celery
juice specifically celery juice with
other medical medium tools
put together and getting rid of people's
eczema
and saving them from terrible eczema
conditions
really incredible so um you guys should
check that out
i mean if you want a good medical
textbook look at cleanse the heel and
back of me i'll lift up the juicer a
little bit you see it right through the
little spot there or right there little
spot which where am i going this way
it's funny um beatrice
larson said uh my husband and i
my husband and son stopped drinking
coffee with the 369 cleanse
369 cleanse right there so that's the
medical medium cleanse the heel book
with all the different cleanses all the
different symptoms and conditions
what to do for them all of that so
important
but you know what i did you guys i was
like let me get you
the medical medium podcast in your hands
just
listening for free no advertisements no
commercials
no infomercials like no commercials in
that podcast
it's just clear free listening and you
know medical media podcast at apple
podcast check the link out in the
description have you listened to it
you're going to get mind blown you
really are um
so yeah and i'm so proud of you guys so
this is this is the deal
is that when i get up in the morning i
don't have a lot of time
i'm working on the podcast trying to get
you guys episodes
i'm working on the book the next book to
deliver you guys
and i'm just i'm working 20 hours a day
right now and getting probably three to
four hours of sleep some night so
i'm working 20 hours a day and
i don't have time to spend all this time
cleaning and
juicing and all that so i like this
model because of that it just saves me
time and a whole bit
um you know start if you if you have a
lot of symptoms you can always start
slow with the celery juice
if you got a lot of symptoms you could
always start slow you don't have to do
32 ounces you don't have to do 30 ounces
you don't have to do 28 ounces start
slow if you want
you can do that you guys can do that
start with four ounces you can do that
as well start with four ounces
you can definitely do that nothing wrong
at all but what it does is
celery juice is a pathogen killer
so what it does is it breaks down
membranes and pathogens
the membrane around pathogens and it
starts to weaken them
and that's what's incredible and people
are sick because of epstein-barr viruses
cytomegalovirus shingles virus they're
sick because of streptococcus different
kinds of
you know bacteria they're sick from all
this stuff i talk about it all the time
sabine says sweeney says i i'm drinking
celery juice for seven months now
and i'm really feeling good about it
anthony thank you so much for all you're
doing seven months
whoa seven months incredible
i love it i love it that's really
special
um and so you guys i'm proud of you guys
because i know you're struggling with
all your stuff
um the moon meditation is helps to heal
the soul remember that helps to heal
wounds
lorraine l says i love the old radio
shows but these new podcasts are like
whoa
lorraine it's it's light years away
right i mean the difference is light
years away i'm glad you love the old
radio shows
but these new these new apps this new
podcast
right packed with information
mind-blowing
i'm not holding back obviously i'm not
holding back
you know i'm i'm definitely not holding
back but i
want you guys to have these this
information the meditations
um and all of that i want to guide you
through your healing with the
meditations
the soul healing meditations share the
podcast if you can share the podcast
please if you can
i don't want to ask much you guys i know
you guys got a lot going on you don't
feel good many of you
you're battling your symptoms and
conditions and but if you please can
share
that's the only way it can actually get
around to help people and
just the organic grassroots movement
because i don't have promotion
campaigns and all that like i don't have
you know big promotion
big you know pr marketing uh the medical
medium
never goes down that route it's all been
about organic grassroots and finally and
actually people healing because of it
because i don't have all that pr
marketing everything i do get bashed by
naysayers and stuff and discriminators
all the time
and because they don't understand like
how can this information be out there
saving lives uh number one new york
times bestselling books how does that
happen with no
pr and marketing and all that i'll tell
you is because it happens because people
are actually healing
so i do i do love when you guys share
though so you can share that podcast
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
help people heal my god um catherine
elizabeth says
the meditations are very powerful
catherine good to see you
um and so the link is in the description
for the medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast the link is in the description
for this juicer
two sixty dollars off it's 20 off uh
which is incredible so that's there too
um beverly says please look look after
yourself thank you
thank you for caring really you know
right now it's like get those episodes
out
get those episodes out i hope you guys
can share them you know it's like
i want you guys to be able to have these
episodes for in these meditations
look since i was a kid it's always been
about like you guys healing for me
like and that's what it's been about you
know and it's like it hasn't been about
me that's why you know that's why when
people say what do you do
what juicer do you use how do you juice
salary and all this stuff that's why you
don't see me doing
you know selfies all day long and making
my platform about me me me in my life
and which is fine if people
do that it's great but i'm all about
like you guys
like how can i serve how can i be a
messenger
how can i be a messenger of information
like the medical medium podcast
how can i be a messenger so you guys
have healing tools like strategies that
save so many people
like in in other medical media books
it's like how do i do that
and that's that's the whole point that's
the whole point
um and
incredible you guys so jennifer mccall
says got it we'll share this
incredible thank you jennifer thank you
seriously um
mary says i love your new podcast mary
mason honored
honored thank you for listening please
share please share
dorothy says how much should i drink
every day well you know i talk about the
medical medium cleanse to heal the book
cleanse to heal the book and but i'll
tell you right now okay
depending i mean you can start really
small if you want i like the minimum of
16 ounces because that's spirit of
compassion's number
16 ounces once a day on an empty stomach
don't mix anything in it
okay that's that's really important i
like that for people i like 32 ounces
depending on what symptoms conditions
you're dealing with
what's going on even more than 32 ounces
too
um so yes i'm really proud of you guys i
really am
so deborah says i've been juicing since
2015 and so much better
incredible incredible i love the fact
that you're doing that
i do i do i really do so once again you
guys
all right like you know how to wash your
celery i showed that to you um that
little trick there
today where you want to get the dirt out
of the inside of the stalks ray
all of that showed you my favorite
juicer where i save money using this
juicer it pays for itself to me that
matters
and because i've used every juicer out
there and um
check out the medical mean podcast at
apple podcast link is in the description
and dorothy says how much coffee is too
much dorothy you know what's
crazy is that sometimes just a drop of
coffee
if someone sensitive can throw them in
an anxiety attack
like panic attack a drop there's people
out there that if they smell it in a
coffee shop
and and they smell that caffeine and the
caffeine starts going into the lungs
into and gets to the brain and they're
breathing in in their sinuses
they literally start falling apart it
all depends on what the person's level
is that can handle that kind of toxin
and poison
because caffeine's a toxin and poison
it's a bad toxin and poison
so it all depends like how much coffee
is too much some people can handle a lot
of coffee all day long
doesn't mean it's not robbing you of
your youth taking from you taking your
trace minerals taking your
beating down your neurotransmitters but
there's people out there with sensitive
nervous systems and they've been through
hell and back
with their health and man they have a
thimble of coffee and
it's awful so anyway so
um anyway but bottom line is guys
uh check out the link in the description
for both you know the juicer if you're
looking for a juicer
for celery that squeezes every last drop
it's 60
off 20 or you know check out the medical
mean podcast and like spread
that information out there send it out
there share that information out there
help it get out there so people can heal
you know sharing
the medical media podcast episodes is a
great way that we can help others heal
um and just so you know there's no
commercials in there there's no
anything so it's not like you're sharing
something and they have to sit there for
five minutes in between the podcast
listening to commercials and everything
um none of that's happening so keep that
in mind it's it's it's a
free resource for you guys the tools are
in there
the information is in there and if
you're somebody that's got a blender and
you learn to use celery juice as a tool
because you listen to the caffeine
episode get your blender out
blend it up if you want it takes a
little more it takes extra work for sure
but get your blender out blend it up
strain it through a cheesecloth or nut
bag or something you can do that if you
really wanted to if you wanted to move
on it quick
um chris flynnell says love your
meditations oh keep on doing them so you
can work on your healing process amazing
uh and yeah and don't add water to your
celery juice don't add water to your
celery juice don't do that
remember that don't add water to it
whatever you do
okay and just just kind of remember that
um
but yeah so you guys incredible so
look take care of yourself know that i
stand with you
um on your side you guys i'm proud of
you all that you're doing
may the angels be by your bedside at
night helping you heal
uh you know if you're somebody that
believes in angels and just you know
make sure you know
they're there they're by your bedside
and take one day at a time
keep a light heart pat yourself on the
back have compassion for yourself know
that i care know that i love you guys
all right
all right take care