how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about the 369
cleanse there's never been a more
important time in history to cleanse
than now if you're somebody that doesn't
feel well and you got all kinds of
different symptoms and conditions and
you've been struggling
you might want to think about cleansing
but not just cleansing cleansing with
something that has worked and has
already saved lives not just one life
but thousands of lives and let's be
clear about something this isn't a
expensive program sales pitch a
nasty dirty pyramid scheme in health for
a water machine this isn't a biohack
game to sell you a bunch of trendy
things like collagen and this ain't no
probiotic gut health micro mob biome
feal implant ice bath bone broth charade
this is the 369 cleanse you could walk
right into your local library and say
hey do you guys have a copy of cleanse
to heal that I could borrow the 369
cleanse has pulled people out of living
hell and back back to life from Lyme
disease multiple sclerosis severe
depression migraines anxiety taking
people out of wheelchairs getting them
to walk walk again and getting their
lives to where it used to be quality of
life and how does the 369 do this by
removing things out of our bodies that
should not be there toxins that thicken
our blood filled with modern day poisons
that never wash away until we do
something about
it yeah I'm in my favorite coffee shop
right now yeah yeah just chilling out
working trying to get some things done
God I'm looking outside right now in the
window I should take a video of this
this is crazy it's just endless streaks
in this guy like here I'll count for you
like it's crazy it's 1 two three 4 8 9
10 11
12 17 18 19 21 this there's got to be 50
or 60 of them up there why am I freaking
out I don't know but all I know is I see
them every now and then but this is like
getting out of control like why are they
doing this it's like planes I think it's
like planes yeah I'm just going to stand
by the door right here I need some fresh
air anyway I've been in the coffee shop
for a little bit let me just take a deep
breath out here it's a nice
day crisp air but I just can't get over
these Trails up there do you think that
stuff is like falling down on us I don't
know I remember at the beginning of Co
the streets were
quiet I was on the highway and there was
no
traffic in fact I drove two miles and
did not pass a car on the other side I
remember hearing and seeing information
out there streets were dead dead empty
streets in cities were dead empty people
were leaving their
houses they were trying to get to a
store then quickly back home
and not too many people were traveling
air traffic was minimal for commercial
flights but guess what there were
thousands of planes in the sky thousands
all around the planet millions of planes
in the sky you can look up in the sky
and you can see 10 20 planes but guess
what there weren't passengers on those
planes they were chemtrail
planes here the world seemed like it was
ending down on the street
it was ending in people's homes people
were in fear they were scared no one was
leaving their
houses and up in the sky they were
flying planes every single day every
minute you can look up and you'll see
them and the streaks were there the
Chemtrails were there it was like
nothing was stopping as far as
evildoers nothing was stopping as far as
the satanic cult behind the chemtrail
movement evil was up high in the sky
that's right evil was in the plains
that's right chemicals being dumped on
everybody day in and day out all night
long all day long it wasn't halting you
would think it would be nothing was
happening everything was basically at a
standstill the Chemtrails kept on coming
and coming and coming heavier than ever
before Darkness was above us dropping
stuff on us and darkness was around us
spreading stuff on us the manufacturing
of the viruses the lab
viruses the manufacturing engineering of
viruses something that's been happening
for over a hundred years classified
medical research and Science Why do you
think everybody's just sick out there
they're filled with viruses of all kinds
but during this time way up in the sky
they were assaulting
us who hired those millions of Pilots to
drop all that chem on us nobody know
knows interesting but they were
assaulting us up there while assaulting
us down here with engineered viruses
like Co and maybe you remember this
maybe you don't but right before Co
there was an engineered flu a flu virus
that ripped across the cities ripped
across the United States around the
world it injured a lot of people and a
lot of people died from it it was a bad
bad bad flu that was engineering
that was released even before Co only a
couple of months before Co so why am I
talking about this all of it project
Chemtrails started in the
1960s and it's still here today and
these Chemtrails are composed of every
toxin possible that the chemical
industry creates this includes toxic
heavy metals Mercury copper it's also
including outdated Antiquated chemical
storage bins that have been backlogged
in storage for decades chemical waste
that has sat in tanks for 50 60 70 or 80
in even 100 years it's a combination of
chemicals both old and new being placed
in planes and dumped out of the sky when
the Los Angeles fires were at their
height days ago because they're still
burning now when they were at their
height Chemtrails were being dropped
everywhere chemtrail planes were flying
above dropping chemtrails over Los
Angeles as the fires were raging the
people behind the Chemtrails are above
even the most powerful public figures
and above the people who seem to run
every country in the world the chemtrail
hierarchy are not on the Forbes list
it's the secret society of Doom they're
behind engineering the viruses that
spread around the world which there are
more to come and they're going to be
worse than the ones before and they're
also behind all the chemicals falling
out of the sky out of the Plains onto
everyone if someone was just to say give
me one good reason to cleanse I just
gave you two pathogens love toxins
pathogens eat and feed off of toxins the
more toxins and the chemicals and
everything else that we have inside of
our body the more these bugs that stay
dormant inside of us can wake up and
feed and grow into something and turn
into sick
turn our bodies into sickness we keep
the toxins away from the pathogens that
are inside of us and we Empower
ourselves if someone's battling
autoimmune they're battling toxins and
pathogens pathogens feeding off of
toxins or they're battling a small
amount of pathogens and a large amount
of toxins the more toxins inside our
body the more chances we can catch
something the second the minute a bug
enters us through exposure of some kind
whether it's on the handle of a shopping
cart Carriage whether it's in a bathroom
a public bathroom on a toilet seat in
the toilet water or by the sink whether
it's somebody that you had a sexual
encounter with whether it's bodily
fluids on a glass that you drank out of
that were somebody else's in any way
shape or form when we get a new bug it's
damage and danger to us depends on how
toxic we are that means if we have what
the bug needs so it can proliferate so
it can actually expand so it can grow so
it can multiply it needs toxins to do so
it needs fuel and the more toxins we
have inside of our body the more
aggressive the pathogen can get and what
about our immune system immune systems
struggle when there's a lot of toxins in
the body the more toxins we have in our
body our brain our liver or spleen our
pancreas or intestinal tract the more
toxins we have inside of our tissue or
cells or organs the more our immune
system struggles and weakens because our
immune system goes up against the toxins
our immune system tries to gobble up the
toxins our immune cells actually go up
against the toxin consume it try to rid
it try to stop it because it's a free
radical it shouldn't be in the body and
our immune systems know this but when
our immune systems are busy trying to go
after metals and all kinds of other
toxins our immune system cells burst
they weaken they get dried out they die
and with the more exposure we get with
the toxins and the toxins building up in
every single cell in our body our immune
system start to weaken pathogens take
advantage of this they feed off the
toxins not only feed off the toxins but
they don't have an immune system to
really battle against so they grow
rapidly and then everything is
fast-tracked every Cancer every disease
every illness mach five cancers are
prime example of pathogens feeding off
of toxins and then creating cancer
pathogens feeding off of toxins toxins
feeding the pathogens viral cells
becoming cancer cells so there's never
been a more important time for getting
rid of toxins and if we don't our bodies
become the bath tub they become that old
moldy rotten stinky bathtub and tiles
filled with mold our blood gets thick
our liver gets toxic stagnant it gets
overworked overburdened it's not
functioning like it should our
intestinal tract gets all kinds of
different buildup Linings of the
intestinal tract and colon start to
Harbor things that shouldn't be there
it's not just toxins but it's a buildup
of sludge and toxin
along with different pathogens that
start to make a home there our brains
get dirty our brain cells die our brain
tissue oxidizes we don't have enough
antioxidants we don't have enough
detoxifiers we don't cleanse enough and
the buildup grows and it grows our
brains start to hold things that it
should never hold and what's making us
so toxic viruses and viral waste matter
Pharmaceuticals toxic heavy metals
fragrances of all kinds bacteria and
other microbes chemical industry
domestic Invaders chemical neuro anagon
ists petrochemicals and solvents
Chemtrails and rainfall exposure
radiation EMF harmful food and
supplement chemicals harmful supplements
harmful foods this is just scratching
the surface and everyone is reaching
their brain saturation limitation when
exposure is small tiny
an occasional here and there you may not
react or experience symptoms if you are
not a sensitive someone may be on a
pharmaceutical for a month or a
pharmaceutical for 10 years someone may
be exposed to fumes for a few minutes at
a gasoline pump or they have some
gasoline spilled on their skin someone
can be breathing in the fumes and get
affected someone may not in the moment
everybody has different exposures and
symptoms to the exposures but all of
this can penetrate the brain the brain
has its saturation limits and people on
this planet are experiencing that right
now when we get exposed to toxins when
toxins actually enter us they are
usually attached to Metals this is how
we get Mercury toxic copper aluminum
lead cadmium barium nickel arsenic toxic
calcium toxic chromium strontium uranium
toxic iron toxic Platinum titanium tin
inside of us we get these in us because
they're attached to other toxins what a
lot of people experience out there in
the cleanse world the detox world is
surface detoxing surface detoxing is
getting rid of some of the Overflow some
of the daily overflow their livers are
clogged up their brains are clogged up
their organs are clogged up but they're
getting some of the lymphatic cloggage
out but that just gets refilled so what
happens is surface detoxing is different
than deep cleansing deep detoxing
surface detoxing won't be enough for
somebody who's truly suffering with a
chronic illness someone who has a high
pathogen load a high toxic load lowgrade
viral infections high-grade viral
infections surface detoxing can be
helpful but not enough and it might not
even be the right kind of surface
detoxing cleanses can't just be
cleansing they have to be nourishing but
not just the word nourishing it can't be
just like this cleanse is nourishing it
brings nutrients it has to be even more
than that it has to be wired wired to
repair a damaged sensitive nervous
system toxins not only have to be
excavated but tissue has to be repaired
we have to bring the person back a
cleanse needs to do that it has to be
set so the person has every chance of
fighting an illness every chance of
recovery and what happens out there is
cleanses aren't Geared for that it's all
biohacks hit or miss and then the
person's body doesn't truly go all the
way with the healing process because
first of all the cleanses and detoxes
out there weren't built upon the
understanding of why the person was
really sick to begin with it wasn't
built on the realization or the knowing
about pathogens what kind of pathogens
which ones which varieties what are they
feeding on how sick people can really
get from that and the process of what
metals and other toxins do is they sit
inside brain tissue and other organs in
the body and what about the immune
system cleanses aren't built to repair
the immune system they're also not built
to understand how the immune system
works in regards to what you're even
cleansing or how we got sick to begin
with a cleanse has to understand all of
this what that means is that when the
cleanse enters the body whatever that
cleanse is there has to be an
understanding of exactly what the body
needs what is the person fighting what
are they struggling from what toxins how
do these toxins get out of tissue how do
the adrenal stay protected how does the
liver function while it's under a
cleanse all of this matters and that
makes the difference to someone healing
and someone not to someone actually
getting their lives back and someone not
and someone rising out of the ashes
recovering and someone not 369 cleanse
cleanses the body while protecting the
brain from atrophy unlike water fasting
a long water fast atrophies the brain
you lose critical nutrients in the brain
critical minerals glycogen storage Old
glucose storage disappears and it's hard
to get any of that back back getting
nutrients back into the brain takes
years it's not easy to do especially if
you're not 10 years old 12 years old or
a baby or 20 years old but you're 40 or
50 if you're 40 and 50 years old and you
lose all these nutrients all that
glycogen storage all the trace minerals
all the neurotransmitter chemicals out
of the brain because of a very long
water fast thinking you're cleansing the
body we get in big trouble we have to
protect the brain while cleansing that's
the biggest and most important thing to
do making sure you're feeding the brain
lots of glucose lots of trace minerals
and that's what the 369 cleanse does
another thing that goes terribly wrong
with cleanses out there is feeding
pathogens take the milk cleanse for an
example the dairy cleanse what happens
is that pathogens feed off of dairy
doesn't matter if the dairy's raw
doesn't matter what kind of dairy
pathogens viruses Epstein bar the
shingles hhv6 hh7 the simplexes all feed
on Dairy so the person thinks they're
cleansing but they're growing pathogens
they may not feel the growth of those
pathogens during the cleanse six months
later a year later boom Wham whack
they're sick a new development a new
problem because the pathogens got
ignited they strengthened and overt time
they grew and that's what happens with
the dairy cleanses another fat-based
cleanse is olive oil the difference is
olive oil won't feed a pathogen so
Epstein bar won't feed off of olive oil
hhv6 won't feed off of olive oil strep
won't feed off olive oil directly not at
all but what the fat cleanses do like
olive oil and overt fat is shuts down
the liver it doesn't cleanse the liver
it shuts it down throws it into
dorcy it hurts the liver it also hurts
the brain because you lose glucose to
the brain instead you're getting fat to
the brain something people don't realize
is not the answer our brains run on
sugar reduce the sugar going to the
brain someone dies that's the whole
point so we don't want more fat and just
that in the bloodstream heading to the
brain cleanses that are based on olive
oil drinking a larger quantity of olive
oil also shock the gallbladder they
shock the gallbladder into potentially
spitting out a big gall stone now that
sounds like a great idea oh clean my
gallbladder maybe I can get a gall stone
out but people usually get a gall stone
stuck in the duct and now they're in the
hospital getting emergency gallbladder
surgery over drinking a few tablespoons
of olive oil every single morning
morning on its own now this doesn't mean
the gallbladder is cleansing not
necessarily at all instead the liver and
the gallbladder go into spasm because of
a crisis what happens when you send that
much overt fat and oil down the chot we
go into crisis that crisis doesn't
release toxins instead that crisis
causes a spasm your liver goes into
spasm your gallbladder goes into spasm
because it's shutting down it does that
because it's going into shock
that shock might Propel one gall stone
into a duct but it doesn't mean
anything's cleansing or moving you
forward many fat-based cleanses atrophy
the brain as well like a bone broth
cleanse just drinking bone broth every
now and then you see somebody out there
they're saying I did a bone broth
cleanse I lost this much on my waistline
and I feel better and I have more energy
but that energy eventually Fades and
over time they feel tired and have
fatigue years later and even months
later don't know why what happened was
their adrenals got tanked it was a no
glucose diet a no glucose diet foods
that are lacking sugars healthy sugars
did not allow the adrenals to get a rest
to get a break so adrenaline was used
during the entire cleanse so someone was
doing the bone broth cleanse they were
on bone broth as a fuel and then
adrenaline as a fuel adrenaline had to
Surge through the body constantly day
after day week after week it eventually
tanked the adrenals bone broth is not
only dehydrating and not hydrating at
all for cells but it's also filled with
adrenaline as well because when that cow
was being killed the adrenals exploded
they filled the bloodstream with
adrenaline to try to save the cow's life
during its death so your bloodstream
fills up with adrenaline hurting your
own adrenals also stimulating your own
adrenals to release even more adrenaline
basically you're doing a bone broth diet
a bone broth cleanse and you're killing
and destroying your adrenal glands many
women who do the bone broth and only the
bone broth and they do a cleanse out of
it pay the price dearly years later and
now are struggling with other problems
like chronic fatigue and adrenal fatigue
and skin problems where their skin
starts to wrinkle quicker and they get
the crept skin much earlier in life
years earlier decades earlier these are
just a few of the cleanses that don't
farewell for the body it isn't even just
some of the diets out there and diet
belief systems that don't farewell
either for the body cause a lot of
problems a cleanse needs to gently feed
the liver gently cleanse the liver while
letting it function you can't shut down
organs while trying to cleanse and
that's what often happens happens you
want organs like the liver to stay
functioning at its best you want it to
improve instead of weaken during a
cleanse you want the liver to come back
to life to get reignited to start to
awaken not go to sleep shock cleanses
cause the livers in people to actually
go dormant to go into shock to start to
dumb down you want the liver to start to
ignite to start to to awaken to be
fueled to know it's safe to cleanse and
that's what 369 does you also want the
liver to cleanse In Waves you want it to
cleanse a little bit and a little bit at
a time and let it go deeper and deeper
and deeper into the liver until the
liver is fully cleansed and even then
there needs to be repair cell repair the
369 cleanse creates cell repair it
offers the liver cells an ability to
regenerate so the liver cells can
replace themselves faster new tissue
grow healthy tissue so it's not just
getting rid of toxins it's about
allowing the liver to get what it needs
to restore and rebirth you need a liver
rebirthing with other cleanses out there
when the liver does release something it
ends up back into the liver and you
don't want that you don't want the liver
getting recycled poisons that it
released and now it's bringing them back
into the liver you don't want a spill a
spill over and that's what happens when
people are doing biohacks they're trying
to shake things up all that creates is a
spillover it doesn't create an actual
cleanse because they're eating other
things and doing other things in those
biohacks or with those biohacks included
that stop the body from releasing any
toxins it's just a mixed bag of nuts
it's a guessing game so now the person
is shaking up some stuff inside their
body and it's got nowhere to go it goes
back into the liver and the Brain
there's no way to cleanse it out so if
they do something to shock the liver or
shock their system all those toxins just
get trapped floating around the body and
they think they're now having some kind
of die off or some kind of cleanse or
toxin reaction or detox reaction when in
reality it's just stuff being shook
around by some biohacks and going right
back into the liver and other organs
including the brain If you hear about
cleanses out there that are detoxing the
kidneys just know this that's utterly
ridiculous you can't detox the kidneys
unless the body's detoxed you can't
detox the kidneys unless your liver is
Thoroughly detoxed properly you can't
detox the kidneys unless your spleen
your pancreas your brain is detoxed
cleansed properly your kidneys can't
start cleansing first it's not possible
wherever your kidneys are whatever stage
they're in they stay in that stage while
you're cleansing now you can strengthen
kidneys you can make them stronger you
can make them healthier you can fortify
them you can feed them nutrients while
you're cleansing and that's what the 369
does it strengthens kidneys you can do
things to help support kidneys and
support where they're at but you can't
per se cleanse the kidney itself the
tissue itself unless everything else is
cleansed but you can strengthen kidney
tissue you can make it stronger you can
make it healthier you can make it more
vital while you're cleansing the 369 is
not a cleanse where you stop eating
where you're not eating anymore or
getting any calories those kinds of
cleanses aren't good they hurt the
adrenals the 369 is designed it's geared
to protecting the adrenals and all
medical ium cleanses are geared to
protecting the adrenals other cleanses
out there are not geared to protect the
adrenals because first of all they don't
know how the adrenals really truly work
when it comes down to eating and foods
and health if you do intermittent
fasting you're hurting your adrenals
even if you're getting benefits even if
you're starting to get improvements
you're losing weight you're feeling more
energy what happens is yes you're
actually giving your liver a Break by
not eating all these fats in the morning
by not having sausages and bacon and ham
and hash browns with oil in it and eggs
and butter in the morning instead you're
not eating at all you're intermittent
fasting you're just living off of coffee
coffee drinks caffeine you're waiting to
eat at the end of the day but Meanwhile
your adrenals suffered and you don't
know it they suffered all day long there
wasn't a balance of nutrients glucose
trace minerals they weren't there
instead it was coffee coffee it was
going without you might have drank water
or you might be consuming something else
but you're starving yourself all morning
and all afternoon your intermittent
fasting this damages the adrenals over
time and cleanses like intermittent
fasting which a lot of people consider
are a type of cleanse do not protect the
adrenals there's never been a more
important time to cleanse on this planet
this planet has grown toxic and it's
getting more toxic and are we truly
adapting
mock five cancers mock five diseases and
illnesses brain problems Alzheimer's
dementia are growing rapidly are we
really getting less toxic no we're not
we're getting more toxic and it's only
getting worse and I get it there's a lot
of ads out there there's a lot of bioh
hacks out there there's a lot of
programs everybody thinks they have the
answer influencers are experimenting
they're experimenting on themselves
they're taking a crowd of people with
them they're experimenting 3 months
later they change they're doing
something different and then they grab a
couple of things that originate from
medical medium like metals and fluoride
and Plastics and microplastics and at
the same time they're screaming that
they're also screaming about processed
foods and food chemicals but what it all
boils down to it they don't know why
they're sick they don't know what's
really causing their sicknesses they
can't see it and maybe not even believe
it and then they're looking at what's on
their plate and that's what it boils
down to they're staring at their plate
and they're thinking okay I got to
change my game I got to start doing
maybe carnivore or I got to get off a
vegan or I got to watch out for seed
oils or I got to do something else and
they look at their plate and they get
confused and then they switch gears
again and then they add some Pearl
powder to it and some collagen they try
to Market it up and some colostrum they
try to sell something at the same time
they're changing everything with their
diet they don't know where they're going
they're getting sick all the time they
got all their healers and doctors and
practitioners they're telling them this
and that and they're just stuck in the
end the 369 cleanse is
freedom the 369 cleanse is free you can
go to your library and just get the
cleanse to heal book the medical medium
cleanse to heal book 369 cleanse has
healed thousands to hundreds of
thousands to Millions now after all of
these years people who healed real life
results that's a 369 cleanse protects
the adrenals protects the liver protects
the brain protects the body moves toxins
out carefully moves toxins out so
somebody can heal if you don't have time
to get down to the library to get it for
free then just head to your bookstore
you can find medical medium cleanse to
heal can find it on Amazon on for
roughly around $20 you don't need to buy
an expensive program $3,000 $5,000
program you don't need to pay a
subscription fee through a pay wall on a
website the information is at your
fingertips and it should be that way
many blessings lots of love and God
bless
you the cleanse that's a
prophecy sitting in a health world of
copycats
and
hypocrisy detox shape shifters dressed
in sheep's clothing so-called
researchers
biohackers creating elixir with no
knowing who are they
fooling around and around they go when
they change their Direction Nobody
Knows trying this now trying that
oh the fear protein or sugar only e cow
did you fall for that a snare every year
in the end down the road they'll be
preaching how plants are the only real
show that saved their ass detoxes that
Rob the body adrenal glands with nothing
left to give a crying
they were hit by a
tsunami it's pretty simple the
information from above is
providential people being freed from the
circus and being
trampled look this cleanse has a history
it works not my words just thousands
knew it took life was worth fighting for
worth living for they bit the bullet
hunkered down learned what to do how to
heal and got rid of the
poison that has been holding them back
forever more so many overwhelmed with a
long time Illness but now they have a
healing
path take the
369 and cleanse to heal to your health
professional make a pack ask them about
it ask your doctor what's right for you
and how they feel about
it original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please site where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or or if you believe in
nothing at all that we're just floating
through space together on this rock know
that the information you hear on this
podcast is separate from all the other
noise out there it comes from a
different place a pure untampered with
Advanced Clean uncorrupted original
primary source a higher source Spirit of
compassion