youtube and facebook
and we're going to be talking about a
few things first of all i'm making a
dish
i'm making a salad you can put potatoes
in the salad that's what i'm going to do
but if you're somebody that's into
animal protein i'm going to talk about
how you know you can incorporate animal
protein into the salad for somebody
who's plant-based vegan
i'm going to show you how to do that too
i got leafy greens i got the spinach
right here
that's really beautiful spinach
it's a baby spinach but it's a little
bit a little bit more than that it's
such a great spinach
and i got some beautiful cilantro right
here too
tiana good to see you courtney thanks
for coming on
amazing sunday thanks for coming on
incredible got some potatoes right here
steamed potatoes are
you guys in the mood for a salad or no
because i really like styles i love
getting
uh the greens leafy greens simple
simply simple healing thank you for
coming on wonderful to see you
jessica great and i got some butter leaf
lettuce back here too you guys
right gonna be talking about a few
things i'm gonna talk about eggs for a
little bit too
about why eggs cause trouble just cover
that michelle
elsie ichoda good to see you glad you
guys are coming on just giving you guys
a shout
out right now because i love to see you
guys and i'm really appreciative that
you're here
um got some leafy greens right there
i'm making a recipe i mean there's some
of the things i don't have
in this but i got the salad this sprout
salad but i'm doing it without the
sprouts so
this is from the medical medium new
edition revised and expanded
a life-saving book right here you guys
and
i don't know if you have one but it's
loaded with so much information it's
incredible
um you know anybody who's sick
struggling needing
any powerful information there it is
there's the recipe great to see you guys
michelle oh my god not the eggs
yeah not the eggs right got some eggs
right here not the eggs
right little a couple of eggs with me
right here but what's this
tomatoes really pretty tomatoes
incredible
lee do you eat all of what you and your
family consume
all of what you make each time i sure do
yeah i mean i just i just totally
snack out on it you know brandy i got my
case of juice ordered
oh incredible you did amazing that's the
um
it's the wyman's oh my god i can't tell
you how much
i love this stuff you know and i talked
about it on the last youtube live
last facebook live and and you know i
see it as just like
gold like just this it's powered
and you guys know i licensed my name out
to these guys and stuff because of what
they're doing because to actually
this is a precious resource a precious
resource um michelle l
i'm still answering that micro bio troll
on tick tock
my god exhausting that troll was just
exhausting
and with the microbiome troll saying
that
strep is part of your microbiome are you
kidding me i mean michelle can you
believe that
i don't even know what to say but you
know what it yeah
that person's not a microbiologist that
person is just somebody in tiktok
googling and i don't know watching
documentaries and i don't know what that
person is doing but the person is not a
microbiologist
is actually really funny yeah yeah
totally right
kimberly my dad ordered himself and i
each a case of juice
kimberly i'm really excited about this
and i was showing you guys how i use it
in a shot glass
maryam what juice is that that's the
wild blueberry juice this is a wild food
and this is actually better than organic
wild foods are better than organic
and that was something i wanted to
express the other day because someone
asked me just recently to watch the last
live if you can
like watch the last one it it's about
the juice
about the power it has all of that what
it does
it's just incredible so that's the
wyman's wild blueberry juice i mean if
you want to if you want to
look forward whatever it's it's at uh
shop.wymans.com
kim johnson ordered you ordered it too
incredible
uh kim johanna yeah the link is in the
description if you want to know where it
is the link is in the description
and i mean this is no joke
this wild blueberry juice but it's it's
a medicine though it's it's medicinal
keep that in mind
it's not something that it's not
something my phone's going off right now
and it's not my pink phone it's not my
ping phone
um this is medicinal
keep in mind so i do a shot of it every
morning
every single day i'll do a shot with a
shot glass two on shot glass it's
medicinal
so you could do two ounces a day karen
says your new egg video was crazy
just thought eggs were bad now i
understand
the lab experiments on viruses and how
they feed on viruses and
i'm going to talk about that in a minute
too as i'm making the salad
so and why is that like why are they
doing that
why are they doing that today why have
they been doing this since before 1920
why do they do that
melissa people were really sticking up
for eggs on your recent crazy egg
oh my god they want to slaughter me they
want me
dead yeah
they'd rather have anthony william dead
then actually you know hear about eggs
not being good and i know a lot of you
guys eat eggs listen i know a lot of
you guys eat eggs and if you want to eat
eggs and still do medical medium
information
of course i mean i want you to be able
to heal
i recommend not doing it if you're sick
or chronically ill or you got symptoms
right
but i get it i mean a lot of people eat
the eggs and
but whoa did people get upset they
really got upset because it's not good
to eat them if you
if you're dealing with conditions and
i'm going to talk about that you ordered
lucas said ordered the 12 pack yesterday
incredible incredible you're you're not
you're
yeah you're not going to be disappointed
but it is
you gotta this is not like a juice even
though it's it is wild blueberry juice
it's not like a juice
it's it's a medicinal so when it's a
medicinal
it's a medicine it's potent it's strong
you got to think about it kind of like
elderberry syrup
and and it's like you know it's better
than any fine wine that's for sure
that means no fine wine can do anything
that's really a great thing
tammy eggs make me so sick i will never
go back to eating eggs
again um you know i mean it's really
really difficult
elizabeth i was happy to know i didn't
have to eat them
here's the deal with eggs you know um
you know
it's just huh
i'm a i'm a fear monger me
wait what did you just say you just
called me a fear monger
i am why because i'm trying to scare
people
out of eating eggs well then what are
you
you're trying to scare people into
eating eggs
because you're trying to scare women
into eating eggs
yeah you're telling them they need the
protein and they're going to die if they
don't eat their eggs
and they're going to have health
problems and that they need
eggs for their heart and it's really
good for them a good protein you're a
fear monger or the
did they actually want them to eat the
eggs you know
i'm trying to help people so they don't
get pushed off a cliff
what am i supposed to do if somebody's
sick just let them get pushed off the
cliff and not
let them know
um anyway how to treat
lupus talk about lupus in the new book
i don't think you have the medical
medium new edition
i just don't think so because i talk
about lupus talk about the epstein-barr
virus i talk about all that in here
the epstein-barr virus right here put
that right on top of these eggs
um whoa that epstein-barr virus is
loving these eggs right now
whoa yep yep i could feel the energy
the epstein-barr virus loves these eggs
he's eaten eggs
it eats eggs inside of us um
but yeah i mean you guys um this
i mean the wild blueberry juice is
insanely good for you i mean i talk
about it in the last
the last live that i did so
um bethany the pink phone of truth
the pink phone of truth courtney says oh
my god awareness
tiana i stopped eating eggs over a year
ago
and have never felt better slowly
healing my acne and eye floaters but so
many of the other symptoms are gone what
your eye floaters are getting better
they are you stopped eating eggs
you better eat those eggs no doesn't
matter if your symptoms are getting
better you need eggs
doesn't matter if you're healing chronic
illness doesn't matter if you're getting
out of bed for the first time
you better eat those eggs you know the
egg fear mongers
they're terrible they're the fear
mongers that's what they are
you notice how that's how darkness works
you guys it's like
gotta shut the dishwasher right here you
know
we're live okay we're live this is no
edited anything
dr faun better than the store bought
here's the thing you know you know how
it works out this is how darkness works
they throw they throw crap at you that
they're doing
that they're doing that's what they do
they'll be like you're a fair monger
no you're the fear monger trying to
throw your
your crap at me you're like trying to
they're trying to fake everybody out
they're trying to trick everybody out
right
that's what they do that's just one
example of a million examples
olivia top ten health benefits of eating
eggs vitamin a
six rda folate five percent
vitamin b five seven percent vitamin b12
that you can't use your body won't use
nine percent
vitamin b2 phosphorus selenium
eggs also contain decent amounts of
vitamin d vitamin e
vitamin k vitamin b calcium
hello hello yeah no i've been sick for
20 years
yeah chronic fatigue been on mattress
island
i spent about 150 000 at the doctor's
offices all these years
huh well you think i should start eating
eggs again because i just finished
eating them the other day and i learned
that eggs feed the viruses that have
made me sick for 20 years
i should eat them again why because they
got b5
so but but is that does b5 and an a
gonna really
fix everything i mean i i thought i have
a virus now
and that i just started working on
healing i i just found out that viruses
eat eggs
but it has b5 i should still eat them
okay time to go backwards again and get
sick for another 20 years
because there's vitamins in here i
better start now
all right thanks so much
all right anyway you guys the bottom
line is yeah
of course there's vitamins and chicken
poop there's vitamins and chicken poop
there's vitamins and humans human feces
so when you do a poop there's nutrients
in there
there's vitamins and nutrients in your
poo
right well better start eating
better start eating some poo better
straining it right now
i got some poo in here i better start
eating where's my fork
well you can test poo and poo has all
these nutrients in it
people's poo has lots of nutrients in
there i better start eating this poo
right here because
there's nutrients in here this poo is
really good
it really is you guys have to understand
sherry dr sherry green
good good i'm glad you're here an
amazing medical doctor
so what happens is yeah there's
something good in eggs of course there
is right
but guess what there's something better
for you in spinach
don't eat the raw spinach god forbid
don't eat spinach but make sure you
eat lots of eggs that's where the b
vitamins
really are really are and by the way i
hate to break anybody's heart
but the b vitamins and eggs don't
convert to human
use they don't convert i talked about it
on the podcast the egg podcast episode
the chicken the chicken's body isn't
like i'm gonna produce a whole bunch of
vitamin b's for
for humans to eat me the vitamin b's
don't convert by your liver
you can't convert the bees in eggs you
can't
you guys are we going to take today's
more serious
because i got to make some food and talk
about some things too
um anyway all right you guys
i got some tomatoes i got some oranges i
got some lemons i got some spinach some
cilantro
i got potatoes here if you're an animal
protein person you can add animal
protein to your salad if that's what you
really want but i try to keep the fats
low because guess what
you're always going to be eating fats i
can't stop you guys if i was a fly on
the wall
if i was a fly on the wall i'd be
watching you guys eat all this fat
well i'm going to have more nut butters
going to have more oil
going to have more avocados i'm gonna
have more chicken gonna have more beef
gonna have some cheese
gonna have some eggs too right if i was
a fly in the wall
i'd be watching all that i'd be left
there going hey
those guys are eating so much fat it's
unbelievable so that's why i want you
guys to actually you know be a little
bit low fat if you can
um ddd i finally feel like um i lost a
comment it went flying up
i finally feel like i'm hearing the food
truth for the first time needy i'm
honored you're here
incredible thank you for being here okay
see you guys
all right let's talk about a little bit
so how
viruses work well you're going to hear
out there that
bugs like viruses are dead they're just
these
strands these rna strands or
they're just an essence in our system
that bugs are dead we'll tell that to
somebody with simplex one who doesn't
somebody with simplex one okay when you
get the fever blister
right you go you go kissing somebody
with that fever blister guess what's
gonna happen
that virus is alive that virus is alive
and when you go kissing somebody and
they kiss you
uh they're gonna have that virus
that's how it works okay viruses are
alive
they're not dead but it's about snowing
people let smoke and mirror
let's snow the heck out of people let's
know them snow them snow them
and that's what they do out there say
viruses aren't alive
that's why with the flu virus if you
sneeze the virus comes out of you
and it lands on a table it
eventually dies okay it eventually dies
it's
it's away from if it's on the table on a
counter it's a way for moisture
it can't get the moisture it needs to
stay
alive okay it can't eat
it can't what happens is oxygen touches
it so here's how viruses work
oxygen keeps them down
oxygen direct oxygen kills viruses right
kills bugs kills pathogens direct
oxygen right our bloodstream is in
direct oxygen
okay it's not it's not filled with
oxygen it's
partially filled with oxygen
not it's not enough to kill off the bugs
the oxygen we breathe as it goes into
our lungs and into our bloodstream
okay and the reason why
bugs really thrive too is we're eating
so much fat
we're eating so much fat the more fat
you
eat right okay the thicker your blood
gets and the less
oxygen is in your blood that's how it
works
so then viruses right proliferate that
they grow
they explode they expand they grow in
numbers
so then the viruses grow in numbers the
next thing you know you got another
virus i lost all the
little bugs i had around here but next
thing you got two
and then you got three and that's how
they work
um but the bottom line is
viruses multiply as the oxygen
levels drop a little bit in your
bloodstream
okay it's it's on a very very tight
scale
but it drops viruses like to hide in
fat they love to hide in your blood they
like to hide in fat so if a virus
is in the blood it likes high fat if
if your liver starts to get fatty it
likes to hide in the liver and all that
fat that's what viruses like to do
because the more
fatty your liver gets the more bugs can
thrive in your liver because there's
less
oxygen in a stagnant sluggish liver and
that's the breeding ground
for viruses the breeding ground for
viruses is the liver
and the liver loses oxygen even if your
bloodstream has a decent amount of
oxygen
your liver okay your liver can get all
stagnant sluggish and
fatty and the oxygen levels in the liver
decrease
so the viruses thrive and they gain
strength in numbers
that's how that works and then when
you're eating something like eggs
you're feeding the virus so let's talk
about that for a second if you guys just
came on
spinach cilantro gonna make food gonna
make a salad in a minute
um talking about some cool stuff here so
why do viruses
feed on eggs when they
don't feed on meat
they don't feed on meat why do they feed
on
eggs they feed on eggs because eggs are
an
underdeveloped protein
underdeveloped the other thing is
an egg does not have an immune system
so if you saw the video right that
michelle was talking about not the egg
thing again if you saw the tick tock
video right you guys
well those eggs had the top of the egg
was cut off
in the tick tock video and then i had
i had a syringe right this is this is
really just for talking about the blood
draw but i had a syringe
and i was putting in some viruses into
the tops of the eggs
during that video and viruses can thrive
in a living egg a raw egg
can thrive and grow in numbers because
there's no immune system in the in that
raw egg
just like a baby doesn't have an immune
system yet in the womb
just like that okay something that's
really important to know but the egg is
obviously different than a baby
but the egg doesn't have its own immune
system the other thing is
is that the egg the underdeveloped
protein so the proteins are
underdeveloped they're not a full
complete
protein like in a piece of meat it's
already been formed so protein that's in
any kind of meat right so
the virus doesn't feed on that it's
learned to feed
on the egg okay so that's
tissue of an animal or another food by
itself
won't won't allow the the virus to
proliferate that's important too
so this is really good information to
keep in mind so we need
when we eat our eggs we're eating our
eggs right
and that's why they used eggs because of
these reasons i'm telling you but so
when we eat our eggs
and we're already got problems right we
got the chronic fatigue syndrome we got
the depression
we got the endometriosis we got the pcos
we got
uh the fibroids we got any kind of
problems that we have
right anything like eczema psoriasis
fibromyalgia
lupus right thyroid disease thyroid
disorders hypothyroidism
i could go on and on and on right lupus
lyme disease
multiple sclerosis ra sarcoidosis
we can go on all day autoimmune
autoimmune autoimmune
okay and what that is is those are bugs
those are viruses those are epstein-barr
so when we eat our eggs when we're doing
that okay
the bugs will eat the eggs inside of us
we
put the eggs in we swallow them they go
through a process
and then the bugs love to feed on the
eggs now if you're healthy you don't
have much
going on yet you don't have a lot of
bugs you could eat eggs for years
you know it could be that person that
eats them and you're not getting sick
and then all of a sudden now
you're hypothyroid all of a sudden you
got hot flashes heart palpitations see
that's how it works covering a little
egg information let's start cooking a
little bit
you call it cooking making a salad
can't let the virus go living in an
animal
because they can't have the they can't
have the virus
sit inside a living animal because of
the living animal's immune system will
work on beating it down
okay an animal has its own immune system
that's how it works so they grow the
viruses
in eggs then when they're released into
the environment
like they have been on us they get in us
and our immune system controls them okay
controls them unless we break down with
all the triggers i talked about
that's how it's done all right
and um until eventually and see what
happens is too is they need the egg to
keep the virus in the egg like
just like in the video right in the labs
they put the viruses in the egg because
they can control the environment
it's just that egg you put the virus
into a living animal you can't control
it anymore it's gone
you got the living animal's immune
system working on it
it's lost in the living animal itself
it's different than when you have it
controlled in this little tiny micro
environment anyway okay all right all
right all right all right
it comes down to just this what
what do i have lyme disease oh no
multiple sclerosis
fibromyalgia too r.a
i got autoimmune i have that
um okay all right
don't eat eggs what about getting oxygen
through
food great hydrogen peroxides not enough
i'm not a fan of it uh polly good
question though
i'm gonna make some good stuff um very
good live today hey thanks it's a good
live because i got you guys here and
that's what makes it good
can you imagine if you guys weren't here
and i was just doing this myself
it would be a bad live
um caney i got canker sores from two
weeks of eating raw
and fat free and i'm still super bloated
um what else are you doing are you raw
and fat free
be your own detective i want you to be
able to be your own detective here okay
all right so um first of all uh no
nutritional yeast
i'm assuming no apples no raw apple
cider vinegar
raw apple cider vinegar do people eat
raw
and they do apple cider vinegar just
keep that in mind
apple cider vinegar not good natural
flavors
what natural flavors are in your
supplementation what natural flavors are
in your raw kale chips
that you might have bought in a package
what natural flavors
look out for that it's a nutritional
yeast apple cider vinegar
natural flavors keep in mind citric acid
not an orange put citric acid that's in
all kinds of products
all kinds of foods all kinds of
supplements keep in mind for that
one too i want you to be your own
detective
very important okay so that that that
alone is is critical right
and now canker virus is already in your
system
so you never got a canker sore ever
before in your life or is this the first
time you got a canker sore
if it's the first time you got a canker
store that broke out okay
where did it come from did it was it's a
recent exposure
which happens to people it's trying to
get you to be your own detective that's
important to know
um and you got to keep in mind that
you're starting to cleanse
so when you're starting to cleanse
you're getting rid of all that sludge
all that stuff inside the liver inside
the body the other thing is um
you know it it's it's you're off fat all
together
so and totally fat free keep in mind
there's no oils there's no avocados look
out for all of that that's something
that could be helpful
um so all these things are key and i
think you're off the fat i'm pretty sure
you said that right
but you never had any bloating before
are you trying to are you you're trying
to fix everything in two weeks
why are you even doing it you must have
had problems so ask yourself
were you bloated ever before in your
life did you ever have a kinky sword in
your life
were you ever were you ever sick did you
have any symptoms because people don't
go raw
for two weeks um and just go raw for two
weeks unless they they've been
struggling no one wants to go raw
so and and did you instinctively feel
something was coming like you
instinctively knew
you had to go raw because something was
on
its way because that happens intuitively
that's how we do it
intuitively we're starting to feel
something we don't we can't line up to
it yet but man i gotta take care of
myself now
i gotta start going raw i gotta start
taking care of myself now it's intuitive
you know and it's like it's in there
like
i gotta start now something was already
on
its way all these things are important
to keep in mind while you're trying to
heal
now what i would do is i would
i would do one of the mono eating
cleanses and cleanse the heel ask your
doctor what's right for you but that's
what i would do
so i would do one of the mono eating
cleanses i would do papaya
celery juice for a couple of days that's
that's what i would do and
take it one step at a time and then you
don't have to be
all raw meaning that's what i would tell
somebody like a doctor friend asking me
this very question
you can then go to steamed potatoes as
one of those meals and do the
mono eating cleanse with steamed
potatoes we've got some steamed potatoes
here
and that's another way of doing things
too
but you know and and so and is it in all
raw from
someone else's all raw like their idea
of all raw or is it the advanced 369
is it the advanced 369 with all the
direction
and the questions answered and
everything under the sun
or is it just some raw diet someone says
hey go do this go raw
and or is it to 28 day cleanse right
is it the 28 day cleanse in medical
medium new addition so these are some
things to keep in mind
because that's going to be very helpful
kirsten
i was diagnosed diagnosed with multiple
sclerosis
and lost vision in my left eye that's
the optic nerve
and and couldn't walk that's in the
inflamed optic nerve couldn't walk and i
ate eggs like crazy
along with dairy for days i love your
books they have been a serious lifesaver
my vision has returned
and i am walking trying to stay away
from the western medicines kirsten
um so um you're staying away from the
eggs
they will make us eat eggs
and kill us with these eggs that's what
they'll do every single practitioner
every single doctor
they'll just they'll just make you doubt
yourself is what they'll do
huh don't stop the eggs
are you sure ah
all right i better eat them all right
i'll eat them every day
eggs in my salad hard-boiled okay
serious protein i'm protein deficient i
have to have the eggs then right
all right all right back on the eggs
back on the eggs i'm scared i'm scared
i've been off the eggs for a little
while now i'm scared
i'll get back on the eggs they literally
scare the crap out of us
is what they do and that's that's what
they do they scare the crap out of us
and that's
that's how they do it gina why is acv
bad acv is bad
um because well first of all i got a
podcast medical mean podcast at apple
podcast have you guys
checked that out medical medium podcast
at apple podcast really important
because that is a really important
podcast right there
and why is apple cider vinegar that was
just one it's the teeth destroyer pulls
calcium out of your teeth and bones it's
the osteopenia creator
apple cider vinegar will dissolve your
teeth you will see it later on
as it destroys your teeth as time goes
on that's what vinegar does acetic acid
that's just one thing
to say about it could say a lot of other
things there's a question there i wanted
to read i think it went up
um i hate when i see natural flavors so
lena i hate when i see natural flavors
and they don't say what's in it very
misleading
see guys here's how the world works
there's bad people in the world okay
i know there's this whole thing where no
one's bad
no one's bad so gassing six million jews
was just i guess a mistake because
no one's bad right so i know there's a
new age
vibe of no one's bad okay
oh no they're not bad no one terrible
things don't happen
uh people aren't killed all the time um
yeah people aren't like murdered okay
people are just no there's no bad in the
world i know there's a new age thing
about there's no bad okay
and i just can't just with it all right
and
the bad what it does it extends into
like the msg world which is all your
natural flavors
msg natural flavors
flavoring flavors natural flavors
organic flavoring they hide it under
that term
that's why you don't hear msg anymore
that's why you don't see msg on the
labels right
in the old days in the old days the
early 2000s i'm just saying the early
2000s everybody in the 1990s right
the early 2000s this is what it was like
it was like
i'm looking i'm looking
uh msg it says it right here in the
ingredient list
m s g let me grab the next thing here
wait what
um yes says msg again msg
and here's what happened people were
starting to freak out
msg caught a bad rap right for a lot of
reasons it's damaging
damaging it's toxic okay and guess what
the msg companies were a law was able to
be
passed out there and then the msg
companies
became were protected they lobbied they
got protected
the protection is they don't have to say
msg anymore baby
msg nope they don't have to they ju they
need to just stick it in the natural
flavoring or
create the msg the new msg which is
natural flavoring
hides it msg factories did not go to
business you think they just went out of
business
you think they're just done you think
they're out of business you think
they're gone
where'd they go they're still in
business and it's in all your organic
food
msg is also sprayed on all your crops
i told you guys this right someone said
like
oh you're you're promoting a non-organic
uh wild blueberry drink are you kidding
me
this is a wild food and what i was
telling everybody and you'll see it on
the last one there is
all your organic produce i washed this
i washed it that's a zucchini right i
washed
that orange surface of that orange okay
i washed
these organic tomatoes because there's
msg
spray the organic sprays
many times are more toxic than the
conventional
sprays they're loaded with nicotine
and msg you have to wash your organic
produce it's loaded with nicotine and
msg
and what weiman's does is they don't
want everybody addicted to that
ms sheets an addiction msg is an
addictive
a drug okay nicotine is an addictive
drug
caffeine is an addictive drug those very
three things are in organic sprays they
spray on everything
and weiman's they do this thing where
you can go a long time without any spray
whatsoever then
they'll do one little area and they'll
do another little area and they'll test
for pesticide
residue and they use they use the
non-pollinator
damaging spray right and organic sprays
with all that nicotine
damages pollinators that's what they use
so people think just because it's
organic means that's it
it's the greatest thing on the planet no
it's not
they spray the heck out of crops three
times a week
and so the why that's why the wild food
is better than organic and i've said
that it's
better than organic that's the why men's
wild blueberry juice but anyway
you know it's important to know when it
comes down to that
m-i-a already healed with your
information and now my psoriasis is back
so bad anthony so you already healed one
time and it's back
all right so you know i'll try to do a
podcast on psoriasis too so that's
important
so if it's actually back okay then you
got to look i'll do it
is there new exposure because that's
what happens
right are you exposed to copper that's
what happens to people
did you get a new medical treatment
any kind of new medical treatment
like hello i'm not um
i gotta watch what i say here
yeah any kind of brand new
medical treatment okay just kind of
looking out here
what a new medical treatment
there's one out there now
listen you know be your own detective
if it's back is it are you doing the
apple cider vinegar you're doing the
nutritional yeast
every time every time i ran across this
over and over again
when i used to work one-on-one with
people it's the same thing over and over
again what's in there now
wait how much fat's back in your diet
what you brought some eggs back in
you're doing nutritional yeast and lots
of apple cider vinegar chewie's
what are you doing and it all kind of
happens and all kinds of habits just be
your own detective and hang in there
um you guys it's good to see you guys
uh and plus do exposure too is there a
new relationship
a lot of times when you've had something
happen and you heal it
you get you do get more sensitive
sometimes when a new
exposure comes like a brand new
relationship
and you get a new book like you know
like a new relationship and then there's
a new bug from somebody else and then a
new bug from somebody else
it's a fact of life fact of life all
right
so i make some food i gotta stop fooling
around
[Laughter]
gotta stop fooling around
all right all right we got
some salad to make
[Music]
let's do that you guys
it's good to see you guys here we're in
the kitchen we're in
the medical medium kitchen
hope you guys aren't bored because i'm
not
i'm not bored okay
i can do this a couple different ways i
like spinach i'm gonna pop
a little spinach in here what about you
guys i just
pee the spinach leaf just touched an egg
over there
you guys the spinach leaf just popped
out of the bowl and it touched an egg
i gotta toss that spinach this spinach
leaf just touched this egg too
i just had the spinach leaf touch the
egg right here all right
guys don't have your
greens touch eggs okay raw eggs whatever
you do
it's not a good thing so i got some
spinach here i'm just gonna
i'm not gonna chop it too finely okay
um am i gonna drive you guys crazy with
the phone
what you saw the egg video on tick tock
when i had like hundreds of eggs out
i'm the biggest food waster there is
are you freaking kidding me that just
hurt my feelings
so i'm like i'm a food waster
how dare i do that well
did you know that those eggs were
outdated
did you know that the grocery store was
going to throw them all out in the
dumpster like they do each week
and that they couldn't sell them anymore
did you know the manager let me have all
those eggs
and they were outdated by a day and they
couldn't sell them
did you know that grocery stores across
the whole country here in the u.s
they dump thousands of cases of eggs
every week in the dumpsters
all the grocery stores at a combined
equals hundreds of tons over time of
eggs
did you know there's people living in
tent cities and homeless people
including cute little families of
of like moms and dads aunts and uncles
and they're all living in tents and they
lost everything
and did you know that there's a law in
the united states
that doesn't allow hundreds of tons of
food that's being thrown in dumpsters
every single day that doesn't allow them
to actually give it to the homeless
did you know that all the homeless in
this country would be fed
and safe and have lots of food if they
would just
take the outdated like literally a day
old
that's all just one day old of the eggs
and all the bread
and all the food and in all the produce
that
gets a little ripe did you know they can
actually feed the homeless and save
countless lives but they won't did you
know it gets thrown in the dumpsters
well yeah maybe before you make a
judgment call on me
and talk crap about me that you know
what's really happening
and stop assuming because when you
assume
you make an ass out of me and you and
that's what you did
all right guys let's make the salad
i'm putting a little spinach in here
what a sick society but there's no bad
people
there's no bad people anywhere right
just the medical medium's bad right
okay just the medical medium is a bad
guy
there's no bad people out there though
right
everybody's so pure in the health scene
there's no corruption in the health
scene huh
with all those advertisers and all those
commercials on all
the podcasts and all everything else and
all the other stuff going on no
there's no corruption in the medical
industry anywhere
there's no bad anywhere
guys i'm putting some lettuce in here
no one gives anything for free
no one gives any thing for free
gonna have to grab this one more time
so you mean me acting silly diminishes
my credibility karen just said that
i just saw the did you see that i know
i just i just saw that too i just saw a
comment that said
when i act really silly it diminishes my
credibility i know
do you think it does i don't know
maybe it does maybe it doesn't
i can't have fun once in a while i
should stop
well what should i do just like stand
there and just be serious 24
7 so that people think i'm more credible
i don't know i'll i'll think about it
all right i love you karen
okay let's go that pink phone
pink phone's starting to drive me crazy
all right you guys
so i'm chopping up some lettuce right
you guys
so i'm making a really nice salad right
here i'm mixing the spinach and lettuce
i got a little cilantro
in there too leafy greens are important
stephanie love your humor don't stop you
sure
ingrid said no way keep laughing
that's funny that's funny look i get it
i get it it's like
humor is one of these things where are
like some people think something's funny
and some people don't think something's
funny i got a friend
that you can make a joke and they'll
just do this
and i'd be like you don't think that's
funny and they're like
i get it you know it's just you know
look
uma i love the ping phone
the ping phone it strengthened it sharon
said it strengths it loves it
love it see if i could speak right today
dr fon let's see all you need to take
aw you need to take my example and be
serious all the time like me you're the
most serious doctor
most serious md i've ever ever known
no i know i know you got a light heart
it's amazing dr phone
a light heart really so i'm making a
salad right here
and sorry guys trying to read the
comments you know
but try to do this at the same time
all right let's go
you guys were back guys i lost you
for a minute did i get you guys back
that was so strange that was like
psychedelic
it was like twilight zone like twilight
zone
right there did i even go where what
happened all right
gonna chop up some tomatoes let's do
that
laughter is medicine
mandy says you put a smile on my dial
i'm honored love your jokes chris said
um guys i'm chopping up a little bit of
tomato i'm not chopping the tomatoes
small i'm just letting you know
can i bring this over susan please
explain why nutritional yeast isn't good
lots of plant-eating folks recommend
it's highly addictive it's got msg in it
hey it's good to be silly we need a good
sense of humor it's got msg in it
it does i don't care what anybody says
it's got msg in it not only that it's
irritating to the lining of the
intestinal tract
so you're ready get ready for this i'm
doing medical medium i better
use the pink phone for this one yeah i'm
doing medical medium
yeah yeah no i i'm just i just don't i
something's not working medical medium's
not working for me no it's not
i should do a post and ruin a whole
bunch of people's chances of healing
right i should because medical means not
working for me
so then i should probably do an
instagram post right and then tear down
the dreams of people healing
that might be trying it or just starting
it because i want to be
you know a mean person what am i doing
i'm doing nutritional yeast really
that's that's that's not medical medium
nutritional yeast isn't medical medium
what do you mean it's not medical medium
oh i never really read the books
oh yeah you're right i never really read
the books and never really learned
not to do like apple cider vinegar and
nutritional yeast and everything else
yeah so now i'm going to take it out on
anthony make sure i ruin it for a whole
bunch of people
because us vegans love our nutritional
yeast and don't want to let it go
so why don't i put that post out still
because you know it'd be good let's give
them some more crap
yeah um because you know what he also
supports animal protein
lovers too so he supports animal protein
people just like he supports us vegans
and we kind of don't like that us vegans
we hate him for that
so yeah let's do the post yeah i know
i'm not feeling good because it's
nutritional yeast you're right you're
right probably is that
okay okay i'll just still say i did
medical medium even though i'm not doing
medical medium i'm gonna say i did
medical medium
i'm gonna put a post out and say i did
medical medium it didn't work for me
okay ready i'm getting ready to write it
let's do it let's totally screw him over
uh anew shut them down my man thank you
hey brother thanks for being here i
appreciate it
get these tomatoes going guys i'm in i'm
in a mood today huh
and um
i'm gonna eat this salad i can't wait
um
you know i was talking about the b12 you
guys are because i saw one question come
up about the b12
the b12 i use is the vimergy b12 because
i use the vimergy supplements that's the
ones
that i only use right now um because i
trust them the best and it's the best
stuff out there
i'm not sponsored by vimergy just so you
know
but the when i was talking about like in
the egg
everybody's talking about inside the egg
how you know oh there's bees in there
and so forth well first of all there's
more bees
inside spinach that actually really get
to the point
but if you're somebody that wants to
take b12 or you're looking for a b12
there's no b12 better than this that's
the vimergy these in victor i
am as in mary ergy so that's just so you
know the one i take
that's the best one there is because i
know that i saw a b12 i thought i saw a
b
question come up because of the egg talk
and i didn't answer it i have a b12
podcast
at medical beam podcast at apple podcast
but i've seen the difference
between what a real b12 does versus a
crappy b12 i've seen people with
fibromyalgia
turn the corner because they got the
right b12 i've seen
people with ra start to get relief
that's what i've seen when they do the
right when they've done brought in the
right b12
and you know i've seen the change in
people
mentally emotionally physically when
it's the right b12
without the natural flavors and without
the other stuff even the other b12s i've
noticed that don't have natural flavors
because they're trying to
they're you know there's only a couple
out there that may not have it i noticed
though it's real
cheap it comes from a different place
it's a cheap version it's not mixed
right
but it's like that's what i've noticed
so i recommend this one for
for doctors so their patients have a
higher healing
factor and that's the one thing so
that's the vimorji
with the no natural flavors the whole
bit
and so that's the one there the b12
because i saw that question
nutritional yeast is vegan crack jenny
it totally is
it's msg and it's total vegan crap
that's what it is and crack but look
i always say if you're going to be vegan
be vegan and be plant-based
i'm very pro-plant-based okay you guys
know that right
but i'm not a vegan propaganda channel
because i believe if you want to eat
animal protein
you can still heal and still do the
28-day cleanse
then bring your animal protein back in
later you need more healing do the
28-day cleanse again
then bring the animal protein back in
later it depends on what's happening
but keeping the fats down because i've
seen vegans and plant-based people
fat themselves to death too much avocado
nuts seeds and oils
right and they just can't heal and then
they're doing nutritional yeast and then
you're doing apple cider
vinegar and they're just they can't heal
and then they they fail
and then they run back to eating eggs
again so then now they run back to
eating eggs now they run
back to animal protein and i've seen
animal protein people fail
when all they had to do was was know
what to do
and they can still keep you know and
they get sick and then they gotta run
now vegan like everybody's running back
and forth
no one has the real answers and it's sad
so um it's about being
keeping the radical fats out while
you're healing
what from when you're sick and you keep
the radical fats out
that's part of it i've seen them all fat
themselves of death nutritional yeast
themselves to death
i've seen it all and it's fine it's like
well whatever but
you know do what you want to do and then
you'll get somebody that's like well
you know intuitively i think this is
right for me i feel good about my
nutritional yeast it's like well your
intuitive powers really really
suck because you're not
you're going to get in trouble you just
are it's like
we lose our intuitive abilities that's
how the system
we lose because the addiction takes over
it's like
it's like it's like people who are
addicted to caffeine they're eating
their chocolate all the time they're
addicted to their matcha tea
they're addicted to their coffee and
it's like you know what i mean
okay i trust your intuitive abilities
okay you're totally addicted
to caffeine which is fine but let's just
not let's just not like get carried away
and think we got it all down like we got
all the answers see a lot of people in
the health scene
that are doing all that caffeine but
they're all on their social media
they're they're all
experts like experts really and you're
jacked up on caffeine because you can't
function without the caffeine
so um i'm gonna put some potato on here
too and that's next
well let's put some zucchini i didn't
have cucumbers
i think i might have them but i couldn't
i couldn't find them you know but
in time but i got some zucchinis here
i'm going to cut the top off i like
zucchini it's a really great food for so
many reasons okay
so what i'm doing is cutting the
zucchini i'm going to cut it in half
down the middle like this
okay and i'm going to cut little pieces
like this i'm going to put a few of
these on the salad
if you want to heal it's good to keep
the fats down now when your animal
protein okay here's the thing
if you need to take a break between your
healing process right like
you're doing the three six nine and
you're working on really healing right
you're doing the 28-day cleanse and
you guys
if you want to cut it back and take a
break and be like well you know what
i want to i still want to eat healthy
but what do i do i eat animal protein
like how do i do this aw like how do i
do it
and well then you can bring your
sardines and you put your sardines on
your salad instead of your potatoes
right you if you're into chicken and
chicken's a thing you eat and you're
always eating your chicken and stuff
like that you put a little chicken
on top of your salad if meat something
you put a little
you know little bit of meat or some
salmon right if you're animal protein
but remember
those are fats and if you're still sick
you want to get to the point where you
drop the fats again maybe do the 28 day
cleanse again
maybe do a 369 like original 369 or
simplify but you keep the fats kind of
at bay or
you do the animal protein once a day and
if you're vegan you do your avocado once
a day at
the end of the day right but keep the
potatoes
out if you bring in your avocado because
you're vegan plant-based and you bring
in your nut butters because you're vegan
and plant-based and you're bringing your
salmon because you're animal-based
and you bring in whatever it is because
you're animal-based make sure
you keep the potatoes out of the picture
details
matter details make or
break natural flavor is a detail
that makes or break nutritional yeast
detail that makes or break blood draw
blood draw is make or
break right there blood draw is make or
break right there okay it's make or
break
you know getting the blood out of them
uh
what we're taking too much blood no
we're not we're gonna take
14 vials from you we need every bit of
it
let me get that blood out of you oh
you're dizzy
uh you're just a wimp um you need some
apple juice
chalk it up you're a wimp you gotta tell
me something you guys
here's how it works okay i told you this
i got the blood blood draw podcast if
you haven't heard it
listen to it and share the heck out of
it okay all right
all right so i got a little blood right
here
that's all you need right there
for your nutritional panel your thyroid
test
okay and a a c-reactive protein
cholesterol metabolic panel liver
enzymes that's all you need
that's it it's all you need that's it
right there another one it's all you
need and they take
vials and vials out and they drop your
immune system it's a massive trigger
so here you are a vegan um i got blood
all over the arm right there by the way
here you are vegan okay
here you are vegan and you think you're
doing good
you're getting your blood tested and
you're not feeling good anyway and they
take your immune system
out with all the blood that's what they
do they take your immune system out
with all the blood they remove your
white count
right your white count okay and
when they do that they take your blood
out be open-hearted says just had blood
work done my ldl
dropped 30 points but my hdl dropped
also to 44
i'm doing i'm doing no fat
um due to fatty liver disease you're
working on healing
be open-hearted just you know glad
you're here um honored you're here
so your bloodstream doesn't your
bloodstream doesn't just
reproduce an immune system comes from
your bones it doesn't happen overnight
okay and your blood fills with water you
can drink water get hydrated and you're
you're getting the tank full but you're
missing your
cbc a big hunk of your cbc they take it
all
right they take it all and then your
immune system goes with it huge trigger
for chronic illness it keeps the vegan
sick
it keeps the plant-based person sick it
keeps the animal protein sick you lose
your glucose and electrolytes you're
sick now you kick back for a week or two
takes three to six months to get your
immune system back your cbc
so i talk about on the podcast what to
do i'm not against
getting your blood taken not against
blood draw right
and i've been recommending lately to
friends and family they're like what
should i do and one of the things i
didn't put in the podcast is
do a shot of wild blueberry juice if you
had blood draw do a shot every single
week before weeks after but
of the wild blueberry juice but the
description of the blood draw podcast is
sorry the link is in the description but
they take way too much blood they take
way too much of your immune system your
red blood cell count right they take too
much and then
that's when the trigger happens and all
of a sudden now you get sicker and
sicker then they take more blood because
you get sicker listen to the podcast
episode
it's called blood draw bloodletting
vampirism it's a really good episode
it's life-saving
life-changing it's getting gross because
i'm getting blood on everything now
um so
putting some zucchini slices on here
make a nice little salad
wow those lobotomists really are
vampires
and in the end it's not even their fault
right it's not even the doctor's fault
it's a system itself m.c
thanks emcee that's awesome
guys good to see you tonight i'm making
dinner
glad you guys are here i got a salad
right here zucchini slices you can cut
them smaller if you want
you can cut them smaller they're
probably more fun
smaller for a lot of people but throwing
a few on here
you can eat potatoes but keep the fats
out
keep the fats out um if you're healing
keep the fats out but you can have your
potatoes you know what i mean if you're
doing your fats keep the potatoes out
that's what i would do i'm not doing any
fat in this meal so i got my potato i'm
gonna slice this potato up
so i'm cutting it right now
there we go i don't want them too small
i want you guys to be able to see the
pieces i don't want to dice them
it's not something i want to do but i'm
making it really nice here
i'm just working on it
california poppy good to see you
where you been where you been
california poppy it's a great handle
um i saw illumination
i saw the illumination word california
bobby
mrs dear what is the blood draw all
about
why is this topic relevant right now oh
my god mrs dear
mrs dear you have to le everybody
can you can you tell mrs dear to listen
to the podcast episode link is in the
description
it's blood draw episode your mind will
be so blown
your mind will be blown you'll think
it's invasion of the body snatchers here
on planet earth you know remember that
movie
yeah that's what they do what's the
bloods are all about they take too much
blood
they only need this much listen to the
podcast so you can defend yourself
protect yourself and still go get your
blood tested
they remove your immune system you go
kick backwards kick backwards you get
sick or sick or sicker
they'll bleed you to death until you die
that's what the system will do
they'll take 170
uh milliliters they'll take 240
milliliters of blood they'll take 300
milliliters of blood to take 400
milliliters of blood
and they only need this much
they'll need that much see all those
little dots i don't know if it's white
it out see all those little dots you
only need that much
it'll take that much okay
[Applause]
you can eat fats with potatoes you can
eat some avocado with potato
you can have fats with potato but but
when you're really
healing or working on healing try to not
do that try not do that just want that
message across on there
okay so i put zucchini in there i got my
tomatoes in there
i got my potatoes in there let's do a
little red onion real quick
miss dixie as a medical professional i
love your books and the
information you share i'm i'm honored
i'm modern miss dixie
i'm honored seriously i really am uh oh
i cut an onion so i know what that means
my eyes i talk about donating blood
what you could do to protect yourself
i'm not anti-donating blood i'm not
anti-getting your blood tested that's
not it
but you can save your life i i just talk
about if you're sick and you're
struggling with symptoms
i mean if i was sick with struggling
symptoms i wouldn't be donating blood
and i would
i would listen to the podcast
cindy lou she's saying hi poppy must be
california poppy she's talking about
[Music]
so i'm gonna put a little red onion on
here
got the nice red onion and my eyes are
going to start crying any minute
i can tell that red onion oh yeah that
red onion's going to get my eyes
someone said aw try to kind of look away
when you cut it
because it's going to get you
cordana sorry
but how do you tell them not to take too
much blood
they just do they just do it
the doctor the doctor if you tell them
not to take too much blood you tell them
to do half files
they'll still send it to the lab the lab
will still take and test your blood
because they only need this much
tell your doctor you want half aisles
done ask your doctor
just tell them you want to have files
done listen to the podcast i explain it
all and the doctor will do it
uh cook your potatoes prior yes i
steamed them prior
guys my eyes are getting so watery that
red onion got me
let's make a um a little bit of a sauce
so i'm gonna do that now okay so that's
what i'm gonna do
i'm gonna have to use the the bowl that
had the poo in it
i got no choice remember you guys i was
eating the poo because it had nutrients
in it
i i so i have to use that bowl
hope you guys are okay with that you
guys want to come over here to eat
dinner with me
you don't want to have a bowl like that
right
all right i know a whole bunch of people
were mad at me for doing the egg
the egg tick tock but i forewarned
everybody i said look
i got a tick tock coming out and you're
just gonna get really upset
because you guys love your eggs it's the
the tick tock with the mad scientist
the mad scientist tick-tock because
that's what they did that that's what
they did with our eggs and still do
it's terrible really no one has any idea
what they really do it's it's incredible
it's actually scary as heck
the egg demo was educational you seem
fine to me hey
chris you're on here on youtube
youtube and facebook
you know i'm going to be on tick-tock
and ig in a little while and i and
and
alicia they can do way less than half
vials
i used to draw blood in a couple of
utah's ers
and you'd be shocked how little they
need
i i'm gonna bow down bow down to the
expert here
you're the expert for sure you get it
that was
really really mind-blowing and yeah it's
true it's how it is
and that's what i've been telling
everybody um i've been telling people
they only need that
right i want a little drop but i've been
telling these people info
um and people just i mean they just
can't digest it
you know they can't digest it and it's
important to know but that that's so
important to know
you're making history right now you know
with learning about this to such a
degree
everybody because you're going to
protect a lot of people you're going to
help save a lot of lives and
and you know and it's it's important to
know
[Music]
making a sauce right now
mustard honey sauce
you know what happens sicker you get
alicia you know this right sicker you
get from big blood draws
they blood they draw more blood i mean
they shorten lives
like so much right isn't that crazy
that's how the system works and they
force they force the nurses to do it
they force
everybody to do it it's just
unbelievable so i got a little bit of
them put a little lemon in here too
uh lemon seed went in there but i'm okay
with that
get some lemon in here let me put some
honey
i got i got uh pandemic info in the book
in the new edition just so you guys know
okay
i got pandemic info in there right
i got um plague information right in the
new book
you guys i hope you guys get the book if
you don't have it that's a new edition
you got to remember which one it is it's
revised and expanded new edition that's
the book medical medium
put a little honey in here okay
so i got that margaret valentine
where you been can hardly wait for the
blueberry juice
i i feel bad that i have it and you guys
don't right now you know or you're
waiting on it i feel terrible about it
but yeah i'm pumped
alicia it's horrible i used to take so
much blood from people for like blood
cultures
these people were already in patients
and they never got better
alicia it's it's yeah i mean you know
you were you were taking orders
you were taking orders from your bosses
if you don't
do what your bosses tell you you get
fired and then you can't take care of
yourself
so it's not your fault every single
nurse is up against this
up against this around the world it's
it's it's criminal
you know what the system does tammy
ward the book new book you like that and
then the
the the it went up
so right now i'm just just mixing up the
so i'm gonna put a little bit of uh
put a little bit of mustard powder in
here okay you guys don't mind
just a little bit don't need a lot of
mustard powder powder
mustard power powder
a little bit of chili powder
right tms
mc he doesn't care if you get it for
free from a library or borrow from a
friend
yes get it free at the library it's all
right
you know why i just need you to have it
so you can heal
that's how it's always been
jennifer jocelyn i am an rn working on
my n
my fnp right now and i'm working
as a pre-op rn i see so much blood drawn
every day jennifer it's it's
they don't even need any of it i mean
they they do need a drop but what i'm
saying is they don't even need 99.9
of it it's so bad i don't i mean i could
see them taking
a few i could see them taking like a
thimble's worth you know which is a lot
of drops but it's just unbelievable
flower mole one two three they stole so
much of my blood and my babies
while i was pregnant i wish i knew
earlier it's it's so hard
and i know that some of you guys got not
you flower mold but some of you guys got
mad at me because you said well why
didn't you tell us all these years we've
been following i did i talked about it
in so many occasions but i guess i had
to make it the entire
platform to really get the message out
yvonne i'm a nurse
and i understand incredible it really is
it's incredible
all right so i got the dressing it's
done
i got my salad right here okay and i
talked about different options you can
have in here you can put
if you want animal protein with the
course you can but this is a healing
meal for when you're healing in the
moment you can do animal protein another
day in your life with it
or if you're if you're plant-based if
you really want to do a little avocado
with it or a little tahini or something
because your plant-based that's okay
right but but but realize that you know
if you're working on your healing
process having a
no-fat meal sometimes would be really
good
and there's fats in all foods remember
that there just is you know there's fats
in all food
margaret valentine a.w i'm loving
radishes
now nearly every day because of you and
spirit those are so good for you
margaret you guys got to take off
i'm heading to ig and tiktok in in a few
minutes okay so just bear with me
i just got to kind of straighten up the
kitchen for a couple of minutes and i'm
going to try to behave
the best i can on ig and tick tock i
know that someone said the other day i
go a little bit more intense and
some things are you know stuff starts
flying and everything but
i'm gonna try to keep it cool and i love
you guys i'll see you soon