hey W invited me here you're so sugar is
not the problem with your teeth
sugar
I learned many years ago that sugar is
the problem with their teeth
the sugar is why you have teeth problems
and conditions
yes you see
[ __ ] when I was a young lad
we learned
that sugar was responsible for all of
our cheese problems hmm there's a bowl
of sugar here brown sugar no wonder
why everybody's losing their teeth
[Music]
I brought my glass of wine glass of wine
there's no sugar in one you see
you can treat yourself to a glass of
wine anytime you're like
it doesn't matter hmm
what is this
aw doesn't start the best of lines
um
[Music]
made my pipe taste good
I want to give everybody a tutorial here
[Music]
I want to show you how you should brush
your teeth every day after you have your
Delights I can have all your chocolate
cake I've had two or three glasses of
wine already
this is a little extra curriculum I'm
helping out ew tonight actually he's
been working hard trying to teach you
all kinds of manners about brushing your
teeth
I'm going to show you how I brush my
teeth here now what I do is I take a
brush after I've had three or four
glasses of wine
and then I have my silver bar chocolate
which AWS here's a nice big bar of
chocolate
and wine
what I do is I take your toothbrush and
I brush like this to each tooth yes
I make sure I brush all my implants
and I make sure I brush my bridge back
here too because I have a bridge
can you
and then what I do is I have a a crown
over here yes right here I brush the
crown very good yes oh yes and I have an
implant here and an implant here usually
oh this doctor says that okay
I'm getting quite bored here yes I
invited another doctor friend to come on
board I know he's a good friend of all
of ours and what the thing is this is Dr
friend here
would you like you were or Dr Nesmith Dr
Nesbitt is an old colleague of Mine He's
a surgeon and he's a board she's board
certified psychiatrist yes thank you for
the counseling session the other day oh
yes you know I have all kinds of
problems Dr nesby he wants a little suck
on the pipe here there you go
not good news but always needs a good
pipe a good pipe here and there
what would you like out of all these
texture Delights you would like the wine
I don't know Dr Nesbit Dr nesbitch Dr
Nesbit stop stop Dr Nesbitt now Dr
Nesbitt I don't know if you actually
have a chicken disease that's going to
get into my wine Dr Nesbitt no Dr
Nesbitt likes you to get your own
computer going now what kind of delight
would you would you like the popcorn Dr
Nesbit just told me he likes the popcorn
Dr Elizabeth would you like some popcorn
here okay Dr nesbeck does like a popcorn
as you can see Tick Tock God Tick Tock
what are we doing on Tick Tock I told my
doctor colleagues I'd never go on Tick
Tock ever ever going Tick Tock you're
seriously some professionals going Tick
Tock there's doctors on Tick Tock what
are they doing on there hmm are they
giving advice uh-huh where all the words
come on and they go oh and they go oh
and they go oh and they go tick tock
and then everybody does a dance and they
all do a dance routine or no Dr
nesbitt's gonna get on Tick Tock and do
a dance routine oh Marissa says Marissa
who's Marissa this I can't stop laughing
what uh I just somebody said what the
[ __ ]
what yes dentist is never oh okay
everybody's on
did you hear about the Apple podcast
medical medium podcasts at Apple podcast
yes jeez everybody's getting drilled
um
or should I say everyone's getting
drilled okay
well we've had our day here I think we
should give everybody else a try Dr
Nesmith
um
Dr Desmond uh you want to show everybody
how you brush your teeth
Dr Nesbit does want to show you how he
brushes his teeth Dr Nesbitt
do you want to show everybody Dr Nesbit
says you have to do this you have to
brush these bottom ones just like this
you see what Dr nesbitt's doing now Dr
Nesbitt has all his teeth
Dr Nesbitt okay Doctor that's enough Dr
Arabic that's enough Dr Harrisburg Dr
Nesbit Dr Nesbitt really likes his
toothbrush he's going to take it home
okay Dr judgment would you like to go
you have surgery to do I think
you're not going to take the wine
tonight no Dr nesbitt's going back to
surgery
okay I'm gonna go find JW and I'm gonna
take my wine and go sit down on the
couch
here's something to read a medical a
medical book and on the couch there and
I'm gonna look more into the sugar thing
yes indeed okay I will be back
hey guys I'm back so we're talking about
teeth did you check out the new podcast
episode we had a tech glitch in the one
of the last lives and we're here again
it's unbelievable so yeah make sure you
listen to the medical medium podcast and
apple podcast on Apple podcast okay
that's important right there so
anyway the whole point you guys just so
you know I am here we're talking about
teeth the whole bit I know so many
people are going through so much trouble
with their teeth the point is is yes you
get a good dentist right you get work
done yep of course right but how do we
protect our teeth so they're not falling
apart as time goes on how do we protect
your teeth so that we actually stay safe
with our teeth teeth along the way and
we don't lose our teeth because so many
people lose their teeth they got molars
missing they got they got front teeth
missing they got bottom teeth missing so
it's really important to take care of
our teeth link is in the description the
episode I just released last night is
called teeth everyone's getting drilled
it's free it's intense there's a lot of
information the details matter just so
you guys know right Details Matter it's
packed with information
and so you might want to listen to it if
you get a chance it's really good info
of course and no commercials no
advertisements or commercials and that's
what's incredible it's a number one
podcast with no commercials no one's
ever done that but we like to do that
that's that's the difference here so you
guys we're talking about sugar earlier
today and I want to talk about a little
bit more for a minute
no matter where you go no matter who you
talk to sugar is the destroyer of teeth
you'll hear so you'll hear that out
there sugar is and it makes people shy
away from fruit it makes them shy away
from
bananas mangoes papayas Cherries Berries
apples it makes them afraid to eat the
foods that actually help our teeth and
that's what happens out there because we
think we lump all sugar as the same
that's what professionals do out there
that's what health Advocates do
professionals whatever they lump sugar
all together and then they're afraid of
having a piece of fruit Olivia Lett says
it's really an incredible podcast for
outbreaking science as usual nobody
knows that advanced science incredible
Olivia incredibly listened to it so
honored and thank you for being here
again right Kara says I just listened to
your podcast on teeth was really curious
about the not doing everything at once
is that just for teeth so not doing
everything at once
so you can baby step to take care of
yourself and your health you know some
people do lemon water celery juice some
people do 369 Advanced cleanse some
people do the monocleanse some people do
protocols for their autoimmune and every
bit counts you know you got to customize
too but the key is right
the key is is to make sure that you
don't fall into Fruit fear because the
fruit fear will get everybody every time
and I'll tell you why what happens is
that when we get fruit fear we then get
afraid of the things we need and that's
how it always works and we end up eating
chocolate once again we end up eating
all the chocolate that's the thing we do
so we go for that because we're not
getting our fruit sugar we're not
getting our glucose right so when it
comes down to fruit you're getting your
minerals your trace minerals to help
restore your teeth fruit is alkaline
remember that alkaline is the way to go
it's not about sugar sugar isn't why
people have teeth problems okay we'll
cover that in another minute so it's
about being alkaline internally but we
can't be alkaline when we're eating
everything that's not alkaline and you
know people say well no that's not true
you know I eat really good and you know
I eat eat lean protein I'm keto or I'm
vegan and I'm keto and I eat beans and I
eat nut Butters and not all that's
acidic so
so we actually eat acidic Foods that's
all we do
so we eat lots of acidic Foods they
don't digest well they don't break down
well in the stomach that's what happens
you know they don't break well in the
stomach and boom
so somebody said hey we lost 250 people
really quick in a blip yeah that's what
happens on here all the time people
actually get kicked off all the time on
the medical medium lives not by us so
you guys medical medium podcasts at
Apple podcast just launched three new
episodes you guys gotta check it out
when you get a chance teeth everyone's
getting drilled important pertinent
information critical information to
protect yourself right Doreen says such
Common Sense fruit is alkaline fruit is
actually alkaline it's about what's
happening inside the body right inside
your stomach your intestinal tract your
gut your liver it's about what's
happening here that protects here that's
the key what happens in here protects
here right that's how it works so we
protect our teeth by what we're doing
inside here okay so people walk around
with stomachs that aren't working good
low hydrochloric acid they don't break
down their proteins they rot ammonia
happens ammonia creeps up
into the mouth when you're sleeping at
night so let's cover ammonia for a
couple of minutes so here's what happens
right
we're really acidic more than that our
HCL doesn't work more than that our bile
reserves are low we don't break down our
proteins we don't break down our food
right our fats and protein it goes
rancid and then we go to bed
we lay in bed and ammonia from the gut
creeps up like the ghost in the night
creeps off the up the esophagus right
goes into the mouth and it sits into the
mouth
while you're sleeping when that ammonia
sits in the mouth while you're sleeping
it goes into the gums and teeth it has a
an ability to basically travel through
bone that's what ammonia does travels
through bone which is your teeth and it
weakens them and people end up having
weakened teeth along the way
so so what happens is when your proteins
and your fats aren't digesting well
because it's not digesting well for
virtually almost everybody
all that gas build up in the gut right
that putrification that rancid fat
builds up
all that ammonia gets produced from it
putrefying travels up the esophagus sits
in your mouth at night when you're
sleeping and starts to break down the
teeth this process can break people's
teeth down real fast real quick and then
things can start falling apart from
there right
so
so um
back to the whole sugar thing right
sugar isn't the problem it's the other
stuff sugar is with
so it's the other things like I was
showing you guys earlier okay this
chocolate cake isn't all sugar see so
when someone says well I quit sugar I'm
avoiding sugar Sugar's the problem
that's where it is
they're really they're only benefiting
not because they're avoiding sugar
they're benefiting because they're
avoiding the lard and the butter and the
dyes and the chemicals and the additives
right in the hydrogenated oils right and
you can even be doing a healthier piece
of cake but that could have vegetable
oils in it that can still have other
things in it and you might think
Butter's healthy and you just got butter
in your cake but either way
what happens is it's the fats or you got
eggs in your cake either way it's the
fats that actually cause the problem
it's not the sugar and so people don't
realize right people be like well don't
have apple pie because all that Sugar
they actually call this sugar I I see it
for years I've seen it for years I see
it now people say oh you don't want a
piece of pie so much sugar yeah they put
a half a cup of sugar in a pie they'll
put a cup of sugar in a Pie when they
make one but you wouldn't believe how
much fat lard and butter is in the pot
that's where the culprit is now
processed sugar is not good for us by
itself we don't just eat sugar all day
long this is brown sugar right here
we're not like did you have your bowl of
sugar today did you have like your whole
bowl of sugar today this is really good
I'm just gonna have my whole bowl of
sugar right now did you have one I have
it three times a day so I eat a whole
bowl of brown sugar three times a day
you guys I better quit my sugar
I'm having way too much sugar no that's
not what happens people get
people get all this fat involved with
their food like the ice cream people
think ice cream sugar that's what they
think they're always like yeah too much
sugar in that ice cream you hear it all
the time that's the problem right that's
not the problem it's actually the fat
and the ice cream right and the protein
the milk proteins right and the fat they
don't break down they don't digest well
they rot in the stomach and your teeth
go that's how it works Marissa spiritual
says thank you so much for bringing Dr
Nesbitt out aw yeah Dr Nesbitt wanted to
come out
so I'm really glad he did
so anyway
shellini says if I do not have iPhone
how can I listen to Apple podcast go to
Spotify but I can't guarantee
it's not going to be glitched out right
we noticed that Apple podcast right and
I've always said that medical medium
podcast at Apple podcast it it's never
censored it's never glitched out it's so
far we've been really fortunate so but
if you don't have your iPhone just you
know Spotify right that's what I would
do
so anyway you guys back to what we're
talking about the teeth episode you got
to check it out when you get a chance
it's an amazing episode in the sense
that it has a lot of detailed
information about how to protect her
teeth
and that's the key because we can go to
the dentist we can brush our teeth but
why are they still falling apart
right for so many people so and I've
always said it right teeth are like time
capsules right they fall apart they
crumble from within years later
and we don't know why but they do and
then if you're trying something new and
then and your teeth happen to be falling
apart in that moment when you're trying
something new you think it was because
of what you were doing right there in
that moment Meanwhile your teeth were on
the trajectory of falling apart they
were already on they were on that
trajectory of falling apart it's all
about timing when do they fall apart do
they fall apart when you're taking a
trip one day and you're going to think
that trip did it are they falling apart
when you went swimming that day next
thing you know next you know that week
it's like oh why am I having a tooth
problem now I gotta go to a dentist was
it because I went swimming that week
it's all about timing did it fall apart
because you tried a new diet that week
right it just doesn't happen that quick
right but it falls apart as we're doing
stuff we're doing stuff for years we're
doing coffee we're doing vinegar you can
talk to like virtually anybody in health
okay except for maybe like a lot of the
medical medium Community but you can
talk to virtually anybody in health and
there's the leading vinegar heck they're
taking vinegar shots not they're doing
vinegar gummies
with people in health are doing vinegar
all the time but it's like whoa that's a
way to kill your teeth real bad Joe
Anderson says I recently heard an
influencer talking about waiting to
brush your teeth after you have a
smoothie or after you eat fruit
yeah well that that makes perfect sense
as far as for an influencer to say that
then missing that's misinformation but
exactly that influencer thought fruit
sugar was going to destroy your teeth
now think about that message right now
if I was to hear that and I was somebody
a follower to this influencer
and I heard that and they were like so
yeah what I like to do is after I have
my smoothie I then well after I had my
piece of fruit here's a mango right here
after I have my piece of fruit everybody
what I do is I brush my teeth afterwards
okay so make sure fruit scares the [ __ ]
out all you because you know what you're
gonna all lose your teeth that's why I'm
brushing my teeth after I have my fruit
you guys so yeah like make sure I scare
you to death about eating fruit oh I'm
having my fruit I'm having my smoothie
but I gotta brush my teeth after because
you're gonna lose your teeth my dentist
told me I'm gonna lose all my teeth
because after my fruit smoothie I better
brush my teeth right
so so yeah I mean exactly right so
that's that's how it works
so then people are gonna be scared
that's what they're gonna be that's what
they're going to be scared of right
but you want to wait to brush your teeth
you want to wait to brush your teeth at
different times you don't have to like
you don't have to worry about that point
that doesn't make a set make sense but
if you have chocolate
you might want to brush your teeth after
you had all that chocolate right so
they're going to worry about fruit
and fruit acids fruit acids are alkaline
fruit acids don't hurt teeth
fruit assets actually kill bad bacteria
in your mouth but they'll go and eat
chocolate they'll have a chocolate bar
and not brush their teeth afterwards
right that's the time if you want to
brush your teeth and you're worried
about something you brush them after
coffee and chocolate right
and um
so yeah so the thing is they they're
trying to brush their teeth after they
eat fruit because they think they're
worried about acid from the fruit and
fruit sugar and they're thinking they're
worried about both that right so people
always worry oh is fruit acidic it's not
it's actually alkaline it helps somebody
is what it does it helps you it's
alkaline when fruit hits the digestive
system it actually enters the mouth like
lemon water it's instantly alkaline Deb
says I don't use vinegar that's amazing
Deb that's so good
so many people use vinegar and don't
even know it I'm glad you know that you
don't right and that's key but vinegar
is hidden Deb make sure you figure that
out now you might not actually use
vinegar where you open up the vinegar
bottle and you're pouring it on
something you might not be using it that
way but is it any condiments in there is
it is it in something like that the
refrigerator is it in your Salsas is it
in some salty head at a restaurant did
you have a salad dressing at a
restaurant did you have like anything
like that is there's packaged food with
dehydrated vinegar on it I saw kale
chips out there with dehydrated vinegar
in it right like it's all that stuff
it's hidden everywhere so you got to
kind of look out for it right Misty
Lewis says yeah before my dentist told
me to stop my lemons and fruits so I
just don't tell him anymore laugh out
loud that I already restarted it at Full
Speed Ahead well that's what they do the
dentist will tell you to stay away from
your lemons stay away from your fruit is
wilted too but what the dentist doesn't
tell you right
is that all these patients the dentist
has that are losing their teeth getting
all the dental work done all the
fillings and everything else they
weren't using lemons as a primary diet
Source they weren't using fruit as a
primary diet source so if you go into a
dentist office and you sit in the
waiting room and you're like hey
uh yo yo um hi uh yeah you know my name
is yeah what do you you eat lemons too
tons of them every day and you know what
happens is people are going to be like
no what are you talking about lemons
like what lemon meringue pie you gotta
check out the episode right it's called
teeth everyone's being getting drilled
and it's it's a medical meme podcast at
Apple podcast you guys that's the best
place to listen to it check it out there
right new episode third episode of the
season
check it out I did the first episode on
supplements second episode on Lemon
Water you've got to make sure you listen
to the lemon water episode and then of
course listen to the teeth episode 2
which is really cool
Olivia says you got a good dentist I
hope people have great dentists so
mineral deficiencies I talk about that
during this episode inherited toxins and
poisons from the family line so we pass
on poisons and toxins like DDT
down the family line toxic heavy metals
right so it's more than just food
that's why someone right someone's
eating a certain way but they don't have
any cavities somebody else is eating the
same way but they have a lot of cavities
because we have lowered immune systems
that's a key right there bad bacteria
right in our body that's another key
there low-grade viral infections mineral
deficiencies heavy metals Mercury is a
big one if someone's high in mercury
they're going to have more teeth
problems and I'm not even talking about
amalgams so you guys I also talk about
amalgams in this episode so if any of
you guys have mercury fillings
silver filling still in your mouth you
might want to hear this right
um Nance says I think my teeth issues
were from doing the vinegar every
morning for years and years diet crap
Etc now I drink lemon water incredible
see the vinegar do so much damage for so
many years for people and when people
think they can use a straw and that
that's all they need is a straw
and then just bypass your teeth it
doesn't work they're misinformed because
it's the vinegar entering into the body
itself the body then has a reaction to
the vinegar what the body does
is the body has to neutralize the
vinegar to acidic
so acidic the body can go into acidosis
so to stop the human body somebody's
body from going into acidosis it has to
release calcium from your teeth and
bones
so the only way to protect yourself when
you're drinking vinegar taking a vinegar
shot apple cider vinegar in your cooking
in a sauce in a dressing the only way to
protect yourself
from the damaging effects of vinegar
is your body
actually taking calcium from your bones
and teeth to neutralize the acid so you
don't get acidosis and your kidneys
don't start going downhill
so important to know Carrie
says my teeth and gums have got much
better since shrinking lemon water and
celery juice thank you isn't that
amazing lemon water like that's
incredible right
and you know what you can do lemon water
and you can do limes too so I got some
limes and lemons right here Maria
actually says a lot of functional
doctors still pushing apple cider
vinegar to help with low acid and
stomach Dear God
would apple cider vinegar does I've
talked about this for years is it
destroys
your gastric glands
so the very HCL producers think about
this inside your stomach are gastric
glands they produce HCL
that HCL is your good asset
so if a functional medicine Doctor is
recommending
vinegar apple cider vinegar
for an acid stomach what they're doing
is they're helping to destroy and
basically fry out the gastric gland so
you can't produce as much hydrochloric
acid to save your butt they actually it
works backwards it doesn't help but
that's how it works in alternative
medicine right you just you just try
different things and been there done
that try things and not all acids are
the same you guys it's not the same
thing
bacteria like streptococcus inside your
gut produces a different kind of acid
a bad acid right that bad acid is
different than your hydrochloric acid
your good acid in your stomach two
different kinds of acids really
important to know
so this acid
is not a remedy for either one for
somebody who has low HCL or someone who
has bacteria in their stomach so that's
critical to know are bacteria inside
their intestinal tract so and that's why
a lot of people they have so many
problems but what is guaranteed when you
do the vinegar route
you're going to have teeth problems down
the road unless you do something to turn
it around right
yeah
and all that's important
so anyway Jennifer says he's having a
hard time being taken hard time wait
he's having a hard enough time being
taken seriously he can't afford to be
funny at this point well Jennifer I try
my best you know I'm only human I'm
trying to deliver information so it's
entertaining as well and I like having a
little bit of fun because I spent 35
years helping people rise out of the
ashes from the depths of hell and back
to get their lives back people who were
bedridden couldn't even walk or take a
shower people who needed to get out of
their wheelchairs been helping doctors
all these years and I'm not like seeking
credibility I want people better and
healing keeping a light heart Joy a
little bit of humor can help people who
are actually on mattress Island right so
it's to keep a light heart and so that's
that's the whole thing right and the
skits I do are actually things that
happen so the skits I do Jennifer this
is important to know the schizo View
there's truth in the skits keep that in
mind right
so when I talk about different things in
all these skits if you look back at all
my comedy skits right
and the parodies and everything I do
you'll see there's something to learn
from it
and that's important the other thing is
if you're sick and you're bedridden or a
mattress island or couch Island and
you've had like a reduced quality of
life because of it you can't work you
can't exercise a light heart and a
little Joy is always a good thing and I
have to think about people who are
chronically ill there's people out there
chronically sick and they can use like a
giggle it's so important Jamie says fun
fun fun love it incredible
accordion says no it's better to be
funny laughter helps the stress it does
Lorraine L good to see you don't change
Anthony we love you the way you are not
wearing the blue shirt though the good
the cool and the Lorraine thank you
Wilma Cali mm is real hey I'm honored
Michelle L we need the humor aw that's
me
oh you guys are incredible really really
I mean you know I just want to be
helpful
intentful spirit says I like how casual
you are with sharing all this instead of
on your soapbox I'm on my soapbox
everybody
yep yep yep soapbox soapbox let me get
on my soapbox here I tell you what to do
for your health every day soapbox
soapbox
Chrissy seemed fine in me humor is
everything
and Allison Saunders people learn better
and retain better when they're having
fun scientifically proven absolutely
and Jamie says love your comedy W did I
tell you that we're on Twitch you guys
the new platform twitch trick every time
I don't know
all right I hope I didn't lose people
that time yo that's all right what am I
gonna do Carolina says yes I like his
sense of humor exactly Olivia says
exactly Tara says I like her humor too
oh my God Uma says love comedy skits
I'll try to do more and then Diana says
be quiet Jennifer
okay and Jennifer hoden says he's doing
a great thing for the world you guys you
guys are incredible
all right as long as I'm not doing dog
waiting for a bone
right now that's good that one's really
funny Christine says why is something so
essential for your health like lemons
have to taste so bad for some people
they're sour for some people Michelle L
they are too accurate because it's
really how it is
well the thing is you know the skits are
actually filled with information details
and stuff and I do some of these skits
in the podcast episodes so if you
haven't listened to Medical meme podcast
at Apple podcast you guys
if you listen to the information anybody
who's worried about like my comedy
aspect you're like oh he's going to lose
credibility or something like that
listen to the information you know but
look
the books are the number one
best-selling books Health books in the
world right now you know because people
are healing and it's critical I think we
could have a little fun too
um
Leia Collins says bet he's good with
kids oh bless your heart Chanel says the
humor skits props make me want to tune
in even more learning a lot well I got a
lot of killer food right here too right
now you know what kind of flavor and ice
cream do you guys like anyway do you
guys like vanilla or do you guys like
what is your favorite vanilla chocolate
strawberry or this green kind
foreign
what's the green ice cream cone that's
what I want to know is it like mint or
something is it like what is it lime
key lime
see you guys
check out the podcast episode when you
get a chance Michael scoots Michael
scoots in the house it's like that Robin
Williams movie where he plays the funny
entertaining doctor only Anthony and
spirit actually help people heal love
you brother love you brother
you guys are awesome see you guys
when it comes down to our teeth I take
teeth seriously man Cara parent says
some of us have been isolated for years
unable to work and had multiple
treatments shoved down their throat from
the wrong people I know I love having a
little chuckle when the process to
Healing gets tough you know look my
heart pours out to you by the way and
that's the whole point is I want to make
sure I I help in any way you guys know
what mattress service I am that's your
service you guys know that you guys know
Jala says I like your humor too you are
fun yay you guys are incredible so
when it comes down to teeth I just want
to drop a few things on you guys real
quick here right
the reason why like medical medium
information uses like leafy greens
and I know everybody gets all burned up
about this but the health movement
wasn't about leafy greens years ago okay
and I was always leafy greens eat a
pound of spinach spinach soup medical
medium spinach soup and people like
iceberg lettuce
Professionals in the health field 25
years ago okay 30 years ago were like
iceberg lettuce was it when you said
lettuce or a salad right I was like no
you've got to have your kale Your
Spinach you've got to have your
different lettuces your wild lettuces
you have to have all the heirloom
lettuces you have to have you know all
of it your mosh like all the different
grits arugula is critical that's where
you get those alkaline
alkaline trace minerals to buffer the
acidity
teeth all fall apart
because we're so acidic in Mineral
deficient
that our immune system can't even
protect our mouth
to stop gum disease
and to stop bacteria from eating away
our teeth right there's people they go
to the dentist they get their teeth
cleaned they got their teeth all taken
care of constantly they're seeing their
dentist once a month well every two
months they're brushing they're flossing
and their teeth are just totally shot
right
because it's healing deep inside we're
talking about Yvette Hopkins says love
your humor honor thank you for being
here by the way I'm honored you're here
truly
I am indeed honored I'm energy here
this is a glass of wine it's a thousand
dollars a glass
I think that's quite the right price
I'm I'm in Napa Valley
this wine is 52 000 a glass
and go by the vineyard
honored you guys are here
all right
when we do lives later in the day I
think the humor comes out more if we
were doing alive and it was like one
o'clock in the morning I think it would
be probably the craziest live you've
ever seen so
thank God we don't do lives at 1am
because I think you got I think I would
all probably lose all you guys like what
is he saying now
Denise is so lemon water is key to our
oral health yes it is Denise it's really
important
lemon water
it's about calcium so just look
the calcium in lemons a whole nother
ball game okay calcium and lemon whole
nother ball game I'm going to tell you
right now
that's the calcium that goes into the
teeth it's this right here okay very
important calcium and leafy greens too
but especially like the lemons
so we're getting that calcium and we're
neutralizing acid
so a lemon which seems sour and acidic
right you think it's hurting your teeth
but what it's doing it's making your
body alkaline so you can save your teeth
that's how it works critical
Kelsey Bach I've regrew my receding gums
Kelsey good to see you didn't you get
rid of 50 symptoms too
I think like 50 symptoms or 54 symptoms
too listen to the lemon water podcast
when you guys get a chance
you know definitely
shell says my daughter won't drink it if
there's lemon in it it's one drop at a
time put a tiny drop
Carolina a doctor told my sister to
drink red wine because she is anemic
dear Lord
terrible I mean listen to the doctor of
course doc doctor's always right listen
to your doctors I I want you guys to
listen to your doctors but man I would
never offer that to like a doctor friend
or a family member
um that's you know it's that's that's
the whole point that's why my advice is
in the skits it's in the wine skits I
think you'll have some red wine I think
he's gonna help my anemia
I'm gonna have a bottle of red wine
tonight I think it's gonna help my
anemia quite right yeah
Liza
Alicia sorry what's the difference in
eating alkaline foods versus drinking
alkaline water let's go into that now
if it's spring water
that's naturally alkaline amazing
if it's the alkaline ionizer water
machines
run for your life
run for your life okay
alkaline ionizer water machines
I can't say enough things about why not
to do that right I've talked about it
I've been hammered by the alkaline
ionizer water uh Ponzi scheme pyramid
schemers out there I've seen it I've but
I've seen what it's done to people over
the years the plates rust and nobody
sees it you get particles of metal it's
a scary as crap so yeah anyway that's
different than natural occurring
alkaline water much different than that
it's a whole other story
yep our roses alkaline water is terrible
full of heavy metals yes indeed meaning
like the machines the ones that produce
it like like alter the water
Frankenstein the water that's terrifying
actually just so you know terrifying so
that's important to know
helps with Liz what you're live again
yeah I'm here again good to see you
I had I had to like I had to get back in
into the game here I want people's teeth
better
I want their teeth better I go to bed
tonight and I'm like did I do good
enough today when I get into bed and I'm
laying there I'm gonna be like did I try
hard enough to get people to listen to
the episode the free episode on the
podcast
did I try hard enough to get them there
so they can protect themselves and then
I feel like you know did I try hard
enough and I'm like I better try harder
Hannah I had generalized gum recession
with over 100 symptoms after Botox
poisoning oh and I am healing myself
with protocols only for the last two
years he actually saved my life
had I not had this info life-saving info
I would be dead by now oh my God Hannah
breaks my heart first of all just breaks
my heart to know you've gone through
that going through all that that you've
been through thank God you're healing
thank God you're doing the protocols
bless your heart bless your heart and it
says thanks aw and SOC give an SOC
Credit Credit words too for sure I
wouldn't know this information I
wouldn't know it if it wasn't for SOC
that's why it's all original unique
information you guys know medical medium
info is not stolen from some paper
somewhere or whatever it's all original
it's all unique and then taken from
there out to the health world and health
World poaches it in bits and pieces
Susan you're working hard today when
will we hear about the new book
where's the buzzer
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding he
said the magic word ding ding ding you
guys did you pre-order
because
there ain't gonna be any copies to go
around once the book's released soon so
pretty soon it's going to be released if
you don't have your pre-ordered brain
saver books both the protocol and brain
saver
he may not get it for a long time okay
anyway and the and amazon.com right now
that's where they are brain saver and
brand saver protocols two books at the
same time I was told I was the only
author that did two books at the same
time in this on this on this scale they
said you just always break the rules
Sue Goldberg says why do children's
teeth sometimes come in and I just enter
discolored slightly hello because of
deficiencies deficiencies from the past
toxins that are passed down from Mom and
Dad yes both the husband too or father
and both the the mom both parents so the
toxins are passed down things like DDT
and different pesticides toxic heavy
metals and usually with kids it's it's
toxic heavy metals that are passed down
if you guys don't have the brain saver
books both of them there's two of them
pre-ordered you might want to take a
look at amazon.com look for brain saver
look for both books there's two separate
pages on Amazon
Sean Paul says isn't isn't that just
genetics passing down toxins
uh no it's not genetics aren't passing
down toxins
um but we pass down toxins physically so
yeah in utero sperm and egg toxins
that's how it's done
yep
so pretty cool you guys I'm glad you
mentioned the books I know I haven't
been talking about the brain saver books
but I want to it's just that I wanted to
get the podcast up and running the
season right look they want to blame
everything on genetics that's how they
do it because it's an easy sell right
such an easy sell if you look like
your parents or look like your relatives
then it's like an easy sell it's got to
be genes everything's genes right but we
passed down generation after generation
viruses Epstein-Barr toxic heavy metals
different viruses different pathogens
right
so and we're and all this is passed down
from generation to generation sometimes
a family can be exposed to all the same
stuff so they all get sick with similar
things as time goes on because they were
exposed to all these different things
right
so that's important to know
so yeah anyway you guys you guys know I
care about you greatly I'm gonna have my
bowl of sugar if you don't mind because
what I do is you guys I'll tell you how
the medical media meets okay he doesn't
eat all this all right medical medium
eats a whole giant bowl of brown sugar
six times a day
I don't I'm only kidding I don't and
neither does anybody else
but what people do
is they
all the fats and the additives and the
chemicals with the sugar and it's all
that acidic fat and everything else you
can be a healthy vegan person like
you're into health and you're like hey
I'm vegan I'm into health I'm doing my
nut proteins I'm doing keto vegan I got
no processed foods and your teeth can
still fall out and guess what the
dentist would be like it was because
you're vegan it wasn't because you're
vegan it's because everybody's focused
on too many fats too many proteins and
they have too many deficiencies and
they're not fixing them and they're not
getting those alkaline minerals in
they're not getting the celery juice in
they're not getting heavy metal detox
smoothie in they're not getting the
stuff in they need they're not getting
the chemicals and the metals and the
pathogens out of their body they could
be a vegan a vegan dude a vegan gal
whatever and boom they're sick now
they're 32 years old and they're getting
sick teeth are going bad it's just
people don't get same thing with animal
protein people the same thing I'm not
taking sides
Dior says dentists said that I had two
cavities on my upper teeth I told them
to wait two months before I get the
X-ray
for two months every time I drank my
celery juice I held it in my mouth for a
while which is an incredible
um piece of information and them we love
that when I got my x-ray it didn't show
the cavities he mentioned from two
months ago
oh my God
now you see it now you don't
Yvette says can't wait to get my brain
saver books yay
you're amazing Austin good to see you
you're amazing Austin says all this food
looks like a heart attack waiting to
happen yes
I think I'm gonna have a I don't have a
heart attack bite right here
Austin would you like would you like to
share this cake with me
Austin me and you will sit down I'll
take half you take half right
we just won't tell anybody just keep it
a secret
I can do that
you guys newsletter weekly videos
newsletter right and what I do on the
Weekly Newsletter videos every week I do
an exclusive video on the medical medium
newsletter go to medicalmedium.com sign
up to the newsletter plus you'll get
notifications when my next podcast is
coming out hey guys coming out with a
new podcast episode next week and you
got to get ready for the ride because
that's going to be an insane One Cloud
swoop says my son gets canker sores from
oranges any ideas
when I've noticed what happens is that
okay if you have the canker sore virus
right
it doesn't like to be killed off
so it doesn't like to be killed off and
fruit will start killing off canker sore
virus canker sore viruses is in the
herpetic family right that means it's
already in your mouth okay so what I
would do
is um you can ask your doctor but would
I would I tell friends all the time
right
is um is a couple of things celery juice
is critical because it kills off as well
all right another thing it's like what I
would tell a friend is they're gluten in
the diet
because if there's gluten in the diet
then the canker sores could happen no
matter what and then if you are eating
an orange
you think it's the orange if you are
eating a banana and you think it's a
banana if you are eating
avocado you think it's an avocado but
the point is is there gluten in the diet
ever is there dairy in the diet ever
this is what I ask friends
when their kids have canker sores is
their gluten dairy corn corn gluten
dairy soy milk cheese butter eggs if any
of that's in the diet it feeds the
canker sore virus the repetitive canker
sore virus so it's a crap shoot whatever
you're eating it's just gonna break out
when it's going to break out that's what
I tell a lot of doctor friends and also
friends and family members
so yeah anyway you guys listen
keep a light heart know that I care I'm
really proud of all you guys so much so
really and um get a chance to listen to
okay yeah Uma Cali says alien podcast
Uma
I got a big surprise
it's not going to be next week it's
going to be an incredible podcast next
week coming out but I and really
considering doing the alien podcast
episode
I'm already on it
all right you guys
hear about you much check out the teeth
episode when you get a chance bless your
heart take care of you guys