it's not therapy plus challenge
for day two how are you guys feeling
we did day one food fear shifters day
two
pathogen exposure shot
[Music]
and we're here and we're live
and these aren't pre-recorded they're
not
pre-recorded pathogen exposure shot
right here
amazing you guys I'm excited about it
brain saber that's what it's from
are you are you guys bumped up
someone says is your diet alkaline
is it alkaline
what diet who's diet medical meme
information is it alkaline medical
medium info is alkaline for sure
you're seeing celery you see herbs you
see asparagus you see brussels sprouts
just right here that alone is alkaline
anyway all right pathogen exposure
here we are this shot can be useful if
you feel you've been around others who
could be contagious due to covet flu RSV
whatever right
you're concerned about having shared
bodily fluids with another person
through shared glasses
a drink
hey I'll take that bottle oh wait whose
bottle was that
so if you're worried about anything like
that too but it's even better than that
too
you're concerned about having shared
bodily fluids through public restrooms
you sit on the toilet seat I'm gonna
read about that in a little bit too you
believe you might have been exposed to
foodborne pathogens and you're concerned
about getting food poisoning you're
eating in a restaurant you're like huh
oh crap I better just do the pathogen
exposure shot later
incredible see guys brain saver word day
two of the medical medium brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge I'm excited
all right I got my ingredients right
here so let's talk about it a little bit
I'm gonna go to page
195.
you guys get your books
okay
all right so I want to read a little bit
if you guys have a second here everybody
coming on this is the medical mean brain
shot therapy cleanse challenge by the
way if you haven't signed up sign up get
your free
grocery shopping list but you got to
sign up go to medicalme.com
and make sure because you can get the
emails that are specifically for this
cleanse challenge all of it so it says
day one through twenty these are the
brain shots we're doing a 20-day Branch
out therapy cleanse challenge call me
crazy
because it's a 20-day cleanse right
where we're doing it this is incredible
and it's day two if you come in here at
day 10 and you want to start then start
you come here at day four then start
then you come here at day two like today
start today start tomorrow either way
we're doing it
people have to realize there are bodily
fluids left on toilet seats
those people don't realize that I know
people that don't even think that they
don't think bodily fluids are on toilet
seats
those bodily fluids can contain
varieties of streptococcus they always
contain varieties of streptococcus
really many strains of which are
antibiotic resistant
definitely E coli
staff
herpes simplex 1 Herpes Simplex 2 are
always on toilet seats public restrooms
Epstein-Barr yes Epstein-Barr can be on
a toilet seat there are shingles hhv6
cytomegalovirus CMV
and HPV can be on a toilet seat that
means that these bugs can be on toilet
seats surfaces and usually are
indeed they truly usually are so public
restrooms that is what is on there
they're covering toilet seats
so this is critical flopping down
straight onto a public toilet seat is
not a wise practice
if there's anything to take away if it's
just one thing and that's all
just one thing to take away from meta
from volumes of medical medium
information
if you want to throw away everything and
take one one thing with you let it be
flopping down straight onto a public
toilet seat is not a wise practice
then there's then there's the toilet
water in the bowl
even if the toilet was flushed but
toilets never truly flush
pretty crazy isn't that there's always
invisible leftover material floating
around in the toilet water
and as you go to the bathroom why do I
think that's funny that's not a funny
thing but why am I laughing here
if you if you go
and as you go to the bathroom
splashes from the water can pop up back
into you okay
it's very easy to get infected in
restrooms because when you're going to
the bathroom you're exposed
for example when someone is having a
bowel movement their rectum doesn't
immediately close
these are really good books these brain
saver books are mind-blowing
as their fecal matter Torpedoes into the
water
it's very easy for that water to Splash
up and enter into the rectum as the
rectum is still closing you guys were
day two of the medical medium brain shot
therapy challenge okay and we're going
to be doing 20 days if you just got on
here reading out a brain saver all right
so I'm excited about this is good
information to be talking about we're
just talking about pathogen exposure
shock maybe you weren't on a public
restroom recently but there's other
reasons through the pathogen exposure
shot it's really a powerful healing shot
in so many ways
before you poo
it's best to place a sheet or two of
toilet paper on the surface of the water
to mitigate splash
this might sound ridiculous for a second
but it's not
how many people don't realize how many
bugs they contract sitting on a public
restroom toilet
dropping a poo in the toilet and then it
sends water right up into the rectum
before the rectum closes
and now they have a brand new
streptococcus one that's antibiotic
resistant that some other person had in
their body because they took 20
billion antibiotics in the course of
their lifetime the kind of mitigate and
keep that
streptococcus under control as it gave
size and sore throats and UTIs and
bladder infections and kidney infections
and
and acne and acne yeah because acne
streptococcus that's what acne is it's
not hormones it's streptococcus
so it's best to place a sheet or two of
toilet paper on the surface of the water
to mitigate splash
because it stops the splash
to protect yourself further it's
important to flush a public toilet
before you even use it if you go into a
public restroom flush the toilet before
you use it
if it's a urinal urinal
you don't want to flush that one I'm
talking about a toilet
not one of those you know urinals right
those when you hit that when you hit
that that thing right splashes
everybody's urine all you know other
guys urine right on you right
but I'm talking about the toilet
it's important to flush a public toilet
before you even use it if it has a lid
put the lid down before flushing it so
when you're in a public bathroom put the
lid down before flushing it
foreign
did you guys expect we'd be talking
about this today at all on day two of
the medical beam breaks out there be
quench challenge
you flush with your foot I just saw
other way otherwise try to turn away or
back away while it's Flushing
I'm on page 195 of the brain saver book
the Mist can project outward with
viruses or bacteria in it so you want to
shut the lid of the toilet
you never want to keep the lid of a
toilet open on a plane
before you flush it
because when you're on a plane if you
don't shut that lid it literally
will shoot up right into your face
if there's a lid laugh out loud then you
got to turn around Jackie B gotta turn
around away like I was just reading
liziam says this is the manual we needed
when we were born
Erica Malik says so many don't have lids
I know
many people won't use enough toilet
paper to wipe
don't use like one sheet
so they'll use one sheet fine I totally
get it but
one sheet right they use a few tiny
sheets perhaps in the name of saving
trees or if they're in the habit of
using less to save money of course or
they just miss the target
they end up with a handful of feces so
what happens when people go to bathroom
they usually 95 of the people have a
handful of the feces of course
that hand will then flush the toilet
so we're talking about the toilet handle
now you guys if you're talking about
there's another handle so someone just
went to the bathroom they wiped their
ass with a couple of sheets they got
feces on their hand and now they're
flushing the toilet right
because not every place is automatic
flush
that hand will then flush a toilet
toilet if it's not automated
it's not automated
then that hand will touch the soap
dispenser and this it's Spencer and the
sink handles
leaving behind more feces particles and
then after they wash their hands they'll
touch the dirty handles again to shut
off the sink
so it's like you turn the sink on you
have feces on your hand you're washing
your hands
the feces is on the handles and then
you're done washing your hands and then
you shut the handles off again you shut
the handle off again and you got feces
back on your hand tear Appleman says the
toilets are flush while you're sitting
on them
yeah that's that's a tough one
all right
even if
their own hands are clean they're
touching handles that other people have
touched those other people could have
touched their eyes
blown their nose
or just touched their face while
applying makeup in the bathroom mirror
then as everyone exits the bathroom
they're touching the spot on the door
everyone else has put their hands on
what I try to do in the public restroom
is I look for any other spot to open the
door if I can a spot that I don't think
someone touched and I'll even ask Spirit
of compassion nobody
anybody touch the bottom of the handle
and spirit confession to say a whole
bunch of people use the bottom of the
handle
hand sanitizer does not stop all of
these hand body exposures it's it's a
noble idea
partially helpful sometimes and yet hand
sanitizer is random in its ability to
kill pathogens it's not good enough we
have to be careful about how we use
public facilities to stay mind hold that
pathogen transmission is common in
restrooms
that's one of the biggest places that
pathogen transmission occurs it's in the
restrooms anyway we're talking about the
pathogen exposure shot this is day two
of the medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge
I got brain Saver in my hand do you have
brain saver do you have brain saver
protocols two incredible books
amazon.com us on sale right now which is
incredible all on its own
you guys I got ingredients in front of
me we're doing the exposure shot pretty
soon and I'm excited about that you have
your ingredients by the way and have you
signed up to the cleanse challenge the
brain shot therapy challenge so I just
want to remind everybody so
sharing food and drink and dining out
be mindful of sharing food and drink
you're also sharing saliva sometimes
even microscopic blood particles
sometimes we share food and drink
knowingly as when we eat off the same
plate or drink out of the same bottle or
glass sometimes we share with other
people unknowingly
restaurants do not usually clean their
glasses properly there tends to be
residue on all the glasses
lipstick residue for example tends to
hold on to pathogens on glasses so
that's just people don't realize the
restaurants and bars they don't wash
those glasses good
lipstick could sit residue on the
glasses just over and over again
lipstick encapsulates pathogens protects
them like a waxy protective cover
keeping the bugs sustained on the
glasses for days
so if you're drinking your glass at the
restaurant lipstick is
holding
and harboring
leftover lipstick on the glasses you
can't even see the leftover lipstick
it's not like see me read a perfect red
print like red lipstick like
it's print on there
check this one out
see if this sounds appetizing
Benny Jen says bars rinse their glasses
a rinse isn't good enough
that's for sure
that would not make me feel confident if
I was in a bar we rinsed our glasses
great all right
um by the way you just touched the glass
from the inside of the glass as you've
got it ready in hand and filled it up
thank you for doing that bartender thank
you for putting your hands inside my
glass
God knows what was on your hands when
you just went to the bathroom is there a
feces on your hands because it's now
inside my glass at the bar
foreign
sounds appetizing okay you guys
many men
have extremely sticky saliva
barf
right I don't know is it does that make
you like does that make when I heard
that from spiritual compassion like how
would how would anybody know that
there's no science on that there's no
report on that there's no study on that
sort of capacity told me that men have
really sticky saliva and when I heard
that I was like we do like what what do
you mean we have sticky saliva I was
like
foreign
many men have sticky extremely sticky
saliva because men often go around
chronically dehydrated
eating protein heavy diets
and protein is extremely sticky
and proteins are extremely sticky Foods
higher protein diets tend to make saliva
very very gluey
men's saliva can sit on glasses for a
week after multiple Washings
hey but the bartender just rinsed the
glass out that's good enough for me
thank you bartender for rinsing out that
glass
you put your hands inside that glass too
when you gave it to me thank you
all right you guys if anybody just came
on here we're day two the medical mean
Branch out there be cleanse challenge
okay
Forks in restaurants oh my God
Forks
dude
Forks in restaurants just like Forks at
home create small injuries in the mouth
small injuries in the mouth
unnoticeable
the steel in Forks is porous
metal forks stick into the person's gums
dislodging tiny bits of plaque and gum
bacteria
this is why I don't use forks in a
restaurant
Olga says even a dishwasher can't rid of
that no way people's lipstick gluey
saliva in in restaurants
notoriously two in restaurants that
stuff doesn't leave those glasses easy
me too 787 on YouTube good to see you
the hot water would often run out when
it was busy at the restaurant I worked
at uh-huh and I've heard that a billion
times by the way but dishes were still
being washed correctamundo
I've totally seen that I've heard that
so many times too
me too that was good thank you
metal forks sticking to the person's
gums dislodging tiny bits of plaque and
gum bacteria
compressing it into the pores of the
fork
you know that right that that's
plaque and skin flakes inside the mouth
skin cells being pressed into the fork
the porous parts of the fork so the
pores in the silverware get clogged up
with cells from the inside of people's
mouths including micro amounts of blood
restaurant
Forks okay
filled with all of that
Forks in restaurants can be biohazards
nobody knew that
watch it be talked about now out there
well poached once again for the medical
meeting books and not cited
they're not sterilized as if you were at
the dentist's office at the dentist's
office before they stick metal in your
mouth you guys they have to put it in
the sterilization machine or open up a
brand new one
they're not doing that at the restaurant
they're not sterilized as if you were at
the dentist's office where a sterilized
tool goes in your mouth even if it's
just poking around on a tooth let me
look here
okay Jessica let's just take a look yep
yep poking in here does that hurt oh
instead eating with bar or restaurant
silverware is like going to the dental
office where they take all their dental
tools and wash them by hand or throw
them in a common dishwasher would you
like the dentist to just take all their
dental tools and put it in a common
dishwasher
don't worry
um assistant
um Dental nurse hygienist nurse
hygienist can you go back at the
dishwasher back there and can you get
all the dental tools out we ran it on
clean
cycle whatever rinse rinse cycle
as is mind-blowing my mind is blown my
mind was blown when Spirit of compassion
gave me the info to begin with I was
like what
I mean I've known some of it that Spirit
of passion has given to me why I go to
restaurants and stuff but when I really
think about the details around it too
it's been insane
because most dishwashers do not get hot
enough to kill pathogens that's another
thing dishwashers in restaurants aren't
hot enough to kill pathogens you gotta
have some serious Heat
before putting them in your mouth or the
next patient
that's why I say that utensils in
restaurants can be biohazards
potentially spreading every pathogen and
disease
and for years I've said that busy chefs
oh I know chefs hate me too
everybody hates me now it's been
building up for years
leaving chefs hate me now and for years
I've said that busy chefs in busy
restaurants often cut their hands and
fingers daily
which is Russian Roulette
for transmitting any kind of pathogen
oh
thought I saw a comment it is brain
saver
someone's asking I'm reading out a brain
saver amazon.com us
it's on sale right now there at Amazon
and brings different protocols make sure
you have them
that means you don't know we're doing
the brainchild therapy cleanse Challenge
and where it comes from comes from the
brain saver book so we're doing the
pathogen exposure job
here are some tips if you have to eat
out so if you're something you have to
eat out here are some tips get ready for
them bring alcohol wipes and wipe your
forks and other utensils it's not a
guarantee but it's definitely something
or ask for a mug get this one this is
what I have always done get ready for
this one
when I'm at a restaurant I'll say can I
have a mug of scalding hot water
like you know for tea
and then I place my utensils in that so
they bring a mug of scalding hot water
lake for tea
and then I'll take my fork in the
restaurant plop that in there like that
and just let it sit there for a while
is that not the coolest or what that's
the coolest
people want to know what the medical
medium does
here's one right here ready
alternatively bring your own utensils or
order food that doesn't require utensils
and eat with your hands
but you got to be careful though where
were your hands were they opening up the
restaurant door like yeah I'm coming in
to eat boom grab the restaurant door
you've got strep covet RSV flu all in
your hands now lupus free with celery
three through three my friend owns
restaurants and she said when the
utensils are still dry so sorry she said
when the utensils are still dirty after
the washer they just dip in water and
wipe them
now I believe it
so alternatively you could bring your
own utensils which I've done but I do
you know
like to put the utensils in a hot you
know mug of water there too if I can
or I'll order something that doesn't
require using utensils then I'll make
sure my hands are clean
ask for your food to go this is an
important tip right here if you're
eating out in restaurants you guys
seriously check this out this is just
incredible ask for your food to come
very hot
if the chef cut their finger while
preparing your meal or there's foodborne
pathogens on there too the heat of the
food and the plate is a great way to
kill viruses that may be in that blood
of the chef that got it on your food
if you're doing a raw dish then that's
not you know raw salad obviously you
can't throw it in heat you know in the
oven but ask for your food to come
really hot if you're ordering cooked
food
that's what I've done in a restaurant
because I worry about eating raw food in
a restaurant because I don't know if
chicken juices went and spilled on raw
chicken on my my lettuce
and I would also do the pathogen
exposure shot when you come home after
you ate at the restaurant and maybe even
before you go
how about this one
ask for beverages that come in bottles
that haven't been opened to avoid
drinking out of glasses I've done that
I've consumed beverages out of bottles
because I didn't want to drink out of
the glass I'd be like can you give me a
bottle
ready for this though
wipe off the top and the neck of the
bottle with an alcohol wipe before
drinking because then the bottle gets
brought to you
by a waiter
that has possibly 10 viruses and bugs
and bacteria and feces on their hands
because it's just going to happen and
then
or the waiter was grabbing everybody's
dirty dishes and forks and stuff like
that and then oh yeah I'll get you a
bottle would you like sparkling water
get you a bottle here it is
wipe off the top and neck of the bottle
with alcohol white before drinking gas
your lips May slip past the part of the
bottle that had been under the cap onto
the area where the server was touching
the bottle as They carried it because
you know when you drink the bottle your
lips might slap you know they might slip
past that top of the bottle
and you know hit the area that's
wherever contaminated
if bottles aren't an option ask for a
can
but then you're dealing with aluminum
but hey look you do the best you can
make sure you're doing the heavy metal
detox cleanses that are in these books
in which case try to wipe down the rim
and pour area of the can before opening
I understand you have to drink out of a
can for some situation I'm on board
whatever
not shaming anybody there's just ways of
doing it right to protect yourself
lesser evils
if you're forced to drink out of a glass
this is interesting
ask for a wrapped straw or bring your
own straw
if you can bring your own cup and glass
to the restaurant too
all right so let's talk about dental
visits for a couple of seconds pathogen
exposure shot here's a comment right
here on oh Miss Candy
it's people like you that cause Mass
hysteria about germs and not wanting to
get them and then staying in and never
leaving their homes really germs are
okay
ah you're one of those people
interesting
well first of all I would like to
respond to that comment very much so
so
if germs are okay
right what about all the people that
have lost your lives to germs was it
okay for them
what about all the elderly people that
were knocked off by covet
was germs okay for them in the moment
how many people died of covid
how many people die of the flu every
year was germs okay for them
I'm just wondering
well we can't ask them because they're
gone
so we can't call those people up and say
you were in a nursing home and they
weren't careful there
and covet ran through it
or you know
Kobe ran through your house and knocked
off your aunt
or your grandmother grandfather but we
can't ask them if germs were okay
with them we can't ask them it's really
ignorant ignorant thing you just said
you don't know the cause of chronic
illness
it's actually pathogens germs
so you got people that are better and
you got moms that can't get out of bed
to feed their children
you got teenagers that are suffering
with autoimmune right now because of
germs viruses and bacteria
but you're but you're really ignorant
about all of this and I'm not blaming
you
but you should probably learn something
here
and not be really
you know
dumb about it
awareness is actually the key of knowing
so you can keep precautions so if you're
somebody really suffering with chronic
illness right now and you had a hard
time in your life and you you already
have neurological fatigue because you're
dealing with a mystery illness because
you're dealing with like a virus like
Epstein-Barr giving you brain
inflammation and everything else like I
talk about the brain books you're
already suffering
you don't need more epstein-bars you
don't need more simplexes you don't need
more Simplex too you don't need more
anything you need more streptococcus if
you're already suffering with acne
because of strep
do you need more more germs do you need
more streptococcus because you can have
even worse acne I mean
you don't want you don't want to pick up
three different strips from using public
restrooms wrong knowing how to take
precautions and and how you know this
has your back protecting you so you
don't live a Lifetime on antibiotics
you pick up two more streptococcus off
of a toilet seat
and now you're gonna like more UTIs and
you're on antibiotics
is that a good thing so you really like
germs
that would probably be the stupidest
thing comment I've ever read in a long
time actually
someone of those people that make people
afraid of germs come on the darkness
wants you to be in the dark and not know
about any of these germs in any of these
bugs they don't the darkness doesn't
want you to protect yourself
classified medical research and Sciences
want you to protect yourself no one
wants you to protect yourself they want
you sick sick or sicker sicker do you
pay the price until you're gone bye they
just want you to go
so yeah
and if you're under that if you're under
that thought
if you're under that belief that germs
make you stronger oh really
oh they do they make you stronger
uh-huh
tell that to somebody who just got mono
and it beat the
crap out of them
it really makes you stronger and now
they got thyroid problems five years
later and now they've got fibromyalgia
five years later because if I've seen
bar oh that made them stronger
this information is so you can be aware
and know how to kill pathogens
that's what this is it's so you can use
your own free will to actually Empower
yourself and be like you know what I'm
not gonna be a sucker anymore and I'm
not going to be brainwashed anymore and
I'm going to have my Free Will and use
my Free Will and protect myself from
pathogens in the whole bit
so you can defend yourself because the
chronically ill they can't defend
themselves
it's hard
the system's not set up for them to do
that there are things we can do and be
smart about as we go along
our way things to protect ourselves with
so when someone says a comment like that
it just shows me how
really out of touch you are and also
you've never been sick yet
with chronic illness but when you get
chronic illness we'll see what you're
we'll see who's laughing down the road
then you'll be all upset
our Schroeder said I love how he reads
all comments either good or bad he's so
honest I try my best and I'm at your
service
and that's your service I'll even do a
curtsy Nicholas Russell says people
think germs strengthen their immune
systems oh really
really
that's why you know so many people are
dying right now that's unbelievable me
too 787 it's amazing that so many are
under the spell of more exposure makes
you stronger but stay away from Grandma
if you're sick exactly
contradictions
constant contradictions
that's what that is exactly
exactly
germs make you stronger let me go pick
up another Simplex herpes one cold sore
virus and now I got trigeminal neuralgia
I'm suffering and I'm on a whole bunch
of freaking oxies
how many people are literally on opioids
prescribed from their doctor because
their trigeminal neurologist making it
so they can't even live
because of herpes simplex one oh so let
me go and catch another and maybe two
more and not be aware
I mean I can go on all day but we're in
the brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
yep
MV Doom over there on YouTube so if
you're completely healthy you should
still be taking all the precautions yeah
of course
of course you should because guess what
no one stays completely healthy and by
the way no one is completely healthy now
in this day and age
everybody has something
gnawing at them
and yeah if you don't stay aware of it
you'll collect all these pathogens and
get sicker down the road
I don't know if anybody's watching the
world right now
but the drugstores have lines of people
sick like never before in our history
the medical industry
is like crashing hospitals are filled
with people
the world has changed everybody's
getting sick everybody's sick you might
be healthy right now strong and
everything's good
and if you don't take care of yourself
and know without what to look out for to
protect yourself boom
the scale is tipped Heidi Curtis says
I'd rather know the truth viruses were
making me super sick until I found
medical meme information I'm so grateful
it's critical to know the truth and then
because you've already been sick from
any kind of viruses you've already had
pathogen exposure in your life it's good
to actually know what to look out for so
you don't add to it sure somebody else
out there who's not sick enough yet or
they're not so sick and they're just
going to their acupuncturist for some
you know little bit of needles in their
back or they're going to get a massage
once a while or they go see their
routine doctor for a checkup
because they get a headache once every
six months those people we're gonna are
gonna get sick down the road too they're
not looking out for exposures they're
not looking into anything they're gonna
get sick later anyway because it happens
every day just because
you don't know about it and are not
aware of what's going on out there
doesn't mean it's not happening that's
where ignoring things bites you in the
butt
anyway
that was a good comment
all right so what else can I
what else can I read Dental visits let's
just run into Dental visits are you guys
interested in this part right here just
curious because I am I'm really
interested in this part right here okay
have you noticed I got all brand new
teeth
I had the dentist give me all brand new
teeth just like the podcast doctors no
they're all my teeth I don't have any
implants or anything and I'm not shaming
anybody for having implant
implant at all in your mouth that's not
it it's just that podcast doctors that
know everything about health don't have
their teeth out there
people don't realize that
all right Dental visits
Warehouse one on YouTube says
it's like I don't even get sick anymore
I do everything medical medium for two
years now it saved my life and continues
to do so every single day
incredible and with this information we
can protect yourself which is great and
look look
it's not about fear if you contract a
bug or a germ or RSV or covid or you
contract Epstein-Barr or shingles or
herpes simplex 1 whatever it is
you still want the information on how to
slam it
and and use your free will to break it
down that's why we're doing the exposure
the pathogen exposure shot right now
and bring the books to your doctor and
ask your doctor's advice on what to do
huh
that's your doctor what's right for you
Dental visits let's talk about
it for a little bit all right
the dentist's office is another place
where pathogens are transferred
often dentists hygienists and assistants
will put oh my God
will put on their gloves and then start
touching everything with their gloves
the dentist and the hygienist and the
the assistant at the dentist office is
wearing their gloves to protect them not
you
foreign oh thank God my dentist and his
sister thank God my thank God that
hygienist is wearing nitrile gloves phew
meanwhile the hygienist is grabbing this
boom grabbing that grabbing this in here
opening up drawers grabbing this and who
knows what's on the gloves right now and
then I was going in here like this
you know
after they had their hands in other
people's mouths too like all kinds of
different stuff like meaning and then
they're touching everything right now
they're touching all those surfaces
again of course it might take a little
handy wipe and go oh well I'll do the
light handle there I'll do this for a
second I'll do this for a second
and they don't even do that
they're touching the handles of the
lights adjusting them and also touching
chairs controls computer keyboards
computer keyboards yeah totally
in the end they're latex or nitrile
gloves are only protecting the
practitioner
dude not protecting the patient
drives me crazy corn EMA says I was a
dental assistant that's so true
bana says they keep saying that if you
get sick your immune system is getting
better I was sick as child very often
and I didn't miss sorry and I didn't see
any improvements in my immune system
it's just really just make believe when
they say that
the more germs the stronger you get
here's a cool Agostino on YouTube my dad
is a dentist and this is true
I believe you
yet the surfaces are touching with those
new gloves may have saliva blood is this
true
yet the services they're touching with
those new gloves may have saliva blood
and mouth tissue cells on them
and those surfaces have often not been
sterilized between patients
that's how pathogens can be transmitted
all right so let me read this next
little part if you guys got another
second
to avoid this situation bring your own
disinfecting wipes to the dentist and
ask them to wipe down high touch spots
such as controls buttons and handles
that they think they're going to use
during your procedure
and ask them to put on fresh gloves
afterwards so after they do all that
have them put on another set of gloves
you can't be afraid to ask your dentist
for better sanitary steps to be taken if
people learn to request this it will
become more common practice in the
dentist office
so I got some more tips here
let me go into a little bit more if you
guys are ready if you guys just got on
here we're doing the brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge we're in ex the
exposure shot which is awesome
you do have some power if you're aware
you can be empowered with this
information you do have some control you
can use your free will seriously you do
have power to make changes around you
and in your life
it's not about just walking around blind
with it all and being ignorant you know
like that person was ignorant about it
like oh he's just putting fear into
people are you kidding
but if you don't know you can't have the
power to protect yourself if you don't
know you can't Empower yourself you
gotta know these things so here's more
viral exposure tips
let's see
Wolfie says on YouTube oh my God this
happened to me I got such a bad
infection after smelling the gloves were
dirty
from previous person as they moved
towards my face I was paralyzed by shock
oh my God
oh man
okay let me read a little bit more if
you guys got a couple of minutes
thank you for your time and energy
because we're doing it 20 day
cleanse it's incredible
we've covered many of the basics of
viral transmission such as even intimate
contact and rest and group restrooms and
tips for how to protect yourself after
basic tip
another basic tip is to practice good
hygiene
like hand washing when you're been in
public spaces that's the thing
you get off out of an airport and you
get some place you want to wash your
hands
Susan Blanda says not Dental phobia get
sick after almost every visit
so it's not Dental phobia you actually
get sick after a revisit I can't tell
you how many people get sick
after a visit at the dental office
especially around flu season
which is now
you know be careful with shopping carts
too then they say medical medium
information didn't work
I started medical medium yeah I've been
doing it for like a month
I'm doing my celery juice I'm listening
to this crazy guy I'm doing medical
medium
yeah and then I got so sick
so sick
my stomach got sick I got a fever I was
so sick I was coughing during that
medical medium meanwhile they were at
the dentist's office picked up the flu
or stomach flu got sick
yeah
or yeah I started medical medium
and it was something else that got them
sick
foreign
you got to worry about shopping cart
handles I've always done that my whole
life you got to worry about shopping
cart handles
you got to clean a shopping cart handle
definitely with a handy wipe there's no
question this is long before covet
pre-all that
it's also important to stay aware when
handling objects we just brought into
our homes okay
I understand if you can do this if this
isn't an option
it just be fine but I want to read this
one thing about packages it's
interesting
okay packages can be a huge source of
transmission like the flu or covid or
strep or MRSA okay especially when
you're setting down packages so what I
do is when I get a new package that
comes there's a delivery a medical
medium book
right I don't take the package and throw
it on my kitchen counter you can but
just remember when you put that package
on the kitchen counter you probably want
to wipe off that kitchen counter space
because these packages have grease
underneath them and all kinds of
pathogens and stuff like that
foreign
says I've had around 10 Dental visits
during last year and after the last one
I did the brain shots and this was the
only time I didn't feel bad or sick
after the visit definitely doing this
again we're doing it now with this shot
we are together
putting that shot together I'm gonna do
it in a couple seconds with you guys
okay
you might not want to set packages that
just came in from UPS FedEx whatever the
UPS wherever it is USPS or wherever or
around the country around the world
you don't want to set the packages on a
cutting board
so my cutting board right here like I
won't put a package that just came in
the mail I won't just put it on my
cutting board
or my kitchen counter placing a new
package on a crib I've seen people they
place it on a crib or on a bed or a
couch I'm like well I wouldn't do it
that that way either
and then grabbing the package and then
you're rubbing your eye you know after
you grab the package you're rubbing your
eye
sure enough it's there's a good chance
nothing's gonna happen but what if it's
at one time
you know you're fixing your eye makeup
or you're moving your hair constantly
while in the middle of opening a package
wash your hands after handling packages
what I'm saying is when you get packages
fresh off you know like you just ordered
something and it came and you grabbed
your package and brought it in put it in
a spot where you don't think it's going
to be a you know a big exposure spot
like your cutting board or your bed
don't put the package on your bed put it
somewhere right and then wash your hands
after you've opened up the package
it's just it's good
find a designated area for your packages
that isn't a high exposure spot in your
home if you are not in a rush to open it
wait a day
unless it's a medical medium book then
wash your hands up here
a practice I call decanting the practice
you like wine decanting the wine
decanting the package
because packages can have people's mucus
and saliva the man especially during flu
season whoa
traces a fecal matter skin flakes or any
other bodily fluid fluids can be on the
packages if you like if they did DNA
testing on your packages when they come
in the mail or whatever delivery they
did DNA testing on there
they got to find DNA of all kinds of
stuff
Amanda says yes I had a client of mine
who worked for UPS delivery drivers pee
in jars in the car no bathroom breaks
the reason why they pee and I'm not
blaming them for peeing in the car in
the jar but it's true I've seen that out
there too now I'm not blaming anybody
for that because I get it if you're
trying to get packages done
it's holidays and you gotta pee
you're gonna pull out a jar
if you give a package three to five days
if you can't in your designated area
there will be lesser chance of being
exposed you know I mean you could
whatever
but wash your hands afterwards whatever
if you do open your package
so know that and take precursive
precautions with your packages learn
this information
here's the question right here
DYI Health says
okay
Simone and yet getting or sorry Simone
and yet people are getting sick he's
advising that we are aware
while we're there asking the hygienist
not to touch other things while they are
working in your mouth yeah
beyond all of this awareness about
exposures and sources you could limit
the damage a virus can do by making your
body an inhospitable place for viruses
how you can limit the other brain
betrayers in your life I talked about
that in here you're working on doing an
exposure shot right here all of it
anyway
and there's a quote at the bottom
there is a greater truth Underneath It
All
there are answers to why people feel the
way they do Anthony William medical
medium
all right you guys
what
let's get moving on we might have a
halftime coming up too anybody in the
mood for the robot I think I need to
wake up I think I need to wake up I'm
awake
I am awake
so I think we needed him I think we're
doing a halftime
foreign
you guys hear the robot
we're just getting started
let's go to page 520.
is what I would like to do
where is it here it is okay guys
all right we're in entry level is where
we're at
so entry level is like you can do
you can do the brain shots you can do a
10-day 20-day 30-day your choice the
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge is
a 20-day the branch out there be one
challenge is a hundred day
we're doing a 100-day brain shot therapy
cleanse Challenge 100 days in a row no I
can't do that I can't I can't do that
right now we're doing a 20 day is what
we're choosing okay drink one brain shot
per day you drink more if you want we
are customizing to add up to three shots
of this of you know
of some of these so you can do that some
brain shot each day of one of them all
right you can pick your brain shot and
you can do three of them if you would
like
you can pick one you want to do
I have the list of what we're doing
yesterday was food fear shifter today's
pathogen exposure tomorrow's nerve gut
acid stabilizer and the list goes on you
can pick the one you want to do and
that's fine too okay
your choice of which brain shot option
from day to day
okay optional incorporate as many other
medical medium tools and recipes as
desired that's why people be like hey
I'm doing the 369 can I still do the
brain shot yeah you still can do the
brain shot
try to drink a minimum of 50 ounces of
water throughout the day
that amount can include coconut water
lemon water be mindful not to drink the
water too close to drinking the brain
shot make sure you space them at least
to 15 to 30 minutes apart
what that means is after the brain shot
we're about to do don't take a gallon of
water and send it down
these are not just random ingredients
put together to make a delicious
delightful
juice
so let's talk about that for a second
so
these cleanses are imperative for what's
to come in this world oh but I'm not
allowed
don't talk about germs
I'm just putting germ fear out there now
don't talk about bad things in this
world
just do all the stupid we want it
doesn't matter
who cares it makes you stronger
these cleanses are impaired by being
sarcastic right these cleanses are
imperative for what's to come in this
world the onslaught of domestic chemical
warfare and the pathogens were up
against I'm on page 516 if you guys want
to read along
they're in our schools it's in our
institutions our society today has
reached catechismic proportions
you know they do when all the kids go
back to college before they go back to
college
they bomb
the dorms
with every single killer
rodenticides pesticides everything
herbicides everything
micro side like sides everything they
bomb all the dorms they're riddled in an
unbelievable level of insecticide
when you send your kid off to school
right
and these things get collected
throughout the years when you embark on
these cleanse options you're using your
free will and your intention to clean
and protect the organ that Harbors the
knowledge of the past present and soon
to be future of your life which is your
brain
and guess what your brain Harbors your
soul too and that's important to know
it Harbors your soul
we're not allowed to know that too
is your information police here
don't say that either
Enlightenment is not about being
all-knowing
Enlightenment is the freedom to be at
peace because you have full control over
what resides inside your brain
enlightenment
is not just about all knowing that's not
the answer Enlightenment is about having
control
and empowerment
since we don't have control about what
resides around us in the world because
you can't control the world you have
control about how you can protect
yourself
these cleanses purify your brain Temple
you are removing the poisons from your
brain that take away your Clarity your
intuitive psychic telepathic Clairvoyant
skills
start to surface when you do
the brain shot therapies and all the
healing
yeah
These Are Spiritual cleanses
this isn't just a physical one the
20-day brain shot challenge
is a spiritual cleanse too in
combination of a physical one
someone asked what a brain shot is
brain shot therapy
it's a therapy inside the brain saver
books
we're doing the 20-day brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge
thank you for asking pick up the book
free at the library or get it on sale
right now amazon.com us or anywhere else
these brain shots are incredible and I'm
going to make the brain shot so stick
around
so you can see it being made
the physical benefits are truly special
and Powerful
with the brain shot therapy cleanses you
embark on removing toxins and poisonous
chemicals from the brain that should
have never been there to begin with in
helping restore what should be in your
brain
these anti-pathogenic cleanses
pathogens we're doing the pathogen
exposure shot are designed for what we
deal with on a daily basis everything
from deficiencies to burnout to brain
acid to emotional brain injuries these
cleanses are designed to rid many
different symptoms and conditions from
our lives
seriously
incredible
all right
yeah I could get lost in this book
this book is so incredible and so
powerful
you guys
it's a medical medium brain shot
exposure shot let's do it pathogen
exposure
I'm gonna bring the juicer over
by the way the 1500 the 900 are on sale
right now
did you guys check out that telegram
message I left how incredible these
juicers are it's just amazing really
I leave audio messages on Telegram
so you should check that out when you
can
all right let's do this
this is the mm 1500 it's on sale right
now I call it the medicine machine the
medicine maker okay
get the mm-900 too
they have high compression
I endorsed these machines for a reason
because they're incredible they're cold
pressed masticating juicers
preserving nutrients but these squeeze
out
everything they can and that saves you
money
food costs are rising
and Rising no matter what you're eating
doesn't matter if it's processed food or
a vegetable
food costs are rising
right but when you're using a medicine
machine that's saving you money so it
pays for itself
it's incredible
it's because juicers don't squeeze
enough juice out and then after two
years most juicers when they break down
you can't get parts replaced 15-year
warranty on the 900 and the 1500
stinkfronto all right
see a mega mm-1500 Omega mm-900
just want you to know because people ask
every day and it makes me want to scream
because they ask like when is the juicer
going to be on sale which user do you
use you guys don't even know how many
DMS come through about your juicers
it's just really crazy all right so
let's start with some time
then knock a little time in here
by the way Omega has a new support group
for medical medium people who purchase
the 1500 or the 900s check it out they
got a like a phone number an email
we got a new support group
so I'm putting about six frigs in here
we go I got my time in here I posted it
on telegram by the way
let's put some Rosemary in here now
two sprigs of Rosemary
this is a serious serious exposure shot
aw in Europe they have trouble sourcing
green asparagus Depending on time of
year his white asparagus okay to use for
sure and now I'm kind of upset because I
don't know if I put white asparagus in
the brain saver book but yes it's okay
to use
and maybe I did put it in there I don't
know I just put Garlic in there so I put
thyme I put Rosemary I put Garlic in
there now I'm putting in asparagus next
now these are small
these ones so I'm going to put in
probably more than two this is two raw
medium asparagus Spears right
but these are like small so I'm gonna
pop in
a couple more they're like really tiny
and dried out
all right
next one is two raw brussels sprouts
really tiny brussels sprouts I've been
having a hard time getting the big ones
so I'm probably gonna pop in a little
bit like that's one right there
so I'm gonna have to put in four of
these because two of them are equal
one more
because they got brussels sprouts in it
like this
these are like that all right
one or two stalks of celery
uh one it's a one to two stalks of
celery
right
I'm gonna put two
pathogen exposure shot is one of my
favorite
it really is
okay here we go
Valerie says I always have frozen
asparagus in my freezer can I defrost
them and use them
yes you can
I had to wait for that answer from
Spirit of compassion
by the way when you ask a question
guess who's talking to me
Spirit of compassion
that's how it works
all right shutting this down
by the way with this juicer
when the pulp does come out
this is so dry this time it's like
coming out like dust
and that's where the money saved is at
which is incredible
it's not like the spinning basket ones
or the centrifuges and all those
they just they just Scorch the juice
because it's scorching literally
scorching it's brutalizing it's not cold
pressed
and on top of it
it's incredible how dry this comes out
it's unbelievable so the amount of juice
that's saved I think is in the profile
link is the description on the mm-900
and the mm-1500
all right I think that moment has come
let me get a shot glass
yeah this is exciting
thank you
how much that glass here
[Music]
are you guys doing this with me or am I
doing it alone
it's okay if I gotta do it alone what
you guys are doing this right now with
me too right
it's okay if you're watching and that's
all you're doing you're just watching
and that's fine too
[Music]
I'm digging that one
foreign
[Music]
Audrey Lynn says on time and rosemary
kind of remove the stems because it's
almost messed up my mm yes well you know
those are real thick stems
you got to be careful
right
there's there's stems that are not thick
but then there's the Woody Woody thick
stems like that one you can't run that
through a juicer you see that
that's the Woody stick one there and you
don't want to put this right here this
Rosemary stick look at that you don't
want to put that in there either those
are sticks you want to instead like do
the like little ones there that that are
kind of soft
all right I'm going to drink this
[Applause]
this one always has a bite to it
ingredients
but from above
the combination this is what hits me
right off the stop right when I first
sip it hits me right off the running
hmm
oh my God
you feel that on this one
right
[Music]
this is hard to go down
you're drinking your hands movement just
right now and that well that's good but
yeah I'm drinking this right now
oh my God I feel it you did it before
Melanie
[Music]
bartender give me another
senior says Hey w
do you keep the green celery ring in the
Omega 900 1500 juicers when making brain
shots I do yes
you can loosen the end cap a little if
you really needed to
you know but but yeah I keep my green
ring on I have my green ring on in here
I do I have it on in the mm-1500
it is in there
oh my God that was great I'm feeling it
I'm feeling it you feel that
that was a large clove of garlic in
there too it was a little larger
Cindy said I had to pluck my nose when
drinking this one oh yeah I totally
understand completely
you guys let me know how your
experiences are what's your experience
with the brain shot therapy cleanse
right
what's your experience with this shot
you're having right now let me know tag
at Medical medium hashtag medical medium
your reels your stories your posts so I
can see them but you have to hashtag
antagon medical medium both at the same
time
have you guys tried this brain shot
what did you feel when you did this
brain shot
what kind of results are you having
all of it whoo
that was really potent
oh and that makes sense though Spirit of
compassion wanted an exposure shot a
pathogen exposure shot that actually
worked okay and then that's why it is so
potent and so strong
Jackie if you said laugh out loud plug
in the nose helps oh yeah
that one was potent definitely potent
okay
okay you guys incredible this brain shot
pathogen exposure shot right there you
know where you can find it in the brain
shot in the brain saver books right here
we ran out of the brain saver book if
you want to know what we did today we
talked about all kinds of different
exposures incredible information
by the way there's cold and flu
protocols right here in the protocols
book and shock therapies cold and flu
protocols and shock Therapies in the
brain saver protocols look you need both
books because you want to learn and heal
and get the information you know you you
want and people keep on asking what book
is it what book is he reading these are
them so I have to show you guys I know
that you guys who have the book might
say oh no he's sharing the book again
but no people don't know
they don't know
where's Dr Nesbitt when you need them
Smith and pepper says Hey aw how do we
know how many times to take the shots
just it's in here in detail just just
took the speaking your truth shot today
hoping it works incredible
you guys I'm like I'm like feeling it
from that shot
like like everything just like my whole
Everything Changes
I start talking differently and
everything Kelly Burke says aw your
bartender give me another didn't sound
so convincing today
bartender
give me another
born Henry give me another
bartender
give me another
Center bartender
bartender
hey it's Marty give me another what'd
you say
yeah yeah
all right
try to be as convincing as possible
okay you guys how are we gonna do this
there's 18 more days to go
like
what wait there's 18 more shots to do
there's 18 more
shots we're doing do I have to say it
again I'll say one more time I'm saying
there's 18 more shots
how are we gonna do this
like what and it's free
by the way the brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge is challenge is five
thousand dollars to join no it's not
it's not five thousand dollars to join
this is a free
challenge
free free free 18 more shots to go
and I am pumped up
heal infertility says great live
amazing
you guys I can't wait
I'm feeling it
I'm making another one liter and then
I'm making another one tonight that's
what I'm doing you could do one you
could do three of them you could do one
you could do two of them
you don't have to do any of them just be
here
and we'll have some fun
that's it aw is tipsy
bartender
bring me five more
I love you guys
I'll see you tomorrow
same time
same place
you guys know I care