we're live right now we're live on
facebook live on youtube
live on tick tock live on clubhouse and
i'm going to tell you guys something
with the gut health thing that's going
on out there there's some key things to
know right off the running i'm going to
give them to you okay
first of all good bacteria does not
battle with bad bacteria good bacteria
doesn't
fight bad bacteria bad bacteria
stays bad and it stays in you and it
doesn't leave
unless you do something to get it out
actively get it out right
so but what everybody's being told
is you gotta up your good bacteria your
good microorganisms your good bacteria
get all that good bacteria in there
but that has nothing to do
with what bad stuff is happening inside
of you
you can have all the good bacteria you
want and you can still pick up more
bad bacteria doesn't matter you can be
filled with good bacteria filled with
good microorganisms you guys
and it doesn't change one thing did you
pick up a new bad bacteria did you pick
up a new strap
streptococcus did you pick up more staff
did you pick up a new e coli eating in a
restaurant
did you pick up c diff somewhere
right did you kiss somebody and now you
got a new strep
and what happens and what people don't
realize
is that we collect this bad bacteria
yeah
and we can get problems inside our gut
yeah and we can get sick over time
but you can play around with all the
good stuff all you want good bacteria
good microorganisms good this good that
it's not going to change a thing it just
isn't
what it is going to change though it's
going to make the empires
rich the health empires rich
it's gonna make all the influencers
or health pros or podcast doctors
rich because it's an age-old
trick an age-old trick that's been
happening for a long time
and it's oh it's all in your gut that's
the problem
you got to get more microorganisms in
there you got
you got to you know this is what you
have to do and
it's an easy like trick it's an easy
psych out
it really is but until you learn
how to kill off the bad until you learn
what that takes or what that entails and
how exposure of getting
new bad stuff inside of you of how to
limit your exposure to
or at least be kicking out the bad stuff
for real
killing off the bad stuff real until you
go there
it ain't gonna matter and that's how it
works and so
right there so that bad bacteria i'm
just saying
right a bad bacteria we're live on tick
tock live on
youtube live on facebook live on
clubhouse
not bad bacteria doesn't care about the
good bacteria
the good microorganisms doesn't care
they don't
battle each other you see that you guys
they
don't fight each other it's not like the
bad bacteria is like whoa i'm going to
go and kill off some more
good bacteria let me go kill them off
let me go do that and it's not like the
good bacteria is going to go
hey i'm going to go attack that scare
away that bad bacteria and make sure
that bad bacteria runs
scare it away doesn't work like that but
see
it's an easy psych out good to see you
guys coming on
really really excited that that we're
here right now okay
just want to give you the rundown all
right um
i'm juicing some celery i'm talking
about what the celery does inside your
gut
how it's killing off the bad stuff
the bad stuff right
it's leaving the good stuff killing off
the bad
stuff really important to know because
bad bacteria runs
on a different charge and celery juice
destroys bad bacteria right
celery juice doesn't destroy good
bacteria
because it runs on a different charge
they don't battle each other they don't
fight each other
but you gotta learn how to get the bad
out it's not about how much good
you get in unless it's elevated biotics
and we'll talk about that in a minute
too
you guys we're live on facebook we're
live on youtube
live on clubhouse making some celery
juice
just so you know medical medium
book one new edition is
49 off at amazon.com us which
is which is psycho really because
when you think about it when you think
about it it
costs more to print the book costs more
to make the book it's 19
so i'm just saying if anybody didn't get
a chance or they don't have the book or
didn't get a chance yet
they got a chance now right and of
course you get it free at the library
too and i tell people all the time
the link is in the description right
there this is the new edition revised
and expanded
it's it's 49
off letting you guys know and like i
said you get it free at the library too
go to your library you want it you don't
want to pay for it go to your library
get it for free but right now it's
incredible really good to see you guys
coming on
so we're live right now it's the way we
like to do it i got my celery here
okay and i got something else what do i
have here
i have a head of lettuce
which i grew right so i'm gonna talk
about why this is important
okay so i grew this head of lettuce
right here okay i'm not saying i could
grow things good
that's not it at all because you know
you know you've got to pay attention to
your garden if you want to grow anything
and keep it growing you got to give it
that tlc right
that love and care but here's a head of
lettuce that i grew
okay and what i love about this head of
lettuce
is it's got elevated biotics on on it
okay so here's how it works
that's the good bacteria right there
okay
elevated biotics are on
this lettuce because it's in the garden
it's growing and millions of
microorganisms are
covered all over this head of lettuce
that's the good bacteria that gives us
something back
right there and even that bacteria
doesn't go into war and battle
with bad bacteria it doesn't but what it
does
is it goes down to your ilium which i'll
show you in a little bit
and these microorganisms they create
your b12 your own b12
right and i tell people everybody's
beaten down inside their guts
they've lost all their elevated biotics
they're good microorganisms that come
from this because they're not eating
out of their garden all the time because
face it we don't get those opportunities
we go to the store
by that time when you go to the store a
lot of time has passed
the elevated biotics are gone plus we
gotta wash our produce from the store
because you can have the plague on it
you can have anything on it the flu
viruses and everything else
but in the garden there's no washing it
you can give it a gentle
rinse a gentle rinse if you grow a
little parsley a gentle rinse
grow a little cilantro a gentle rinse
not even barely i mean i don't even
rinse the rosemary i pull out in my
garden
so it's loaded with elevated biotics
it's those elevated biotics those
that do things for us and that
is what science research is not up on
but what you're gonna see is all the
paid for
bs the trickery to sell you gut
products galore you guys are supposed to
be those suckers you're supposed to be
those people that they're just
they just dump all that stuff on they
got ads everywhere
campaigns everywhere everybody's selling
some probiotics some good bacteria so
and so some
microorganisms some fermented food and
that's what they do
and meanwhile it's just money spent
for some you you know there's nothing
wrong with spending money yeah
spend money spent you know spend money
build yourself a little
garden tray somewhere grow some sprouts
spend some money on some seeds right you
know
plant something if you live in apartment
building get a pot
get some soil grow a little bit of
parsley because when you pluck that
piece of parsley
off there you're you're getting you're
actually eating something that has the
elevated bio so this is important
information
that i'm giving you guys i'm gonna do a
little celery juicing right now
let's do that so and here's the thing
okay
bad bacteria right
bad microorganisms in your gut
are not the very thing though causing
all this crazy
inflammation necessarily right
so you can't you can't if you don't know
how to kill off your bad bacteria
though if you don't know how to kill it
off like that bacteria in your gut's not
giving you
tingles and numbness it's not giving you
fatigue
it's not giving you brain fog confusion
bad bacteria in your gut bad
microorganisms in your gut
is not giving you spasms and back pain
neck pain bad bacteria in your gut isn't
giving you
insomnia it's not giving you
vertigo so you have to know this like
everybody's walking around symptoms
they've got all kinds of stuff they got
brain fog they got vertigo they're dizzy
they don't feel good they got body pain
they got ringing in the ears they got
burning skin
jaw pain neck pain body pain back pain
like i said
that's not bad bacteria in your gut but
what to do is
doesn't matter what's wrong with you
keep on selling you those probiotics
keep on selling you all that good
bacteria
keep on selling you the fermented food
it won't fix any of that
you can eat all the fermented food you
ever dreamed of
while you got your fatigue while you got
your
lupus and cfs diagnosis and hashimoto's
thyroiditis
you know thyroiditis diagnosis you could
eat all the good bacteria you ever
dreamed of ever wanted to and it's not
going to fix any of that
has nothing to do with any of that you
can take your probiotics fermented foods
your gut products in it it's not going
to fix your
ra it's not going to fix your lupus your
aches and pains it's not going to fix
your neurological lyme
it's not you know how many lyme patients
were given probiotics all
through the like the early 2000s
just in all kinds of probiotics in them
this neurological line patients doesn't
fix it
it doesn't fix it important to know you
guys um
i'm juicing with the mm-900 hds the sale
is on for the juicer letting you guys
know okay
82 dollars off it's the one i use
and for me it's done nothing for me but
save me money
okay because that's what it is it's like
how can we save money
you know and this is one way to do it
and i'll tell you how it does it pays
for itself i use
half the celery than i ever used before
and i've used every juicer out there
and so you get the pulp comes out dry
you squeeze all the juice out of the
celery
and that's what i love about um
the mm-900 and that's what's incredible
so it's at
megajuicers.com i want to let you guys
know
i'm always asked what do i do what do i
do what i do and i try not to like talk
about it too much
but there is a sale on so it's like this
is the chance
to like let people know this is a chance
for people if they if you know they want
to break
it's 25 off
and it's like i'm telling my friends
everything
you know you get 82 off but it's the mm
900 hds
is the one that does the celery plus it
does everything else which is incredible
but it does the celery right
so running some celery now through it
which is it's just such a great such a
great juicer
so this is a medical tool that's how i
see it
it's a medical device and where things
are going you guys with everybody's
health
we're going to need everything we
possibly can
you know i tell people like every time a
new doctor reaches out to me
and wants to know medical medium
information and under
under my tutelage wants to be like look
teach me
every time a new doctor reaches out and
says you know anthony teach me because
no one has the record right now of of
that many people healing tens of
thousands of stories of debilitating
diseases
and so when a new doctor reaches out the
first thing i say
is you're going to have to juice you
know what a lot of them say to me
oh well you lost all the fiber you lost
all the fiber
that's not good juicing's bad because
you lost all the fiber the fibers where
it's at i'm like the fiber's not where
it's at
it's not you get plenty of fiber
you can get all the fiber you want and
you can still stay
sick there's people that have done
everything under the sun for their lyme
disease their ra their cfs or eczema
their psoriasis their vitiligo i don't
care what it is
they've done it they've done it
and they've eaten all the fiber plenty
of fiber
you know and so you'll get this
information that's not helpful
you guys were live on youtube live on
facebook live on tick tock live on
clubhouse
so you're gonna get plenty of fiber i'm
not saying
never eat a fruit and vegetable at the
same doctor
or doctors or a nutritionist or somebody
that would talk to me they would say
okay okay but what about what about
don't eat any fruit i'm like why are you
getting rid of fruit when there's your
fiber so here you are telling me don't
juice but you're telling me not to eat
any fruit
and this is where all the misconceptions
are out there there's so many
the fiber misconception so
what what i'm doing what you guys are
witnessing right now
you're witnessing an herbal extraction
that's what you're witnessing you're
witnessing a medical health tool
creating an herbal extraction
you see see the difference on what's
happening there so you're you're
witnessing
a medical health device and you're
an herbal extraction fiber
has nothing to do with what we're
trying to do besides you want that
pulp and fiber out of here just
like when you have a medicinal tea
you don't break open the tea bag
after you've had your tea and start
trying to
choke down that tea do you is that what
you guys do when you have your chamomile
tea
when you're out for lunch you open the
tea bag at the end when you're sitting
there with your girlfriend
or your boyfriend or somebody and
you're sitting there and you're gonna be
like oh wait hold on i have to
go in the bottom of my tea glass here
and i gotta rip open the tea bag
and start eating it because i better get
my fiber
does that make sense john does that make
sense on clubhouse
right steph does that make sense on
clubhouse you guys right
and pearl does that make sense on
clubhouse and tick tock you guys does
that make sense
does it right you're missing the fiber
you better eat that tea bag you better
break open that tea bag you guys
because you're gonna lose the fiber
because some nutritionists or some
doctor lorraine l good to see some
doctors some nutritionists
was like oh yeah you got to have your
fiber you got to have your fiber
you better eat your celery sticks well
what people don't realize
is celery's not a vegetable that for
right there
red flag red flag red flag
i remember the media totally totally
just attacking the medical medium over
and over again about the celery juice
because so many millions of people were
drinking it to get their lives back
and the media were so curious and they
were just like
they were like they were like well wait
a minute here um
you're juicing a vegetable and you know
every time they would write something
they would bring on
somebody that was paid to try to like do
a smear
on celery or me right and they would say
well he's
he's wrong the medical medium's leaving
out the most important part the fiber
and the medical medium is just juicing a
vegetable and leaving out the fire first
of all this is an herb
so what you guys need to know is you're
looking
at an herb right here
you're looking at an herb that's an herb
so what you're doing is you're creating
herbal medicine
that's what you're doing you're margaret
valentine good to see you
you're creating herbal medicine
keep that in mind and so in today's
world with the plague out there
right and the new plague that's going to
come and the new plague that's going to
come
and then five years later a new plague
is going to come because you're just
going to let it out of a lab somewhere
and they're going to let another plague
out of a lab because they love to do
that
and they're going to then they're going
to let another plague out of a lab again
and what happens is when each new time
we get these
these flu related plagues and however
right
it's important to have medicinal tools
it's important to know how to use
herbs and herbal extractions and
with everything happening with immune
immunodeficiency issues which are going
to be growing
leaps and bounds coming up majorly
majorly people are going to be
struggling with their immune systems
more than ever before in history
starting now
and moving forward so and in that
we're not just so here's medical medium
he's just juicing a vegetable and
keep the fight he's kicking out the
fiber so
he must be real stupid because the fiber
is the most important
part i'm a nutritionist and a trainer
and he's just
he's just doesn't know that the fiber is
critical what a dumb
what a dumb ass that medical medium is
right you know or some doctor
that's paid to actually be out like some
doctor that doesn't they're not a doctor
because they don't they've never seen
patients before
but they're paid to be on social media
and they're like oh let's rip apart the
celery juice movement
let me let me get out there and do
something in an article or something
and they're like uh celery the vegetable
celery really isn't that good for you
it's got some nutrition but
there's no research in science about if
it helps anybody
there's no studies that say that celery
juice helps
you of course there's no studies so
celery juice hasn't been studied yet
except one way and one way only
millions of people drinking it and
getting real results in their lives back
right that beats out any study because
here's what i've seen my whole life and
maybe you guys have too
are you guys seasoned are you guys
seasoned enough for this
right are you guys seasoned enough to
see what i've seen my whole life
people sick and studies not helping them
people sick they're sick endometriosis
pcos
um you know fibroids um hashimoto's
severe cmf cms c you know cfs
me cfs hostimoto's ra
hyperthyroidism uh all kinds of problems
left and right right
vertigo dizziness brain fog adhd did
studies ever help any of those people
tell me now what study what study what
citation to a study has ever helped
anybody a single person
people stay sick they stay sick they
stay sick and they stay sick
you know so that's what studies do for
chronic illness i'm not talking about
rocket fuel
i'm not talking about rocket engine fuel
that takes
math that's all math chronic illness
they don't know what causes chronic
illness unless they
steal the information from medical
medium published books which they have
which they have
many times now okay and
what happens is that we you know we just
we walk around thinking oh that little
that study are you waiting for that
study
are you gonna wait another 10 years for
that study
which is basically an article written by
somebody in a university in hopes that
they did a study
oh what's that study going to be a
cellar juice is helpful
maybe it is helpful how stupid meanwhile
millions of people are drinking it
getting their lives back and guess what
no one's gonna spend 200 million dollars
200 million dollars to find
the subgroup sodium that is actually
turning everybody's life around
that's the macro sodium that's in celery
juice right
the macro sodium and then you got the
subgroup right there
the trace mineral salts that live in a
soap in a living solution
a living solution around the macro
sodium they're not going to spend 200
million dollars to prove medical medium
was right
think about that who's going to do that
who's going to come up with 250 million
dollars
right so and then and then
have teams of scientists working around
the clock
just to prove anthony william wright
because he gets his information from a
higher source that's already helped
people get their lives back because no
one else thought about
doing therapeutic celery juice and
getting your lives back
and then you can't make money so here
you put 250 million dollars
into trying to prove anthony william
right when you can't make a dime off of
it
that's not going to happen so this is
going to be ranking on
sell oh you can eat it with crudite you
can celery is good for you if you keep
the fiber there and you have crew today
like you have it with your dip right
but those sodium cluster salts those are
one of the big secrets inside celery
juice
but celery isn't just celery it's herbal
medicine
and you have to take the fiber out to
make it work
you do you got to take the fiber out
really important to know all right and
the other thing too is what you'll hear
too from nutritionists or
from rds and i there's a lot of great
rds that follow medical medium
information and work with it there's a
lot of great nutritionists
you guys i'm sure some of you guys are
here now that
work with medical medium information
doctors too of course right
but what you're gonna hear is well
you're wasting all that
pulp so where's that pulp going by the
way
that's all the pulp we have that's what
i love about the mm900 hds
you're looking at the pulp between my
fingertips
right all that celery juice and you're
looking at the pulp
between my fingertips and it's dry and
it's dry
and that's why the juicer pays for
itself
over and over again i'm buying
less celery okay less and less celery
and
i'm actually the juicer has paid for
itself i say good boy
good boy every day i'm like good boy you
just paid for yourself again
even and right now it's on sale it's 82
off right now right
it's like it's you paid for it it pays
for itself and pays for itself because
i'm buying half the celery
that i ever ever bought before and that
pulp is
dry to the bone and i've never seen that
with any juicer and i've tried them all
and that pulp is dried to the bone
but it's the mm-900 hds it's not just
any omega juicer so
it's the mm-900 hds right and you guys
know i'm working with omega because
when they created this i was like yeah
you better believe it
if i can if i can save people money
like half the cost in their salary bill
then i just we just
all of a sudden we just did it we did it
because that's what anything i can do to
help
pressing prince good to see you this
juicer is hands down the best
i have ever had thanks preston prince
it's really
awesome that you're here and i'm honored
you're here a monitor here i'm going to
pour the celery juice now you guys
um
here's the funny thing get this what do
you guys think about this is this a head
scratcher for you
like i was just wondering because it's a
head scratcher for me all right
is this a head scratcher for you okay
what you'll hear from a professional in
health
is you're wasting all that pulp
you're throwing all that pulp away um
so i'm con i'm confused
so when you eat the celery
you're pooping the pulp out in the
toilet
and it's going down into the sewer are
you going to save your poop are you
going to save your poop is that what
you're going to do
is that the plan i want to know because
i've seen this over and over again i've
seen his articles written against
medical media
so much smear against medical means
ridiculous it's spiritual racism
100 hands down in spiritual
discrimination
right but the point is is one bad thing
comes out another and here's what
they'll do they'll say this here's one
of the famous bad things is
medical medium is wasting teaching you
how to waste
all that fiber and pulp and now you have
to throw it out
what a waste um so that means you go
into the toilet and you take out all
your feces
is that what you're doing you're trying
to save all that pull so are you doing
that sure you go in the toilet
i got a whole bunch of poop right here
on on this plate
you guys on tick-tock whole bunch of
poop on this plate yes
clubhouse i got a plate of poop right
here just so you know
and so what do you do you go in the
toilet
is that what everybody's doing so i'd
like to know what that that
the registered dietitian health of liz
how are you doing right
yeah health food list said yes it's
absolutely spiritual racism 100 percent
because health is you're not allowed to
tell a friend sometimes right
like hey you know check out medical
medium stuff he's saving lives
and because he hears it from a voice
since age four
right and he has that gift to hear it
and the information is is unique and
original it's no
hands down can't go near that because
it's the spiritual racism card that's
that's happening out there so that's
what they they do
they just do pull they throw that on you
it's like instantly they're no no that's
bs and they try to use that that try to
use that as their card
and so what you see is what do you guys
do with with so
okay so what i like any nutritionist to
know
because i'm scratching my head on this
one any registered dietitian any doctor
i'd like to know if you're so worried
about the pulp being
all thrown away and you're juicing and
wasting pulp and fiber
and that's like a waste creating waste
what are you doing when you're pooping
every single day i didn't know you're
collecting all that
so all these nutritionists and
dietitians and and all these smart
people
and all these smart doctors they must be
collecting all their
and straining it to get all that fiber
back out of it
what are they re-eating it they eating
it after they strain it out of their
poop and re-eat it
because i'm confused because they're not
saving their fiber
it's going out the other end fiber can't
be digested
so you guys can are you are you figuring
scratch your head here's the one thing
you're gonna find about medical medium
you don't have to like me
you can hate the way i look you can
think i'm ugly
you can think i'm annoying you can think
that
i'm all big on myself you can think i
got some ego
or i'm arrogant or you can think i'm a
nice guy whatever you want to think
okay the one thing you're going to get
for medical medium information
is it's sensible because if you read
every article or hear anybody on a
podcast talking about health
instantly it's not sensible
non-stop not sensible it's constantly
like this
fiber can't be assimilated nor can it be
digested
you eliminated out the other
end you guys
so you have all these so-called
professionals that have all these
degrees
all these degrees i graduated from blah
blah blah i got
i graduated
i graduated i have my certificate
i have a degree hanging on my wall
i'm so damn smart he's wasting all that
pulp and fiber
then anthony williams is wasting all
that pulp and fiber
really because use a dummy
use a dummy you might have paid for that
degree
you might have worked hard in school but
use a dummy
a real dummy and you know
because what you'll find with mm
information it's why doctors around the
world reach out and contact
it's why other people around so i've
helped the most powerful people in the
world
for many years running okay
and because it makes so much
sense so much sense
it's unbelievable what happened to
everybody
what happened to everybody in the health
movement
why are they just talking like good
bacteria
the more more you put in it helps you
against the bad bacteria what are you
talking about
that bacteria and good bacteria don't
even talk to each other
that bacteria sits in you and does its
own thing
and that's what it does what type of
juicer lori
parker mm 900 hds
82 off but in megajuicers.com that's
where the sale is
to megajuicers.com okay and
and you know kelly's the best person
ever um that's what people must say
about you
right and because you you know because
exactly
you're obviously amazing person but the
whole point is
right that when you think about
it you can scratch your head all day at
the
nonsense the stuff that's not sensible
common sense man
common sense it's almost like
it's almost like i mean is it the
twilight zone because i'm just wondering
you got all these so-called smart people
they don't even know that celery is an
herb did you know that they're just
figuring that out now because they've
been
burned so bad every time they've been
trying to you know attack celery
and then someone from the medical medium
community stands up and says it's an
herb you dummy it's an herb
you don't even have it right
professional health professional
yeah um
yeah it's it's ridiculous so
stephanie said somebody sent me a video
about how
celery juice has too much vitamin k
and removes the fiber
well yeah i put that video out
yeah yeah yeah you remove too much fiber
when you juice celery uh-huh so i wrote
a bad article
out there do i have a degree yeah i do
i'm a nutritionist
and i have oh i have some other letters
after my name too
uh-huh i was a dietitian
yeah i put the slanderous article
against celery juice out there
was i paid to do it uh no
i don't think so what
uh yeah it's you're losing too much
fiber anthony
is wasting fiber what do i eat my
what do you mean do i eat my
because i what i'm pooping out fiber
every day
yeah i had a celery stick yesterday with
lunch
yeah i pooped yeah the fiber went down
the toilet
i didn't save it no
uh should i should i save it
because i'm wasting all that fiber okay
i did the thing about the vitamin k
yeah uh-huh what
what causes chronic illness and
autoimmune
i don't know then why am i an expert on
vitamin k
i don't know i just trying to
i gotta go this is embarrassing
um the whole thing about
something really important to know okay
it's there's holes everywhere out there
you see them everywhere you guys on
tick-tock you see them everywhere
people are damaging themselves with all
the apple cider vinegar you guys still
do an apple cider vinegar
at all you guys still do an apple cider
vinegar acv you guys are clubhouse still
do an acv
you're going to lose your teeth you're
going to lose your teeth
you're going to break them down over
time you're going to
vinegar is the teeth destroyer there's
no common sense out there
right but nutritional yeast you guys
still do nutritional yeast out there
right you're gonna burn your neurons out
with that msg
that glutamic acid it's a different
variety of glutamic acid
derived in yeast that's different than
any glutamic acid
and you're going to burn your neurons
out and you're going to just irritate
every nerve in the lining of your
intestinal tract eventually
right and people don't know this stuff
you know here's what's funny
the same people that will sell you all
those probiotics
all the fermented food and all any
any kind of microorganism they can
possibly conjure up and bottle the same
people
will tell you it's okay to do your acv
did you know apple cider vinegar acetic
acid destroys all your good bacteria
i'm just getting you guys this is
important information take some notes
acv destroys all your good bacteria
another thing too coffee coffee
destroys all your good bacteria right
coffee does vinegar does
destroys annihilates your good bacteria
so this next nutritionist
doctor slash who knows another
professional has slash trainer whoever
it's going to be will make sure you're
you should do your apple cider vinegar i
sell an apple cider vinegar too
here take this probiotic too that the
misinformation is so
heaped up peeped up and heaped up
it's literally mounds and mounds of
misinformation everywhere
um so why do you celery juice
why do it right one of the funny things
is is that
once in a while i'll have this moment
and be like you know what everybody stop
doing celery juice everybody stop
just stop right if
you're having that you're if you're
there's that much of a battle and a war
about
it out there just stop okay
just don't even do it anymore don't let
everybody just get sick that
get sick and die and just get sick stay
sick and get sick
i mean but you know what i just don't
have it in me
to ever think like that you know it's
like
we want to save lives and it's
incredible
like when you think about it how evil
works and darkness works out there in
the world
darkness wants to stop something that's
literally bringing people's lives back
think about that and it pays
a heap of people with degrees
to try to stop something so incredible
michelle good to see you and um
it it's incredible when you think about
it so i wake up in the morning i'm like
you know what there's such a
there's so much crap i get from it it's
unbelievable just everybody stopped
drinking it then
i don't know what to say and then and
then two seconds later i'm like
i'm like yeah no it's worth the fight i
want people better
it's worth the fight it always is
it always is so let's go into a couple
of things that are really critical to
know
right if you guys just came on here this
is the mm-900
hds 82 off right here okay omega
juicers.com
it's the celery model you can juice
everything in it what's incredible right
here give you the rundown
is the pulp is so dry there's no there's
nothing moist in this
there's nothing i can't even feel any
moisture right now
it's literally dry to the bone right
there
and that's that means you're saving
money you're buying less celery and
people say it all the time
say it all the time so let's talk a
little bit about the gut
real quick here you guys let me just
move my celery over
um page hall says
it beats us down though it's exhausting
fighting for the truth all the time
paige i totally get it and i'm worried
about you guys
let me just tell you i'm actually
worried about you guys
because you've had to fight for the
medical mediums information you have to
fight for the medical medium too
you've had to fight for the truth you've
had to fight for your own truth on how
you healed
with the information you have to fight
and that
isn't out there other than this
community
but it's a special brew of people here
it's a special brew of people here
that has that fighting that fighting
um gift inside of them
and spiritual power too inside of them
it's incredible because you guys you
guys
you have a tremendous amount of faith
and you're like you know what i'm so
sick
i've been everywhere done everything
seen everything seen it i've tried
everything
yeah this guy this guy you know there's
all this crap written about him because
he
gets his information from above right
and it takes this like something in you
to be like i'm just gonna do it i gotta
do it
i gotta do and you know and i respect
that
believe me i respect that like you guys
can't believe
um so right here i got this anatomy
dummy in front of me right and i'm just
gonna give you the quick run down
the minute celery juice enters your
mouth it's doing something for you guys
right off the running right away right
when it enters
the mouth okay celery juice has the
sodium cluster salts i talked about
that break the membrane down on all the
bad bacteria
because bad bacteria and bad viruses run
on a charge
in electrical charges you guys know that
they run on electrical charge
a destructive one inside your body a
destructive one
good bacteria like the elevated biotics
i was talking about on my garden lettuce
right here
on my garden lettuce the microorganisms
that
that are on life not on death
they are on the opposite charge of the
bad stuff
celery juice is herbal medicine sodium
cluster salts go in
go in and start to annihilate bad
bacteria
so instantly when it goes in the mouth
now your stomach
just so you guys know okay your stomach
right here has got those stomach glands
and i was telling you the other day
those stomach glands get burnt out by
all that apple cider vinegar all that
red wine vinegar all the other vinegar
the balsamic vinegar
gets burnt out all the caffeine the
caffeine has
burnt out you think chocolate chocolate
is just
safe and fine and dandy and you could
eat these things chocolate i still want
you here i still want you learning
but i'm gonna tell you that caffeine
burns out your stomach glands inside
your stomach
and then you lose your fighting
mechanism
your fighting mechanism you guys is your
hydrochloric acid your hcl
medical medium information okay unique
information
talks about it's a seven acid blend in
your gastro glands
not just hcl hcl is in hcl you guys know
that
in the human body hcl tear appleman good
to see you
um hcl is not just hydrochloric acid
when it's inside your body
it's a special blend of seven acids
and our stomach glands
have they become disabled
and then your hcl can't kill anything
anymore
your hcl is the killer of all the bad
microorganisms that
that microorganisms that enter your
mouth
or grow inside your gut the bad stuff
your hcl is the killer
hydrochloric acid doesn't just stay in
the stomach it actually goes down you
guys and research and science doesn't
know this
this is really incredible information it
goes
it goes deep down throughout your whole
intestinal tract that's what your acl
does
it travels and it destroys you know why
people got bad bacteria when your gut
health doctor your
functional medicine doctor or whoever it
is that's helping you out it's like oh
you got bad bacteria we did a
stool sample and you got this and you
got that
that's because your hcl is gone it's
blown out
your gastric glands are blown out celery
juice
brings back those gastric lands that's
why people's lives are being turned
around
it's bringing back those gastric glands
so what is this juicer
or any juicer you can use any juicer you
want okay i'm just saying
that this is the one that's saving me
money it's the one that i love
it doesn't have the metal gears
the metal gears a friend of mine i told
you a friend of mine was trying to make
me juice and i was like great
looks like i'll be doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie
because of the metal gears the metal
gears they grind into each other and
they grind into each other you don't
think little tiny
tiny particles of metal aren't
eventually wearing off you know what
your car engine does
eventually your shaft and your car
engine
your crankshaft wear down you got a
hundred thousand miles on your car you
got 60 thousand miles 150 000 miles
all your bearings metal all your cranks
your crankshaft your camshaft
all starts to wear down your valves all
start to wear down
that's how it works so i like juicers
that don't have that on this juicer is
exceptional it's an entirely different
beast all on its own the whole point is
is cold pressed by the way
the whole point is is that's why i call
juicers medical devices
for where we're heading for where we're
heading with health and what's going to
happen
it's one of those things that's critical
cellular
celery juice cured my acid reflux
in addition to helping with other stuff
shauna shawna simmons
amazing and but hey
that person saying it's too high in
vitamin k and you're losing all your
fiber
unreal people need vitamin k by the way
and celery juice isn't high in vitamin k
it's got vitamin k
that's high in something way more
critical way more critical
sodium cluster salts that's the thing
that rebuilds your hcl
that's the thing that rebuilds your hcl
and your hcl is the
killer of the bad stuff in your gut
and when you and you know what else
celery just does too it rebuilds your
bile reserves so you can break down fats
you guys
so you can break down fats
think about it people aren't breaking
down their fats anymore they're not
they're just getting caked into their
gut caked into their gut
they're not breaking them down so
this is just one powerful reason why
celery juice is so important
so back to the herbal extraction you
guys going to open up your tea bags
you start gobbling down all that used
tea because you don't want to waste the
fiber
just wondering you do that you're out
with a friend you guys are in a
restaurant and you guys
can have herbal tea can i have a black
tea
it's just caffeinated but can i have a
herbal tea
yeah wait a minute wait i still i know i
drank my cup of tea already but
i still have to gobble down all that the
tea
inside the bag i'm ripping it open your
friend's gonna be like what are you
doing i gotta rip open this tea bag
because
i don't want to waste a single bit of
fiber it's an herbal extraction you're
supposed to
lose the fiber you have to
it's critical you have to it's an herbal
extraction is what it is you guys
you guys um medical mean podcast at
apple podcast moon meditation i'm still
doing the moon meditation
still am michelle l says because celery
is not recognized
as an herb and it is it's an herb
you guys it's still a full moon going on
i just want to remind everybody
lorena you're still doing the um moon
meditation
i'm doing the moon meditation still
tonight
i'm doing it for the next few days in a
row probably about three four days
because
it's still powerful when the moon's at a
different
angle it's still powerful and then
with where the angle the sun and the
moon is it's still
powerful um so you still do all this
healing because it's still really a full
moon even though it's not at its fullest
moment right now
so that's important too you did the moon
meditation you love it incredible
darlene
amazing i'm gonna do it again so yeah
so keep keep that in mind about
the herbal extraction um
you know the whole point about it so
celery juice is an herbal extraction
you're doing herbal
medicine and so when you hear people
talking crap about it and writing crap
about it
you're you you're way educated you
actually you're in the know
you know the truth and then you see how
either
what are they are they just uneducated
you could say that or they just don't
know
are they ignorant maybe they're ignorant
or they don't care or maybe it's just a
slander
or are they smart how many you know did
that
doctor that wrote that article how many
people did they get better in their
lifetime because medical meme
information has healed millions
around the world i mean more
people around the world than any other
place
or would you know how many people
did that person help that trainer help
did that trainer reverse diseases
in tens of thousands of people who
ripped apart celery juice
did they reverse tens of thousands of
people's diseases and got their lives
back now they can drive in cars they can
feed their families they can work again
they can take care of themselves
are they just worried about trainers is
worrying about building apps with
someone who hasn't been sick yet
you know so we get and then they're
sitting there ripping apart celery juice
gotta think about these things
and i know don't get me wrong it's a lot
of great traders that follow medical
meme information they learn about celery
they're doing celery and here's the
other thing and then there's the dirty
secret
the dirty dirty secret so many people
are drinking it behind closed doors
because when you talk about it you can't
make money off of it
and the other thing is when you talk
about it all you do is give medical
medium credit
that's a lot of people in the industry
right now they're so sick of hearing
about medical medium and they're so sick
you hear about people bringing their
books to the doctor's offices
they're so sick about people bringing
their books to their nutritionists
they're so tired of it that just sits
they just like don't
don't want to hear it no more about
celery just but yet they're doing celery
juice
so many people are doing celery juice
and they get snagged
they're like doing their youtube and
they got their celery juice on the side
but they don't want to talk about it
it's just happening every day like that
you guys listen um check out the moon
meditation when you get a chance medical
medium podcast at apple podcast
this is 82 off just so you know this mm
900 hds the sales still on right now
um i call it a medical device that's
what i call it
and you guys um and check it out check
out medical medium
new edition revised and expanded which
is
49 off it's 19 right now on amazon.com
or get it free of the library if you
want
if you got a juicer that you like stay
with it use the juicer you like
okay i'm happy you're juicing because no
matter what it's a medical device too
because that's the whole point that's
how i see juicers in general just
letting you guys know
because and we're going to need them for
the long
haul um love you guys
and uh i'm going to ig i'm going to
instagram
you guys i'm going to keep t i'm going
to put tick tock back on i'm going to
put clubhouse back on
just give me a few minutes to kind of
prep some stuff i want to clean up the
mess a little bit just give me a few
minutes you guys
and uh lorraine thank you as well
margaret good to see you
good to see you guys coming on there i'm
tic toc good to see you guys
um and i'll see you soon right we're
going on ig in a little bit
and we're going to have tick tock back
on we're going to have clubhouse back on
all right guys take care and i'll talk
to you soon austin good to see you too