and we're juicing celery we're talking
about the power of celery it should
never ever ever be underestimated
it's the number one fresh
produce crop in the world
it's not the number one crap in the
world because you know what the number
one crop is right you guys in clubhouse
are you guys on youtube you know the
number one crop is
it's gotta be what which one is it is it
corn
is it sugar is it caffeine
right the number one crops right there
it's like corn
offer and medical use right gmo corn
and then sugar right of course like
processed sugar
caffeine those are the big crops but
fresh produce crop
i mean they're building they're building
and creating
farms celery farms right
talking about doing some good on the
planet
good to see you guys we're live on
facebook live on clubhouse we're live on
youtube we're live on tick tock
talking about the power of celery going
to talk about the sodium cluster salts
i'm going to talk what about what
happens when you're eating
all of your pork all these years you had
pork 10 years ago
it's still inside of you it's still
inside of you
it is it hasn't left right
you carry it around inside of you even
if you're in shape or you think you're
in shape you're working out you've got
some
abs you still got the pork inside of you
and it doesn't come out celery just
helps get the old pork all that old
bacon fat
and bacon grease out of you and that's
one thing celery juice helps us do is it
gets gets that
bacon fat out of us where's the bacon
fat sit
sits inside the liver you can be you can
be some
some dude you could be in the gym you
got some abs you're working out
you still got the bacon fat inside of
you
and it sits there it sits on the inside
lining of the intestinal tract inside
the lining of the colon that's where it
sits
and it just breaks our system down i've
seen a lot of people
fall apart when they start getting older
just they could be
going good going good going good and
they just start breaking down and
falling apart and everything just starts
to fall apart
and then you know where are we there you
guys so
i'm excited gonna juice some celery by
the way the juicer
this juicer mm-900 hds
is 82 off
82 off right now so it's on sale at
omegajuicers.com right it's an omega
omega it's 82
off which is incredible i've not seen
that before it's 25
off 82 off but
don't get it confused because this is
the one this is the one that i'm i'm
working with with them this is the one
that does the celery plus other things
but this is the celery juicer the mm-900
hds celery juicer
so that's the one like i said 82
dollars off right now on this juicer so
i can't help but to do
um you know i can't help but to do this
bring the celery out
because it's a chance for someone to
actually get an incredible juicer and
i'm going to show you how it works we're
squeezing out every last drop of juice
out of the celery where the pulp is dry
but we're talking about look we're going
to um we're going to talk about the
power of celery what it does for us how
you cannot underestimate it how people
drink it when they get off of it it
their symptoms start to come back or
they
feel it they're like wait a minute i
feel something because that's how much
it's doing for us
right and and don't get confused
why like who's doing celery juice well
everybody is because they keep on
building more farms more farms more
farms
thousands of celery farms right
but everybody keeps the hush hush quiet
quiet you guys
quiet don't want to tell anybody i'm
drinking it don't want influencers don't
want to tell anybody they're drinking it
anymore
uh audrey says it's amazing best
purchase in years this juicer right
it really is it i'll tell you what the
juicer has done for me if you guys want
to know
all right so what would i let me just
give you some history okay
i've tried all the juicers out there all
the cold-pressed juicers out there
all right um nicole says so this juicer
does
juice other items yes it does not just
celery yes it juices other items
and what i find is to juice other items
better because
it has the ability to squeeze every last
drop out of them and that's what i love
about the juicer
um this this model is made specifically
for celery
and you can use it for anything what i
find is i use it for everything and i'm
happier with that
than other juicers i've tried all the
all the juicers out there i'm just
letting you know
and i'll tell you a little history about
it okay
and you guys could get any juicer you
want look you guys can use any juicer
you want
it's just that everybody's always asking
me and i hold it off for a while and i
hold it on for a while i hold it up for
a while and then it finally just like
all right all right this is the one i
use
and but like a little history about it
for me right
tried every juicer i don't care what
juicer somebody throws out at me like
did you do this one did you do that one
did you do this one i tried them all
okay and they
haven't saved me money i buy a lot of
celery
like i buy a lot of celery you know and
i got a lot of celery right here and
you know it costs money absolutely but
when you squeeze
that juice out of your celery
like squeeze more of it out of it
you're saving money so then when i got
this juicer
i was buying less less celery than
buying less celery than buying less
but wait a minute i was still drinking
the same amount of juice
and so i was seeing where it was saving
me money so then what this juicer did
which the other juicers never did for me
is this juicer paid for itself you guys
on clubhouse it paid for itself
that's what it did and i'm like wait a
minute so this juicer paid for itself
and then paid for itself again and then
i noticed
it paid for itself again okay
now as i as i calculated that it was
really awesome
nazil says it was a life changer when i
switched to this
juicer the mm-900 hds and
don't get it confused with other ones i
used to get two cups of celery juice
out of two bags of celery now from one
bag
i make two cups of cj and you guys
that's that's for real that's what i've
been trying to tell everybody about like
all the time
that's what i'm like i tell my friends
that well what's the difference between
this juicer i'm like what are you
kidding
um hazel said i started with a different
juicer and it soaked me dry with
money and not enough juice i love the
omega juicer the mm-900 gives me more
juice
and it pays for itself it pays for
itself
so check this out right now having a
juicer pay for itself is one thing
right and that's what this juicer did
when no other juicer did that for me
but it paid for itself again right and
then it paid for itself again
and then again because i did the
calculations for how much money i spent
on celery
it turned out that the m m 900
paid for itself a dozen times for me
so it's like wait a minute just got
another juicer well just got another
juicer
wait it paid for itself again it paid
for itself again
and i i couldn't believe it so i'm just
letting you know how it works for me
and i'm excited about it um so it's the
mm-900 hds just so you guys know okay
omega juicers.com that's where you go
and we'll talk about some juice you know
we'll talk about some celery juice so
you go to megajuicers.com
right now make sure it's the mm900 hds
or you just
end up with the wrong juicer you'll end
up with the wrong juicer
you'll end up with an omega juicer but
the wrong one just letting you know
so you guys we're live on tick tock
right now
[Music]
good to see you guys i'm juicing some
celery
you know last time i did this i didn't
have the container underneath right
you guys remember that and it just was
pouring all over the counter
cutting board don't add anything to your
celery juice
you guys i see it every day out there
i'm putting ice in my celery
i'm adding lemon right someone will be
on the internet who like i added lemon
make sure you add lemon
yeah you just destroyed your celery
juice
you just ruined your celery juice
you ruined it i'm not talking about the
flavor i'm talking about
you ruin this opportunity to really do
what what it needs to do for you and i'm
going to give you a rundown on how that
works
mc good to see you emcee on youtube
right
um mc says keep the juice raw
yeah you of course you want to keep it
raw you don't want to cook your celery
juice
um good to see you guys coming on
everybody
you guys there's some you you might get
build up but you get filled up with
every single juicer
so you get build up from your fruits and
vegetables you're juicing
you get build up i use a little bonnie
and amy that's what i do put a little
bonnie on me on the sponge
i said yeah i got right underneath my
sink right here and i i get that
i get that build up owl is what i do
so i'm doing a little juicing right now
obviously let's run some celery sticks
through here
um can you juice the leaves can you
juice without the leaves they make it
taste horrible of course you can cut the
leaves off
there's nothing wrong with cutting the
leaves back
uh that's fine you could cut them back
as much as you want you guys
i'm just reading your comments can you
add a little ice susan says can you add
a little ice
no you can't you can't add ice
you can't add water you can't add
supplements
you can't add you know
anything because if you add something to
it
you dilute the sodium cluster sauce
sodium cluster salt i'm going to show
you guys a little bit about really quick
okay i'm just gonna shut this down for a
second right
so here's how it works okay
let's get this off here this cap um
you guys see this right here all right
i'm holding up a white board right here
okay sodium cluster salts okay
that's your macro sodium right there
okay that's in celery
that's your macro that's your macro
sodium you're looking at it right there
okay now here's the difference with
celery
this is why people heal all around the
world i'm going to give you guys a
rundown
okay it's not what science research says
where oh there's sodium there's this
much sodium in celery
we calculated how much sodium is in
celery
okay that's what they say right there's
sodium
you know yeah true right what no one
understands
okay is that there's a subgroup of
sodium in celery
how come it's not discovered yet why
should they discover it
first of all the industries want us sick
they want us dying
they want us buying drugs right they
want us buying pharmaceuticals they want
us buying
you know medications right they want to
keep us sick right the industry does
because if you get better then everybody
go
in the industries they lose all their
money okay so
who's going to pay 50 million dollars
100 million
who's going to pay 200 million dollars
for a whole team of scientists to
actually
find the subgroup of sodium who's going
to pay for that do you ask like
think about that ask yourself who's
gonna come up with 200 million dollars
put a team together just so they can
prove anthony william right
and then more people around the world
heal does that make sense to you
is that doesn't make any sense so here
it goes okay
the macro that's the macro sodium inside
celery so inside your sodium inside your
celery stick okay and
around it is like it's like a solar
system around the sun
right so when you
dehydrate your celery into a powder
you lose the solar system you guys you
lost the subgroup of
the sodium cluster salts the subgroup
sodium you lost it
bye-bye now it can't heal you now it
can't help you
right this gets suspended in a living
solution
that when you squeeze that celery
stick you get the subgroup the sub
um you get the subgroup of sodium
which is that solar system around the
macro
sodium that's what you get these are
trace minerals
designed by planet earth by mother
nature
the miracle of mother nature these are
trace minerals that are
only bonded in a living solution
around the macro sodium
letting you know you add water to it you
just disturbed and diluted it
you add lemon to it you just dilute it
that solar system that's around okay
that's subgroup of sodium that's around
the sodium the macro sodium you just
disturbed it
you add another vegetable in there
another fruit you destroyed it
it doesn't mean you can't eat celery it
doesn't mean you can't have celery in a
juice you can put celery in a juice with
other things
it's still good for you but you won't be
able to
access that miracle that subgroup
of sodium you won't be able to access
the sodium cluster salts
which is the trace minerals that are
designed specifically
to be swimming around in a circle like a
solar system around the macro sodium
you won't be able to actually have that
you won't be eligible
to heal through celery juice if you
destroy that
okay in science research they want to
just they
just want to keep everything dumbed down
oh there's a little bit of this in there
there's a little bit of potassium in
celery there's a little bit of this oh
a little touch of vitamin c but no one's
going to take 200 million dollars
assemble a massive group of scientists
to start fishing for something they
don't know is there and that's why it
takes so much
it just you can't just wake up one
morning be a scientist and then
look look into a scope and find
something when you don't know where it
is it takes decades for them to find
simple things and no one's gonna do that
and so because first of all because then
it'll be like whoa
celery actually can help you heal
because it's already healing millions
worldwide but everybody wants to ignore
that
the media doesn't care anymore it
doesn't matter how many people get their
lives back like get
literally their lives back and people
just ignore it right
but it's that subgroup of sodium right
there the sodium cluster salts
these are the trace minerals that are
bonded in a solution
okay of living fluid it suspends them
around that macro sodium that's how it
works right there you guys
um giving you kind of a little rundown
on that
how long does it take celery juice to
help a chronic fatigue syndrome
it's a healing tool right
so it all depends learning about
what your chronic fatigue is matters so
you
learn about what your cfs says right
that's critical right there so i'm
holding the medical meeting new edition
which is the book of all books about cfs
okay and
[Music]
when you learn what's causing it then
you'll realize
look i may have an epstein-barr virus dr
faun good to see you md
i may have an epstein-barr virus in me
if i got cfs
i may have two epstein-barr viruses in
me if i have cfs you see how it works
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
so once you learn that you know why
you're using celery juice you're using
it
to help destroy epstein-barr because it
breaks down the membrane on the virus so
we're gonna go there and it also depends
what what else are you doing
celery juice is one of the tools i've
seen people get rid of fatigue
with celery juice yeah i've also seen
other people
move the needle but they need to do
other things too
celery juice fixes some people like that
you see it every day out there okay
other people
it's moving the needle to get them there
to the finish line
right so that's important to know how
that works
[Music]
antivirals are important you may need
additional anti-virals i talk about that
in the medical medium new edition
right so what what i here's how i look
at a juicer
i look at a juicer as a medical device
that's how i see a juicer okay now
i see it as a medical tool bottom line
that's how i look at it
every day
because what is it what is a juicer
why are you juicing the juicing for the
fun of it
right why bother juicing just eat pizza
why bother juicing just eat cheese and
pork
just eat fried eggs every day why why
bother juicing
when you think about it um
you're juicing because you're you're
trying to save your butt or you're
juicing to try to fix something or
you're juicing to try to heal something
it's like oh let me go out and buy a
juicer
just for the fun of it let me go spend
the money buy a juicer i feel great
living my life but let me get a juicer
anyway
right so when you guys think about it
it's it's
you know we're we're getting a juicer
because something's wrong like
we're not feeling good or we're trying
to find an answer
to healing or we're trying to improve
our health because something's not right
and so what is a juicer it's a medical
tool
that's what it is it's a health tool
it's a medical tool i see it as a
medical device
if you guys just got on this is the
mm-900 hds
incredible sale i haven't seen a sale
like this from omegajuicers.com
it's 25 off 82
off this juicer this is the
celery model but it does everything else
too that's what i love it was telling
everybody earlier how it paid for itself
over and over again it just didn't pay
for itself once and someone else said
that i think two people said that
um i saw the in the comments and it just
doesn't pay for itself
once it's paid for itself a dozen times
for me i buy so much celery
and and it's just it's such a great it's
such a great tool so i just did some
juicing just now you guys let me just
move this towel right here
so in in this in this bowl here
i have extremely audra says great juicer
thank you i'm so glad you like it i feel
the same way
i have this thing a pulp in my hand
right
and i show this every time that pulp is
dry
it's dry i mean i've had the wettest
pulp from all the other juicers spitting
out wet pulp
you name it i've seen it all out there
right and
this is nice and dry that's it this is a
pulp
and this is very fibrous celery i'm
dealing with
this is extremely fibrous so
if it was another batch of celery there
would probably be
this much in there only right
this is extremely fibrous celery so
because some
some celery um bunches batches
it's just basically all fiber right so
it takes
it's you know it takes a lot to squeeze
that juice out and that's what i love
about the juicer it's all dry
and that's where the money is at the
money's at
how dry the pulp is that's where the
money's at cold white spring says
i just got the juicer it's great so glad
you got it
incredible it's the mm900 hds
uh john says that's really true it pays
for itself totally worth so glad
got that in the beginning and what i
like about it's easy to clean the other
thing to you guys
is it's quiet i can juice at five
o'clock in the morning i'm not waking up
the house
and falcon says how long is juice good
for how long will that container last
uh you and does it get degraded over
days
of course anything you know you juice
you want to drink right away if you can
you want to drink
quickly if you can 24 hours is kind of
the limit
but yeah of course you can drink your
celery juice in two days it'll still
have
power it'll still have its healing
sodium cluster salts right it'll still
have these but when you go
too many days when you go too many days
that subgroup of sodium right that's
circulating the macro
mineral sodium right that sub subgroup
sodium of sodium
that starts to weaken after a couple of
days in the fridge so then your celery
juice is getting kind of old
which brings me to the next thing
which is hpp hpp
is not good for me remember those words
that's basically the slogan it should be
is hpp
is not good for me and that's something
that people need to know
hpp is high pressure pasteurization so
you walk into the store you think you're
getting your celery juice
you're getting it out of a that was
bottled
and that stuff is dead it'll they're
allowed to say
raw or fresh because
they're using a non-heated
pasteurization
but still it destroys the sodium cluster
salts it still denatures
the very thing your celery juice is
trying to help you with
so you'll see somebody out there i tried
celery juice it's not helping me i
didn't find any
i didn't find any way it helped me i
tried some celery juice that didn't work
it's like you've been drinking hpp off
the shelf every day
if you go to a juice bar and they juice
it fresh in front of you that's the
fresh
juice that's the fresh juice you guys
that's it right there
and if you juice it at home like this
that's the fresh
juice keep that in mind hpp
does not work you can't get the healing
you need
from the hpp high pressure
pasteurization it's a trick out too
total trick out going to the store it's
in the cold section
it's sitting there on the shelf you go
and grab it you think you got something
good you go buy it you're drinking it
the stuff is already bad it's gone bad
gone bad in the sense that not rance it
but
it's been changed it's not like you
think it really is because that high
pressure pasteurization is experimental
and it collapses cell structures
of the juice that's what high pressure
pasteurization
pasteurization does it collapses
cell structures so what happens is
celery juice is something that is so
powerful inside the body
helps us so much inside the body but
it's got to be intact to do it and
that's one of the keys right there
so this is important now i'm gonna i'm
gonna pop it in here real quick
um do a little
fill this glass jar so i got one celery
juice right there
which i'm excited about so you want to
strain it you see how i got a strainer
you guys
yeah you can let this really sit and
then completely drip out
and then you can press it with a spoon
too and get every single
last drop out i love having control over
you know over the celery juice you don't
have control over it with these other
juicers too it's like the stuff spitting
spatting out anywhere
and when it's a juicers where it's cold
press there's
metal gears inside of some of them
metals going against itself so here's
something that's really important
someone says
oh well you know he's just trying to
sell his
juicer so uh you know i've seen some
really good users out there and
and the whole bit in the vegan community
and anywhere else and
you know he's just he's just hooked on
to a mega and that's his brand right
well that's funny because with some of
those juicers you guys
there's metal gears metal gears
do you guys know what that means right
metal on
metal think about it metal on metal
what does that mean where's over time
right you use that juicer for five years
and those metal gears are banged up
all that metal went inside of you it
went into your juice
so i'm just going to sit there and
collect more metal over the years and
more metal
i don't have to worry about this with
this machine so
and and i was at a friend's house and
they were making me juice and they had a
good juicer
they did but it was the metal gears
right the metal gears and i was like
uh looks like i'm getting a dose of
metal today in my juice even though it's
so my new
in the moment it adds up over time and i
was telling my friends you know
how long you had that t-shirt like i had
this juicer for three years you know
and the parts broke down once in a while
and i've ordered some more parts and
i've gotten it whatever and happens to
every juicer like that
and it's like it's like they're like
okay but you know that that the metal
gears
they're they're they're grinding into
each other to make your juice
you know what that means right oh yeah i
guess metal on metal i go yeah kind of
like the brakes on your car you guys
ever have a car where the brakes finally
went
and now you're literally metal on metal
your metal rotor
and your metal brake pad is now scraping
and it's going
right squeak squeak and so
i don't have to worry about that with
this machine so
i don't have a metal gear two metal
gears
in there crunching together and that's
another reason why i like this
health with liz good to see you on tik
tok um
kerry says it's 80 off now 82 off you
just ordered it carrie
mm-900 hds right right
so um we'll cover a couple little things
too i just wanted to cover
that information it's all important you
guys i talked about sodium cluster salts
you guys know that
right so it's one thing to like
juice just don't get me wrong here right
there's one thing
to just juice right a doctor friend told
me the other day like
you know and he said well juicing yeah
juicing is great
everybody should juice i'm like wait a
minute wait a minute
don't give me that juicing bs
don't you know and he laughed
he laughed right you know he goes
no juicing is great for you who doesn't
know juicing isn't good for you i go
don't give me that bs
because there's a difference between
making sure you juice your celery and
you juice it right
and you know how to you know how to do
the celery juice the whole bit the
details matter so i just want to cover
that right there the details matter
they matter you know and important to
know
um the details matter
so you can sit there and juice all your
carrots and your cabbage and your
whatever and juice all your stuff like
that right
people did that people did that people
did that for years
it doesn't mean they got their cfs
better it doesn't mean they got their
five real better you guys it doesn't
mean they got their multiple sclerosis
better it doesn't mean they got anything
better
sure they might have got something a
little better but then it all went
backwards
again but the bottom line is it's like
celery juice is a whole
nother level it's a whole entirely
different
therapeutic medicine way of dealing with
things
of handling things with your health so
it's like
if i was to have a juicer it's going to
be for celery
and yellow juice other things for fun
yeah there's ways of doing medicinal
juices there are
like spirit has talked to me about all
the different medicinal juices different
ways of
of combinations which i'll share over
time but the point is is this is
important when it comes down to
celery that's that where the details
matter
instead of like oh yeah okay just i
threw some celery sticks in my juice
no it's about making sure you do your
celery juice right
that's how we move the needle um
so that's important so don't get plastic
into the body from that machine
you're never you're never going to have
non-plastic exposure on the planet
you're exposed to plastic 24 7
everywhere
it's falling out of the sky it's in the
air it's it's on everything
like we can't run from plastic it's in
the water supply
we can't run from plastic right but
plastic detox is really easy
detox is really easy plastic comes out
of the body
really easy it can come out the next day
if you're doing the right things to come
out the next day plastic comes out of
the body a lot of times when you're not
even doing the right things but the
whole point is
is that metal doesn't come out of the
body easy
and that's something to know right there
okay
and and this is and just so you know
this is like the innards here
this is bpa-free right so that's
important to know
but um you guys by the way it's free
shipping in the us right now too
so it's 82 off 25 no 82 dollars yeah you
save
25 off you guys but
metal scares me because if you're not
that's something you've got to work hard
on like with the medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie
and you don't want to be getting more
metal in you all the time and that's why
i don't like the other juicers too it's
it's all the
metal interaction it's a big
part of why you know i don't like that
um this is this is one piece
instead of gears grinding against each
other
or or centrifuges with metal spinning
and grinding right and if you got those
fine
use them juice your celery i do want you
to get celery juice in you no matter
what and that's the goal
so keep with the juicer you have if
that's the one you have
but it's that metal situation it always
gets to me it's always has so that's why
that's why i got that's why i backed
this juicer that's why i backed i was
like you know what
uh you know what i want to let people
know i'll work with you guys at omega
i want to let people know okay so the
sale is at a mega that's where it is
it's at their website
not on amazon important to know so the
sale for this juicer isn't
at amazon it's omega juicers.com
so mega juicers.com omega
and there's just so you know you got to
look for the mm 900 hds or you're not
going to get the right juicer
somebody asked that question so i was
answering it so
what i love about this user too is it
cleans so easy
and that's important to know how it
um so there's always a question that
comes up why am i allergic to celery
well it depends when you eat celery
is something does something crazy happen
does your throat close up
do you start coughing and choking when
you
drink celery or eat celery do you have a
reaction when you have crudite
like is it the kind of allergic reaction
of celery where you're
at a friend's house and you take a
celery stick and you dip it in some
hummus or you dip it in some sour cream
you know dressing or something or
whatever it is and you all of a sudden
you eat that celery stick and it's
definitely the celery stick and you're
choking swelling your throat swelling
that's that's different
that's an allergic reaction someone can
have with any single food i've seen
people have that with meat
seen that people have the chicken i've
seen the people having peanut butter
i've seen it happen with seeds nuts oils
i've seen it happen with any fruit and
vegetable right
so and i've seen it happen with all that
right or is it something where you had
a food sensitivity test and you're told
celery is one of them
okay because i got a doctor calling
right now
who i got a doctor that's calling right
now and he's gonna give me my
food sensitivity test he's gonna tell me
about my food sensitivities and all that
so he's calling it a little bit i don't
know when he's he's calling and
he's going to fill me in on everything i
wanted to do this i wanted him to call
me
when we were doing this live that's him
right here
dr zolgar dr zolgar
hey yeah tell me so what does my blood
test say
you did the food scan the food
sensitivities the all cat what else the
food sense
okay i'm allergic to what celery
okay all right i'm allergic to chives
okay i'm allergic to pine nuts
oh okay that one too pine nuts
i'm allergic to cilantro well i didn't
know that
what else am i allergic cinnamon really
i had cinnamon the other day
um i'm allergic to
pine bark weed okay
what else i'm allergic to turnips
turnips okay all right i'll let
i gotta write this down you got this all
for me so i can keep the list with me
okay i'm allergic to pecans really i
haven't had a pecan in years
okay i'm allergic to broccoli i didn't
know that either
what else am i allergic to really
i'm working strawberries and
i'm allergic to squash
what about melons oh i'm allergic to
cantaloupe
all right how does these tests work do
you even know how these allergies come
up
you really don't know okay
so basically all right how am i allergic
to these when i never react to any of
them
oh i'm not allergic to eggs dr solgar i
could eat eggs
oh fantastic i have a couple eggs right
here just hold on here let me get the
eggs
wow doctors over i said i'm not allergic
to eggs though
i got so i got two eggs dr zulgar i got
two eggs i'm working on frying up
yeah right here yeah i just fried them
up
i had them sitting there i could eat
eggs then
okay that's amazing that my food
sensitivity test just like i heard my
friend's food sensitivity test too
they're allowed to eat things too that
like eggs and they're allowed to have
pork
i can have pork too oh that's fantastic
did you hear that buddy
we're gonna slaughter you later
and i'm gonna make sure we cut you up in
a lot of pieces
can i have can i have buddy's feet like
pigs feet
i can't i'm not allergic to pork okay
i'll do that i'll make sure we do that
so i can have things like a little bit
of pork that's not on the list
is an allergy that's interesting but i
got to worry about the strawberry what
other berries do i have to worry about
uh black raspberry i haven't had one of
those i don't think ever
okay all right well i'm glad thanks for
the food sensitivity test
but i'm allergic to celery right okay
okay thanks dr soldier
just so you know that's how it is with a
lot of people if you guys ever
experienced that
right that's how it's that's how the
system's rigged
basically they don't know what you're
allergic to unless you they still don't
even know if you're allergic to
something if your throat swells up
they just gotta eyeball it you can when
you eat something
and someone's throat swells up and
they're having their anaphylactic shock
they still don't know like it's how it's
possible or if they're allergic to that
never mind
why is it possible a doctor can run all
those tests food sensitivity tests what
a scam system that is
and they'll give you 30 allergies
to like 30 fruits and vegetables and
herbs and you'll be all of a sudden
allergic to someone's
a scallion you'll be allergic to some
other like
wacko thing and that's how it's rigged
exactly i mean is that how it is
you guys know you guys seen this you've
gone through this i know many of you
gone through this
so anyway um
here's the thing about what i love about
celery juice okay so
here's the thing what i love about
celery juice
that's that's an immune cell right there
okay
immune cells need mineral salts
that's what they need they thrive on
them so what happens is that subgroup of
sodium
right there sodium cluster salts
helps to fortify and strengthen your
immune cells
right it's one thing right there it
helps to get little gobble it one up
a white blood cell will gobble one up
when it gobbles up a solar system right
here because it will
it's to be super strong that's one thing
that's interesting
another thing that's really good is that
celery juice that sodium cluster salt
right there that i was showing you guys
that subgroup of sodium
it eats away the slip cover
on bacteria and viruses so there's slip
covers out here
really important to know all the bugs
inside of us
have a protective sheath and that's how
they stay alive and stay strong
so they can evade all kinds of problems
right so the sodium cluster salts eats
away at that slip cover
but you may think you don't have any
bacteria you may think you don't have
any viruses
fibromyalgia aches and pains tingles and
numbness
mystery tingles and numbness ringing in
the ears vertigo ever
all that's viral okay chronic sinusitis
utis
bacteria right styes right
if anybody has cold sores fever blisters
boom viral
right these are just some things if
you've been diagnosed with anything
ms lupus lyme disease pathogens right
viruses but that's just some things
fatigue bloating aches and pains
feeling like you're 100 years old when
you're only 50.
you know all these things right feeling
like you're 100 years old when you're
only 22.
okay the viruses and bacteria that make
us sick
feeding off the toxins inside of us okay
have a slip cover on them
and the sodium cluster salt eats away
that slip cover
and blows them up explodes them
important to know
really important information um
so if someone gets like diarrhea
they get runs they get the runs from
their celery juice
okay you're killing off
pockets of bacteria so let's do this
right now let's do a little
run down on something for you guys real
quick okay
so
so inside your gut lives a whole bunch
of bad bacteria
right and viruses too but they hide
in pockets of rancid
fat that stuck to the walls of your
intestinal tract
they thrive in pockets that are in the
colon too
okay and so putrefied proteins that
didn't digest well
because everybody has crappy digestion
rancid fats that are caked onto the
intestinal walls and linings
right that's still there your pork fat
you had
i wasn't kidding about that it's still
sitting on the lining of your gut and
what's behind that pork fat
are the bugs so that's important to know
right there
so what's sitting behind that pork fat
are the bugs right and
those little guys you know and they
colonize in there
now you might be somebody who says oh i
got a good good practitioner i got a
good doctor i'm all these gut health
protocols
all these probiotics well good
microorganisms
they don't fight bad microorganisms
so good bacteria doesn't fight bad
bacteria they don't care about each
other
you can put all the good bacteria you
want inside your gut all the good
probiotics
inside your gut you can put anything you
want inside there
it's all good right microorganism world
and guess what you can put it all in
but it doesn't care or go against or
defend you from the bad bugs
the bad bugs just sit there doing their
thing they'll still cause harm
to still create more pockets they'll eat
away at your lining over the year scar
it up
cause scar tissue right and they'll
cause problems
they'll multiply multiply release toxins
because of it
keep you more sick and toxic but you can
put all the good microorganisms you want
inside your body and it's not going to
defend you
at all against the bad stuff and
that's one of the things you can stay
sick you can go do all the gut health
protocols you want but you stay
sick if you're really sick you're going
to stay sick over time
or get sick again because the bad stuff
is always in there
and um why don't they ever see this
stuff during colonoscopies
we're talking microscopic levels right
we're talking the
microscopic world that's why right
but i've talked to surgeons there's a
lot of stuff inside there's a lot of
putrified linings
with rancid fats petrified proteins in
the gut
and the the scope just goes right by it
it's it's all there
on the lining of the walls but what you
mistake
what happens is what you mistake if you
ever look at the pathway of the camera
going in
you think you're looking at your
intestinal tract lining
but we're looking at a layer over the
just keep that in mind and then when a
polyp comes out of that intestinal tract
lining when a polyp pops out
they'll see the polyp but you're still
going to have a layer
of all the putrified proteins putrefied
rancid fat you're still going to have
that there
there's still that layer and it's in
pockets too when that scope goes around
and everything
it's not catching every pocket every
bend that's important to know right
there
okay and the majority of the garbage
is up here that's the majority of the
garbage
it's up here it's all in this area here
and then you have plenty of it in other
areas too
but what people mistaken i've talked to
a colon surgeon about that
he says what people don't understand is
you're right he said
that lining is not technically the
lining that the camera is looking at
that's a lining of
of putrified junk that's adhered
it's adhered to your colon and
intestinal tract no one
gets to see a fresh colon lining
when they're doing a scope you've got
years of the junk all stuck to the sides
and that's one of the things to know but
the microscopic world
the cameras can't see the microscopic
world no way the scope going up their
rounds not looking at the microorganisms
and if the good and bad ones are doing
their thing um
anyway if you're sensitive with the
celery juice and you're having diarrhea
you're having loose bowels build
yourself up
do a little bit two to four ounces or
ask your doctor what's right for you
okay that's fine ask your doctor what's
right for you
you can do that it's perfectly fine
um but anyway you guys just wanted to
let you know that
82 dollars off which is
incredible right it's 25 off but 82
is the break you get but it's at a
megajuicers.com
omega megajuicers.com
and that's where the sale is and it's
mm-900 hds so you know if you don't get
the mm-900 hds you're not going to get
the juicer it squeezes
all the juice out you're going to get
another juicer that doesn't squeeze as
much juice out
and that defeats the purpose of what
you're trying to do
you're trying to get a juicer to pay for
itself
and yeah that's the key you guys i'm
heading over to ig
instagram and i'm gonna turn tick tock
back on and i'm gonna turn
clubhouse back on so i'm heading over
there now so i look forward to it i hope
you guys come with me
and we'll talk about those sodium
cluster salts a little bit more i want
to cover more that i actually forgot to
cover
just now so about how it works inside
the celery juice
and all that stuff so you guys i'm
heading over to ig in a few minutes
gonna turn tick tock back on so you guys
stay on and i'm gonna have the clubhouse
back on too
i love you guys