we're making the Mexican potato hash and
we're doing the medical medium shock
therapies but we're specifically doing
the medical medium aloe shock therapy
you don't want to miss this stomach
problems anybody digestive problems acid
reflux gastric pain burning stomach
ulcers AG pylori anything else did
anybody get diagnosed with gastritis
we're talking about aloe vera lifesaving
tool but it's all about how you use it
I'm going to teach you guys a lot of
different tricks on how to use aloe vera
it's going to be really fun we're going
to talk about how you eat it we might
blend it in some water we're going to
talk about what it can do for us all of
it this is going to be a big deal we're
going to read a little bit out of the
book on the medical medium shock
therapies going to talk about stomach
problems and stomach issues and we're
making the Mexican potato hash this is
going to be incredible a great episode
right here hope you guys relax sit down
enjoyed if you if you have the book
already we we're looking at the wrong
thing really quick let's go find it now
if you guys that's why I like being live
if you guys actually have the book on
hand and you actually have the Mexican
potato hash with you that's totally
awesome hey let's start putting it
together I'm excited but we got a lot to
cover a lot to talk about stomach
problems wow I know I know
ooh
o hold on hold
on got some flatulence that's trying to
move through me and uh guys just have to
be like patient patient here with me
here I just got to kind of like sit over
here for a second I got to get that gas
out so just bear with me right now I
know it gets in the way um that happens
to everybody all the time out there
people have stomach problems they
they're like holding in their farts
they're holding in their gas they're
holding in their
flatulence I mean they're holding it all
in if they're around people their
stomach is cramping and they're crossing
their legs they're trying to keep the
farts in they're trying to keep the gas
in they're trying to make sure it stays
in because they have all kinds of stuff
going on what they have going on all
kinds of different things if they went
to the doctor and the doctor why we
don't know really what's wrong with you
you can have this you can have that all
of it a lot of people have different
things but bacteria is one of those
things right there
bacteria causing problems in the
intestinal tract viruses causing trouble
in the intestinal track big big stuff
right there so right here I'm going to
bring this
over let's go into a little bit if you
guys just got on here we're doing
medical medium shock therapies but
specifically we're doing medical medium
Alo shock therapy a lifesaving tool all
kidding aside on all levels it is a life
saving tool for so many people that
couldn't eat who have food sensitivities
chemical sensitivities problems with
their digestion they don't know what to
eat they're having stomach pain after
they eat they're suffering every day
with either a bloating cramp issue
gastric spasms all kinds of different
diagnoses with their stomach from sibo
to gas you know Gast gastritis to
Crohn's citis to IBS you know
flip-flopping to all three of those
sometimes just hey you got H pylori or
we don't know what's wrong with you but
so many people struggle and suffer
inside their gut diverticulitis
diverticulosis another great thing we're
going to talk about with this right here
ulcers this in my hand is a life-saving
tool for so many people out there if you
know how to use it you know how to do
the medical medium Alo shock therapy and
know how to apply this it is mindblowing
lifechanging for a lot of people I
believe there's a whole whole bunch of
people that are going to watch this
right here and watch the replay on this
and they're going to learn what how to
use this what's in my hand and they're
going to be like oh my god I've been to
20 doctors they didn't know how you know
to get my bloating down or my cramping
down or my my gastritis that keeps on
coming back I've done all the different
antibiotics for my sibo and my problems
with my intestinal tract problem my
microbiome doctor is telling me I have
this wrong that wrong I've tried all the
different pills and formulas and
everything and the antibiotics
and then boom suddenly they learn how to
do Alo shock therapy and their life
changes it is
mindblowing their life changes so I want
to just give you a little rundown really
quick I got an intestinal track in front
of me right here in front of you too and
what happens to people is bacteria over
time creates so much gas because it's
feeding off of things that it loves to
eat now over time Pockets develop in the
small intestinal tract expansions feal
matter starts to build up it gets
trapped In Pockets the pockets grow they
stretch and they
expand and in those Pockets more
bacteria lives lives happily it feeds
has a Feeding Frenzy it hides underneath
fecal matter undigested proteins it
hides under hardened encased fat that
sticks to the lining of the intestinal
tract and the colon and the bacteria has
a field day in there it produces ammonia
and other gases toxic gases those toxic
gases put pressure on the intestinal
tract lining when that pressure is on
the intestinal tract lining expansion
occurs elasticity starts to go away the
actual lining of the intestinal tract
starts to
weaken very important to understand and
as it starts to weaken expansions and
Pockets
develop and then we have more and more
problems with our intestinal tract
gastric spasms peristaltic action issues
pain burning
cramping it can be so debilitating it
could leave somebody in fetal position
on a daily basis after they go to
bathroom before they go to bathroom and
then there's the whole I didn't go to
bathroom enough I feel like I'm not
finished that's a whole another problem
all on its own I feel like I haven't
gone to bathroom enough like not enough
came out of me I didn't defecate enough
I didn't eliminate enough huge thing
that happens to people every day out
there they don't feel
satisfied and that's the thing they're
satis they're satisf action when we go
to the bathroom it's like we feel like
we emptied everything out we feel good
about it we feel like everything's
working okay the Plumbing's working okay
we feel good about it but then our trust
starts to break when it's not working so
good and our stool doesn't feel right or
a lot of our stool doesn't come out just
some of it and we feel bloated and
inflamed and all hung up in there if you
guys just got on here we're talking
about medical medium aloe shock therapy
one of the most powerful medical medium
tools one of the most powerful medical
medium tools and a life-saving one I've
seen people with crohn's colitis about
to get surgery mystery intestinal tract
problems for years do Alo shock therapy
and free themselves from surgery I've
seen it I've witnessed it I know doctors
who have seen it and witnessed it
through the medical m information so
this is probably one of the most
profound
episodes medical medium history right
here we're going to talk about how to
use aloe I'm excited and we're going to
have some fun make a Mexican potato hash
too so let's get into it a little bit
more in the intestinal tract and the
colon okay
so I want to move this
over
all right let's get into
it so we eat our food we eat our food
goes down into our stomach our HCL is
not strong enough doesn't break down the
proteins enough proteins drop into the
dadum from the dadum they enter the
small intestinal tra not properly
digested not properly broken down from
there
the proteins start to rot and then we
get gut rot with that gut rot is ammonia
a gas that's produced from the rotting
food the rotting food attracts
menaces those
menaces are
bacteria
viruses yeast fungus unproductive fungus
even some different varieties of
mold but either way one thing's for
certain bacteria is going to lead the
way and it's going to be the one that
actually starts to feed off of all the
food that's rotting the undigested
proteins that are rotting as bacteria
feeds off of those undigested proteins
the bacteria
releases gas and toxins and spews and
releases excrement the bacteria
basically poops out
the excrement poops out the undigested
proteins the food and then now it's more
toxic than ever before and producing
more gas than ever before as this
process is happening pockets and
expansion start to occur in the small
intestinal
tract these pockets and expansions make
it so then we feel like we got a
stitch we actually have a stitch like
ooh what is this this is like whoa I
kind of feel this after I went to the
bathroom I don't know why this kind of
hurts these are what I call stitches not
the kind of stitches when you cut
yourself and you go and you get sutured
up not those kind of stitches stitches
where they feel like a sharp knife
jabbing you or like a pricker bush
inside of you or something where it's
sharp and Jagged and it gets you for a
minute and then it moves on along after
a little
while that Stitch can shift and now that
Stitch isn't up here anymore on the left
side now that Stitch is down lower on
the left side or that Stitch is down rer
on the right side down rer on the right
side down lower but the Stitch can move
and shift around so as our food is
rotting inside of our gut producing
ammonia gas and then a Feeding Frenzy
occurs bacteria mainly feeding off all
the different undigested proteins and
and the foods you're eating as this
keeps on going every single day week
after week week after week we get
expansions but we get expansions before
we get narrowing and narrowing is
another topic right here that's very
important
expansions are the first thing that
occurs and then narrowings come later
now how does a narrowing occur inside
the intestinal tract and what is a
narrowing it's when the intestinal tract
back starts to shrink in an area think
about a pipe and in that pipe a part of
the pipe has a different diameter a
smaller diameter so as food's going
through it ends up hitting a narrowing
but before we go into the narrowing I
want to finish up with the expansions
first thing that happens in people with
digestive problems is they get pockets
and
expansions so that means the intestinal
tract is pocketing out this isn't
diverticulosis or diverticulitis this
can be a healthy intestinal track that's
actually expanding from pressure not
just feal matter pressure that's
building up but ammonia gas pressure
from pathogens like the bacteria feeding
off of undigested
proteins as the expansion occurs to
regularly the the lining of the
intestinal tract the wall weakens when
the lining starts to
weaken we end up getting a narrowing the
reason why is because the lining is now
too
weak the flexibility goes the opposite
direction goes inward instead of
outward because the lining was stretched
so as Pockets develop in the small
intestinal tract and the Linings are
stretched CU these pockets are
outpocketing the lining weakens and then
Falls
in and so as it falls in we now have
narrowing so what happens to people with
stomach problems and intestinal problems
they have pockets and narrowing so they
have some parts of the intestinal tract
where it gets
narrow some parts of the intestinal
tract it's wider and a pocket and this
can change and shift in different parts
of the intestinal tra over time but it
causes a lot of problems chronic
gastritis chronic gas chronic bloting
chronic stitches gastric spasms chronic
IBS chronic
constipation chronic
diarrhea we got all these different
issues because of what's Happening
inside inside the intestinal tract now
that's the intestinal tract I'm talking
about I'm not talking about the Elum and
then the ascending colon and then the
descending colon and then eventually out
the door I'm not talking about that
that's a whole another problem where
bacteria loves to sit now when people
get a sibo diagnosis what they're really
getting is a strep diagnosis inside the
intestinal tract inside the gut so when
someone goes to the doctor or the
practitioner and they say hey you got
sibo take this antibiotic you're blow in
this let's do a blood test let's do this
and that let's try to determine what you
have let's do a stol sample let's look
at some urine and in the end they'll
just be like well you have
sibo you have small intestinal bacterial
overgrowth
right but what kind of bacteria is it
the bacteria that's leading the way even
over sea diff inside people's guts is
Strep strep is that one bacteria that
reeks havoc and people have more
varieties than one
they'll have 10 varieties of strep
they'll have the strep that gave them
strep throat they'll have the strep that
gives them acne all over the place
they'll have the strep that gives them
stomach problems they'll have the strep
that gives them
UTI bladder infections and kidney
infections or commonly known as a yeast
infection which really is a strep
infection where there's yeast Gathering
but the St is the root
cause so what people do is they'll do an
antibiotic protocol maybe they'll start
with that then they'll be told lots of
lots of
probiotics and lots of prebiotics so
they'll be on all these probiotics and
all these
prebiotics and they'll be doing and
they'll be back and forth of this is
they get more stomach problems they
start to go away then they get stomach
problems again they get gastritis again
bloating constipation cramping diarrhea
IBS irritable bow syndrome which amazes
me because the
industry named it irritable bowel
syndrome made everybody think they
actually knew what was wrong but they
didn't it was just you got an irritable
vow that's all they had to offer was Sir
ma'am you got an irritable vow that was
it so people walk around with an IBS
diagnosis for years they're like well I
got IBS I got IBS well what is it oh
it's uh the doctor said it's IBS it's
irritable vowel syndrome so what the
doctor's saying is you have an irritable
bowel not why do you have an irritable
bowel or this is what's irritating it
and so forth Celiac suffers all the
same people walk around with a diagnosis
but they don't know what's causing it
Crohn's colitis Celiac
IBS gastritis it's another one all on
its own gastritis what's behind
it what's behind most of these
conditions is the bacteria and strep BAC
bacteria SEI can cause some problems
with people but CI is either on or it's
off it's hot or it's cold strep is hot
all the time and warm so it's always
there it's always wreaking havoc because
people don't know how to rid it or clean
it up or get rid of it and it waks Havoc
it sits inside their intestinal tract
forever and it causes problems so if you
guys just got here we're doing aloe vera
shock therapy you see a blender here cuz
I might pull off some aloe vera water
but I'm I'm going to show you though
different ways of eating aloe show you
some tips and how to cut it what you're
doing how you're not doing the green
skin so stick around because we got some
stuff to do and we got some ground to
cover right now we're talking about
digestive problems inflammation inside
the small intestinal tract and
colon and we can even talk about stomach
problems too for a little bit we might
head into there now
so I have a stomach in my hand right
here and inside a stomach are stomach
glands the stomach glands or gastric
glands they have to stay strong they
have to be superpowered that's your
gastric juice your gastric juices a big
part of how we break down our food break
down our proteins all of the above with
food they weaken in people people are on
coffee and vinegar and all kinds of
other things and they're under a lot of
stress and their gastric glands start to
get beaten down broken down and they
can't break down their food their HCL is
non-existent so their food is passing
through them and starting to rot as we
talked about
before another thing that people are
dealing with that are have gut problems
is liver issues so the minute someone
gets diagnosed with any kind of gut
issue whatsoever cron colitis IBS
gastric problems stomach cramps
gastritis whatever it is you have to
think liver is going to be
involved a weak stagnant sluggish
overburdened overworked liver that's
what's involved right there
and a liver that's getting fatty a fatty
liver even if it's not diagnosed such
livers are fatty before getting a fatty
liver
diagnosis you can have a liver issue
without having elevated enzymes liver
enzymes you can have a liver issue long
before there's an elevation of liver
enzymes important key to know might be
like hey my liver enzymes are good
doctor said I'm fine but I still got the
cramping and the bloating and my stomach
hurts or the burning in my stomach or
extra gas or my bathroom isn't right
however you see it or feel it the liver
plays a role so stagnant slish livers
and what happens is that strep bacteria
will sit and live inside the liver along
with other pathogens such as viruses and
so forth but the bacteria the strep live
in the liver it'll live in a
gallbladder it'll live in your stomach
it'll live live in your small testal
track your colon and it'll live right
outside your
anus right outside someone's anus strep
loves to be
there and it ends up on people's hands
and when it ends up on people's hands it
ends up on everything from grocery store
shopping carts the door handles to
everything else someone touches if
they're not washing their hands enough
they'll have the strep on their hands
and strep is interesting because when
people don't wash their hands and they
have it on their anus and they get it
back on their hand they end up putting
it back on their anus from their hand it
goes back and forth a symbiotic
relationship from somebody's hand to
their anus the strep passes back and
forth that's how how actually
tricky strep
is and crafty it is too all right let's
go into some aloe vera let's move a
little bit
just giving us a little bit of a rundown
on how gut
health to jrea
Works let's get into some
aloe to make some
room and I'm going to get a blade
out here we go little pairing knife
right here
onig the video was paused if the the
video is paused you can go to
medicalmedium.com watch this live right
on medicalmedium.com you can watch it
live on Rumble right now you can watch
it live on Tik Tok right now too ig's
having problems Tech problems over there
at IG so they're just everybody's
getting kicked off they're keeping our
numbers really low on there um we went
up to like a th000 when we turned it on
and then everybody was getting kicked
off and it went down to 700 so
anyway try those other places can watch
it on YouTube live too that's where we
are but you don't want to miss this
medical mum shock therapy going to talk
about it a little bit we're going to do
the Alo in a second so let's get down to
it I want to go into the section of the
book where it's medical medium shock
therapy it's like one of my favorite
sections of the medical medium
books and I'm going to it as we speak
let's see if we can find it here we are
medical medium shock therapies so if you
want to know what book it is it's the a
protocols book if you don't have this
book it's a great book to have give it
to somebody for the holidays Christmas
gift Thanksgiving whatever have it there
family gatherings or just give it to a
friend it's an incredible life-saving
tool this book is packed with
information it's not just the heavy
metal detox um cleanse it's not just the
advanced heavy metal detox cleanse it's
the shock therapies it's so much more
it's protocols supplemental protocols
teaches you how to heal teaches you how
to get better and move yourself forward
medical medium shock
therapies okay these are powerful
healing tools to rebuild your immune
system by fueling it with what it needs
to fight an infection why are people
sick why are people sick they just
magically get sick that's it magically
get sick that's it you're okay one day
and then you got a problem and that's
all that's all she wrote that's it what
you'll see here is these are powerful
healing tools to rebuild your immune
system immune system by fueling it with
what it needs to fight fight for you an
infection fight an
infection when you actually take in this
information the power it has now if I
was sick and I was going here to De door
to door wherever trying to get an answer
trying this and trying that and I was on
Tik Tok looking for the hack of the day
and I was just looking for something to
heal me and I just didn't know really
what was going on and I learned that I
had an
infection right there something happens
inside the brain something happens
inside the body like boom I got an
infection whoa that means I have to heal
that infection what is this infection
what's going on what tools do I need our
immune system needs to be strong all
these things
count okay
even in emotional challenges the shock
therapies help us digestive problems and
so forth rebuilding our systems and
fortifying our systems and immune
systems medical medum shock therapies
have a profound record of helping people
overcome serious health obstacles you
guys just got here reading out of
protocols if you don't have the book
you're missing
out these supplement therapies can be
useful for almost anything you're ailing
with medical medium shock therapies are
powerful whether you're up against
intense stress or need a shift from a
longstanding chronic illness roller
coaster ride who's been on the roller
coaster ride of chronic illness like
who's been on that ride I
like got a doctor's
appointment yep everything's going okay
ch ch ch I still feel sick ch ch ch ch
ch ah
[Music]
my
God who's on the roller coaster ride
right there right are they upside down
loop-de-loop roller coaster
ride
yeah medical medium shock
therapies are critical to this day and
age where there's Co there's flu there's
the like there's all of it there's epin
bar in every corner everybody's passing
bugs around we get exposed by everything
from toxins to
pathogens we're bombarded by fragrances
that are literally like gassing people
to death the stuff is so
toxic medical beam shock therapies are
critical for this day and age oh yeah
that's right though you're not up
against any of that no you're one of
those people that are not up against any
of that no not at all everything's good
until it's not everything's great until
you get sick everything's perfect till
it isn't
anymore a Darkness try as Darkness tries
to destroy all all that's good we Rise
Against Darkness using light created
Health weapons to regain
empowerment that's just so so powerful
name of the book somebody was asking is
medical medium brain saver protocols
when you read this book you you will be
mind blown it's nothing like anything
you've ever seen seriously go to Amazon
it's I saw it was like I don't know 40
or 50% off or something like that crazy
on Amazon don't quotee me on that but
it's it's on sale on Amazon right
now as a Changing Times bring additional
stress upon us has has The Changing
Times brought any additional stress upon
you guys because The Changing Times is
pretty rough and it's brought stress
upon me throughout my life the
quickening and everything are things
happening fast out there right now
things are happening at lightning Pace
right now that's how crazy it is out
there
as The Changing Times bring additional
stress Upon Us humankind goes into a
deeper Health deficit than during
previous
decades sickness now dominates the lives
of billions of people did you hear that
sickness now dominates people's
lives billions of people now on this
planet sickness dominates their life why
do you see why do you think you see
people on social that you would have
never saw even 8 years ago 10 years ago
on social
media why do you see that 10 years ago
you didn't see 181 19y olds 20 year olds
freaking out they were so they're so
sick and they're on social media like I
just got diagnosed with lime and fibro
and chronic fatigue syndrome and I got
all kinds of problems and I got acne and
this and that like it's out of
control it's out of control sickness now
dominates the lives of billions of
people Medical medium shock therapies
are here to help level the playing field
baby level the playing field where
chemical and medical Industries are
playing dirty against humankind you
don't think they're playing dirty
against you you don't think they're
playing dirty you guys know what's up
you know what's happening out there you
know how the industries work you got a
good idea you know the dirty games
that's going on with People's
Health it's crazy so the medical medium
shock therapy there's a zinc shock
therapy which is really powerful I'm not
going to go into that right now cuz
we're doing aloe vera shock therapy
today there's so many powerful ones
right here there's the vitamin C shock
therapy which is really incredible
there's the lemon bomb shock therapy for
nerves which is amazing there's the
golden seal shock
therapy there's the time tea shock
therapy there's the propolis shock
therapy which is so sick so good and
helpful there here's the aloe vera shock
therapy many people struggle with gastro
problems gastro problems gastr pain
gastric issues gastric problems
intestinal pain that radiates all
through the abdomen torso without
realizing that it originates from the
stomach or intestinal tract you know
what people can literally have gastric
problems that take them out in the
shoulder right here the
shoulder they think they have shoulder
pain they think something's wrong with
their shoulder and then it goes
away it hits them takes out a shoulder
and they're just like oh my God my
shoulder why is it hurting so much oh
right up here in my shoulder it's a
stomach issue it's an intestinal tract
issue it takes them out on the shoulder
and there's people where it takes them
out boom in their neck and shoulder like
takes their neck out and their shoulder
there's people where it takes their
upper back out their upper back just get
taken out and it's their stomach in
intestinal tract and it's taking out
their shoulder and their upper back what
do I mean by taking out I mean you're in
pain you're just like what's going on
it's after I ate or before I ate or I
got too hungry or I'm not hungry enough
whatever it is that's going on people it
hits them hard and it hits them in the
strangest places you couldn't
believe I just couldn't
believe aloe vera has chemical compounds
that neutralize acid and Cal nerves in
the intestinal tract lighting so let's
go into a little bit we're going to be
showing you how to use aloe we still got
a Mexican potato hash to make which I'm
pumped up about all right so let's hit
the intestinal track a little bit real
quick here important to know
right
so that intestinal tract is lined with
nerves little tiny nerves that
eventually find their way two bigger
nerves and so all these little nerves
that are in in the intestinal tract
lining become hot I call them
hotpots for over three decades been
teaching people how to heal their gut
how to heal their intestinal tract and
it's a term that came from Spirit of
compassion long time ago where it's hot
spots in the intestinal tract hot spots
are little inflamed areas of the
intestinal tract lining that are
saturated with nerves and when anything
touches them the the nerves light right
up boom they light
up so you got food going through here or
a gas bubble going through here and the
minute that gas bubble touches one of
those hot
spots the whistle
Blows the Whistle blows the minute
something moves a piece of food
something happens something shifts or
peristaltic action occurs where all of a
sudden now your intestinal tract is
twisting it's twisting because it's
trying to move the food through a
message is coming from your brain right
to your intestinal tract lining and it's
twisting and try to get the message
through and get the food through and
when that happens hot spots occur and
you're like whoa whoa or oh whoa or oh
whoa and then you can be somebody that's
inflamed in one area right down here in
the Elum a lot of people are inflamed in
the
Alum and as they're inflamed in the
elium down here deep right that little
section it stops food from passing
through easy so then they get bloated
and all the gas gets trapped in here and
builds up all the gas gets built up and
trapped in here it doesn't even reach
the colon your gas is way up high all
trapped
here we're in aloe vera shock
therapy all right Al has chemical
compounds that neutralize acid and calm
nerves in the intestinal tract Linings
slowing down and stopping intestinal
spasms so the goal with the aloe is to
slow down and stop intestinal tract
spasms aloe neutralizes acids and
inhibits bacteria and viral growth as
well as yeast unproductive fungus and
mold
growth she got all these people
something's growing inside of
them all these people out there and
something's growing inside their gut
unproductive fungus bacteria multiple
strains of
bacteria aund different strains of
bacteria that could not be good ones but
they're bad
ones unproductive fungus even
unproductive mold growth but a lot of
people have stuff growing inside their
guts and they can bombard the [__] out
of their guts with probiotics they can
try this probiotic and this one and this
gas thing and this whatever and this and
they can do all the pill popping they
want and they can do all the powders
they want they can do all the
antibiotics they want and they can just
put stuff down and because they want to
heal their gut and it's not going to do
the
trick everything in there that's growing
that shouldn't be growing is growing and
growing and
growing it's why the medical medium
protocols in general
in general are so powerful like The
Liver Rescue smoothie heavy metal detox
smoothie the monoc cleans like all of
these different parts and tools for
medical medium information that's why
they're so powerful like the celery
juice because it inhibits and it's it
knocks down that bacteria it knocks down
that fungus that's
unproductive so let's go into this a
little bit suggested
applications for medical medium aloe
vera shock therapy for go in that one to
read a little bit more aloe vera also
sooes the Linings of the intestinal
tract calming inflamed intestinal tract
nerves back to that again our nerves get
inflamed inside of our gut it causes
these hot spots to occur things light up
and you're hurting you're bloating
hurting cramping
burning in
trouble all
right suggested applications for medical
medium aloe vera shock therapy stomach
pain
pain gastro pain intestinal and stomach
pain that rises into the chest or runs
through the back and up to the neck and
shoulders like I was talking about
before gastric pain that runs up to the
shoulders to the neck up to the chest
heartburn heartburn what the hell is
that what the hell is
heartburn I love that one like what is
that greatest science in the world here
in the United States or on the planet
right in the west the greatest science
greatest science Minds in medicine it's
heartburn millions of people walked into
millions of people walked into their
doctor's
offices right doctors from the best
medical universities on the planet
scientists the best there is
right and they got a diagnosis of
heartburn what the is that heartburn
your your heart's burning your heart's
on fire it's burning is that what
heartburn
is but no instead they don't get it
gastric spasms low
HCL overgrowth of
bacteria peristaltic action hitting
nerves that are inflamed pockets and
narrowing and then what happens is
boom that pain
that wake rides up hits Us in the
shoulder hits Us in the neck hits us up
here in the chest hits us
here real
explanations understanding what's going
on in here is critical passing it off is
heartburn the 1940s you got heartburn
mister Mr Jones you have
heartburn Pi an
aspirin that was it and it carried all
the way until the microbiome guys kicked
in which is the functional medicine
doctor microbiome guys and they're just
bombarding everybody with probiotics
like just gous it with this here take
another bottle of probiotics take this
gut health product take this take
this that's like the same
[__] just different
day Crohn's kitis IBS Celiac acid reflux
ulcers stomach burning each pyl who's
had H
pylori what I love about medical medium
aloe shock
therapy is it's incredible for h
pylori sibo who's ever had sibo anybody
get a diagnosis of sibo this is
incredible incredible tool for sibo
stomach pain I saw somebody else ask
what book it is brain saver protocols if
you don't have this you're missing out
amazon.com it's on sale right
now watch out for the impostor books
it's crazy stomach pain shortly after
eating a meal who gets stomach pain
shortly after eating a
meal who gets stomach pain shortly after
eating
anything intestinal cramping gastritis
severe bloting that's painful
constipation and what about
gastroparesis that one too I love aloe
vera shock
therapy for an adult consume 2 to four
inches a fresh aloe vera gel skin
removed every two to four waking hours
let's hit
it all
right so here's what I want to do right
here can we get a closeup up there we go
awesome
um all right there's your aloe leaf
right there just going to move stuff
away a little bit so we can kind of get
a focus there it is what I what I do is
you see this knife right here you guys
on IG you probably can't see the closeup
but everybody on YouTube Rumble right
you guys can see
it so what I'm going to do is cut this
piece off here little too bitter you can
use it if you really want but it's kind
of hard to use this area so I like to go
just just deep enough like this so I
discard this or you can use it you can
put it on your skin you can do that if
you want to put it on your skin you can
do that like you
know can save that
piece all right 2 to 4
in of aloe so what do we do we can
measure it if we want I just just call
it by I that's about 1 inch right it's 2
in somewhere around there 3 in 4 in so
you can do 2 in so let's do that first
okay so I'm going to cut it just like
that you guys with me right here here
guys with me next there's a little
sticker on here this one's a store
bought
one and this one's from my garden right
here I'm going to open that up in a
little bit too my garden one doesn't
look as nice as the store bought one but
it is nice though all right so I'm going
to remove that sticker right
there okay what you do is you take the
knife and you don't cut it completely in
half I don't like to do that I cut just
the
top part down and then I open it like
this see this you guys now check this
out you would think that and you could
if you wanted to you can think that you
can use this knife and then slice the
green off now just so you know you don't
want the green involved you don't want
to eat the
skin you don't want to have the skin
mixed up in a blender you don't want to
grind it up you don't want the green
skin you just want the gel inside now
I'm going to take a
spoon I'm using the spoon see how I got
the spoon this way not that way right I
don't have it facing down I have the
spoon facing up what I love about this
trick once you get the hang of this it's
the best way to do it I take the spoon
facing up I stick it under this lip
right
here and
then I keep the aloe
down and the skin up see what's
happening right here so I'm using a
spoon to fillet the skin look how cool
that is look at that right
there see what I
did there you
go then I can do the same thing here I
can actually fillet the skin with the
spoon the spoon facing
up now I cut that skin so that one's a
little weird there so it is what it is
but there you go so right now I have
that set up now I like to do shot
glasses put it in shot glasses it's one
option right there what I have right
here is a shot glass in front of me
check this
out that's one option the other option
is I just like to eat it with a spoon
that's what people should do they should
learn to eat it with a spoon
the aloe water is a great way to do it
and I'm going to show you how to make
that in a little while but I challenge
you to learn how to consume this in the
most potent
way the most potent way is not in the
water that's not the most powerful way
to use it to heal and to use it as a
powerful healing tool no the most
powerful way is eating a shrink
right here eating it straight so you
take the
spoon and you go down and you scoop it
right off like that and that's the most
the best way to eat it is this way and
that's the most powerful
way
yeah H to taste really good if you don't
like the taste of
aloe over time you'll learn about it and
mean mean sorry over time you'll
acclimate to the flavor and you'll start
to enjoy it and you'll start liking it
now I'm going to put in a shot glass now
you got the shot glass right
here so I'm going to take this next
piece with a
spoon and I'm going to put it in the
shot glass just like that now you can
actually scrape down to the skin and get
a little bit more but remember this the
closer you get to the skin the more
bitter it
is like medicine bitter so the closer
you get to the skin to get the aloe and
I do that I scrape it down to the skin
but I know that a lot of people aren't
going to like that because it's going to
have like what feels like a nasty
taste when it's down to the skin so you
can you don't have to do that you don't
have to scrape it down you just
don't but what you do is you can make a
shot glass right here you can put them
in the fridge and you can have it set up
so when you're doing medical medium aloe
vera shock therapy and you're doing it
every two
hours you're doing it every four hours
you can actually just have it in shot
glasses prepared ready just like this so
I'm going to move this over just's cut
another
piece
okay all right now couple of things to
know
As you move down this
Leaf it's going to turn pink or red so
if you keep this in your fridge it's in
there for a long time the aloe leaf will
eventually start to oxidize and it'll
start turning pink or red and it usually
turns pink or red down by the tail in
the lower
sections so if you're you're trying to
keep the aloe around longer for like a
week in the fridge or two weeks in the
fridge or something like that you might
want to start eating from bottom up
believe it or not where you cut the tail
off discard that cuz that's hard to
really get that aloe out unless you
squeeze it out and you use it for
something for skin or so forth
right all right so let's go let's cut
another piece now 2 in you can do a 4 in
now I like bigger pieces like
this right there see that I like a nice
big piece like that so I'll show you one
more time how to do this and we'll pop
this in the
blender so I'm going to take the knife
and I'm going to cut right here on top
I'm not going to cut deep I'm not going
to go like that okay I'm going to cut
right on the top just the
surface like
this open it up just like that take a
look right once again you take the spoon
face the spoon up this is the best way
to do it I promise you this is the best
way to do it when you play with aloe
this is the only way to do it take the
spoon facing
up and you follow the skin like this
there you
go right on down it doesn't get any
better than that that's the way you
fillet a fish an aloe fish it's not a
fish and then I'll get the other side
right
now once you learn
this there you go that's how you fillet
aloe vera right there until this day
I've never seen anybody do it that way
out there never seen it
ever and it's the best way by far to do
it so let's go into this a little
bit um
so let's talk about like how often to
eat it and so forth medical medium Aliva
shock therapy directions in protocols
make sure you get this book if you can
go to the library and get it for free I
don't care I don't care if you go to the
library and get it for free just get the
book for free
then that's fine or Amazon on sale but
make sure you have the brains saer
protocols for an adult consume 2 to 4 in
that's 4 in probably 5 in right there 2
to 4 in a fresh Alo vera gel skin
removed you saw how I did that every two
to four waking hours so you wake up in
the morning you
start every 2 to four waking
hours this is for a cute attacks people
got a a cute gallbladder spasm a cute
maybe they're going to the doctor all
the time the doctor's like you you're
having gallbladder problems come back
and visit me in a month we'll check it
out we'll take a look at your
gallbladder and you're having these
acute attacks or chronic ones this is
when you can do you can do an aloe vera
shock therapy and you can really take
this on if your doctor allows it ask
your doctor what's right for
you okay continue this therapy for 1 to
7 days you can do aloe ver shock therapy
anywhere from 1 to 7
days I have helped so many people over
the years with aloe vera shock
therapy having them eat the the the
shock therapy aloe after meals so I'm
going to talk about that area too let's
go into it after three or four days off
elevator shock therapy you're welcome to
cycle through 1 to 7 days again so if
you're somebody and you're doing your
first day you do it for 7 days you can
take a few days off cycle again for
another 7
days you can do two or more inches of
fresh aloe vera gel daily or twice a
week it's another thing too you don't
have to do the shock therapy where
you're in this crisis or you want to do
it every 2 to 4 hours cuz you're in this
crisis you're really inflamed maybe
you're somebody with colitis and you had
a relapse with your colitis and it
you're so inflamed and you're suffering
that could be a time to do also the the
shock therapy you could do the shock
therapy you're somebody with chronic
gastritis but you're welcome just to do
it daily where you buy aloe and you're
doing a piece of aloe every single day 2
oz every single day okay to prepare the
aloe gel carefully slice open your 2 to
4 inch piece of aloe vera leaf I love
how the directions are actually in here
trimming away the green spikes now what
you'll see is I did not trim away the
green
spikes you might be somebody where you
actually know kind of like to stay away
from these you just don't don't grab it
like squeeze on the spikes or anything
like that and you'll see um I'll show
you twoo like this these spikes some of
them are just razor sharp like a cactus
I mean they're just really sharp some
are kind of dll these are a little bit
more dull on the dull side but
anyway make sure you do not use the skin
as you're scooping out the Alo gel try
not to scrape to the skin like I taught
you before the chemical compound in the
green skin can be irritating for some
people so you don't want to eat the skin
I can't tell you how many people I'm
like you got to do some aloe it's going
to really help and they take the skin
and everything they throw it in the
blender and then I think even somebody
on social like I don't know if it was a
year ago or two years ago they were
showing people how to eat aloe or
something it was like a chef and they
just threw the whole leaf in the blender
skin in all and spikes in all and I was
like oh man I was like holy crap that's
not good I I feel bad for anybody eating
that right there I was like oh my God I
mean I was scared for people because it
could be
irritating I was I was just don't know
why people do
that and eat the gel straight if
possible for best results but if you
have to put it in the fridge in a shot
glass or a little glass bowl you can do
that remember cut off the very edge as I
talked about and discard that it's way
too
bitter okay so that's some of the tips
right here which are really cool you're
welcome to prepare all of your aloe gel
for the day at once you can do that as
well put it in airtight airtight
container in the
fridge if you're storing a partial Leaf
wrap the cut end in a damp towel or
plastic wrap if you really want and
place it in the refrigerator avoid Alo
leaves where the gel is very red inside
like tomato red inside okay it's
oxidized it's just going bad so keep
that in mind these leaves aren't fresh
they're starting to Decay when doing the
aloe vera shock therapy eat it straight
or Blended in water do not add to
smoothies it doesn't work the same when
it's added to smoothies very important
piece of
information all right
let's
roll a little bit
here get this uh blender over here for a
moment yep plugged in ready to
roll let's scoop some
aloe make some aloe water you can do it
this way I love it this way too don't
get me wrong it's the second best option
versus eating it keep that in mind nice
it's getting
slippery but that's just how the story
goes all
right we got that in there let's add
some
water up to you on how much water you
want to add I don't like adding a
lot
so
all right that's
good you don't want to like fill your
blender like this High unless you have a
lot of aloe in there that's 4 in a
little bit more it's a really healthy
size
Leaf run let's
go
you guys on Instagram that's not us
kicking you guys off that's not the
medical medium
team that's Instagram kicking everybody
off see so you can go to Medical me.com
or rumble or Tick
Tock got your aloe water right here
there it
is now a lot of people would prefer this
they don't want the slimy texture of the
aloe they feel like it's too slimy it's
too um it's gross some people will just
think it's just gross
but the most powerful way to consume it
and eat it is like I was showing you
before taking it scooping it right out
eating it direct let's go into like when
to eat it after meals if you're somebody
that suffers with digestive problems
after they eat acid reflux gastric pain
bloating maybe burning in the stomach
that's a really good one too A lot of
people have ulcers or they're just
burning in the stomach because their
nerves are on fire because they're
inflamed so their intest inal nerves and
the nerves around their stomach are just
hotwired because they're inflamed and
because of that they're going to feel
like burning instantly or there's
somebody that's dealing with H pylori
they got mini ulcers that aren't even
detectable with an endoscopy not even
detectable in any way shape or form
maybe an ultrasound doesn't show
anything and they just have burning it's
mysterious burning going on that means
that you could have these little micro
Fishers they're just undetectable
they're really tiny from H pylori from
strep bacteria from different varieties
of bacteria in the gut and when that's
happening okay even viruses too like
viruses that are behind
colitis either way eating aloe directly
after eating food is an option so if you
had a meal of some kind whatever that
meal is do aloe if you had a melon do
aloe after melon if you had bananas do
melon do do aloe after banana Bas if you
had
apples do um your aloe after your apples
or maybe you had something else maybe
you had avocado maybe you had a salad
maybe you had fish maybe you had chicken
maybe you had a steak whatever it is
that you're eating and you got stomach
problems have the aloe directly after or
20 minutes after or half an hour after
and if you're experiencing gas pains or
any kind kind of other issues you can do
aloe then too doesn't even have to be
after you eat directly it could be when
you're experiencing a problem in the
moment maybe you're somebody where
you're bellowed over you're just in pain
like oh my God here it comes again and
you're feeling that pain it could be
then as well you might be someone who
needs to consume a leaf a day keep
open-minded on that and ask your doctor
what's right for you but you might be
someone that needs to do about a Leaf a
day or a half a leaf a day doing the
aloe vera shock therapy out of the
protocols
book and you're doing like a half a leaf
a day or a leaf a day keep open minded
about that too these things are no joke
all of these protocols tips suggestions
right here for people who are struggling
take them to your doctor ask them if
it's right for you bring the book to
your doctor healthcare provider
practitioner ask them if it's okay to do
it let's start some
potatoes and I forgot I have a shot
glass right here of some aloe
mhm FY good
M that's really
good bartender give me
another it's going to take time to learn
how to eat it that way for a lot of you
guys but man it's lifechanging It Coats
the stomach It Coats the intestinal
tract it inhibits growth of things that
are growing in there that shouldn't be
growing in there you guys check out
brainsaver protocols let's make a recipe
let's find the
recipe it's so soothing on the gut the
gut
lining it is so soothing you know it's
not soothing on the gut lining all the
makeshift crap out there that they're
selling for people guts and they're
dumping it in that's not soothing on the
gut lining bentonite clay with
probiotics zeolite with stuff fulvic
minerals fulvic acid humic acid right
chil every all this stuff people are
doing powders herbal powders and they're
just sending all this stuff down they're
mixing it up they're putting you know
whatever they're sending it down they're
popping pills scratches the the crap out
of your intestinal tract lining all of
that goes down in there scratches up the
lining doesn't inhibit anything from
growing everything still grows all the
same and you're doing all that and
you're back at the doctor's office and
now you're doing some antibiotic for
your stomach then you're back here
you're back there then you're everywhere
and meanwhile something that's soothing
for the lining the medical medium aloe
shock therapy
medical medium brains saer protocols
let's make the Mexican potato hash let's
see if we can make it
right all right got the pan on let's get
some potatoes on here boom throwing that
heat on
maximum that's right going to move my
aloe water I'll drink that later going
to get rid of this too I'm
excited I'm taking a shortcut I'm using
steamed potatoes the recipe calls for
raw
potatoes I'm taking a shortcut because I
wanted to first of all I had steamed
potatoes on hand second of all you know
we're just you know we're spending a lot
of time we'll be here for 4 hours if I
have to do it that way all right let me
move these over a little
bit let's make this happen got some
potatoes right here look at the size of
this potato this is crazy let's cut this
up I'm going to like do a little cubing
on this so what I'm going to do is I'm
going to cut it in half like that maybe
another here like
that I'm just going along with the
program here in the sense like you know
what I want them cubed so let me go
along with naturally happens right here
so then I'm going to cut it like
this cut it like
that and then maybe even cut it like
this I want these nice cubes here it's
not going to be perfect but we're going
to have something and then check this
out
boom look at this I might do a little
sawing action
here looking for a nice specific look to
it okay next one there all
right okay here we go see this like
little cubes now if it was a raw potato
those cubes would be like hard they
would be solid so you you have to
understand this is going to be a little
bit Messier because it's a steamed
potato all right look let's do this now
check this out okay there we
go ready guys we're going to cube these
up nice love that that one came out
really good there let's get another one
the size of this
potato it's a hot potato it's
hot it's not hot it's not hot it's good
it's good all
right let's cut these just
right there we
go
okay guys checking this out we're going
to do these cubes again I got the pan on
I got The Griddle
on griddle getting hot
there we
go now I'm going to cut these nice
little
squares there we
go for some reason that one really held
together really looked
good it's a starchy
potato let me get these pieces
here all right let's do another
one
nice okay let's try
it same same
technique you guys I really feel bad for
so many people out there suffering from
um intestinal track issues and stomach
problems I
mean I mean you guys know a lot of you
guys have gone through it or you're
going through it now it's really
difficult it's a lot of suffering if
unless you've been through it yourself
you'll never be able to explain it to
somebody else like you can tell people
and they'll just they'll just look at
you like what do you mean like go to the
doctor you know right did you ever have
that happen where you're you know you're
struggling you've been to the doctor
you've been places it's like go to the
doctor man why are you suffering with
that intestinal tract
problem you know people will say
that
it unless you really know what it's like
okay we're going to cut another one
here let you know what it's like it's
hard to explain to somebody like yeah I
have intestinal tract problems I can't
go to bathroom or I got the runs all the
time and I'm really struggling and I'm
in pain I'm gastric you my my system's
so screwed up and people are
like they look at you and be like well I
I had food poison at some point that's
the only way I can reference it that's
another thing too aloe vera shock
therapy for food poisoning recovery
chemical sensitive people when people
are chemical sensitive they're afraid to
do anything they're afraid to take
anything they're just so nervous they're
so scared and they do aloe
vera it's so gentle on them probably one
of the most gentlest powerful way for
somebody who's chemical sensitive they
got food sensitivities it's it's another
thing too but the problem is a food
sensitivi is you go to a doctor you get
the allat or you get like a food
sensitivity scan next thing you know it
they put aloe vera on the list you're
sensitive to aloe vera well I never had
aloe vera before they're like yep you're
sensitive to it then you lose an
opportunity to
heal I'm going to be using spices today
if you have digestive problems you don't
have to use the spices you don't have to
have the spices I'm going to be using
spices though
okay um if you're sensitive in any way
you can leave the spices out all right
or use less of them how about that use
less of them Pan's getting hot let's get
an
apparatus for the pan I think I'm going
to try this one
here okay
um basically what is like for the taco
seasoning there's all kinds of different
spices and all that you can minimize
those you can I'm going to put those in
now but I want to just make sure I have
enough potatoes I'm going to go with one
more I want to make sure I got a really
big dish of potatoes
here there we
go let's knock this
out
nice let's get these cubed up
boom not bad not
bad now now we're talking here this is
what I'm talking talking about you ever
hear anybody say that this is what I'm
talking
about all right got some seasoning in
here let's roll okay onion powder about
a tablespoon heavy on the onion powder
that's what I like to do the recipe
calls calls for that
nice nice all right let's get a little
bit of
cumin let's try
that here we are okay about two
teaspoons of ground
cumin you guys like cumin remember you
can keep a spice out you don't like
cumin that's fine nice this is going to
be insane it's going to taste great
paprika you'll notice there's no fat in
here where's the oil where's all the oil
it's not in here one teaspoon of paika
nice one teaspoon of
that smells so
good smells so good garlic powder come
on let's
roll
boom teaspoon of garlic
powder glic
powder
just kidding
around I just like to fold around this G
this garlic powder hardened up a little
bit
nice let's
go
boom move that over all right
chili powder we got
it little bit of
that all right let's keep it going red
pepper
flakes this one has never been
opened what I'm going to do is pop open
this part
here whoa
whoa yeah let's get some oregano in here
you
guys what's going
on it's going to taste really
good this is cooking nicely I'm going to
bring down the heat this thing is like
pumping
away
[Music]
okay mix it up a little
bit
okay I was thinking about today and I
was like you know what is this the dish
to make yeah there's nothing in here to
kill your
liver there isn't a whole bunch of oil
in here there's no grease in here
there's no butter in here there's no
pork fat in here this is fat free over
vert fat free which is incredible let's
make the
Pico let's
[Music]
go no pressure no
pressure all right let's go one cup
diced tomato I'm going to do a little
bit more than that let's get these
Tomatoes
rolling all right I don't want these
Tomatoes really um really big I want
them kind of like also like smaller size
so you don't have this massive piece of
you know
tomato let's dice these
up going to take a little extra minute
here but we'll do
it do you guys like tomatoes you're not
afraid of tomatoes right you know what's
crazy medical medium
information we crushed the night shade
fear you hardly hear a squeak or a peep
out of out of anybody about it now we
crushed
it you know what else medical medium
information did we crushed fruit fear
yeah there's still some people still
scared a little bit but we annihilated
it in the medical medium book series
millions millions of people around the
world saw the
information let's get this on here we
crushed The Nightshade fear you know
what else we crushed you still hear a
little bit of it right out there night
shades still hear a little bit of it we
crushed cruciferous fear that's medical
medium that did that information out
there we busted it no one was friendly
with cruciferous no one in the health
movement was we cracked that wide
open no one was friendly about fruit
fruit fear nobody was nobody was
friendly about night shades nobody in
Health nobody in the health Movement we
busted It Wide Open I took my lashings I
took my beatings I took I took the Flack
but we we crushed it we crushed
it and that's what we
did it it's actually a dead turkey out
there man you only hear once in a while
somebody squeak out there and they're
like but night shades night shades right
you only hear a couple of them out there
now or a couple of them like crucifer
cruciferous um goitrogen compounds right
you only hear a couple of
them but we crushed
it it's crazy what has happened with the
medical mum information fruit fear now
everybody even carnivore people are
eating fruit carnivore anti fruit people
now they're eating fruit that's how
that's how bad we like annihilated fruit
fear it just cracks me up because it's
it's movement forward in the health
world love
it cut a couple these bigger pieces down
a little bit there we
go all right just going to mix this up a
little bit you guys bear with me this is
coming together
nice smells so
good yeah keep that going
add a little bit more heat to that all
right what else did we knock
out we destroyed the liver flush you
know where you drink a gallon of olive
oil we annihilated that very few people
do that
anymore right we totally annihilated
that one
all in the good name of just making sure
we can protect people so they're not
hurting themselves that's what the
medical medium information has done it's
allowed people in the health movement to
eat fruit without getting like without
getting their brains bashed in about it
anyone who is eating a banana they would
just get attacked by everybody in health
the health movement all the health gurus
and stuff they'd be attacking you
weren't allowed to eat a banana you
weren't allowed to eat a berry years ago
even that it was like is it low glycemic
it's not low glycemic enough you can
only eat a green apple do you guys
remember that in the health movement
only a green apple was allowed and even
that was shunned upon you were
shunned you eat a green apple you were
borderline shunned you eat a red apple
man you were just you were like totally
totally you were totally shun guys
remember
that
yep okay
yeah let's get a few more
Tomatoes what
else guys remember that we destroyed the
lectin crap all the lectin stuff we
destroyed
it I don't hear too many people like
lectins lectins oxalates we totally took
oxalates out too the medical mum
information taught people about
oxalates very few people talk about
oxalates
anymore we're making the Mex Mexican
potato
hash I am at your service I am your Chef
for the day I am a hired Chef yes you
must be some very wealthy people you
have hired me I am your Chef
yep I'm I'm glad and happy to be
here I'm going to head off to the
farmers market to pick all your lovely
vegetables and your food and I'm going
to go to The Butchery and get your best
piece of meat butchered I'm going to
bring it back to your mansion and I'm
going to do chefing for you cuz I'm your
hired Chef for the
day oh no don't worry I got the cooking
covered you get your facials get your
massage yep do your steam
bath get your seaweed wrap on your body
your trainer's coming in good good have
your trainer come in make sure you get
your training and your workout in I will
slave away and do all the cooking here
at this
Mansion thank you for hiring me
on
okay looking
good okay let's chop up some
onions
onion
all
right I got an onion
here onion
here here we
go I said somebody yelled at me one time
and they like a w you you got to use the
skin on the onion you're losing all the
B vitamins you got to use the skin like
dude I'm not going to I'm not going to
force my guests or anybody else to try
to munch on that skin of the
onion okay you guys this is what I'm
making right here Mexican potato hash
here it is want to show you guys right
there on Tik Tok you guys hanging in
there for the ride
boom all right you guys are psyched or
what yep got a friend with us
too I have lots of guests
feed just peel the skin
back got an
onion here it
comes
no no
oh
no little
pieces my eyes are burning
already
[Music]
no get nice little pieces of this onion
here let's
go okay it's going in the
bowl
h
not
yet all right let's get some small
little cubes it's what I want to do
small little
[Music]
cubes all right you
guys what else did we knock out we
knocked out the canola oil baby medical
medium information knocked out the
canola oil on the
scene took years but we did
it mm info knocked out natural flavors
yeah it's in everything but I'm noticing
a lot of people are a lot of companies
are taking it out of stuff medical mem
info Donnie said all the major healers
are talking in mm terms but don't like
to admit it he is ahead of his time
thank you it's all because of so or I
would just be like
them
okay and I wouldn't know all right these
onions are going in
here I'm going to put a little bit more
onion in here
too this is coming out really
good we're going to make some incredible
cheese for this
too seriously thank you for recognizing
that I really appreciate it
seriously it might help somebody
actually use the information and work on
their healing
process there we go we did it get rid of
these we
[Music]
go
back
here what else did we Crush alcohol and
tinctures we crushed it very few people
are doing alcohol and tinctures and you
see people you know Guru is now like
don't do alcohol in your supplements
don't do alcohol in your tinctures that
came from medical medium don't do
alcohol in your supplements now we
crushed the alcohol in the tinure game
think about what we've accomplished you
guys all these
years the list goes on and on and on we
brought the term long coid into the
scene long flu long Co is originally
medical medum information and published
medical medum
information the list goes on and on and
on and on and on toxic heavy metals
being the cause of mental health
problems is medical medium
information we brought that to the
world and now clinics are taking the
info we published it first fragrances
and sended candles being bad for you
medical medium information goes all the
way back and we're crushing it because
now there's like doctors coming on Tik
Tok going stay away from scented candles
like they discovered that stay away from
scented cand candles everybody's like
sended candles oh my God sended candles
it's medical medium information been
talking about that for years we're
crushing that
too don't you want to be on the winning
team we want to be on the winning team
this is where the stuff is like crushing
it all right let's go what else some
cilantro
leaves and we got a little bit of flat
leaf parsley today cuz that's what I
want to use in this one but you can use
cilantro but I'm going to use this
beautiful flat leaf parsley out of the
garden so I wanted to use that so let me
go and do
that
boom
Oh you hear that sound you hear that
whisper down the lane what is it what's
that whisper down the lane I hear it
what is it it's Vegas nerves Vegas
nerves everybody everybody talk about
Vegas nerves original medical meme
information Vegas nerves and symptoms
based upon Vegas nerves mm
info all
right I'm just stating mere facts I'm
not boasting I'm not talking crap I'm
stating mere facts that's all facts and
then of course the elusive
notorious Epstein bar baby I was called
the Epstein bar boy the Epstein bar guy
I was ridiculed made fun of there were
freaking like YouTube's about it making
fun of me everybody's making fun of me I
was the Epstein bar guy now everything's
Epstein bar and they're testing for
Epstein bar for every Lyme disease
patient because of medical medium
Epstein bar multiple scoll is the cause
of multiple sclerosis is Epstein bar
published first by medical medium books
taken later by Harvard Epstein bar
literally across the board is on the
table now because of medical medium I
can do this all day I could do it all
day long and talk about this stuff all
day long let's get a little bit of this
in
here nice see what else we got that's
going to be so good so
good
nice look at that it's hot piping
hot wo let's get some um ripe hot
pepper whoa some ripe hot pepper right
there these are these cayen are really
hot really
hot but seriously I'm
serious so says on YouTube seriously
nobody ever mentioned the Vegas nerves
until after you started talking about
them a lot no one mentioned the
fragrances no one mentioned the blood
draw problem that they're starting to
talk about now because medical mean put
it out there nobody mentioned the vegans
never said eggs were bad for you did you
know that the plant-based movement I'm
serious if you can hear me out the
vegans and the plant-based people never
said anything bad about the egg they
just said because they're vegan they
won't eat the egg because they're
plant-based they won't eat the egg they
never knew eggs caused inflammation by
feeding pathogens it's medical medium
information the health movement has
changed because of mm info it is not
what it was it has changed and if you're
young and you don't know this you have
no idea where 80% of all this stuff came
from the mm information it's completely
tipped over on its Edge it's changed
completely and then the liver problems
here's another one that's medical Med
skin issues caused by liver problems
liver problems creating eczema psoriasis
skin problems dermatitis weight gain you
see that now doctors are like if you
have a sluggish liver you have weight
gain there's no science behind a
sluggish liver and weight gain that's
medical medium information published
first yeah and the beginning of most
every chronic illness the liver having a
problem in many ways cuz the pathogens
and everything
else and the reason why they talk about
the the liver now is because of the
infamous Liver Rescue book that has gone
around the globe published in almost
every single country in the world and
that's
what I'm
exhausted kidding kidding kidding
kidding all right and then what about
the zinc and the B12 thing and the lemon
bomb and the cats claw medical medium
nobody was using cat's claw for lime
disease that's M info nobody was using
cats claw cats Claw is in every one of
these now immune system supplements out
there medical medium going back for
decades no one's done it mm stuff first
lemon bomb all of it I mean you name it
and the zinc phenomenon and the B12
phenomenon stems from medical medium
information restoring the nerves nobody
knew it restored the nerves they just
thought V12 was for the body but they
didn't know it restored the central
nervous system
dude I can go on and on and on and
on all
right it's important people know so they
can get back to the original source and
work on their healing process don't you
want to know you want to be on the
winning team why do you think mm St why
do you think mm's attack the most out
there because the biggest threat because
literally we changed Health as it is
today and we showed them how it's
done all right let's make some
cheese I put some pepper in there some
hot pepper in there let's Stir It
Up someone asked the other day hey
medical medium how come you still like
use metal
utensils when you're dealing with
stainless steel when you're dealing with
stainless steel right
the the the
mildest of All Metals right and you're
doing your wild blueberries and you're
doing their heavy metal detox smoothies
and you're doing all that you're doing
your spirulina the right stuff you're
doing all that yeah you're you're not
you're not even this will never be in
you this will never be in you this is
different so I do use wooden a lot but
I'm not afraid to use a stainless steel
utensil all
right let's make the
cheese everybody say
cheese all right let's
roll okay thumbs up if you like this
show if you don't like the show thumbs
up hit the button hit the
like if you can if not no
worries
okay let's make some cheese let's
roll I think I got what I needed yeah I
do okay you guys all right I'm over here
by the steamer see know it didn't leave
you I'm by the steamer and it got really
hot potatoes right here
okay I'm going to break them apart
they're right out of the steamer you
heard the steamer running and these
suckers are
hot boom don't do that right there don't
like grab them with your hands and do
that I for some reason I can grab really
hot things and be all right but some
people they just can't do
that
okay and then what about the infamous
strep causing
acne that's medical medium in
information all
right now that's out there and you'll
notice there's like strep formulas they
got like all the things medical medium
talks about as far as knocking out
pathogens let's get this let's get
carrots in
here all
right I got some steamed carrots right
here you guys going to pop these in
we're going to make some cheese I don't
want them too kot I mean love carrots
but I think that will just be perfect
right
there and then what about this one do
you guys remember this one you
can't eat collagen to fix your collagen
and now everybody everybody's talking
about that now health professionals out
there saying yeah you can't eat collagen
to make collagen it doesn't work that
way you have to have the building blocks
already published already done that's
original mm info that people are
poaching and then women's hair loss A
adrenaline issues adrenal issues now and
how hair loss can happen when you have
like you have something terrible happen
in your life or some kind of emotional
SP spill happens or you're you're going
through something an emotional struggle
a loss and then N9 months later your
hair falls out or you have a baby 6
months later your hair starts falling
out you know it's like it's adrenaline
and people don't understand that that
with the hair loss thing but now they're
talking about it they got it from the mm
books it's original info here all right
let's turn this on let's go now I'm
going to actually add some spices to
here actually so let me do that I'm
going to go with some lime juice
nice might need some lime juice for that
right there
too put some lime in
here nice ripe
lime
boom
okay
we're going to some onion powder some
garlic powder some
paprika let's do
it onion
powder garlic
powder
nice some
paprika I going too fast now and a
little bit of
[Music]
water
let's get it
rolling Dr Fawn influencers need to
thank you for giving them content to
talk about not only that no they don't
do that though Dr fwn No instead they
just talk
[__]
um I mean before medical medium info out
there that people you know got you know
like not originally like years ago
before it was getting out there and
getting out there and getting out
there if you got sick you got just no
there was just no Direction there was
just
none all you can do is just pick like a
diet for your blood type or do the gaps
or do you know or do something or do the
fod map or just you couldn't you
couldn't get anywhere you just stayed
sick you laid in your bed you stayed on
mattress Island and you stayed
sick that was it that was the way it
went I don't know if you remember that
that was just a part of the
story you didn't have anywhere to go
back before the medical me book one book
like you had nowhere to
go nobody knew not to get all their
Mercury fillings out at once this
original mm info do one at a time like
nobody had they had a direction it was
really sad it was Wild West truly or
just the long lost world of
sadness all right this is ready and
perfect let's get a plate
going all
right going to clear the playing field a
little
bit we got a plate I'm excited about
this let's plate
it all right see if we can take a look
here there we go These are nice and
toasty they toasted up in the pan keep
in mind keep in mind I did
not keep in mind that I did not add
water to this pan you didn't want mushy
potatoes you wanted them cubed you
wanted them kind of toasty you see
this this is what I'm talking about
right
[Music]
here right
there look at that that's what I'm
talking
about
uh-huh
let's get let's get the cheese on top
next let's go let's drizzle a little bit
of that cheese on
top
okay all
right that looks freaking good I love
when it comes together
nice oh yeah guess what's not in this
cheese
Bine that's not in here I'm not saying
you know I mean if you're into Bine
stuff that's fine right but I'm I'm just
saying there ain't no Bine in here there
ain't no natural flavors this isn't
vegan cheese oh man I hate vegan cheese
vegan cheese is the worst the junk
that's in vegan cheese MSG and the
natural flavors and all the garbage
that's in vegan cheese it's really bad
I'm going to be
honest some vegan cheeses just have all
that soy in there some vegan cheeses
have all that canola oil in there some
vegan cheeses they be like oh no it's
all almond but then they have all this
other garbage like keragen and
everything else in there guar
gum I mean seriously all right it looks
pretty
good it's looking pretty good extra
cheese
please extra cheese please all
right now that peo got you
ready all right let's get that on
here
yeah thank you for coming to Medical
medium kitchen a medical medium cooking
show we covered life saving information
for so many people wait till you
actually apply some of that information
maybe you get the brainsaver protocol
book if you have the book read it start
to learn this is looking really
good and what I'm doing
is there we
go that's looking so
good love it all right okay you got it
I'm just going to get this together you
guys we're not done
whoa all right now let me get a
lime that's a nice lime right there
okay okay why do I have to throw it in
the
air why why do I have to throw it in the
air can I just get a couple of nice
really nice lime wedges right here
there's
one okay I'm going to get
another and I'm going to get
another at these lime Wes here I'm going
to put a couple over here you guys okay
with
this I hope
so did we just do it like for
real
okay you guys see that is that set
you guys see that on IG what about Tik
Tok what about you guys up there you
guys see this is that insane I'll bring
it up
closer
right how crazy is
that how crazy is
that does it match this at
all right here NE prot calls book you
guys on Tik Tok you guys thank you for
being here on Tik Tok thank you I feel
your love seriously
same thing IG I feel your love YouTube
Rumble right everywhere else I feel your
love you guys you guys are amazing what
about that right there can I have some
now you guys don't mind I I can't eat
without grou with me at all times now
for something for some
reason I have to have grou
here when I I
eat gry do you want any okay oh this is
this is so good take a look at this
right here some tomato on here do you
guys see oh my God look at that so this
is incredible this is this is
insane you ever have anybody important
to Fork at
you that's fruit so
good that is
seriously that is insane you can take a
little lime spray just put it on top
like that do a little
squeeze
that this is off the charts this is off
the deep
end I even know what to say all right
you
guys rock and roll healing foods that
can be Gourmet insanely delicious that's
what I'm talking
about I'm I'm in the habit of saying
that now every minute that's what I'm
talking about all right a medical me and
brainsaver protocols book right
there this book is packed make sure you
grab one on sale at amazon.com us
seriously sign up to my telegram get on
my telegram page man because I'm going
to start leaving some telegrams and just
so you know for the
record I'm going to start shooting off
my mouth soon enough about all kinds of
stuff so yeah so get ready cuz I've been
holding it in and it's going to have to
come out I'm letting you
know that when it does the shit's going
to be shocking as hell anyway check out
my telegram be on there if you can
medical medium newsletter sign up for it
so you don't miss out on all the stuff
sign up to my Tik Tok I'm going to do
exclusive stuff on Tik Tok I'm
eventually going to do exclusive stuff
on Rumble I'm going to do exclusive
stuff in all kinds of places yeah yeah
Rado 144 good to see you did you see the
party treat
recipe email that went out did you check
that
out anyway you
guys did you see that did you see that
email did you catch
it pretty
amazing pretty
amazing all right guys
love you much