[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now as
I've always said before who has 10 or 20
or 30 years to wait for answers to their
illnesses life is precious and there's
no time to spare and that's true you
know that really is we know that life is
precious you know that you totally know
that I know that other people know that
I'm sure maybe not everybody on the
planet knows that now we we do we do we
do have that guess that there are some
some people on the planet that don't
really think life is precious and and
you know that's that's true but for the
majority we do know how precious life is
and that really matters and who has the
5 or 10 years to get an answer and you
know someone came to me just
recently and you know they were they
were sick for about 2 years 2 years they
were sick and what it was was they had
this stomach and digestive tract problem
and discomfort and floating and and they
just you know went to practitioner to
practitioner one say it's got to be
candida another said it had to be Lyme
disease others which didn't make any
sense to me to have you know digestive
trouble and it be Lyme disease anyway so
you know that and then you know you name
it it was like one said it's irritable
bow syndrome it's IBS another person
says well it's just emotion all
emotional and you're just making it
happen you're just so
emotional and so so this person this
young woman she was just you know
searching and searching and searching
for no answers and she said to me I've
already wasted two years of my life two
years of my life I said that's it 2
years I mean and you know and she said
well yeah two years is a big deal it's a
big deal to me Anthony it's 2
years and I said hey look I totally get
it I didn't mean to sound you know like
I was being kind of like pointy about it
by saying oh two years that's all I
didn't mean to do that you're right two
years is a long time okay and it is a
long time to not have answers to not
know what you need to do and she goes it
took two years to know that all I had to
do was drink celery juice and raise my
hydrochloric acid with celery juice even
though I knew about hydrochloric acid
but there was no way to fix it and then
I stumbled across your celery juice deal
and you the celery juice thing and and
information and I fixed my hydrochloric
acid my liver started working again and
my bile started producing again my food
started digesting and all my problem s
went away and and she said and I wasn't
I was just I said you know she goes I
was just at the beginning of still
shopping around looking for answers I
was you know I was eating fermented
foods my stomach was blowing up like
crazy eating fermented foods you know I
was drinking lots of bone broth thinking
that could help I was doing I was doing
the eat once a day thing then I was
doing the eat twice a day thing um then
I was doing the intermittent fasting and
then I was doing um you know then I did
paleo and then you know and then I did
vegetarian and then I did this but I
didn't know that all I had to do was
start getting 16 ounces of celery juice
once a day in fact she did 16 ounces of
celery juice twice a day twice a day and
her problem started going away she
couldn't believe it she said two years
of her life and and and okay and I said
to her I said to her I said two years
that's all and yeah that got her upset
that that got her upset and it dawned on
me absolutely rightfully so rightfully
so and yeah I felt like a real ham for
the moment or real you know a real dummy
because yeah the reason why I was saying
it to begin with is cuz I know people
that have 10 20 30 years that they
they've gone looking for answers maybe
you guys know maybe you know someone
who's been sick with lupus for 10 years
maybe you know somebody who's been
struggling with their thyroid for 20
years with no answers as to far as far
as what even causes the problem I mean
thank goodness for Spirit in the
information we know now and it's getting
out there and you know thank God we know
this
information because it's important but
so I felt bad that I said oh 2 years
that's all because in her world in her
world from being perfectly healthy when
she felt all to having all this
digestive stress for two years with no
real answers it's candida it's this it's
lime it's that it's what you know you
know going all over the place looking
for help
and it it it seemed like a world of time
for her and I had to fall I had to get
into that Vibe for a second and say you
know what I'm sorry you're right you're
right you know it shouldn't have to take
two years damn right it shouldn't have
to take two years and it it should you
know to find an answer and and she's
right but you know but but at the same
time of course I know I know people that
came to me after 20 years 30 years of it
and or or search and came to find
information that we offer all the time
and they've been through 20 years of no
answers with fatigue and just you know
all kinds of random symptoms and
neurological symptoms that they don't
even know it's neurological cuz no one
even tells them it's neurological
because no one even knows and that's a
whole another problem as it is nobody
knows what symptoms are you go to a a
dozens of practitioners and they can't
even figure out what the symptom is oh
we don't know what that tingles is I we
don't know what that numbness is oh we
don't know what ringing in the ears
really what causes it you know we don't
know what the vertigo maybe it's the
stones in the uh in the inner ear
causing the vertigo no vertigo is
neurological it's neurological so the
point is that and depression is
neurological and it goes on and on and
on but the point is she waited 2 years
it was a world of time time in her life
you know I I you know I wasn't taking it
seriously enough and I said well hey
that's all you waited and because of the
fact so many people waited so much
longer but I but I have to respect and
realize yeah 2 years is a lot and she's
totally right and so she found some
answers and the answers are the celery
juice and she contacted me contacted me
to tell me this has completely changed
my life I just spent 2 years this
looking and searching celery juice fixed
it and more people need to know about
this information I said well that's what
we're trying to do so you know time is
you know precious life is precious and
we need to know and get the healing to
happen now and we need to and we we need
it we need it clean what I mean by Clean
is is the information that comes through
here and gets handed to everybody along
the way is is it's it's pure information
what I mean by that it hasn't gone
through already the internet in a
million different ways and then all
these different people trying to get a
name in in in the business or the field
out there they you're taking it and and
altering it and moving it and then it
gets lost and then who do you go to and
then this whole bit and what I mean by
that is I mean that everybody like you
guys have been keeping the information
clean for me and I just love you for it
you know you've been you've been you've
been cting meaning cting back to you
know where it comes from from Spirit I'm
seeing it there I'm seeing it on
Instagram I'm seeing it on Facebook
where people are like like wo that that
came from you know medical medium and
and and so I just appreciate the fact
that you're sourcing it so that people
can find it and not have it all of a
sudden changed where it's not 16 ounces
of celery juice anymore it's 4 o of
celery juice you know 3 oz of this 2 O
of that 8 O of this and 6 o of that and
it's just changing and and thank you
guys for just being so strong with it
with the Instagram you know picks of
celery juice and everything else and I'm
just really thankful you guys are
keeping that the purity of it all of the
information that you're really that
you're really you know taking and and
using for yourself and spreading out
there and and assisting people and I'm
honored I'm grateful for it believe me
so hey today we're talking about angels
today we're talking about the life
changing Angels so today's show is about
these life-changing angels angels that
are really taken for granted in the
greatest way the greatest way possible
are these life-changing Angels nobody
knows about the life-changing Angels
when I found out from Spirit when I
found out from Spirit a long time ago I
was just I I was just I was overtaken by
it I couldn't even imagine I was like
what did you say and spirit was like
well I'm telling you about these
life-changing Angels you need to know
about this for the future because you're
going to have to get the information out
there and I was blown off my seat I was
just blown away and it moved me greatly
because I didn't know that there are
these angels that did what they do like
the life-changing Angels do around food
around food you know so this is really
going to be a powerful show a great show
this is exciting so you got to you know
put your seat belt on for this we're
going for a good ride today this is
going to be fun and uh we're going to be
in the sun today going to be in the sun
today and the light today and that's
what we want to do so hey um what a
couple things to run by you check out uh
the life-changing uh book life-changing
Foods book check it out that's where the
life-changing
Angels uh information is in there but
check it out when you get a chance get a
hand hand get your hands on a copy you
know when I put this whole entire
chapter of life-changing angels and in
life-changing Foods book you know I said
you know what this has to be here and
spirit said spirit said yes it has to be
in here and it's something that you just
don't expect to be in a food book that
talks about you know protecting your
family giving your family everything you
know it your family needs to survive and
thrive in this world longevity in the
way it's supposed to be the right kinds
of foods that stop disease and illness
the foods that help us emotionally the
foods that help us spiritually with
spiritual lessons you name it and you
didn't you wouldn't think that there'd
be an angel chapter in this book but it
was the perfect place I didn't want it
in the first book because this is these
are the angels that govern the food on
the planet and this is a whole different
pack of angels one that's really
forgotten not just forgotten unknown and
needs to be known in its time and spirit
wants everybody to know who's supporting
them who's supporting you in your life
how these angels are there supporting
you in your life and the power of that
what could really happen with that so
this is really exciting if this is the
first time you've ever heard my show and
this is the first show it goes back to
me it it it goes back in my life at age
four four years old and spirit spoke to
me from the outside of my ear and told
me that my grandmother had lung cancer
and told me to actually pronounce
announce and say that grandmother has
lung cancer so that all started for me
at age four when I had to announce that
at the dinner table I had to get off my
chair walk up to my grandmother and
spirit said say grandma grandma has lung
cancer I had to pronounce that and then
spent the rest of my life helping people
and giving them information about what's
going on with their health and
well-being and what they need to move
forward and heal so I've dedicated my
life doing this and um and helped tens
of thousands of people along the way and
we're still helping people and
technology has brought even more ability
to help more people and um and I'm I'm
thankful for it all and so I'm here now
this is what I do this is what I'm doing
is making sure you get the information
that you need to protect your family to
take care of yourself to make sure you
don't get sick to make sure you can get
healthy to make sure you can move
forward that's what matters that's what
matters to me right there you know right
there you know you can live in a Palace
you can just live in a palace a massive
massive Empire Palace and if you're
sick it just really it doesn't help and
it doesn't matter meaning that when
you're sick no matter what circumstances
or where you are in your life whether
you're in a palace okay or you're on a
ship somewhere or you're or you're you
know where ever it is or you're just you
know living it up in a spaceship going
to the moon when we become sick it it
takes us out of our situation that we're
in whatever that is meaning whatever is
going on in our life you know what I
mean by that is there is someone that
there was an athlete that uh contacted
me pretty recently one one that's well
known and the athlete the athlete was
like look everything was going great I'm
doing great all this is um you know I've
always been healthy I've always exceeded
I'm well known for it here's my records
this is what I've done and now I'm sick
and I can't see it anymore I can't see
it it's it's not there in my vision
anymore and I said you know what that's
that's what happens and that's what I
meant that's what I meant by you can be
in a palace you can be on a ship you can
be uh in a spaceship going to the moon
and that's your thing whatever ever your
thing is you could be an athlete you
could be here and there at your best you
could be whatever it is that you do in
life you can be an executive you can be
you know someone who works you can be an
intern somewhere but when you get sick
and you don't feel good you can't see in
front of you anymore you can't see it
just literally just all of a sudden
starts a s short circuit everything is
happening in in that moment in your life
and it's about what do I I do where do I
go I don't feel good why am I sick
what's happening and you can't see your
job so easy and you know I I hear this
from people in all walks of life in all
different places in their life is what I
mean and they lose hope they lose hope
they lose faith and it was just like I
was telling you um earlier and and just
you know a few minutes ago was telling
you about this person that came to me
after 2 years and said if it wasn't for
the celery juice I don't know where I
would be took 2 years 2 years to get
this digestive problem better this
bloating problem everything else wrong
with it took 2 years to get better and
you you know and in her life her life
had to basically stop it wasn't about
anymore about you know what was
happening and by the way she was engaged
to be married and that was that was all
of a sudden falling apart because of her
digestive problems so her her you know
um you know her spouse I mean they're
married now but he was thinking well do
I want to be with the sick girl that's
what she told me she told me that he was
like I don't know I don't know if I want
to tie the knot I mean I could back out
right now she's got digestive problems
for the last two years and they seem to
be getting worse and I can back out I I
don't know if I want to put a ring on
her fingers and you know and say her
vows and do this and so you know the
celery juice she she also says the
celery juice saved her her you know
marriage that started brand new marriage
that was able to happen and that that's
what I mean in this world we lose hope
we lose sight others around us lose hope
and sight and you know that's the
difficulty
involved and like I was telling you
about this athlete this athlete was like
it was just I was fine I was at the top
of my game I was at the best of my game
I started getting sick no real answers
can't get better all I see is I don't
even see the game anymore can't play the
game can't see it I'm lost in a fog so
it doesn't matter where you are like I
said you could be all happy and on you
know on a trip to the moon in a
spaceship and you get sick and you
you're not even going to Care not even
going to care about when you're about to
land on the moon because you know what
you're sick and this is what happens and
we get blinded by our illness and our
sickness and our struggles we get
blinded by it it's like an instant
blindness so why am I talking about this
why am I talking about this because the
angels can help us with that that
blindness so when you lose your sight
and you're struggling no matter where it
is what direction of struggling the
angels can help with that sight even
though we can't see the angels I know
we're in a world and you guys know this
I know we're in a world where if you
can't see it it ain't real so if you
can't see it it's not real if you can't
see it it's not real it isn't
real you know that's what we think
that's what we think um you we have to
see it to believe it I told you that
before you know that but you already
knew that anyway it's a it's you know
you have to see it to believe it kind of
world that's what it is and I understand
that I understand that it happens to me
until people come to the events you know
because people who don't know me and
they say oh yeah yeah he hears a voice
people who don't know me or anything and
know what I've done they're just like
okay he hears a voice okay I'd like to
see it to believe it and then they go to
the event and they walk out of there in
shock and and yeah but it's like it's a
see it to believe it kind of world we're
in and what happens is is when we're
sick you know when we're sick and we're
getting sick it's hard to see it from
the outside it's like you're not sick
you look fine you can't be that sick you
look okay unless you just have a stroke
and you're just flat on your face and
you're break your jaw when you when you
fall on the
cement and that's another story then
somebody would be like oh yeah yeah no
there's there's there's a man down here
there's a man down but when we're sick
we're walking around with all this
different chronic illness like like
example of the person the woman I was
telling you about the young woman I was
telling you about that had the digestive
trouble and the the trouble in the gut
and the bloating and the stomach ache
and the all that going on everybody else
around her was just saying you know I I
don't think you really got this going on
the doctor can't kind of figure it out
they're all throwing different things at
you and so maybe it's in your head and
that's what her her um um boyfriend was
saying before they were married that's
what that's what her partner was saying
he was saying well yeah I don't know if
it's really actually happening with her
I can't tell she says it's bothering her
but she looks fine she's acting fine
it's cuz she was struggling to persevere
through she was struggling to push
through so you know but here's the deal
with the angels we don't see him so easy
okay I know people who have seen
him I I definitely know people who have
seen him right and I've seen them too
I've been blessed to see see him I mean
I don't know if you've read the the uh
my first book when if you've read that
with the first chapter where I was
saving my dog's life and I was in the
freezing cold Frid cold water and um
Spirit told me to dive down and I dove
down and open opened my eyes and there
was an angel in the water holding on to
my dog 8 ft
down and you know that that you know i'
start getting a little choked up and a
little emotional even telling that story
and so I saw what I
saw it lit up underneath that water it
lit up it was a flash of light
underneath that water and I saw an angel
8 ft down in that water and I swear to
God I could breathe under that water I
wasn't even holding my breath anymore
and I was breathing under that water
that's what I felt like and maybe I
wasn't breathing under that water
obviously and maybe I was still holding
my breath but I felt
free I felt free for that very moment as
that angel lit up under the water
holding on my dog holding on to my dog
deep in that
water and and I I just felt like I had
all the air in the world inside of my
lungs and and so you know it it it's
it's sure we have to see it to believe
it but here's the thing if you haven't
seen an Angel yet in your
lifetime you might have not even known
it think back go through all the
different steps of your life all the way
till
childhood do you remember ever seeing an
angel you remember possibly seeing an
angel at at all and any any possibility
is it there it could be you might have
seen an angel absolutely you might have
seen two you might might have heard an
angel you know in this world we're told
to just not go there we're told to not
go there it's not a place where we're
you know where we're allowed to play in
it's not a place where we're allowed to
you know it's imaginary in this world
it's like it's called
imaginary and what that does is it shuts
out it shuts out our ability to have
that faith and have that
Vision so you know in your life you
should you kind of surf through your
life a little bit and see where you may
remember an angel in some way some shape
or form it could have even been this one
person that helped you at one time that
had that Angelic
nature and that matters too greatly that
matters greatly that Angelic nature that
can be in someone to help to help you in
a hard time you know people tell me they
say you know this person helped me in a
hard time I swear to God they're they're
my
angel they're my angel and you know and
this does happen in our lives some of us
are fortunate to have that help and so
think back a little bit and search and
if you can't think about it now and you
can't remember now it's going to come CU
we bury it we bury it when we're young
and we bury it when we get older too so
when we have an experience that an angel
was involved with that could have helped
us in any way or showed us a way or
showed us a direction in some way you
name it if that happened we could have
buried it because we can't really talk
about it and who are you going to talk
to about it and some of us don't have a
lot of options of people to talk to it
about and that kind of thing that we can
express our feelings about
angels and you know when you think about
Ang oh yes yeah an angel sure sure you
know
butterflies
fairies you know the whole bit
leprechauns you know um you know the
thing is is this it's it's angels are
real I'm going to give you a little
background of some angels right
now right now happening there's a battle
going on there's something called the
quickening occurring right now that
means things are happening faster than
ever before in
history the days of kind of moseying on
into your house okay and grabbing a
newspaper and sitting on a rocking chair
in front of the
fireplace those days are not really upon
us anymore as they used to
be and I'm sure listen that doesn't mean
you can't sit on your favorite rocking
chair and read a paper it just means
the day of that is
changing the day of that is changing you
know the world is changing things are
happening really really fast right now
and you know it you see it I mean come
on and that that speed of which
everything's happening right now Spirit
calls us the
quickening and that quickening also
means that angels are working harder
than ever before in history and and
human history and Angelic history to
protect us in any way
possible angels are dying out fires left
and right on the planet dying out fires
left and light right all over the planet
because there is a battle because
there's this negative energy that
encompasses like the
greed and the Darkness on the planet and
the evil okay now if you say what is he
talking about greed darkness and Evil on
the planet what kind of what kind of
thing would you say that for well I'm
talking about you know all the adversity
that's created by the Wars created by
all of the anger created by all that's
happening all that adversity all that
non peace all that unrest that's fed
that's fed by this negativity that the
angels have to battle all the time so
there's a war and the angels are trying
to do everything they can
to stop anything and everything that
shouldn't be happening on the planet so
they're really busy with this this
spiritual war that's occurring right now
I'm giving you just a little tidbit of
it it's much more vast than that I we
can do 10 shows on it I'm just giving
you a little fraction of of how it goes
a little bit and so we have to respect
that the angels are really busy so but
we also we also have to understand that
the angels are there to help us to too
that they're there looking out for us to
help us too in our time of me need I
want to tell you a little story okay
this is this is a man that came to me I
didn't know him when he was sick I
didn't know him when he was sick he came
to me and he told me that the
Angels the Angels cured him that's what
he told me I had to hear this I had to
hear the story so I didn't know him and
um you know this is at one time in his
life and he's been waiting to tell this
story and he wanted to tell it to me and
I said I want to hear this I want to
hear this and I was enthralled okay so
he fell ill completely ill he was in
this you know cat catatonic State I mean
he was just in this you know paralysis
state of paralysis and he fell ill he
couldn't eat he couldn't even sleep he
couldn't walk he couldn't
talk he was in he was in hospital for
quite quite a long time
and you know for a good long time in the
hospital and then they moved him at home
and it was he it was too hard to work
with him at home he was he was you know
he was on a feeding tube he was on a
breathing apparatus most of the
time and he told me that he was awake
and they moved him into um a nursing
home where basically to die and then
from the nursing home you know from the
nursing home home maybe back to the
hospital I think he told me he went back
to the hospital a couple times and back
to the nursing home and he said that he
was conscious he couldn't speak but he
was conscious and he was awake but he
couldn't move he couldn't write he
couldn't do
anything but he was positive he was
going to die at the nursing home he was
just left to die and then he
remembered he
remembered the angel on top of his
Christmas tree when he was a
child he remembered the angel on top of
the Christmas tree when he was a
child okay and he was just totally
hopeless at this point thinking he's
never going to come out of
this and he heard he
heard sometimes in and out of it all the
doctors talking about how it's a mystery
illness they can't see a stroke they
don't know what's causing it but he was
wasting away and he was dying and losing
his life and it was just unknown to what
was wrong in and out of the in and out
of the delusion of the
sickness in and out of that but he said
at one time he said when he lost all
hope and he thought he was going to die
and he thought he was going to leave it
it appeared to him to think about the
angel on top of his Christmas tree he'll
never forget that angel he said it had
beautiful sparkly wings
it had a soft
Angelic
face and it had Golden
Hair golden
hair and it had white like a white Veil
all around it big wings and it sat on
top of the tree when he was a child and
then he remembered his aunt had an angel
at her house that was on top
uh it was in it was on the coffee table
in the living room on top of the coffee
table and he remembered that
angel and he said to
himself are there Angels there must be
there must be angels I at least have to
connect to the angels somehow that's
what he said to himself innately because
of not because he was taught about the
Angels he wasn't taught about the Angels
no one taught him about the Angels it
was just on top of the Christmas
tree
and then he envisioned the Christmas
tree angel lit up cuz he remembered that
if the Christmas tree was unplugged the
angel on top of the Christmas tree would
would go out and he always liked to see
it plugged in and so he would ask his
family to plug it in all the time so the
angel would
light and he remember it lit up and he
remembered it and he remembered the
other angel on the coffee table and all
he could think about instead of
dying instead instead of being sick and
paralyzed instead of wasting away all he
could think about were these
angels and he became
obsessed obsessed in a good way about
these
angels and he called it obsessed that's
what he said to me became obsessed with
them and he said after a few days what
he feels like went a few days by cuz he
couldn't tell time he said after a few
days gone
by he said
that he it was about 3:30 4:00 in the
morning which he feels because it was
the summertime and he felt like the
light was about to come out in the
little window when he cracked his eyes
open cuz he could see partially and he
said that he saw some light coming up in
the window and coming up like it looked
like Dawn was
coming and he closed his eye and he went
into some kind of
vision and the vision was seeing Angels
come down come down from the sky and
break through the nursing home to break
through the nursing home ceiling and
come down and land on his bed by his
side he said there were three or four
Angels standing looking over him
standing over his body he saw these
angels he saw these angels one of the
Angels was holding the angel on top of
the Christmas tree in the Angel's hand
to give him the
identifiable message that we have come
to help the Angels did a dance around
him they walked around him he said they
sat on the bed with him they walked
around and they had joy and they had
happiness and they were
lighthearted they were light-hearted he
said they were free from pain from
suffering they they were free from Agony
they were free from
hardship but he said they had compassion
to all compassion could possibly have
they had immense compassion and freedom
and a light-hearted nature and a
joyfulness inside of them and around
them and they looked at him and they
touched his body and they said you're
going to be okay it's going to be
okay and then they left they lifted up
and left that morning he started getting
feeling to his body now he was a long
way from Physical Therapy a long way
from Physical Therapy but he got feeling
in his body and he was able to move his
arms which was witnessed by the nurse in
the nursing home it was witnessed and
from there on he recovered and he
recovered rapidly and then went through
physical therapy and recovered and he
had to tell me the
story and that's the power of angels so
we have to have some faith we have to
care here's one thing you have to you
have to
know here's one thing the Angels knew he
couldn't speak out loud or speak at all
in order to access the Angels but they
knew that when you're in that kind of
position and you can't access them they
will help you they will help you
regardless of being able to voice out to
voice out to the
angels and but one thing you have to do
if you do have a voice and you can speak
like I'm sure most if you can you want
to ask out loud you want to definitely
ask out loud it's really important to do
that when you ask out loud it's
important it's really important it's
critical
actually and so you you what you do is
you say you know angels can you help me
and you could whisper it you you can say
it louder you don't have to scream it
you don't have to yell it it's that
important because the people that I've
seen ask out loud get the help they need
from the Angels one way or
another and so many people ask for Angel
help but they don't ask for it they just
can't come to asking for it they can't
they can't get themselves to ask for it
or they don't know enough to ask for it
out loud and so they lose that chance
where it's not as easily done and the
reason why is because angels have a hard
time searching through all the Agony you
have meaning all the thoughts you have
all the stress you have all the
different things going on in your mind
the party that's going on in your brain
and angels have a hard time getting
through all that but they look out for
the people who cannot speak that are in
that dire need all that entire dire need
that moment of just just desperate need
and say look out in that case so that's
okay if you can't speak but you want to
be able to ask out loud I was talking to
a friend of mine you know Michael
Bernard Beth Beckwith
and he said when he went through a
situation he said he got the help when
he asked out
loud that's when it hit him that's when
it happened that's when he got help you
know he was out swimming had some
problems with some massive waves and he
had to ask out for help and he called
out for help and that's what saved him
the Angelic power the the Angels when he
asked out for help and he felt like if
he didn't ask out for help he wouldn't
have been
saved and so and so if you hear from
other you know Angelic experts or
sources that that's not true that you
don't have to ask out loud no no you do
you do it's critical and you have to
okay that's information that came from
Spirit that came from Spirit that taught
me that you have to ask out loud for
help taught me when I was younger and
how critical that is and it really does
matter now if you to have the inability
to ask out loud that's a different story
and that's when the Angels come for a
different reason they come with the help
and that's okay so I want to talk about
the life-changing Angels the
lifechanging
angels are very interesting because
they're different than all the other
Angels they're different the
life-changing angels have everything to
do with food that gets to you that gets
on your table food that gets in your
hands food that grows seeds that get
what they need so they can grow and feed
the planet and Feed Us
angels that have everything to do with
our digestion and digest you digesting
food and consuming
food angels that play a role in
everything in anything that has to do
with your well-being and health related
to food food issues food Gran the rain
the weather all of this combined
including protecting bees which right
now it's not an easy job for angels to
protect bees they're trying to protect
them wherever they can because bees are
a critical part of our life and us being
here because they're the ultimate
pollinators to keep our food supply
going so that we
survive so let's talk about some of
these life-changing angels and and
here's the thing if you if you think you
don't have a lot of faith or you think
you don't have any faith and you even
believe in an angel you have faith
remember that build off of that try to
build off of that so if you're someone
who thinks you're lacking some Faith or
you don't have enough faith and you're
concerned your your faith is really low
or maybe you just don't have any faith
at all if you believe in angels even
just a little bit your faith is building
up that's the practice right there that
alone so there's 12 lifechanging angels
that are out
there and and these Ang angels are they
responsible for major
tasks and they're like for instance some
of these angels are trying to win the
war on GMO crops and some of these
angels are communicating with the people
that are
responsible for making GMO awareness as
being a bad thing so they're getting
Angelic help without even realizing it
so there's Angels responsible with
trying to actually help with the whole
GMO crop thing that's going on GMO
destru
so there's Angels involved and those
same angels are trying to trip up the
GMO
factories they are they're working on
constantly trying to trip them up it's a
hard job and there's a lot to do so
let's go over some of these angels
there's one Angel called angel of
disarmament okay this is a life-changing
Angel so it's it's when you have to eat
produce you know it has that you know
it's been sprayed by pesticides or
herbicides or fungicides but so you're
you have to eat conventional produce
there's people out there that have to
eat you know conventional produce
absolutely and it's okay it's okay as
long as you're getting that avocado in
you get the conventional avocado if you
have to you know get the conventional
celery just give it a good washing which
of course there's going to still be
residues inside of it but the point is
is don't stop eating fruits and
vegetables just because you you have no
choice because of financial reasons or
availability and resources to e
conventional don't be afraid to still
eat fruits and vegetables the angel of
disarmament okay helps you when this
food has been sprayed and you have no
choice but to eat it or even be being
contaminated by GMO
crops okay you can call upon this Angel
to disarm the chemicals so that they
could have the minimal effect on your
body body protecting you now I asked
Spirit about this angel I said well can
the angel literally get rid of every
pesticide inside of that food and spirit
said no but they can actually minimize
the effect it has on your body so what
this Angel does is this Angel actually
helps your body handle whatever minimal
whatever pesticide or herbicide that's
on that conventional produce to handle
it and so you can process it and
eliminate that pesticide with ease so it
helps that process happen so you can
call upon the angel of disarm let me
give you another one angel of
abundance this is the Angel you want on
your side when you're growing your own
food so if you're totally into growing
your own food you got your little Garden
or say you got a big Garden you know I
ran across somebody that has such a big
Garden that I couldn't believe it it was
massive I was like this is this is crazy
this is incredible
and so if you you know if you're growing
your own anything herbs if you're
growing your own herbs in a planter some
Rosemary some time or if you got an
apple tree whatever it is and you're
growing your own food you want to call
upon the angel
abundance so that she gives you more of
a bountiful crop and she can if you call
upon her and nobody knows about her
nobody knows about her you're hearing
this for the first time here you're
you're hearing it here and it's in the
lifechanging Foods book but the
information has to get out there the one
thing I like about Spirit a spirit
really knows which Angels really exist
and which angels are out there because
it's coming from Spirit it's not coming
from just you know you know just a
thought process that we have kind of in
our head this is coming from a spiritual
source so I just I love when spirit
gives me these angels for us so we can
help really get the help you need and
get this information out there and I
promise spirit I would actually make
sure this information got out there it's
important angel of
provision I love the angel of provision
her job is to root food to people who
are undernourished or
starving so people who are
undernourished and starving the angel of
provision has the power to somehow get
food sources to these very limited
places and people and soup K kitchens
and food banks they're responsible these
angels for getting people to actually
create food banks that's the whole point
of why somebody wakes up in the morning
and says I'm going to start a soup
kitchen to help people that are
starving that's getting that's a message
coming from the angel of provision but
the angel of provision gets no
credibility no credit no
respect no respect because the angel
provision doesn't need any respect it's
not like you know people who they need
to have respect or whatever so the angel
provision these are the most taken for
granted angels of all time that are in
life-changing Foods book so so so it's
about getting someone to start a soup
kitchen literally providing nourishment
for Hungry
bellies you guys want any more cuz
there's plenty of them we got some more
angel of
enrichment this Angel enhances the
nutrition of the Holy four the holy four
is the fruits the vegetables the herbs
and spices the wild Foods all in
life-changing the life-changing book so
this Angel and amplifies and strengthens
phytochemicals in wild blueberries in
our food vitamins minerals and other
nutrients actually lift up they lift up
in their power from the angel of
enrichment it makes your food extra
medicine well that's what I do before I
eat I say angel of enrichment enrichment
please make this food more powerful the
phytochemicals more powerful enhance
them for me I want that in my
life so let's talk about another one
angel of
Harmony angel of Harmony is amazing when
you want to become one with your food
and enhance mindful eating so that's
when you're into mindful eating if
you're someone that's into mindful
eating which is really awesome and
you're sitting there and you're thinking
about the food you're eating and you're
enjoying it and you're tasting it and
you're being aware of it you're being in
that moment while you're eating you know
when you're right there and present
moment while you're eating cuz present
moment's really good while you're
eating and then you call upon the angel
of Harmony and it's going to enhance
that mindful eating it's going to make
it an experience that you never even
expected it's going to heighten an appre
that that appreciation for your meal and
bring you in tune with your
body so this is the kind of angels we
have that are here working for
us what I like is I like Angel of
addiction cuz we all have addictions we
we all have some addiction or not that's
that's hit us whether it's chocolate
cake or some kind of something some kind
of addiction that we've had or had or
having whether it's alcoholism out there
or it's something else addiction is just
rampant people are addicted to to their
own adrenaline their own
adrenaline so angel of addiction if
you're addictively drawn to the wrong
Foods if you have a food addiction the
angel of addiction can stomp on that
food addiction to really help you break
I love this angel I love her she's
wonderful so if someone you know
overeats all the time because they have
that addiction or someone you know feels
you know they feel like they're drawn to
the wrong Foods you call upon the angel
of
addiction that's what you need to
do I like this angel angel of Mother's
Milk angel of mother's milk this angel
protects a new mother's milk
supply and allows communication between
the mother and baby during breastfeeding
this Angel's involved with the child
with the baby breastfeeding and the baby
and mommy breastfeeding this Angel's
involved making that as good as it can
possibly be so the nutrients in the
breast milk lift up and deliver into the
baby there's a communication going on
the angel allows to make that happen and
we never knew that we never knew there's
an angel of Mother's milk that's
actually making that connection
happen that's the power of these
angels and then let's hit angel of
insight let's hit this one
now angel of insight she's
amazing when you want to eat more
healthy food you call upon the angel of
insight because the angel of insight
will boost boost up your spirit and will
so you'll want to eat to be inspired
because so many people they're not
inspired and they just can't do it and
they can't eat the healthy food I know
you guys I get it I totally get it 100%
if you can get one good food in you that
I talk about I'm I'm blown away and I'm
happy I'm really happy the angel of
insight helps us get more of those Foods
it gives us like a a an inspiration
inside of us a desire that starts to
occur to like a magical inspiration to
want to be on track and stay on track
with our foods and that's really
special so these are the Angels we're
talking about and let's not talk let's
not forget about the angel of
honesty here's what I like about the
angel of honesty you guys got to hear
this you got to hear this you ready are
you ready for this one the angel of
honesty okay let me tell you what she
does
if you're in a situation where you're
uncomfortable because you're not sure
the source of the food that you're
buying or eating and you want it to be
you know like and you want it to really
be free range or wild C caught or
organic or
gluten-free or you want to be sure that
it's not genetically modified or if you
want Insurance assurance that a dish
prepared at a restaurant so if you go to
a restaurant and you're getting a dish
prepared at a restaurant you want to
make sure that dish prepared at a
restaurant is made with olive oil and
not canola
oil you call upon the angel of honesty
to help you get a straight answer so
when you're at that restaurant and you
say to the waiter or waitress and you
say listen I really need to know that
this isn't the olive oil let's blend it
with canola oil that this really is pure
olive oil can you can you ask the chef
please and then what you do is you ask
ask the angel of honesty to come help in
that moment what happens is the angel of
honesty comes and has a conversation
with the chef and the waitress without
them even knowing it to make sure they
come out and they say no this is the
fake olive oil it is the canola oil and
I'm so sorry we'll get you real olive
oil to make you
happy and that's the angel of
honesty so you know hey look it it it
takes my breath away
blows me away and there's more Angels
than that there's more Angels than that
so when you go through the lifechanging
angels and you learn about them and when
you get the life-changing Foods book you
know take your time process it learn
them they will work for you they won't
let you down they're there for you
they're on your
side and it's going to be really helpful
I promise it's going to going to be
really really
helpful so look let's cover um let's
cover a few things I want to just check
on you guys I want to do a little check
on you for a minute and I never do that
I never check on you enough I never
check to see how you're doing and how
you guys are doing okay are you are you
are you eating pretty good I want you
guys getting a spinach salad in salad in
you once in a while get a spinach salad
could put a little avocado on it that's
totally fine I want you to do that okay
the angels will help you with that too
you can call upon the angels to help you
out if we need to there's nothing wrong
with that I want you to get the celery
juice in in you when you can if you like
other green juices get one in if you can
okay don't be afraid of a smoothie make
sure the Frozen wild blueberries are in
your
smoothies okay so put the Frozen wild
blueberries in there maybe some bananas
put a couple of celery sticks in the
Smoothie a little coconut water and you
can put other things in there if you
really want make sure you're taking care
of yourself make sure you have some
steamed sweet potatoes or even some
baked sweet potatoes if you really want
make sure you have those every day make
sure you're bringing some of these
things in there if you're someone who
likes hummus have a little bit of hummus
and that's important you know if you
really like it if you're someone someone
was telling me the other day they like
quinoa salads they can't get enough of
it that's okay let's do the quinoa
salad and you know bring some of these
things in when you can remember to bring
garlic in remember to bring ginger in
when you can maybe some ginger water if
you got a belly ache bring in or you got
tummy problems bring in that celery
juice bring in aloe vera juice I'm doing
a little checkup on you guys making sure
you're doing all this stuff and you can
bring in one of these things if you need
to if it's too much to bring all of them
bring in one all right and take one day
at a time make sure you're eating every
couple of hours every hour and a half
you're snacking and grazing especially
if you have adrenal fatigue or you think
you have adrenal problems or you have
neurological fatigue the thing we always
cover it's caused by viral issues you do
some snacks make sure you doing that
listen it's all about you healing it's
all about you getting better when I was
given this gift when I was younger it
wasn't for me it wasn't given to me for
me it was given to me for you it was
only for you and that's the whole point
so you take one day at a time you know I
care you know I stand behind you you
know I believe in you you can get better
you can heal we'll move forward together
take the angel information keep it
tucked in by your side don't lose it
know that I love you and I stand behind
you
100% God bless you take care
bye-bye