doing the healing broth
how was the light Blast for you guys I
just wanted to ask you and connect with
you about it because that was really
really really really
intense that's for sure so I just wanted
to kind of I want to reconnect with you
guys about it all really you know anyway
this is about like a reflection about
the light blast I'm making a healing
broth which is an incredible
incredible fuel source after the light
blast okay
so I don't know if you guys have what
you need to make it maybe you can make
it later you can make it tomorrow which
is fine too good to see you as well I
want to see how you guys were doing and
everything want to check in see how
everybody was
the light blast was incredible
wow incredible that's that's amazing
the the last Light blast right
the last one that Spirit of compassion
sent down that's that one right there
that was at full power
and
I don't even know I don't even know what
to say I actually was speechless after
it I actually was speechless and I had a
just that was it I had to
um
how are you guys feeling so I just
wanted to connect with you guys okay
when I'm making a healing broth
the light blast was phenomenal
amazing what kind of experiences did you
guys have
so we're live right now you guys this
isn't pre-recorded this is right this is
the day after the light blast
the night after whatever and and you're
here your body so Lisa Marie says my
body was cool when it was done that's
amazing because here's what's incredible
about the light blast it's it does
something different for every single
person because it depends on what you
need
it's not a one-size-fits-all light blast
everybody's different with their
emotional challenges their emotional
hardships all that they've been through
in their life all that they're
struggling with physically mentally
emotionally spiritually it's not like a
one-size-fits-all light blast the light
comes down and it does something
different for each person you may feel
it something different when it's
happening
umakali the whole experience was so
special amazing it's honored to have you
there too
seriously and Jackie you love the light
blast amazing and you know I think that
here's the thing about it right now
expect
other Sensations expect other healing
things to unravel for you too because
when the light blast comes down
it has the power to fix some people
literally in seconds some kind of
emotional release
and then it has the the power and the
ability to elongate it right for another
person it could take a little bit longer
because it's supposed to happen for that
person they're supposed to release it as
the hours go by and as the days go by
you know what I mean so it's not going
to be some somebody it's gonna hit the
first when the first light blast came
down Spirit of compassion was telling me
there was a bunch bunch of people
where boom it just
rocked all the all the negativity right
out of them just shot right out of them
right
and I couldn't Express all that in the
moment right there because I'm trying to
focus I'm trying to line it up with
Spirit compassion I I have a I'm going
blind on top of it so literally I'm
losing my eyesight completely as it's
all happening right because
it was a it
and then so I can't explain everything
as it's happening in that moment
but what I heard from Spirit of
compassion because so much information
was coming through
was that there was a bunch of people
where that first that first light blast
that came down it just literally shot
the negativity right out of them
and
you know people can call it what they
want they can call negativity some
people call negativity like demons
around people some people call
negativity just like negative energy
right negative energy
so whatever
belief system you have
whatever you believe in
you know whatever religion belief system
Faith whatever it is
you can see it in a different way right
so Spirit of compassion was telling me
that literally on that first blast when
it came down
there was a whole bunch of people where
it hit like that and just everything
went out like everything went out of
them
that wasn't supposed to be there
naturally right
I was just so blown away by that all on
its own and then and then there was
people where
it had to be a time release they were it
was like gradual to each light blast as
it was happening
and then the final light blast is what
did it right
and then there's people where it's going
to be now Time released because the
power of that final light blast it's the
time release that's going to happen
today right now right now things are
happening within them
emotional blocks
are actually healing being released
negative blocks being released so
there's this time release it's everybody
is different
so as the light comes down
every single person is going to be
different with how it's happening for
them
the whole thing is just so incredible
this is healing broth
and I'm making one right now
so we're going to talk about this I want
to see how you guys are doing
so how are you guys feeling that's
something you want to ask you guys how
you're feeling too
good to see you too as well
amazing I'm just going to prepare this
and just get a little bit of this in the
pot if you guys don't don't mind there I
got the burner on and making some
healing process a perfect perfect meal
and Fuel and food and recipe for
something like the light glass it's so
it works really hand in hand
Melissa said chills throughout the whole
time
incredible I mean and
you're a bit tired today educating
myself you said you're a bit tired today
absolutely depends what comes out of you
but then think about what's going to be
gained
Kristen says the light blast took away
the Dark Cloud that's been hovering over
me eased my depression that's incredible
and IG I said I felt a lot so nicolina
says I felt a lot of release from
the light blast I believe my dog felt it
as well
I had my hand on her the whole time and
after that last last Light blast the
last one whoa she jumped up from laying
down
incredible Erica Malik
very emotional experience kept crying
every time he sent the light down
I was trying to keep it together right
for a whole time
on IG sarri said we felt we were
floating afterwards also my chronic
nerve pain in my neck stopped suddenly
I've seen that in the what happens is
that when I used to do the light blasts
in the in all the big gatherings and
right the concerts and everything would
we do the lectures we do the light blast
and
people with their neck pain and back
pain and shoulder pain it would just be
blasted right out of them
and
Jackie B after the second life last
second one I felt energy running through
both my arms
you know I love hearing this because
everybody's going to have a different
experience but there's a reason and
spirit of compassion has always told me
there's a reason why people have
different experiences
Axel says the light blast made me feel
like I was floating for a full few hours
after I actually felt like I was
floating after
so afterwards it's that that's that's
how I felt felt I was floating the whole
night Laura said I cried and felt it
everywhere
just incredible I'm gonna just get this
going right here the healing broth
so I'm chopping up some carrots here you
can chop them up any way you want
just don't chop your finger right
so I'm just getting a few carrots in
here
that
that griddle's getting hot I hear it
sizzling guys if you just came on here
we're talking about the light blast
this is the afterward of the light blast
this is reflection having a discussion
right
because
it was an experience
and when you have an experience like
that it's good to kind of get together
that's actually really good to get
together afterwards talk about it
because everybody's going to be feeling
it today and after today and the day
after but it's fresh right now
it's actually fresh
like I feel the light still in me
foreign
there was a lot to say but I had to
focus and stay focused
sort of compassion was telling me a lot
of suffering that you guys were going
through
there were people in wheelchairs
Spirit was telling me about
foreign
for them for being here for being there
last night being here there right last
night
and
I was really happy about it
but I also felt
their pain and suffering what they've
been through
Spirit of compassion told me there was
somebody there last night that suffered
from severe severe depression
catastrophic depression
Spirit of Ashley knew who was out there
knew everybody that was out there
there's times I wanted to cry I actually
got really emotional
I'm not a big crier in the sense where I
cry a lot
because
um
because it's it's not about me it's
about what the other person is going
through
so I do shed tears
but I have to remember
if I if if I Cry
if I cry then then I gotta think about
everybody who's going through so much
I'll be crying all day all night
It Won't Stop
because spiritual compassion is always
telling me so many people are suffering
so I would never ever stop crying
it would be the minute I woke up in the
morning to the minute I fell asleep
every single day seven days a week I
would only be in tears
Michonne J says the final light blast
was powerful the final light blast
was so powerful
it was so powerful that
my description of what I felt in the
moment were that's when I totally went
blind completely blind but but I just
felt like I was transported when the
final last Light blast came down I felt
like I was transported
I couldn't even describe it
I'm making the healing broth you guys
I'm feeling so much calmer today why
blueberry
said
this is my this is the healing broth
this I like the healing broth after a
life last because it's gentle on the
system it helps with releasing emotions
that are trapped it helps with healing
it helps to rebuild the immune system I
love having the healing broth after the
light blast it's definitely something
that we should all do if you get a
chance
foreign
that's not the only light blast we're
gonna do
God willing
I'm gonna put some parsley in here you
guys I just put carrots I just put
celery in here making the healing broth
now I'm gonna put some parsley in here
you just got on here we're talking about
a reflection and discussion about the
life last last night
it was incredible
Grace Cooley says thanks so much for the
wonderful light blast yesterday I loved
it so powerful
I felt like I was transported to another
time and place
the most bizarre feeling
Lorraine Hendricks says I woke up with
much more energy too
with a whole bunch of these right after
that
I'm gonna put a little turmeric in here
I'm gonna put some ginger in here too
just lost that one
gotta love doing the live thing I'll
tell you we were live on that light
blast
that light blast was live all right
we're live now too you guys
trying to get this all in here
I'm gonna pop a little water in here if
you guys don't mind
we're gonna pop some more into
you guys are just getting on here
I just want to say something
okay if you don't know what we did last
night we did the light blast last night
super compassion sent down a blasted
light
the first time it came down and landed
on everybody's head right on the crown
of everybody's head
right
sort of compassion told me it literally
shocked and
and sent flying like shrapnel negative
energy out of a whole bunch of people
but like I said during that light blast
there was a lot of tough cookies there
and so Spirit of compassion said look we
have a lot of tough cookies we have a
lot of people with stubborn blocks
and so we had to do more than that first
light blast then we had to do another in
the the second one
shot out a whole bunch of negative
energy out of a whole bunch of people
just just right out of them like like a
grenade like shrapnel it went flying
and their soul and their their body were
being was being freed
so many people are conditioned and have
no idea how brainwashed and condition
they were through this process of being
on planet Earth
and that light blast is freeing people
of that
please share your experience you guys
of the light blast if you can tag at
Medical medium hashtag at Medical medium
I would you know
I would love to share your reels and
your posts
so if you can that would be incredible
so I can share it with the community
foreign that would be incredible
so 21 000 people
is all we could take in that light blast
we're gonna do it again
so you guys want to look out sign up to
the newsletter so you know when that
light blast is coming and I apologize if
you missed it because we had a problem
with technology a few things happened
it turns out a lot of people share the
link
and there were thousands and thousands
and thousands of more people trying to
get onto the light blast and they didn't
sign up originally
and so it exceeded 21
000 and it went way past it and it
crashed our entire system
what I'm trying to say
a lot of people didn't
sign up the the right way so that we
could all have a good experience instead
because the system went down because
there was a lot of people
that signed up when they missed their
chance to sign up and they were like no
way I'm not taking this crap I'm gonna I
got the link from somebody else who gave
it to this group and then this group in
this group we're all gonna get the light
blast it doesn't matter what aw says
about 20 000 people when we allowed to
sign up we're gonna do it and next thing
you know it the whole system went down
and my whole team of people were working
feverishly feverishly and we were trying
to get it all back up so we can do it
and finally we can do we did it but it
turned into a mess as far as technology
wise
foreign
you guys could not experience a light
blasted for some reason you signed up
but then could not
you know hear it and be a part of it
we're gonna do it again
we're gonna do it again and I'm hoping
that people don't give the links out to
thousands and thousands and thousands of
people
lupus free with celery three through
three it's a cool handle my kids were
blocked in different places my 13 year
old's hip hips my 15 year olds knee and
Ankle we all slept soundly incredible
incredible
foreign
see lot said
how are you feeling
would that be more
would that be me
well I can just tell you right now
I was shot from it afterwards but that's
okay
because
they do take a lot out of me but that's
all right because
I slept good
woke up this morning I was like let's do
it again
let's do it again Spirit of compassion
I mean it's look I'm not gonna sit here
and and
tell you something different takes a lot
out of me
absolutely
but that's okay
because guess what
here's how it works if you guys just got
in here I want to talk about how the
light blast Works a little bit so you so
you know this this is really important
to know the light's not coming from me
so I'm not I'm not doing I'm not doing
the light blast so if you go and get
like if you need a light worker A Healer
right
because we all have light inside of us
right and we can all project light okay
right the problem is with that
is that
that light has gone through a human
right
foreign
so that's a different situation
so this isn't light that's coming from
Anthony William himself personally right
there this is a light coming from above
streaming down that light is pure that
light is untampered with it's not
tainted by baggage there's no baggage in
that light
I'm not discrediting healers I'm not
discrediting light workers not at all I
believe we all have light inside of us
but we also all have a crap ton of
baggage
a lot of baggage I've seen throughout
the years
I've seen Healers
I remember this one Healer many years
ago
right that would work on people that
were getting help from me
and what was happening is he was doing
light work
on women
but he was taking light away Spirit of
compassion told me
he was taking light away from them so he
was kind of like an energy sucker
he was doing light work on women
this healer guy but he was kind of
vampiring their light away right energy
because
he was like a negative energy blob that
needed the light
it's interesting how it works I'm not
saying all light workers are like that
that's not at all
I'm just saying that
no one's perfect on this Earth and that
no one's perfect so what I mean by that
is
we all carry baggage
and I want people to do light work
on themselves and loved ones absolutely
100 but the difference here with what
happened is that light
carries no baggage that came down
that light is not for me
we all have baggage I'm not a perfect
human being I'm a messenger a spirit and
spirit of compassions information right
but I have never said I'm a perfect
human being on any level
it's not easy to live here on planet
Earth right
so what happens with the light blast
here and what I've done all these years
as this is coming from above
and like and like when we were doing
that light blast all together last night
sort of compassion said look behind the
Stars
because that's where the light was
coming from and it was heading down
and it was this big ball light that was
heading down and I had to line up with
Spirit of compassion the impact and and
when the timing of when I had to
actually because what happened was all
everybody here that was signed up gave
their permission to receive that light
thank you
a new day says on YouTube I feel calm
amazing incredible everybody gave their
permission to receive that light
and so that ball of light coming down I
had to line up I was the messenger
with Spirit of compassion
I had to be that
that soul that individual
that made that happen I had to be the
middle man to make that make sure that
light came down on top of everybody
there
some people might be tired because
they're fighting a flu right now there's
a rampant set of flus
there's the sea going around an
explosion of it right now there's the
RSV going around an explosion of it and
there's a flu going around an explosion
of it
everybody's coming down everybody and
then some
their moms their cousins their
grandmothers are literally all coming
down
with a bug in the next coming couple
weeks today tomorrow it is rampant right
now hospitals are overloaded and full
some people might be tired because
they're fighting a flu they're fighting
RSV they're fighting C and don't even
know it some people already have fatigue
keep that in mind too
and some might have some tiredness today
because their body's doing some healing
and yes some people so much emotional
grief was shot out of them that they're
definitely going to be feeling more on
that subdued level today
rise of Melton said I feel a bit
emotional and tired feels like a
hangover well
I have something for The Hangover right
now because yes you can feel a hangover
yeah she came through a hangover and
this is what I'm doing now that's why
we're doing the healing broth the
healing broth is for post light blast
foreign
it does help with that light hangover
and yes there is a hangover that comes
with the light there's no question
true true
en says I feel so light like a feather
or a balloon after the light blast was
over
incredible
and that's on YouTube on IG I started
laughing after the first two and felt
Giddy and felt lighter after all of it
but I didn't think much had changed
today the joint pain feels less because
here's how it works
so many people are going to feel the
effects of that light blast a day later
a day after
they're gonna feel the effects as each
day goes on some people feel in the
instant when the light hits some people
feel an hour later some people feel it
throughout the night the next day and
then so and so on so on Jackie Dale says
so much energy today I feel incredible
and so many people are gonna have more
energy because of it
heal your body with food on IG says it
was an emotional experience I cried too
thank you for bringing us the light did
you guys hear me I almost started crying
at the beginning
when I was talking I actually was I I
was holding back a cry because I knew if
I started bawling then we wouldn't be
able to get it done
that'd be on the ground sobbing Luma
Kelly says I felt a profound sense of
peace and calm after the light blast
incredible
over there on YouTube Uma and on IG I
felt like that even when we were waiting
very intense charged atmosphere of
course because
because what happens is as we're waiting
there's here's what's here's what's
going on so
I was talking to you guys
at the beginning of the light blast
right
and we were taking some deep breaths
right and I was talking you guys through
I was being told information from Spirit
of compassion the moment
to just be present and be there and
communicate because Spirit of compassion
was getting the light ready
the timing is everything
about the timing and everybody that was
plugged in in the moment everybody 21
000 people plugged in in the moment it
was all about timing and all of it
you giggled at the first blast and
because it was joyful I saw that over
there in IG
and you almost cried over there as well
on IG
okay so I have some healing broth
cooking up
and I'm drinking healing broth too on IG
Joanne hickling said I cried after the
session when I was trying to explain it
to my husband
you're getting me choked up
so I have to I have to kind of giggle
because if I don't giggle the I'm trying
to giggle because you're getting me
choked up
I almost cried during it I don't know if
you heard me my voice was starting to do
something weird I was like oh no oh no
see Rockette says I giggled big time on
the light blast
on the last blast on the last one yeah I
was actually nervous about the last one
because I was listening to Spirit of
compassion on
the Amplified power of each one
and so I was having a conversation with
Spirit of compassion like
is there gonna be another one coming yes
we're only at like 40 percent
so when it was when it was going and
then everybody was blocked not everybody
but almost everybody had a blockage in
the pit of their stomach blockage in
their chest a blockage in their throat
and in their neck
there was
I almost laughed
also during the late blast because there
was this one moment where Spirit of
compassion told me one person out of the
000 it didn't even it didn't even get
down to their ears
there was one person where it went it
was like and he the reason why I laughed
is because I asked Spirit like how's
that possible and spirit compassion said
that person is known in their family
their co-workers and their friends as
being very very very stubborn
very stubborn
but it was it was a guy
really nice guys for a profession but
point is is an amazing person right but
point is it's really stubborn so
stubborn
that the first lay blast
hit the guy's head on top of his head
and spirit of imagined and he stopped at
his ears
the second one went right through and
then hit here
and the third one hit pit of the stomach
and then
right
incredible
Lisa said after the first blast I bawled
like a baby
foreign
said so healing the light blast I first
felt dizzy had pressure and waves in my
back later in the evening I felt relief
and lifted thank you SOC ew
so you guys just came on here we're
making healing broth which is an
incredible way
to soothe everything and the soul
to support the body physically
emotionally spiritually after the light
blast
that
raquette said so I was floating
afterwards I felt really floaty
I stayed where I was
I was sitting down
when I was doing it
Sam key Training said feels like my
heart broke on IG feels like my heart
broke open I've been crying a lot and
releasing so much of my pain that's so
good let it out thank you from the
bottom of my heart incredible if you
have tears that have to come out let
them out
let the cry out
you know release
don't hold any tears in
you're going through this light blast
just just whatever happens
make sure you let those tears out
Linda said I think I was really blocked
felt warm in my stomach and hips over
there in IG
a lot of people are going to feel that a
lot of people are going to feel that
when that happens here's what's really
incredible
we're gonna do it again
are you guys going to want to get a
second light blast
because and we're going to try to open
the door for more people than 21 000
we're going to try to get the technology
to handle more than 21 000 people
because what people don't realize
because someone
a friend called me up this morning and
said how come you don't have the
technology to do more than 21 000 people
that's because it's not just about the
technology
it's about the supernatural
part of it all
can the technology handle the
supernatural power that's coming down
medical medium Army said my mom did it
and when I talked to her this morning
she sounded so much happier and joyful
in her voice on IG incredible it's
always good when Mom is feeling better
more joyful all of it I'm just moving
this um incredible
incredible healing broth around if you
guys don't mind
Kristen said much less brain fog and
better mental state today that means
everything a better mental state from
that love it get rid of the brain fog
wild blueberry love
I was crying too my neck stopped hurting
incredible educating myself said yes a
lot of a lot of less pain for sure
I mean incredible you guys
Michonne Jay I felt light on my feet
after I rested for 20 minutes incredible
and this is this is
Katrin says I felt so much love and pure
happiness during it
amazing Hannity good to see you when you
asked us to imagine the light behind the
Stars I saw it so vividly that's
incredible like I was encountering God
getting choked up again
Grace Cooley said very emotional so
powerful I felt it gets stuck in places
he felt like when it was coming down
right because it comes down like this
boom and then finally go all the way
through and then down into the Earth so
powerful well that's a thing
red light will go right through you and
out of your feet and down into the Earth
Joan Adams said I was so excited but it
didn't feel anything I'm so disappointed
well
I can only give you these words of
wisdom from Spirit of compassion right
now
remember when we were when we were doing
the life last night right
do you remember when I said for some
people they may not feel anything until
a month later things change in their
life look for the signs though
thank you
there could be a windfall emotionally
anything could change and look for those
signs
because that light blast in some people
are going to show
right they're going to show waves of
other things that are happening in their
life because of it
so things are going to be altered and
changed emotionally spiritually even
physically throughout the next couple of
weeks it could be tomorrow for you so
Joan it could be literally tomorrow it's
only the day after
and so tomorrow will be like a day and a
half after and then you can start
feeling it and I talked about that
during the light blast
Smoky Mountain Paradise Michelle yes my
whole body was tingling
still tingling slept like a baby after
oh incredible and on IG let's see blue
child Moon said I started laughing after
the first two
that's incredible and I felt Giddy and
felt lighter and after all of it but I
didn't think much had changed today the
joint pain feels less that's a prime
example Joan these are prime examples
like that one right there your
experience there that
everything could shift along the way
but make sure you sign up for the next
one whenever that is
I don't know how
you know
look
take advantage
of these light blasts you know
um they're not easy to do
takes also a tremendous amount of
resources
team and Technology
time and energy right
there's no charge for it it's free
but take advantage of it because
you know
I'm giving it my all right now but what
if I'm like I can't do one
you know for some reason right
so
if you want to experience it get on
board now
it's a Once in a Lifetime
possibility
be before this I haven't done one since
2016.
meaning in a large amount of people like
this
a wounded animal yes
I have
okay family member yes I have
but a large large crowd
I have not done one in a long time
Lorraine L says the final light blast
was amazing
I felt different afterwards on a deep
emotional level Lorena Richard comment I
think it was on the last YouTuber on
YouTube
rising out of the ashes says on IG it
was interesting what happened with the
sun after the life last year said no the
solar flare
it was very interesting
because that ball of light that sphere
of compassion
had directed down
to us
definitely affected the sun in that
moment
the direction that ball of life
and where it was heading
that ball of light is massive that comes
from Spirit of compassion like the
direction from Spirit of compassion that
ball of light is massive
and it has to hit everybody on the crown
of the head wherever they are in this
planet
it's a tremendous superpower
Hannity can you talk about the reasons
why people have different experiences I
would love to let's do it why this while
the healing broth is
cooking up
so why do people have different
experiences right
because no one's the same and nobody's
soul is the same
we don't have the same Souls
your soul is different
my soul is different
and then
on top of having a different soul
we have different experiences with our
soul
some of us
have a really old soul
and then some of us have a young soul
but every single person has a different
experience to their soul
that happens
in all of the lives that they've had
right
now if you don't believe in having
any lives before this one
your soul is still different and it
still has different experiences
take any belief system you want
clearly you are allowed to have any
belief system you want it's your free
will and your soul and your
individualism right
say that your soul is only here this one
time ever right now in this moment in
history in this present moment in
history this is the only time your soul
exists in a physical form and a human
body experiencing emotional experiences
mental spiritual right
physical experiences and this is your
only time your soul is going to be down
here right now in Planet Earth
it's still different and your
experiences are still different
but say you believe your soul was on
planet Mars 10 million years ago and
maybe your your soul was on another
planet 50 million years ago maybe your
soul was just here on this planet
years before
it's still different and your
experiences are still different whatever
you whatever direction of what you
believe in you want to go
Mandela said
I felt
the light blasts exactly as it was
called
light blast
it went straight through my body down
into my feet
lots of tingling in my feet for around
seven seconds thank you aw and SOC
Spirit of compassion says that there
were a lot of people that felt it hit
every time
boom
I blast
and there are some people
that felt like they were just
transported
some people that felt like
they even didn't even exist in the
moment for a second and that was a
clearing of energy
there's a lot of experiences
the light blast finishes different for
everyone and the last Light blast that
came down that went through everybody
everyone's going to have a different
experience some similar some almost the
same but everybody's going to have a
little bit of a different experience
Adria says Anthony
eight explanation points I feel
incredible after it
a whole bunch more explanation points
all my pains and aches went away this
thing works I'm honored thank you so
much
I even feel lighter incredible thank you
for being there and I want to say
something to you guys
like thank you for wanting to be there
okay for wanting to do additional
healing
thank you for for being there
seriously I got an incredible healing
broth cooking right now
Tomatoes carrots onions onions
there's no onions in this oh my God
oh my God
I am guilty of not getting my hands in
the healing rod
summon an oxym in right now
yep
you guys I want to make an announcement
are you with me
I want to make an announcement
are you ready for this
seriously are you ready for this
I'm just asking I'd like to know
oh my God
20-day brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge
a 20-day brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge do you guys remember the last
one the 10-day print shot therapy Cloud
challenge right do you remember how
insane that was you remember how
horrible that is the 20-day
Branch out there be a challenge
January 10th
it's happening
sign up download your free
shopping list sign up to the challenge
so you can receive right daily recipe
shopping list information all of it
please do this
all right let me get an onion in here
January 10th we are doing
the medical medium brain shot therapy
challenge cleanse
said it backwards right
foreign
if you are not signed up you will not
get the daily emails with page numbers
recipes and more
you guys got to sign up
so you can get your shopping list in a
whole bit we are doing the brain shot
therapy question I just want to say this
you can sign up and you don't even have
to do it if you don't want to and if you
just want to be there with us all we're
going to have a great time and there's
going to be a lot to learn a lot to talk
about brain stuff everything plus all
the healing that's going to happen but
try to try to sign up and try to do it
with us
all right so I'm getting some onion in
here
making the healing broth we're talking
about the light blast we're reflecting
and we're having a discussion about the
light blasts
sorry for
being so loud about that announcement
Lincoln profile and description check it
out for the brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge the link is in the profile and
description or go to medicalmedium.com
foreign
so what you're seeing right here
is the healing broth
I like simmering taking some time then
we're going to strain it and then we're
going to make
some broth
and being that the RSV and the C and the
flu is going around rampant right now
like rampant right now
a healing broth is actually something
that has multi-purposes not just after
the light blast but because protecting
our immune system keeping our immune
system strong during what's happening
right now where hospitals are overloaded
with people that have the RSV flu and
the sea
so in the next couple days
people are going to feel more Sensations
more things
more emotions leave more
insight
so more insight too at the same time
Catalan says I feel very light like a
reborn and endless peace
it's incredible
incredible you guys
on IG before the light blast
my husband had congestion and a cough
for over a month today it's completely
gone he said his head and chest feel
clear than they have in months thank you
so much
remember at the beginning of the light
blast you guys remember when I said why
are you here
I said why are you here where do you
want this light to be directed to
where do you want and here's the thing
the light is so powerful if you haven't
directed someplace it's still going to
hit other things in other places and
other parts of you
Lindsay said the late blast was amazing
I felt it healed my brain and more of my
soul came back to me
that means everything to me okay
because
when anybody's blocked or they've been
tattered or beaten down because this
world's so hard any kind of Freedom we
can get
I really believe people's free will get
so like controlled and stifled and
it's really it's really so hard what
people go through
so Sonny said I felt like Joan initially
but feeling more emotionally today and
just notice that my knee is not stiff
today that's what used to happen too
when we used to do the light blast sort
of compassion I used to do the light
blast during lectures throughout the
years past and concerts what would
happen is a lot of people it would hit
him in the moment
there was somebody that actually walked
when they were wheelchair bound right
afterwards and then other people the day
later their knees stopped hurting a day
later something got better some
emotional release happened a day later
two days later
the last two or three light blasts I
felt like the energy was storming
throughout my body yep
rushing down with intense power
incredible so guys if you just got here
we're making the healing broth do you
have the ingredients for the healing
broth you want to write it down right
now you can also go to medicalmedium.com
and check out the healing broth right
and check out the healing broth recipe
but we got the carrots you got the
onions you got the celery you've got the
garlic you got the ginger you got the
turmeric you got the tomatoes and the
parsley
let it simmer put eight cups of water in
there you can you can always make a
bigger one if you have to give the
healing broth for the whole family or
friends or you want extra you can make
it bigger this is a pretty decent size
right here
and so what I do is
I always have a fresh one but I also
have the one you know from the night
before or something that I can easily
reheat and I have that in this mug
but right now here's the the fresh one
I'm making with you guys right now
my God so many experience experiences
you guys are having
it's just absolutely incredible
so someone just I saw the comments are
going up pretty quick on me but someone
said they felt like it went just Midway
through and it got stuck
did you feel the final light blast when
it rushed through
Spirit of compassion said it was going
to be at full power the final one I
actually got nervous
because I didn't know if there was going
to be any scragglers left number one
number two I knew that that full power
was going to be really strong
and when it came down I actually was
nervous on that last one
I had the sense of Joy getting this and
emotional kind of like
also was choked up at all at the same
time
Joanne said I've been trying to heal
from Decades of emotional wounds light
blast stuck in my stomach a few times
then it broke through to my legs amen I
feel so light today
you know when I was with you guys
last night
and spirit was telling me many of you
have been through a lot in your life
like a lot of things people don't know
unless they've unless they walk in your
shoes unless they've been in your shoes
before
and
they don't know what it's like unless
they've been there
to all the doctor's appointments and all
the hardships with other people in your
lives and relationships and
and family and
friends and co-workers in difficult
situations
they don't know
they don't know what you feel unless
they've really experienced themselves if
people need to reference from their own
experience right isn't that how people
are
like I know people that they'll just
never understand what you're even
talking about
unless they could actually reference it
to like oh no I I've been through that I
had I had that car crash and
you know my pelvic my pelvic was
fractured I had my I had that car
there's people just they have to like
experience it they have to reference it
for it to be like legit or something too
that's crazy
but there were so many people last night
that had so much
we've been through so much
and I felt it I felt it
you guys right now the healing broth is
amazing for anyone who's sick right now
with the sea or flu or RSV right
and then you also got the brain you got
the brain saver books you got the shock
therapies too right
she's got the shock therapies cold and
flu protocols and the shock Therapies in
the brain saver book
do you guys have the book
and right now that's like an incredible
incredible sale
on amazon.com us right now for these
books I mean protocols is like 22 or
something insane protocols and shock
Therapies in the brain saver books right
here I did live streams on things that
can help you so check them out at
medicalmedium.com so you can see the
live streams that I did about helping
people with RSV and the flu NC right
but I'm just showing you the books in
case you don't have the books you might
want to have the brain saver books but
I'm giving you if you're new and you
don't like and you're like you don't
have the brain saver books for warning
there over 600 pages each and they're
packed with so much information that's
never before been seen these are the
greatest books
of all time you'll you'll know when you
actually crack them open you'll be like
dear Lord
okay the shock therapies and the Brain
Savers right the brain saver books are
incredible
and the and the C is rampant right now
and RSV is rampant and the flu is
rampant right now so that the protocols
in here for the flu the flu protocols in
here are really incredible protocols so
I'm just letting you know
check them out when you get the chance
protect yourself
have it ready for you here's here's the
problem here's what happens right now
I'm just going to tell you right now
what goes on
people don't prepare
the minute they get the flu or RSV or C
they don't have anything they need
what I tell my friends and family make
sure you have the protocols
make sure you have what you need
so that the minute it comes you're
prepared and you can do the medical
medium shock Therapies
so you can do the zinc shock therapy you
can do the golden seal shock therapy so
you can actually do the shock Therapies
when a family member contacts me and
says aw a dubs
I'm coming down with something right now
I'm like all right all right you got
your zinc shock therapy ready right you
got your golden steel chakra
um I don't have any zinc and goldenseal
right now nope but don't have my stuff
said these books hold the most important
info in the world right now
Lee Kate says we had C in the house and
your protocols protected us
incredible so I'm telling people be
prepared because
what's coming right now and it's another
reason why I wanted to do the light
blast is because what's coming right now
is a crap storm
the bugs
and it's going to be like this every
week throughout
January February March April
so if you're skating by and not catching
the sea or the flu or RSV in the moment
it's just it's like Russian Roulette man
what week is it going to be
me too 787 I got teary-eyed with
Imagining the home behind the Stars I
think I missed that place
here you go again he gave me choked up
I gotta kinda gotta kind of giggle a
little bit because I
I don't want to start crying right this
second
I'll do that later
I'll have a cry later
Mary said several people were waiting
and misdue to technical issues
can you share a spirit knew they were
there and still sent the light
I can tell you this
that we're doing the light blast again I
don't care what it takes
I don't care what I have to do
I don't care
if I go completely blind afterwards and
I don't care if
I feel
very tired or whatever
for being kind of the catalyst
we're doing it and we're doing it again
we're gonna
come together and do that light blast
again
next year I said all you do you talk
about the soul
my healing broth is almost ready
I'm very excited
the thing about the healing broth is I
tend to I Love The Healing broth the
broth that's the whole point of it it's
so light you don't have to digest really
much of anything because then you give
your immune system and your body
everything it needs to fight that's what
helps to fight right you're not filling
your stomach with a lot of food where
your digestion has to go to the food
then your immune system you know it it
gets busy with all that instead
I like the healing broth because it's
fortifying you've given you fuel giving
you all the electrolytes right in in the
sodium cluster salts and everything else
from the celery and all that is in the
healing broth
and then
you have more fuel to fight
any kind of Invaders
but I do love the fact that it's
incredible all on its own it tastes such
a delicious no matter what
anybody's welcome to do the light blast
I don't care what faith it is or a
religion someone has that's okay
everybody's welcome
if you need to think that light is
something else and think that light is
something else if you need to think
whatever you need to think it's okay the
light is still going to hit the crown of
your head no matter what if you're there
at that light blast that light is still
going to hit the crown of your head and
go through your body and by the last and
the thing is
the amount of light blasts that come
determine how stuck some people are and
the incredible part is if the light ran
through you already by the third time
and the light went through you
completely or by the second time or even
the first what happens is
every light blast after that that
somebody else is stuck you're getting a
whole nother round right through you
going right to the ground
a whole nother light blast is hitting
the crown of your head and running right
through your body
as we have to do it over again because
somebody else they're a tough cookie
they're stubborn and because they're a
tough cookie it's getting stuck here
here here here here right
and so the other person who went through
all the boom they get a whole nother one
how blocked people are kind of
determines also to the to the degree of
how many life lasts are gonna occur
so if you say it says how can we access
other forms spontaneous
healing
if you look into the medical meme
information there are endless tools for
healing
I mean just in the brain saver books
alone
just in the 20-day brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge we're doing January
10th that alone
is incredible
whether it's a heavy metal detox
smoothies whether it's heavy metal detox
cleanses whether it's the mono cleanse
whether it's the morning cleanse
whether it's the 369s whether it's a 369
advances whether it's the anti-radiation
tea whether it's the angels to
communicate with
whatever it is you can look into it
medical medium there's a lot of tools
make sure you follow
that make sure you um
follow a medical medium on Telegram
it's an easy way for us to communicate
and quickly communicate especially
during a light blast and leave audio
messages they are collecting Stones was
the last audio message I left I'll leave
others
have you guys done the collecting stones
that talking talk about incredible
spontaneous healing tool is collecting
stones
what a tool that is it's just it's just
incredible
Luke Roger says I was signed up
for the light blast but missed it I am
so sad about it Luke hang in there we're
gonna do it again can I say what
happened for a second if you guys don't
mind
what happened was a whole bunch of
people and I'm not I'm not saying
anything
bad about anyone
a whole bunch of people
wanted to help up a whole bunch of other
people
so they gave out the link
it turned out not only just 21 000
people which our system was only geared
up for
there
but because the link was given out so
much to large groups of people and and
it was passed about it moved it up
thousands and thousands of more and it
crashed the system for everybody else
so we fought desperately my team
did I have to give them the credit
fought desperately to try to get it up
and running to get the engine up and
running again so we can do that light
blast as Spirit of compassion was
waiting for us to do and everybody else
was waiting for us to do
Stephanie said see I didn't sleep much
at all still I didn't feel tired when
waking up
incredible
cholanta said after light blast I felt
so peaceful afterwards amazing
I'm just proud of you guys seriously and
I'm honored you were there
Lana says I felt the light hours after
the blast
it was mind-blowing I am changed and I
feel so much lighter
when I think about what that light's
doing when it enters into everybody and
what it's doing I'm mind blown about it
myself because I know so many people are
stuck with so many different trapped
emotions trapped emotions in their
organs trapped emotions in their soul
wounds and scars hardships and losses
relationship breakups divorces hardships
and all kinds of way all kinds of
different confrontation they dealt with
in their life emotional wounds
everything negativity negative energy
all of it and depending on what you
believe like what faith you have or what
you believe in some people believe
demons were knocked out of them some
people believe negative energy was
knocked out of them some people believe
that the light is directly coming from
God and some people believe this light
was just out there waiting to come down
but everybody has a different belief
system and everybody's welcome to
experience it
because it's not one size fits all it
was there for everybody and what's
happening in their lives and their
individuality of their souls McCallie
says your voice was so calm yesterday
even after all the tech issues yeah you
should have seen me during the attack
issues
Uma
that would have been a funny one if that
if that was hot miked
during
during the time where we're having all
the blow ups and the system went down
right
that would have been a really good one
to air
foreign T and I was like can we get
please get this going again
everybody's waiting we need to get the
light to everybody
I was like please
Agostino maybe maybe someone tried to
stop the life last from happening
okay you have stumbled across something
I do have to say
because that was something else we were
figuring out as well my team was
detecting that there was also a little
bit of sabotage along with it
because
that's what happens
anyway if you guys just got on here
20-day brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge coming up January 10th
every brain shot
is an experience on its own I do them
every day
I am pumped I am psyched
if you don't have a juicer check out the
mm1500 mm-900 which leads me to say one
thing
that's very important
if you have an mm-1500 or mm-900 did you
know that the it's the only juicers out
there the warranty I mean
it's like literally covers everything
and I'm going to talk about it on
telegram because I want you guys to like
hear about it
but whatever just make sure you're there
even if you don't have the stuff you
need because guess what if you're
watching the brand shot therapy child
punch challenge you can join in three
days into it if you wanted to do we're
doing a 20 day in a row
foreign
leave a telegram about it too
Christine said you look so good today I
can't believe it
because I was called every single name
in the book during the holidays
by influencers that hate medical medium
foreign
I was called so many names this holiday
season between Thanksgiving and and
Christmas
that it was unbelievable really
I think there was a list
of like a hundred names I was called
and ugly was in the list so thank you
for saying I look okay
Bettina
when the first light blast entered my
body I cried
Spirit of compassion told me that there
were people that literally had tears
coming out but it was a good crying
it was such a relief first it only
entered my head and felt like a soft
Flash and each time it went deeper
incredible
I think somebody on IG said your 10 year
old and your husband said that your
bodies were tingly from it
I heard that too I I heard that from
some friends
and some family that were
um they were also signed up for the
light blast
and they said that they felt like a
tingly a whole tingly thing happened
you guys I'm gonna strain this I think
we're pretty much we have an incredible
healing broth I just love to simmer it
down if you simmer it really down too it
just it comes out so good I'm gonna get
a bowl ready
whoa
you guys don't mind I'm just
[Music]
getting stuff together here
I'm excited about this healing broth
there's no chicken in this healing broth
I just didn't want to put a bird in
there well Spirit of compassion said the
healing broth is the healing broth it's
it's the ingredients that
synergistically come together with what
with what you see
so if I wanted a chicken in here
no go I think I'm going to pour it out
now we're done
so there's no there's no chicken in this
broth and good reason there's no chicken
in this broth
um I don't think Dr Nesbitt would really
appreciate if there was Chicken in his
broth Dr Nesbit just try not to get too
close to the pot Dr Desmond says it
smells pretty good and it's chicken free
which is actually really helpful oh
wait
on IG apparently Dr Nesbitt you're not
being seen so easily on IG so there you
go Darkness but are you sticking out in
the corner there
yep anyway I'm Dr Casper yes that is
your
yes that's your tick tock
Dr nesbitt's Tick Tock yes
Dr nesmet we were permanently banned on
tick tock yeah
that's your Tick Tock we're using Dr
Nesbitt we're using his Tick Tock he
knows that you guys
I got a Dr Nesbitt will you come back in
a little while I think Dr Nesbitt wants
to come back in a little bit
right
Michelle says when you said
there are some tough cookies in here
Michelle where'd you go there's some
tough cookies in here I knew I was in
that crowd
shall
okay
you said some people may not so
so Audra Lynn said
comments that go flying around
I'm trying to find that comment I'm
going to strain this please hang in
there
here we go
nice
okay
shut that off I'm gonna put this over
here
guys we're in the kitchen
all right
okay okay okay
foreign
that is the healing Roth right here
pretty incredible
and they have a new
smug I'm going to use for this
all right you guys
all right showing IG
my body said getting banned on Tick Tock
legendary equals legendary I'm not just
banned on tick tock
I'm permanently banned on tick tock
that's only just for a few
so maybe that is legendary
permanently banned
it's pretty funny
only cool people get banned on tick tock
on IG that's what you said
once again I'm not just banned on Tick
Tock I'm permanently banned on tick tock
there's a difference by the way so do I
take the do I take the award
because seriously
something for your soul on T on IG said
on IG said permanently banned what
that's flipping harsh permanently banned
I think that's only for
I don't know one person on the planet me
thank you very much I was permanently
manned on tick tock
and guess what they gave me no reasons
they actually gave me no reasons
they gave no real reasons and guess what
you guys they gave me no warning
and no way to appeal or come back
that's what Tick Tock did not only did
they permanently ban me not banned me I
might be the only one this has happened
to that's what we actually think by the
way
permanently banned with no way to reach
back to them
no way to appeal
and they did it right when
these babies came out
right when they came out
I wonder why they didn't want this
information to get in the hands of
everybody huh
I wonder why
hmm life-saving books
yeah no it's a record
Luca says why did I feel heavy oh during
the the light blast
it's incredible
I love that like that's an individual
experience for sure
Reggie Natura says I was euphoric
when it started amazing get the healing
broth in you if you can go to
medicalme.com or or just get it on the
medical medium books the recipe
Gabriel said I couldn't
here you are I couldn't be there for a
reason but I am so happy for those who
receive the light blast and heal
for what I'm hearing from aw
I am very happy for these people thank
you aw and spirit that Gabriel we're
going to do it again we are going to do
another life blast I don't know when but
we're going to make sure it happens
we're going to work hard on it we're
going to work very hard to make it
happen
we really are okay I I got my team
working hard on it it's free too okay I
don't want payment for the light blast
I just I don't want to charge people for
the light blast
we're gonna use our resources we're
gonna use our money our resources our
time our energy I want to make this
thing happen I want people to experience
this
and we're going to do it again and we're
gonna do it soon so just keep a lookout
sign up to my newsletter at
medicalmedium.com go there and sign up
to the newsletter so you don't miss out
because here's what's going to happen
when we do announce
the sign up for the light blast the next
light blast It's Gonna Fill up quick
try to keep like your eyes on that it's
going to fill up quick it filled up
to 21 000 people and that's all our
system could handle so we had to stop
with admissions we didn't stop with it
but it was going to keep on going and
keep on going and keep on going and so
we but we couldn't do it and we're going
to try to open the gate for for more
people so we're going to try that next
time to open the gate for more people if
we can but you have to be on the
newsletter so you know when that's
coming if you're having a problem and
not receiving the newsletters but you
hear other people receiving it
try to reach out to us to let us know so
we can help in some way can you freeze
the broth yes you can
you can freeze the broth
but if you freeze the broth it's not
going to be like a fun thing to drink
it's going to be a solid ice cube and
you're going to go
like this I'm kidding you can thaw it
after you freeze it we know that
that that's really hot right now and I
don't feel like burning my tongue or
burning my my lip
it's so good
foreign
I just love that feeling when it's going
down
Kathy said I didn't feel it at the time
but I do feel so much lighter today A
lot of people are gonna feel it that way
like I was saying
some people they're going to be getting
out of a wheelchair some people they're
going to feel all this weird sensation
some people emotions are going to fly
everywhere and some people are going to
feel it the next day some people are
going to feel it a week later but it's
if they were there and they were getting
the light blast something's going to
happen
including even protection for certain
things helping people
incredible I just want to say
that I'm honored you guys were there I'm
honors you guys are here right now thank
you for hanging out with me and and
communicating
okay this incredible light blast
reflection means so much to me I can't
even tell you guys
Jess hey Jess
e Lane
I even had no pain or discomfort in my
shoulder back issue
I've had for a long time after life
blast incredible you're on YouTube
thanks Jess
Elena
my hands feel better Anthony I asked for
my hands to heal also flu symptoms
disappeared I had severe flu or sea bug
emotionally feel so much better feel
like my soul is healed incredible you're
on YouTube I see you leave comments on
YouTube
you guys I read the comments if you
don't see me respond it's because it's
literally impossible for me to respond
to comments because I'm I'm working so
when I read the comments I'm working on
other jobs
but I read the comments if you guys want
to leave comments on YouTube please do
I'll read them all I'll read them all if
you want to say Anthony you're a pain in
the butt and
and you're not a handsome guy and
whatever whatever you want to say on
YouTube or wherever you want to leave
comments on all the places I will read
them all
Jackie says why are some of us so
blocked
everybody has different experiences in
their life they've been tortured
emotionally a lot of people have had
mental abuse a lot of people have been
injured emotionally a lot of people have
been scarred emotionally so many people
had so many different issues throughout
their life a lot of people had hardships
growing up they've had difficulties with
with family growing up they've had a lot
of things people everybody has their own
stuff going on they got their own
baggage they got their own stuff going
on we all have that and so that light
that light coming down each person it's
going to be different as it's coming
down until it finally goes through and
out and all the way
Monica says when are you planning the
next light blast we are planning it soon
please keep a lookout I don't want you
missing it
in this lifetime we're all in together
and I want to say something that it's an
honor to have you guys in this present
day like on the Forefront
of history in this lifetime that we're
in being on this planet right now alive
together at the same time is really
an incredible blessing
I can't even say it enough
I'll see you on the telegram
later tonight I'm gonna leave a message
love you guys