medical medium information obviously
really changed my life I was sick for
about six years going through um all my
health symptoms and I tried so many
different ways to try to heal myself I
tried nutrition and functional medicine
all these different diets herbs
supplements Chinese medicine everything
and I was still not getting better and
then I ended up breaking out into hives
out of nowhere and I was drastically
searching the internet I literally
Googled like natural remedies for hives
and this blog about celery juice came up
and 3 days my hives were gone and I went
back to the blog post and I was like
where did this information come from and
it said medical medium and I immediately
bought all the books read them solved
because I finally found answers and
within 6 months I was medication free
and I was able to reverse multiple
chronic illnesses autoimmune disease and
now I help other people do the same
[Music]