[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello my name's Anthony William
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week we talk about
the most advanced healing information on
health that's out there anywhere there's
no other show no other book no other
podcast no anything that has the
information we offer it's well known at
this point what we're doing at the
medical medium series books and how this
information is decades ahead of what's
out there now if you're new to the show
just giving you the 411 on that so you
know we're going to we're talking today
about liver myths liver myths so what's
what's a li what's a liver myth
basically what that means is things like
liver flushing liver Stones we're going
to talk all about that that's
interesting right I think it is and it's
important to know we're going to talk
about eating liver how about that one
what about Ox bile and you know this is
out of the liver rescue book but just
please know that this is a
fraction of what's in Liver Rescue and
it's literally a fraction like just a
grain of rice to a silo of rice as far
as what's in Liver Rescue and even in
the section the chapter in Liver Rescue
about myths and you know liver myths and
so forth so um even with this this is
just a couple of things compared to
what's in there so just letting you know
so you don't think oh I heard about that
and oh whatever you just missed out then
you missed out so go to the library take
out the Liver Rescue book um go to
amazon.com get it there too whatever you
need to do the information in Liver
Rescue is decades ahead ahead of what's
out there now that's the whole point you
know you need you need information that
actually can take you someplace that
actually can help you heal and it's
really important that you you become
that expert so you can take care of your
loved ones and your health and your own
health and I mean your loved On's Health
your friends Health your family
everybody co-workers it's it is really
that important I see people struggling
out there for many years I've helped
thousands of people over the years
celery juice the very thing we started
uh medical medium uh the series started
you know back a few years ago and even
before that I started celery juice um
getting it out there for people that's
taking the World by storm helping people
recover in so many ways and it's so
helpful for the liver too and it's still
the very little is known about celery
juice except for here the source of
where it started and we're going to talk
about celery juice a little with this
because when you're dealing with things
like liver stones and you're doing liver
flushes and you're you're trying to get
your bile better by taking Ox bile
really what you need is celery juice but
we're going to go into the myths and
we're going to take a look at this and
see where we're starting let's start
with eating liver okay so eating liver's
been around for a while you guys know
that you've heard of that right you have
turkey turkey uh stuffing might have the
turkey Liz turkey gizzards in there
whatever you call them about to say
lizards the tur turkey liver right
chicken liver um that's something that
you know people do eat cow liver um so
liver is actually something that's
that's been around people eat it they
fry it in a pan they bake it in the oven
they broil it or whatever and they do
things with liver and the the reason
people eat liver there's two reasons I
always say one reason is they like the
taste so that's one reason the other
reason they think they're getting
something they think they're getting
something nutritious something yummy
something good in them not just good
yummy but something that's really
fortified something that's get building
their blood giving them iron building up
their you know building up their blood
building their hemoglobin building up
their whole you know all kinds of
different things but that's not how it
works it's not how it works I'm going to
go into this right now and this is just
a fun one to start with before we get
into Ox bile and liver flushes and liver
Stones so you guys are going to have a
good time I'm having a good time but
it's really it's really this is like one
of one of my favorite things to talk
about because it just goes to show you
how misinformation travels and becomes
law or travels and becomes some kind of
like popular Trend or something
meanwhile is it really helping no it's
not eating liver is really not a good
thing it's highly toxic so you have to
know how things work the the a liver in
an animal
is there to collect poison that's what a
liver is doing it's there to collect
poison bottom line our livers are
collecting poison you wouldn't want to
eat somebody else's liver fill the toxic
heavy metals in there petrochemicals
solvents Plastics
Pharmaceuticals you you wouldn't want to
eat another person's liver yeah of
course you wouldn't want to duh right
the whole bit but seriously though
can you imagine can you imagine and you
know what the same thing with the cow's
liver there's still all kinds of
pollutants all kinds of heavy metals all
kinds of toxins Generations from the
cow's life going back meaning before and
and and and so forth and and how the
cows were breed it doesn't matter if
it's grass-fed the the livers fill the
to poisons and toxins and and that
happens all I mean that's just the way
it is that's what the liver does
naturally even if planet Earth was PR de
with no mercury in the waterways and no
dioxins everywhere even if it was dioxin
free U Mercury free everything free you
know what's funny you know what's really
funny and this has nothing to do with me
liking animal protein or not or whatever
or not or liking veganism or not or
liking plant-based or vegetarian or
whatever it is it you know it's it's
kind of funny we say you know grass-fed
grass-fed free range pasture you know
pasture ranged or whatever we just I'm
probably not even saying that right
right now you know what I mean we say
like whether it's homegrown okay free
range grass-fed however it works we say
all that right but what about the other
things too is it Mercury free is there
traces of mercury how much dioxin is in
is in there even some of the best parts
of this country here you can have cows
grazing in a field and build up dioxins
heavy inside the liver and build up
other things heavy inside the liver and
that's how what you have to understand
you know what I mean when somebody says
hey is it is it is it is it free range
is the whole bit well wait a minute is
it free of mercury is it free of dioxins
no one know no one would know who cares
nobody cares about any of that when it
comes down to livers when it comes down
to livers it matters it's just same same
thing with like with plant-based is it
organic yeah because you don't want
pesticides in there right you don't want
that kind of thing in there right but
still there's always dioxins and
everything and all that it's just that
with animal products that gets
concentrated more but still it's going
to be a dioxin inside a walnut without a
doubt there's there's going to be there
and no one's saying that like wait a
minute is this dioxin free you know it's
organic but wait a minute is it dioxin
free okay so back to being you know and
that has nothing to do whether I like
animal products or I'm or I like
plant-based or whatever I'm just telling
you how kind of funny that is but the
bottom line is with the liver it is
filled with dioxins it is filled with
dioxins it really is and animal livers
are loaded with them it's the place
where it's concentrated heavy duty
really concentrated if you're eating
liver you're getting a high dose a high
dose of metals dioxins and other
pollutants lots of other pollutants so
you always have to remember that and
depending on what you know if if is it
really yeah it matters if it's grass-fed
it matters if it's not grain fed it
matters if it's not um if
Pharmaceuticals weren't used on the
animals that all matters it does because
then the liver would be yes more
polluted if you were to eat the liver
but the liver is not a place to gain
nutrition it's not a place to gain
nutrients or gain speed or gain anything
in health eating animal liver is
definitely something that's not helpful
whatsoever unless it's the only food
source you have you live somewhere in
the world and the only thing you can
find is an animal liver to eat then yes
okay you better believe it you should
eat it 100% you should eat that animal
liver
100% if it means survival if it means
that's going to put food on your table
for you and your family damn right you
you better eat it and put it on the
table and I support you a billion per.
absolutely but if you have choices any
kind of choice whatever it is if you're
into animal products don't do the liver
do something else in the Animal product
that in the Animal product world that
you like absolutely so it's just you
know and really when it comes down to
the plant-based people they're not going
to be eating animal liver so unless
they're not really plant-based but if
they're really solely plant-based 100%
And and that's what they're they're
doing then they're not going to be
eating livers they're not going to eat
stuffing with chicken liver and it
they're not going to eat stuffing with
turkey liver so it's really I guess for
the animal protein people
just stay away from liver desiccated
liver and supplements stay the heck away
from desiccated liver and supplements
whatever you do if there's supplements
you're taking and you look at the
ingredient list and you're like oh my
God wait desiccated liver desiccated
kidney desec no no no no no get rid of
it get rid of it what what it really
should say be really should say is
desiccated dioxin you know infested
liver okay inside the supplement or
however you want to say it that's what
it should be something around like that
because in the end that's all it is so
yeah so eating livers out bad idea all
around and a terrible idea for your own
liver and that's the other part you want
to hurt your liver eat liver because
then your liver is going to have to
absorb everything that liver was trying
to absorb to protect that creature so as
that liver was protecting the cow or
whatever it is the Lamb or what whatever
it is or the duck hey that's right duck
liver I forgot about that duck liver
right so so when that duck liver I'm I'm
pretty silly today apparently that duck
liver is protecting that duck and that
duck is you know swimming in whatever
Lake whatever Pond you know eating
whatever toxic algae eating getting
exposed to whatever toxic anything
environmentally environmental so that
liver is soaking all that poison up and
waterways are not clean clean I'm sorry
all waterways are not clean all of them
rivers in pristine country still is
polluted you know the craziest thing
about rivers you could be in the country
in the mountains and you could have the
stream rolling through and be like w it
just looks so clean as pristine we're up
here fresh air there's no nothing around
for Miles meanwhile you know back 50
years ago 50 years ago could be a shack
right on the side of that River a shack
that that was there from that 1940s
1950s and what they did in there was
they had all kinds of just stuff going
on and they were dealing with metals and
some kind of manufacturing or some
anything they were play they were
playing around in that shck I mean you'd
be surprised and it's just garbage and
crap I've been I've been in the woods
for most of my life in some of the most
pristine areas over the years especially
when I was younger and I've I've hiked
up like pristine rivers and stuff like
that and then seen like an Old Mill that
was there that was there back 80 years
ago that's still bleeding tons of poison
into into the pristine so-called River
anything like that I've seen little
Shacks that that are on you know sides
of little streams like tiny little
streams and the Shacks like there's all
this rusted garbage in car parts and
mercury and thermometers and all this
garbage all sitting there by this little
stream but if you walked 2 miles down
the stream 3 miles down the stream the
stream would be like it's like pristine
and it's coming out of the mountain it's
like whatever yeah you just the bottom
line is everything's polluted in the
waterways even in the most you know
benign sense or whatever the most
minimal sense the serious sense so the
bottom line is you know what happens is
when you eat liver you're polluting your
liver your liver has to do all the
cleanup on that basically it's like hey
you got a filter your filters your liver
inside your body let's clog that filter
up faster 10 years faster than it would
clog up from whatever the heck you're
doing wrong anyway how about that okay
so that's what it's like when you're
about to eat liver be like hey I'm about
to speed up my liver getting clogged up
right now let me have a piece of this
liver this is good oh iron ooh hemog oh
it's going to build up oh red blood oh
this is going to be good this is going
to get my anemia in a better place let
me cut this little piece let me eat this
right here let me just speed the hell up
my liver dysfunction my stagnant sluggy
sluggy sluggish fatty liver let's just
move that forward into Super stagnant
sluggish you know fatty liver fast
instead of it happening by the time
we're 40 and we get our hot flashes and
then we think it's hormones cuz doctors
have no idea it's just a liver problem
instead of getting you know instead of
the hot flashes and we gain weight and
all that cuz our liver gets sluggish why
don't we move that up quicker a 10 years
before that by keep on eating pieces of
liver that's how silly it is that's how
silly I look I can go on for that
forever with that one but we got better
ones to talk talk about anyway we got
bigger fish to fry we got bigger livers
to fry how about that one we got bigger
livers to fry that's actually really
funny all right I got to stop cracking
myself up you guys I think I'm a little
little too little too giggly today lot
of celery juice I
drank okay so let's go back let's go to
the next one let's talk about let's talk
about uh Ox B since we're on eating
things let's talk have you he about Ox
bile are you taking Ox bile to what
improve your B production or are you
taking Ox bile to digest food better oh
man this one this one look I'm not going
to be able to cover the whole Ox bile
myth or theory in this show so I'm going
to cover a good hunk of it move on to
liver Stones move on to liver flushing
and so forth but I'm going to cover a
piece of it if you want to hear the
whole story about Ox B you got to get
Liver Rescue you just got to get it and
you know so I mean bottom line you just
you just have to you have to just for
that and believe me that book is massive
I mean it's a huge huge book so you can
I mean there's so much information in
there um just this loan is worth the
price of admission and if you can't buy
a book cuz you don't have the money I
understand um I know I know people to be
like I I can't buy a book right now
things are that bad I be like we go to
the library and they like yeah you're
right and they're at the library and
they're taking out the book it's it's
the best thing ever it's such a great
service I love that service it's amazing
means a lot to me actually so here's the
deal dealing with Ox bile you're
consuming something that's actually has
undiscovered chemical compounds in it in
science of research that are damaging
see there's not enough science and
research to oxb because there isn't
going to be now if we were going to fund
nasso we were going to fund space travel
fun funded like giving it infinite
funding you wouldn't believe where we
would be right now no one's going to
give oxp infinite funding in fact
nothing really good in general gets
infinite funing funding and even things
that are bad like oxp don't get infinite
funding so and it doesn't get indefinite
funding so the whole the whole point of
the matter is when it comes down to
something like
oxp is it's not good for us but what's
what's not good force in it still isn't
even really even discovered there's
really nothing going on with Ox B I mean
how much money has been dumped into the
research and the ramifications involved
in the body and everything else really
nothing so when you think about it that
alone's a little spooky but let me tell
you why it's bad let me tell you the
whole thing so when you're taking Ox
pile what you're doing is you're trying
to a it possibly improve or help your
liver and maybe the production of its
own bio Reserves and it's not going to
happen it's not going to happen that's
not even possible and I'll tell you why
in a minute B you're trying to digest
your fats better you're trying to
actually you know disperse your fats
better which it won't because it's only
our bile that can do that it's only our
bile when we eat food we eat food and
it's identified by our body immediately
for the food it is the food we've been
eating for hundreds and hundreds and
hundreds and hundreds of years and even
go down thousands of years that's how it
works
and and it's our bile that disperses the
fats I mean that's just a fraction of
how it works so here's the deal first of
all when you put Ox in you you're
putting in what's kind of like a foreign
foreign alien kind of um you alien
substance inside the body so the liver
sees it as alien too it the makeup is
entirely different everything about Ox
bile is entirely different than human
bile and that's important to understand
and you're not going to build up our
strengthen your liver's bile reserves
with Ox bile you're going to weaken it
what happens is if you want to weaken a
liver you throw in something to throw it
you throw in something to confuse it you
throw in something that completely
throws it off in every way possible and
that's not a good idea to begin with but
I'm going to go into the more heavy duty
reasons why it's just disastrous so
first of all Ox B's chemical compounds
and the structures inside are completely
different like I said earlier than human
B to begin with they're not going to
spend millions and millions of dollars
to to actually figure out what those
chemical compounds are so that alone is
actually dangerous to our liver and to
our body to to a point it's not the
worst thing in the world but it's not
good at all chemical compounds can be
life-altering in a bad way in a very bad
way with our health and here's one of
the reasons why it's not a good idea
concentrations are not going to be
appropriate no matter what an ox is a
gigantic animal compared to a human
being Ox bile the concentration of ox
bile versus the concentration of what
human bile is and those levels has
hasn't even been tapped into isn't even
understood so even if Ox bile was a good
thing in some way the concentrations
would be detrimentally off it would be a
bad situation as far as the
concentration levels you have to know
that so if you're taking some
idea of how much Ox B to take or some
company some pharmaceutical company that
wants to make money and benefit off of
ox bile because it's a trend and you
want to take that the dosage itself is
not even going to even line up remotely
to what would be there it wouldn't it
would be impossible to know the dosage
on that on any level whatsoever so
that's something that's important to
understand and how is that important a
it's damaging to the liver it's a much
more concentrated form and it's like an
alien source to to the liver so it's a
highly concentrated form of bile added
alien form to the liver the liver has a
right to produce bile it's a human right
that the liver has it's a working
chemical function of of almost 2,000 or
over 2,000 chemical functions that the
liver has science and research only know
of about 500 chemical functions that the
liver possesses and they don't really
know a lot about those 500 very little
at all if any
and with the liver really truthfully
having over 2,000 chemical functions how
is it possible to understand what's
going to happen when you pop in when you
pop in that Ox pile one thing that you
have to know is that the liver Has Its
Right to manage its own bio regulation
and it's all it cares about is managing
its own bio regulation you take Ox bile
it goes down into your gut down into
your intestinal tract then it goes
through through the walls of the
intestinal tract because it starts to
get assimilated it starts to get
absorbed when it gets absorbed that
absorption occurs it goes up the hepatic
portal vein up the highway heading to
the liver and it shocks the liver that's
how it works it's the wrong
concentrations because it's not a human
concentration to begin with that's
number one number two when it hits the
liver it can shock it can put it into
shock because the liver has never been
up against something like that before
it's it's it's almost equivalent to
doing something like totally crazy like
I mean I can't think anything off the
top of my head right now but it's like
it's like replacing a loved one with
another loved one but yet it almost
sounds the person almost sounds the same
has the same name bile okay the whole
bit think about it but it's not the same
person but the person's bile that's the
name of the person and it's almost like
you're trying to get along with this
person a whole bit it turns out wait a
minute this isn't even this isn't even
my family member or this isn't even my
friend I mean that's not even a great
way of even you know you know kind of
laying this out but I'm just telling you
that it's it's even far worse than even
that okay so why why would it be so bad
first of all when the liver has its own
ability to produce human bile that's the
whole point it's been doing it for a
long time not in your lifetime hundreds
of lifetimes it's been doing that very
thing thousands of years it's human it's
the human nature it's the liver's right
to produce bile and regulated in the
concentrations and dosage it needs to
now here's the deal if your liver
sluggish and stagnant if it's sluggish
and stagnant and under producing its own
bile or under producing the strength of
its own bile because you have a stagnant
sluggish liver or fatty liver or
problematic liver because you've been
eating diets way too high in fat you've
been hurting your liver eating diets way
too high in fat in the then the trend is
high protein high fat right now how do
you like that which is high protein is
high fat that's the trend so we're here
diminishing the trends or diminishing
people's livers your liver will get
diminished because of that get weakened
get lose its strength and everything
okay so that's what it does but if it's
under producing its own bile out of
being weak and sluggish do you think
having Ox bile driven up the hepatic
portal vein through the intestinal tract
and up the hepatic portal vein into the
liver would is going to then all of a
sudden somehow prompt the liver to
produce more human bile more human bile
it's not possible it's not humanly
possible it's not scientifically
possible it's not anything possible all
it is is just foreign garbage going up
into the liver to the liver it's foreign
garbage at concentration dosages and
chemicals in it meaning chemicals
undiscovered chemicals in there that the
ox liver possesses that no human liver
does is inside of this with information
of an ox liver's information basically
what it is it's a whole thing about the
ox liver for generations and centuries
of oxes and that's inside there so think
about that so your liver is running on
information that's thousands of years
old for humans and human liver um um you
know the human liver body communication
and everything about it to sustain life
to sustain you and it's sitting there
running on that and it's designed in a
way to take care of you in that way and
everything else and designed in a way to
produce its own bio in the way it needs
to and everything else and you got this
foreign bile driving up into the liver
that's got its own information about an
ox's life for generations and
generations and thousands of years
concentrations completely different
chemical compounds in it completely
undiscovered completely different the
liver doesn't work like that it doesn't
like to be pushed the liver doesn't like
to be pushed into anything it not one of
those organs that can handle being
pushed that's how the liver works very
important to understand and it doesn't
like to be poisoned so it actually has
to take that Ox bile and it actually has
to store it away is poison it actually
has to it has to put it into its poison
Banks into its garbage Banks that's what
happens it slows down the liver more
weakens the liver more because bile is
not supposed to do that where you're
supposed to take this bile that was was
was eliminated out of another animal's
liver and then have it go backwards up
into your own liver you can't do that
the liver creates its own bile it
creates it you see there isn't a bile
duct coming from your intestinal tract
to carry and deliver B up into the liver
you know as if that's the way it works
or something it doesn't work like that
it just doesn't so there's no kind of
boport in your in your gut that's
sitting there connected to your liver to
your ass okay and you're and you're and
you're eating you're eating bile that
comes from another animal's liver what
in hopes that it goes up some magic kind
of like bile duct Port right up into the
liver it doesn't work like that
the liver is drawing blood and nutrients
yes up into the liver but it's not
supposed to be drawing another foreign
species another animal creatures bile up
into the liver to to enhance or or
create or you know or help the liver
itself actually you know develop bile it
doesn't work like that celery juice does
though when celery juice actually shakes
up the liver and helps it detox and
cleans and rejuvenates the cells that
produced bi that produced bile the
chemical functions that that actually
develop inside the liver to produce bile
that's that's where it's done that is
where it's done it's really important to
know that's how it's done not throwing
something in there and it all falls into
that whole thing of thousands of years
not even thousands of years ago you know
even recent when you eat something like
to F you think you're going to eat
something to fix something that that
whole stupid thing I'm going to eat I'm
going to eat kidneys to get my kidney
better I'm going to make sure I eat
kidneys it's good for my kidney I'm
going to eat liver to make my liver
better I'm going to I'm going to eat Ox
bile to make you know to make my liver
better to actually get Ox I'm going to
get I'm going to eat Ox bile to make my
bile better if that's not the the
silliest thing ever it was a theory
hundreds of years ago in medieval
medicine medieval medicine okay and in
chronic illness we're still slightly
medieval by the way in chronic illness
not in other parts of medicine other
parts of medicine we doing amazing but
in in the medieval days okay centuries
ago I'm telling you right now it was a
big practice you eat a part of a body of
an animal body to fix your part that's
wrong that was the the consensus because
it was an amazing Theory think about it
if you got an eye trouble eye problem
you eat eyeballs you eat eye that's what
they did but it still carries on today
it still carries on today that's why all
these supplements still have like
desiccated brain oh if you need if you
got brain problems you should be eating
brain if that's not the stupidest thing
I've ever heard if that if that makes
sense to someone they have to learn and
get educated on how the Body Works to
the best they could build it because if
that makes sense it's unbelievable
because and you know what you know what
I'm you know what I'm completely wrong
about something because it seems like it
could make sense sure if I got a brain
problem I should just eat brain that
could fix it and you know what that kind
of does make sense it kind of does so
I'm sorry I even said that it kind of
makes sense but it but but but it's that
bad it's that bad if I have you know and
that's the whole thing that's why it's
like desiccated spleen desiccated liver
any supplements desicated brain
desiccated kidney whatever and it's in
there oh desicated adrenal desicated
whatever oh my God it doesn't work like
this it just doesn't and the thing is if
you're confused about thyroids and how
thyroids work you should read thyroid
healing my book thyroid healing the
medical medium thyroid healing and I
explained why thyroid medicine was the
only thing out of all the ages that ever
did anything the reason mean thyroid
medicine meanwhile desiccated thyroid
the only reason why is because it's it's
a steroid that's why it's an actual
steroid there's steroid compounds in
there so that's one of the reasons it
has a steroid effect and but but but
eating liver and eating brain has no
steroid effect nothing else it was only
the thyroid that some people would
subside some some some symptoms because
it's steroidal that's the whole reason
why medicine gives steroids out for
every single thing that goes wrong any
kind of inflammation so when you have
when you have hashimotos
thyroiditis it's
inflamed and and steroids is what they
use they use both different kinds of
steroids and then they'll use desiccated
thyroid which is a steroid I I've talked
to tons and tons and tons of doctors
over this a doctor friends talk to all
different kinds of people that are in
the best field of medicine in this and
they'll say this they'll say you're
right no it's a steroid it's steroid
compound that's what it is and when you
use steroids for anything you can
actually get some relief because it CS
down inflammation that's what it does
that's what steroids do but that's the
only exception to the rule that's ever
happened ever happened over the years
was the only exception to the rule was
the steroid compound there other than
that for every other exception it
doesn't exist it just doesn't you eat
you eat another animal a part to it I
mean it doesn't fix your aing part heart
it just can't that's how it works and
and with Ox bile it's it's not it's it
sure if you were to eat some brain maybe
it wouldn't be bad maybe it wouldn't be
bad if you ate some brain unless there
was you know mad cow's disease or
something you don't want to eat the
brain of a Mad Cow the point is the the
whole point though it's if it if it's
actually you know wasn't in that kind of
disease State then yeah I mean would it
be that bad probably not same thing is
if if you're eating it would kidney be
that bad probably not liver is actually
bad cuz it's the most toxic organ in the
body so that's actually bad but the
bottom line with Ox B though it's really
bad because it's like Alchemy you
shouldn't play with that's what it is
because an ox and an ox liver is so
different and everything about it it's
got chemical functions that even surpass
the human liver in a sense too many that
live liver could not even figure out
what to do with that
information if anything it can confuse
completely harm the liver I'm just being
straight up and how it works so we got
to be careful and the fats that humans
eat are not what oxes eat whole whole
another thing too so it's a whole
another thing too so Ox bile is geared
for something else and that's that you
can go on and on and on I mean honestly
I can and I can spend forever with the
ox bile because it's it's that you want
to get your liver better you know when
you're bile is having trouble producing
its own bile what it really needs
instead of ox bile is a glass of celery
juice is what it really needs to help
heal and restore itself and that's
that's a big deal that seriously you
know um the bottom line is it's when you
take it one day at a time with your
health and you really get the right
information and the right direction you
could do something about things you
could get your bile strength back up you
can get your body in a place where wow
you can get things to work again if you
get the right information and celery
juice over Ox bile trumps it kills it
it's a billion times better than it it
makes that much of a difference so the
last thing you want to do is push your
liver over the edge and that's what Ox
can do it can push the liver it's
already toxic already sluggish already
stagnant already problematic possibly
already fatty and fill the toxins filled
with all kinds of other levels of toxins
and everything else and you could push
it over the edge and that's not a good
thing Ox bile contains chemical
compounds responsible for chemical
functions that do not occur in your body
in human bodies it also contains
undiscovered amino acids that have no
role at all inside the human body amino
acids that are not supposed to be in a
human body it's different than ox meat
Ox bile is is different than ox meat
it's different than red meat it's
different than an animal meat or
whatever that's entirely different the
the amino acids inside the bile itself
literally that are not monitored un that
are undiscovered that are not being
looked at carefully have no place in the
human body and can I tell you something
playing around with amino acids can be
actually dangerous playing around with
amino acids can be problematic and
dangerous and even even I've seen people
even do amino acid therapies and get so
sick and that's amino acids that
actually do have a role in the human
body the body is very sensitive you got
to be very careful with amino acids and
that's something to really think about
that alone when you consume the Oxo
filled with all these extras all these
extras I'm talking about just now that
your body can't even use amino acids and
everything else that are completely
undiscovered chemical function compounds
all that the extras go down from your
stomach they pass the dadum they absorb
right into the intestinal tract head
directly like I said before into to the
bloodstream the highway up to the liver
meaning that your liver must process
this Blood filled with foreign
oxb so that's why it's not good all on
its own and all for a theory and all for
a theory so look I can go on and on and
on with that one but I want to talk
about even a more fun one which is liver
Stones because I think that would be
actually that would actually be a good
one we'll do uh we'll do liver Stones I
I think that's a great one so let's go
right into that so have you heard about
liver stones have you heard about that
you got these great Brainiac guys out
there now that are that are out there
selling uh selling you know all kinds of
cleanses and everything else and it's
almost like you you get involved and you
know what I mean and you you have to buy
all these supplements and all these
herbs and all this stuff and you know
you have to rack up the money and just
you know and just do your detox do your
detox and what you're doing is you're
you're trying to flush the liver and
you're trying to get liver stones out
and all that I don't know if you guys
has experienced that yet you got to be
careful with that stuff because that's
not how you heal the liver that's not
how you do anything for the liver and
that's not how you get better it's
important to know that there's so
there's so many things you can do that
are so much better and in Liver Rescue I
actually lay it out I lay it out in
there all the things you can do to
protect yourself and do things that
actually do work and heal and so forth
when it comes down to liver and
everything else let's talk about liver
Stones okay so flushing liver stones and
seeing all these liver stones in the
toilet and everything else I'm not
talking about gall stones and I'm going
to talk about that too in a little bit
but but we're talking liver Stones first
of all if you got somebody that's saying
there's liver
Stones then then you you you need to run
you need to run because there are no
liver Stones the liver doesn't produce a
stone it doesn't that's not how it works
so the liver isn't there isn't a bunch
of stone sitting inside in this in in
the middle of your liver so the if
because that's what happens people
imagine this all the time and they get
totally confused this is one of those
myths and theories that are just beyond
me really I honestly when I talk about
this one the ox bile one isn't so bad
this the the the Ridiculousness of the
the ox bile one it's almost like not
that bad even though it's terrible it's
it's just it's it's still that's how bad
this one is so how does it work with
liver stones in the whole bit well
practitioners and and and healers or
whatever and gurus out there with
cleanses and everything else and not
everybody but they they all they think
that the liver produces a
stone and so you need the flesh that
liver flesh the stones out it's not
possible liver doesn't produce a stone
it doesn't work like that the liver
can't produce a stone it can't the
liver's too hot to produce a stone one
of the most advanced pieces of
information you'll ever probably read
well maybe not ever in liver rescue
there's so many Advanced pieces of
information but one that's actually is
up there is up there with with with so
many that are in Liver Rescue and which
is incredible is that the heat of the
liver actually can't create the stone
anyway there's no Stones anyway inside
the liver I mean I've talked to surgeons
I've talked to surgeons there's no
Stones inside the liver I've talked to
surgeons there's stones in the
gallbladder yeah there's stones in the
gallbladder without a doubt you know
made out of strong Billy Ruben there
is but that's not they don't get into
the gallbladder because they went up a
duct from the liver so they don't go
into the gallbladder because they went
up the duct from the liver into the
gallbladder that's not how it works if
that's the case there would be thousands
upon thousands and even more so than
gallbladder surgeries there'd be
emergency liver
surgeries um there would be thousands I
talked to a surgeon that told me there
would be so many would be ridiculous it
would be like it would be like aidomes
it would be like that t
tonsillectomies it would be like it
would it would it would rise above
override tonsillectomies ectomies and
and and other things like that it would
override it would it' be in a class all
on its own the reason why cuz everybody
has stones in the gallbladder because of
their dirty livers and and and what
they're eating and their high fat diets
and they high protein high fat diets
they all have they all have Stones even
if they're small even if they're Sandy
even if they're large they all have
stones in there and what happens is the
stones develop in the gallbladder
there's no such thing as a liver Stone
in the liver and this isn't because I
talked to
surgeons I already know this information
and think I wrote that's why I wrote a
whole thing on it it's not the the whole
thing in here and live a
rescue you can't have a stone go up the
duck to the gallbladder man I know that
because what happens is it'll get
clogged right down at the base of the
duck down there I mean people would be
opened up every day because it because
unlike the gallbladder which the stones
sitting there forever they only they
only get jammed up and the duct leaving
the gallbladder once in a while I mean
there's people out there dealing with it
a lot but it's nothing because they
usually just sit inside people's Gall
the gall sack just sitting in there you
know you know growing over time but a
stone can't sit in the liver over time
and pop up to that duct as if it's
sending up going up the bile duct into
the gallbladder I mean like I and like I
said there would be so many surgeries it
would be such one of the most first of
all it' be a really hard
surgery really really hard one really
awful really awful I mean you have to go
deep in there that would be a terrible
surgery if that was happening all the
time that would be an awful one so what
happen happens is the liver's too hot
and research and science doesn't know
this part they don't know they don't
know this the liver is too hot to forge
a
stone it's too hot it basically keeps it
keeps the substances that form stones in
a liquefied state due to the heat of the
liver that's how it works but the
gallbladder is cooler it's cooler than
the liver is what it is it sits and
perched in a spot on top of that that's
cooler than the
liver that that degree of
coolness that the gallbladder has and
versus the Heat of the
liver okay makes a difference to a
forged Stone to forging a stone when the
liquid Gunk comes out of the liver from
toxic livers from overburdened livers
from livers filled with all kinds of
poisons and toxins Pharmaceuticals
petrochemicals heavy metals everything
else Under the Sun and and then sitting
there eating the high fat diets whether
you're animal protein high fat or your
vegan high fat that's there's there's no
difference in there there's not really a
difference in there like plant-based
people I've seen them like just chug the
nut Butters and cashew Butters and my
God tahen and everything and lots and
lots of lots and lots of avocado and
then they're told that this is the way
to go and then they get themselves sick
and think they need to go back to animal
protein diet then they go back to animal
protein where they got sick to begin
with because nobody starts out vegan
like you know what I mean so they they
go to vegan they're like who my God and
they're but they're eating all the high
fat that way too and they they then they
get themselves sick and then they're
running back to animal protein and the
animal protein people they're eating all
the high fat diet now plus they're
Switching gears they're eating less
animal protein now I don't know if you
know this but if you're animal protein
person you have you seen that yet animal
protein people are eating less animal
protein why is that I wonder why that's
happening isn't that funny because
eating too much animal protein is bad it
is too much is bad I'm just just saying
I'm not against animal protein it's too
bad it's bad eating too many nuts seeds
avocados is bad too for the plant-based
people it's bad I'm sorry but it is I
know I get the I know I get the vegans
upset I know that I know I get the Paleo
people upset but I don't care because
it's about you it's about you having an
answer so you can protect yourself and I
always say you're worth that you're
worth getting the right answers to
protect yourself it's worth protecting
you I mean that's what I'm doing on here
I think it's worth it it's why I'm here
I'm here yelling talking about this all
the time so the deal is when the liver's
burdened with all that high fat going up
the hepatic portal vein and all the bile
that needs to disperse the fat and wears
its bile Reserve out of the liver and
everything else it overheats and all
that junk and all that poison and old
Pharmaceuticals from 1989 or whatever is
in your system and everything else going
on is all in there that Gunk it stays
liquefied but mcky and gunky and the
liver has to send it up the bile duct
sends it up the bile duct into the
gallbladder where it's colder and then
the stones form they coal kind of like
liquid gold cools liquid metal
cools and in that Gunk are heavy metals
sure science and research they hav even
looked at those stones good enough you
think they're going to put that much
money into it you know what's in those
stones isn't just old old red blood dead
red blood cells and Billy ruin or
whatever it else that's in there and
everything it's not just all that stuff
and cholesterol those stones are filled
with Metals junk garbage I mean you
wouldn't believe Industrial Age stuff
going back before your time for your
forefather's time and passed on to you
and passed on to you're can pass on to
your children all that Gunk that's how
it works and it cools down and the stone
is formed stones are formed in the
gallbladder so when you got it's
unbelievable that I see out there these
you know these natural doctors or
whoever doctor or whatever whatever and
is you know promoting these cleanses you
got to buy for liver
Stones I mean I I can't even but this is
a prime example of how the
misinformation is so thick out there
it's like literally it's not just the
Wild West it's like something far worse
it's far worse out there it's like
literally like anything goes and
anything stupid goes that's how
incredible it is out
there that's unbelievable so and this is
a part of it I'm being sarcastic because
I've seen people hurt by this stuff and
wasting time and tons of money tons of
money time and energy and I've seen
people hurt by it and it's depressing
it's depressing you know someone asked
me if I ever had depression before they
you know they said have you ever had
depression before because I know that
people suffer from depression and I know
why they suffer from depression because
they got the Epstein bars dropping in
all this all this neurotoxin feeding off
the toxic heavy metals and heavy metals
in the brain and neurotransmitters go
they they dampen and let your lights
drop and depression hits and people go
get depressed they get they fall into
this depression and then they go they
try to take brain altering medication
like the anxiety stuff and all the
different anti-depressants and
everything else and I get it I know why
I've never had
depression until I I see what's out
there over the years till I see what's
out there you know my depression hits I
said you know I never had depression I
said you know what I I got something
that's it won't it it's not even like
depression I guess
but I got sadness sadness I got sadness
on the misinformation and anything goes
out there and what people get pushed
into and what they have to spend money
on and everything else they have to do
unbelievable like with Liver Rescue I
put a whole recipe book in Liver Rescue
so there's two books in there because I
don't want you even spending $1 more dos
for another book to play that game I see
what authors do they got there they put
out their book and then they try to put
out another book side of it which just
here's the recipe book for that now why
couldn't you put in the same book and
save the person $15 you I've seen it all
out there and the whole point is is this
okay is this it's about you and that's
what matters it's about you that's
that's the point that should be taken no
matter what it's about you and what we
what can we do for you what can that's
what people need to see that are selling
all those those expensive supplements
that are selling all what can we really
do for you how do we protect you and do
it in a sensible Manner and give you the
right information so not out there just
guessing games of theories and
misinformation due to you know people's
pockets and so liver Stones is a big one
that's why I'm on this rant right now
you guys because liver Stones is a big
one the whole liver Stone thing I got
people say oh they flushed all these
stones in the toilet these liver stones
in the toilet it was all the herbal
concoctions they were sold all these
alcohol concoctions alcohol in the herbs
all these liquid herbs and all these
dried powdered herbs and all this stuff
and they're taking all these herbs and
mucus gets collected in the intestinal
tract because it's reacting to all these
herbs being thrown in there and the
tannins and the herbs and herbs that
shouldn't even be in people some of
these herbs that's somebody has some big
cockman idea some practi has a big
cockman idea and they throw all these
herb powders in you and all this other
stuff and then you're sitting there
pooping your brains out and you're
looking for Stones when it's really
mucus and old debris that could just be
in the testal tract for your food or
food attached to mucus and you think you
see stones in the toilet liver stones
and you get delusional when easily
delusional when you're sitting there
spending all that money taking all the
stuff feeling like crap and doing this
you you want to believe something's in
that toilet I swear to God I've seen
people go through this so many times
it's ridiculous and let's go push into
liver flushes well we have a couple more
minutes left liver flesh is the one
thing I'm going to tell you right now
and I put in Liver Rescue so you know
the liver does not like to be pushed it
hates to be pushed in any way it's like
you wouldn't want your son or your
daughter being pushed by a drug Pusher
that's for sure you wouldn't want your
son and daughter being pushed by any
anybody by a bully and pushed down in
the playground you wouldn't want your
son and daughter pushed by anything okay
and that's the bottom line and your your
liver is like basically a family member
it's a family member and it's watching
you and it's got your back and
everything else you don't want to liver
does not like to be pushed it doesn't
like to be pushed off the diving board
the first time in a first time on a
diving board like a child having its
first time on a diving board
contemplating how the child is going to
dump in he or she is going to jump in
and dump into the water or whatever how
you know what happens is is that when
that's happening and someone comes
behind the child and pushes that child
in it could be a bad memory it could be
a shock that child didn't deserve I've
seen that happen too I mean it it you
know that's that has happened or a
brother or a sister pushing a child you
know pushing a sibling into the water
it's basically what the liver does not
like to be pushed into anything
especially flushing and I'll tell you
why cuz when you flush the liver the
wrong way or you try to push the liver
to flush it all that poison and all that
toxin goes into the bloodstream and you
know what the liver does it tries to get
it all back in it immediately to save
your life because it's not going to be
pushed what happens is when you push the
liver and try to flush it like like a
lot of these people are doing out there
now like thinking they got liver fleshes
thinking they got liver fleshes let's
keep on doing this it's unbelievable
what
happens what you want to know what
happens you shorten your life and not
even know it you may not know it you may
be going everything's fine and dandy but
you took 5 years off off your life if
you were going to live to be 80 you just
you you're now going to be Liv to be 74
75 it could even be more than that I'll
tell you why when the liver push too
hard it ends up dumping all this poison
into the system the poison hurts the
heart Untold damage for the future can
happen now you can you can you can look
you can heal your liver and heal your
body if you've done those things so that
you can get get those 5 years back and
then 10 years back back on top of it if
you're doing the right things that's
important and you can you can do all the
right things for your liver I put a
liver cleanse for the liver that's
gentle but powerful it doesn't push your
liver I put that in Liver Rescue for a
reason I put that in Liver Rescue for a
reason and what happens is when that
liver dumps all that poison into the
bloodstream it's injurious to the heart
and
brain it's not good for the heart and
brain and the liver freaks out because
it has to reabsorb that that toxin back
in is fat fast as possible so then it
sends out signals it sends out hormones
to trigger off the adrenals to release
adrenaline at a dangerous Pace even
though even you may not feel it but
there's a adrenaline is re releasing out
when you're doing those liver flushes
because the adrenaline's there to
protect the brain and the Heart Is as
fast as possible the liver calls out for
help it weakens your adrenals the
adrenaline has to be all absorbed right
back into the liver along with all that
poison you know what the liver does
right after that it shuts down and it
stop stops letting you push it so when
you're still doing your liver flesh
after that and you're still doing it
Whatever It Is 30-day liver flesh or
whatever you got going or bought into
and you're still doing it your liver is
now not even working because it won't
let anything out of the gate
anymore that's how it works because it
let so much out of the gate so much that
was
detrimental and that's how it works and
if your liver does let it out of the
gate again because it has no choice
because it's been pushed by some strange
concoction
and that's even worse and has to do it
all over again to try to protect you
liver
flushes that are unauthorized by the
human body and the liver itself
unauthorized by the liver itself is not
a good thing it's not a good thing at
all and if you're someone that's new to
the show and new to my information and
you're confused and saying well I don't
get it then what makes your information
like any better or
whatever it is it because of the
countless people I've helped recover
over the years and the decades is it
because of that or is because of my
source that I have yes it's because of
my source it's because of all that it's
a source it's the people I've watched
heal and know that have healed it's all
of that
combined because my source is not funded
my source is not There's No Agenda to it
my source doesn't have you're not trying
to buy some big kit from me and I'm
trying to tell you my way is better
there's nothing in there meaning in a
sense of that way there's nothing behind
it that's like okay let's make a whole
bunch of money off of people okay let's
get an agenda going there's nothing
there there's no interest groups behind
it there's no there's no fundraising
that had to be behind it there's no
anything there's no bogus studies behind
it that are contaminated as Pure Clean
information and what you're going to
find you're going to find Pure Clean
untampered with information to help you
move forward just like the straight
celery juice that has healed so many
people over the decades that I've
actually put I was the first to put out
there you better believe it from Spirit
and my source and if feel you don't
trust my source it's fine with me it's
fine with me that's I totally respect
that 100% you don't trust the source
that I was boring to hear and you know
when I started hearing at four years old
if you don't trust it I I'm completely
fine with that 100% fine with that then
then then and that's totally good that's
fine fine go go out and spend $155,000
and $20,000 $30,000 on all kinds of
programs and everything else I'm not
even selling you a program or nothing
like it you know why because I love you
because I want you to heal because I
care and I care about everybody and I
know the suffering that occurs I've seen
it I've had to learn this my whole life
and spirit has given me the information
like and Liver Rescue to protect you and
make sure that you do careful cleanses
make sure you gently help yourself make
sure that it doesn't cost you thousands
of dollars and make sure you can protect
you and your family and of course your
liver and you can get yourself better so
you're not investing every minute of
your life trying to recover instead
you're living a quality of life and
moving your life forward and moving
yourself forward and that's what car and
that's what matters and that's why I
wake up first thing in the morning it's
the first thing I say is what what can I
do for everybody that concludes liver
myths this is unbelievable I love you
guys I hope you catch the next show take
one day at a time I stand behind you I'm
proud of you I'm proud of all of you and
I I love you dearly okay bye-bye now