[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium this is Anthony William the
medical Medium you're listening to the
medical medium radio show where each
week we talk about the most advanced
healing information out there ever in
conventional and alternative medicine in
chronic illness it's important to know
that because you know we don't discuss
some of the amazing discoveries in
science and research with medicine
life-saving medicine and everything else
because we don't need to they're doing
great but what we need to discuss is
where it's disastrous where it's
negligent where it's literally falling
apart millions of people in the US alone
are so sick not functioning quality of
life down the drain all of it all of it
and that's what we're up against with
chronic illness and it's only getting
worse by the Year by the month every
single year every single decade been
watching it happen for decades so we
have to do something about it so we deal
with the most advanced health
information today we're talking about
the liver's own immune system the
liver's own immune system very important
topic unbelievable science and research
doesn't have a clue to the degree of how
the liver's immune system works what's
happening inside the liver what's going
on how it's protecting you and
everything about it so it's the heroic
liver this is all about liver rescue
live a rescue book um pick up a copy if
you get a chance you can't afford a copy
of a book just go to the library and try
to get it out there soon as you can head
to the library because you really need
this and you need to get better and you
need to you just need to get the
information it's so important to
understand your immune system that is
really a critical piece I'm going to
tell you something right now when you
were
born when you were born your mother's
liver sent a message to your your own
liver that it could take care of itself
going back thousands of years in the
history of
humankind this has been ingrained in who
we are as human beings this is how it's
always been it's always been a part of
us our livers we don't offer them a
helping hand we never give them that
helping hand so as we go through life
they have to take care of themselves and
so the knowledge has passed along from
our mothers to us liver to liver that it
has to fend for
itself a very important understanding
right there and and you know it's not
that it couldn't use any help it does
need our help our livs do need our help
without a doubt it does face limitations
over time as it weakens though and
breaks down from lack of our support
you know when we don't know what the
liver is doing for us and don't have a
clue and that's why we're talking about
the liver's own immune system
personalized immune system the heroic
liver I call it in Liver
Rescue you the reason why we're even
doing this is because it's important to
know about the liver's immune system and
how it doesn't get outside help from us
ever it needs and deserves its outside
the outside help from us it really
does and so as the years go by the
liver's own immune system which is
literally not understood by research and
science except for just one basic aspect
of it and I'm going to cover into detail
about the the real thing that's going on
inside our liver get ready to be mind
blown just get ready to be mind
blown and that's
important all of it's important about
the liver and it's important to actually
be mind blown too so you can be like hey
I remember that I need to take care of
my liver
my God I can't believe my liver does
that exactly so then you can actually
you can actually remember it remember
the information if something's at
mind-blowing like your liver has six
types of immune functions meaning like
six varieties of immune cells only one
is flagged by research and science this
is going to be a fun show it really
is so as the liver loses strength and
grows toxic Through The Years yes our
livers grow toxic through the years
years you better believe it the liver's
immune system becomes a tattered Army a
tattered Army out in a field in the
trenches with holes in the boots and
holes in
socks and and tears in in the in the you
know and tears in the uniforms and tears
in the
eyes and that's how the liver that's how
the liver and it becomes desperate for
food and water and it's and that's the
whole point low Amun I supply low immune
system and and that's the whole deal we
can shift it of course we can do
something about it we can build the
immune system we can protect ourselves
protect our liver and build our liver's
immune system up there is a way but
first you need to know your liver has an
immune system that's the big thing this
is this is revolutionary information
mean it's Advanced by 10 20 30 years I
don't know maybe even 40 years you know
what when I'm dead down the road just
gone whatever just
gone you know 50 years down the road
whatever it's going to be this this the
you know maybe science and research will
actually teach people how to take care
of their livers so that this is on the
radar but wait a minute we're here right
now what does that matter we're here
right now what am I talking about what
do you mean 50 years down the road
what's today right there you can know
now how about that you can learn now we
can learn right now as we speak yeah
isn't that exciting that's really
exciting
so okay we can shift this of course and
we can do something about it we can heal
and avoid disease we can protect the
liver its reserves and precious immune
system we could change the direction we
can not be sick and recover we can alter
things we can get out of things we could
change our destiny yes we can when you
know what is going on and you need to
do this is so important to know all of
it we can change the way our liver works
and our Health Works we need our livers
and our livers need us I'm telling you
right now and knowingness is the biggest
piece of the
puzzle knowingness is the biggest piece
of the
puzzle while medical denial can keep us
in the dark we can play it
smart by knowing that the liver's immune
system is always kept in the light of
knowing it understands our liver and it
understands what it's doing but we need
to help it in some way you don't think
this is exciting I think this is
exciting that's all I can tell you this
is a big this is a big deal if you get
Liver Rescue just I mean just know you
the book is got so much information that
it's I can't cover it in a radio show
I'm talking about the liver's immune
system it's actually a chapter a whole
section in um in Liver Rescue but I can
only scratch I guess just a couple of
things in there but this is going to be
still incredible if you want to know the
you want to get it all you just got to
make sure you go to the library get a
copy if you can't afford one or just go
to Amazon or whatever and get a get a
book wherever you go to get a book go to
the bookstore when you hear about the
term immune system you guys we tend to
think about our bodies like defense
mechanisms with sniffles runny noses
right don't you think that I mean it's
the whole point and some people think
cancer they think cancer now they're
like immune system cancer you need a
good immune system so you don't get
cancer so some people are thinking that
it's not a lot of people that are going
there but we often think about runny
noses fever sore throats coughs yeah
rightfully so you don't want that you
don't want the flu cuz that's what it's
about you don't want the flu protection
against flu is critical like it's a
critical function of the immune system
that's why we we learn as kids take
Vitamin C I think or get a good night's
rest or plenty of fluids I think mommies
are teaching kids that so that's a
beautiful thing um but this this this is
just a fraction of what our immune
system is made up of because there's all
these
Invaders I hate going into spooky land I
hate going into spooky land but I have
to there's all these
Invaders there's all these viral things
going on there's viruses and there's
some bacteria but there's a lot of
viruses that's really what's taking down
people in this country alone never mind
globally and making it so they can't
function making it so they literally
can't they can't get out of
bed making it so they can brain fog
giving them everything under the sun I
mean brain fog Just One symptom I'm not
even talking about migraines headaches
Tremors shakes aches and pains tingles
numbness tentis ringing in the ears
popping in the ears floaters in the eyes
black spots in the eyes white spots in
the eyes weak limbs weak arms weak legs
feeling of fatigue neurological fatigue
which I actually which comes from me
neurological fatigue just so you know
okay it's just always been fatigue all
these years it's actually neurological
fatigue it's a central nervous system
being bogged down by neurotoxins by
viruses that's medical medium
information that's Advanced information
that's that's been hit in the scene from
from us but the point is is that with
all the different neurological
conditions you can have including hot
flashes which is actually a central
nervous system condition all these with
all these things you can
have with with you know Focus
concentration everything under the sun
there's viruses that sit behind all of
this so our immune system it's just not
about the flu it's just not about that
kind of thing it's not about hey you
know let's let's guard ourselves from
the flu let's not try to get the flu
it's not it's not about that it's about
so much more evidence of Invaders isn't
always so obvious that's what I mean
it's just not obvious to the doctors
it's not obvious to anyone you even
getting Epstein bar test you're not
going to think your Epstein bar is even
doing
anything because they don't
know viruses and bacteria especially
viruses wage attacks beneath the surface
deep in there and they don't create a
lot of noise sometimes they're nice and
quiet not trying to go into spooky
spooky land but I I just you know it's
either you you you learn or you don't I
don't know what else to say I mean we
can be in the dark about everything and
we can be in denial I can't tell you how
many people even on social media they're
like oh yeah you know you see it out
there and you're just like yeah I got
this these symptoms and everything and
they they don't even know they're viral
they don't even know they're viral they
have no clue they think oh it's just a
gut problem Oh my gut I went to this
functional doctor at whatever think a
gut problem or I think I just get
they're
viral you know you see it there's a lot
of 20-year-olds there's a lot of
whatever 30y olds and they're just you
know they don't know it oh yeah I got
hypothyroidism they don't that that's
actually Epstein bar causing
hypothyroidism you see it out there it's
unbelievable how far we're still off
about getting the information out there
but these viruses they just sit in there
so viruses bacteria they wage attacks
far beneath the surface in organs and
glands you know that's how it works
fibromyalgia you know multiple sclerosis
rheumatoid arthritis you know you know
ra you know myalgic contis all kinds of
different things chronic fatigue
syndrome MEC CFS
right you know lupus shingles Lyme
disease hashimotos thyroiditis
hypothyroidism and add another hundred
other conditions to
it are all from a virus starting out in
guess where guess where just make a
guess right now um Liver Rescue book um
talking about the liver's immune system
where do all those conditions where do
they all stem from where do they all
start from right you you're figuring it
out I mean you know probably bunch of
you guys want to smack me in the head
right now probably be like we got it
it's the liver stop we got
it yeah it's the liver it stems there it
starts there that's where it starts more
than we know we rely on the liver's
immune system so much so it's it's
unbelievable how we rely on the liver's
immune
system it's unbelievable actually
and it protects us from becoming ill the
liver doesn't like viruses and it
doesn't like bacteria either residing in
it so when it can't stop them from
entering it does everything it can to
keep them
contained so viruses enter into the
liver that's how it's
done they enter into the liver and if
the liver can't stop it if the liver's
immune system cannot kill off that bug
cuz the liver's immune system is weak
because guess what we're on high fat
diets all fun in games all those cute
little trendy diets out there I talk
about that in Liver Rescue more than you
guys could ever know I mean wait till
you see it wait till you see it you
won't believe it all the trendy diets
out there all high fat diets keep on
doing it keep on putting out more high
fat diets high protein diets keep on
doing it I'm not talking about whether
it's animal protein or vegan they're
they're both they go but they both go
high protein high
fat let's keep on doing it out there
yeah you're going to get temporary
results for many of you but yet
everybody's still going to stay sick
down the road I mean you know it's
unbelievable you got to bring down the
fats it weakens the liver so the liver's
immune system cannot stop viral
infections at a chronic long term so
that when you're and when you're in your
20s and you think you're indestructible
and you're in the gym right and you're
on your trendy low carb
diet give it 20 years give it to when
you're 40 40 comes around man it comes
around and when you're sick you got all
these symptoms and craps happening left
and right it's got two viruses inside
the liver and no one cared and no one
even knows and no one wants to know and
and whatever's going on and it's just
you know wreaking havoc and then coming
out and hitting the thyroid and giving
you your first case of Hashimoto
thyroiditis and and everything else
Under the
Sun and you're gaining weight and don't
know why you've been working out eating
good pretty good all these years because
nobody knows how it works it's
unbelievable look it's either you you
know or you don't
I could I could stop the radio shows I
could stop putting out the books I mean
should I maybe I should maybe I should
shut it all down all of it I'll just go
find some wooded spot and live in a in
in a
tent
somewhere maybe I'll do that I did it
when I was a
kid okay so let's do Let's do let's do
this let's do this I'm being pretty
silly I'm in a silly mood
today so the bottom line is the livers
get beaten down we rely on them liver's
immune system more than we can possibly
imagine and when the liver can't kill
off because it's been weakened over time
and over the years by the wrong diets
because of just experts not knowing
anything about how the body works and
all these other things when when when
we're under all this stuff or we're
Contracting viruses through
relationships or however it goes and all
these different things that it that we
get it we get these viruses from and
from food and restaurants and everything
else our liver has to work on destroying
it its immune system has to be strong
and it has to be able to annihilate a
bug entering it cuz that's what happens
when you're new relationships all the
time the bugs they get in the mouth and
they get down to the gut and then they
transfer from the gut up the hepatic
portal highway right into the liver
that's how it's
done I mean that's just one way in a
relationship
you know there's a few other ways in a
relationship that it could happen too
but the point is is this is what what
goes on you get in a restaurant you got
all these chefs I mean cross the country
and there's nothing wrong with chefs
it's just their people which just means
you got all these people and and they
got Band-Aids on their hands and they
got you know all kinds of stuff I mean
it's unbelievable and yeah they get cut
and they're still got to work you just
got to wrap it up I've seen I've seen
chefs some of the the best chefs get cut
and they just throw electrical tape on
it on it they just wrap it with
electrical
tape and and throw on yeah they throw on
sometimes a a nit trial glove but at the
same time they still got blood
everywhere and on their hands and they
throw on the Nitro nit trial glove
there's blood on their nit trial glove
but they're still I mean they're trying
to whatever and they throw wrap
electrical tape and they're in they're
In the Heat of the Moment of just trying
to get the food out I mean it's it's
like one of those High pressured
situations stel
and then boom I mean we're eating food
and just got another Epstein bar don't
know why we got chronic fatigue
syndrome again at age
38 either way I'm not trying to scare
the crap out of us too bad basically
what I'm doing is the liver it's up to
the liver it's so up to the liver it's
so up to the liver to make sure it
destroys a new bug coming
in and if it can't destroy it it locks
it up it imprisons
it it imprisons it the liver is a
genius it's the
gatekeeper it's
everything it's underestimated it's
disrespected it's disregarded it's
treated badly just like people are
treated by the
way it's
used it's like people get used it's
terrible it's all of it and we need to
do something about it we need to do
something so it kind of works like this
let's go into us this is really intense
so I mean get
your you know get yourself ready for
this one so here's here's the
deal the liver
contains whatever it can that's possible
possible then it will send killer
cells after viruses to keep them at
Bay and they keep them deep guarded in
the fabric of the liver so basically
what these killer cells this is just one
set of killer cells wait till you hear
the rest of this and that's just to keep
it at Bay inside the
liver and this is really important to
know when a virus starts to get out of
control it tries to to leave the depths
of the liver that it's been shoved down
and stored in locked up tries to leave
the depths of the
liver special white blood cells are
there to destroy it a different variety
all on its own a different
variety the liver also brings in white
blood cells
randomly to control viruses living deep
within it like I was saying
before but why doesn't the liver send
its white count to out and out destroy
all viruses and other pathogens in the
liver why doesn't it do
that because the liver is putting
tremendous number of resources already
into trying to fight off new pathogens
entering by the second by the day by the
week by the
month through the hepatic portal vein
which and and hepatic artery these are
entries into the liver and it's trying
to kill those off as they
enter the liver gets
exhausted so it's trying to kill off
Invaders entering in in the first place
as it's using all of its reserves to try
to stop viruses entering into the
paddock portal vein and Paddock artery
the highways into the into the liver
that's where all the viruses are
entering that's where they all come in
and your liver's immune system is
sitting there at those
gates at the the gates of that highway
right there trying to annihilate
everything that comes in everything so
when you're at you're at a cocktail
party when you're at a bar or a club and
you get you drinking out of dirty
glasses and whatever and sharing drinks
and whatever's going on and all of a
sudden you just picked up a new kind of
strep and that strep goes right in the
gut hasn't really prospered or done
anything yet but it goes right down in
the gut heads right down in there goes
right through the wall of the intestinal
tract lining that's how it does it goes
through the wall it literally through
osmosis gets vacuumed through right up
theor hortal veins right through blood
vessels right up to the liver and that
liver of yours sits there with it all
its immune strength and all its immune
system sitting there waiting by the
gates and annihilates the crap out of
that that brand new strep you just
picked up in that club or at the
cocktail party or at your friend's house
or whatever I'm just just you know I
don't know I don't know what people do
these days wherever wherever we can get
anything
or you know or the toilet or some toilet
in some gas station that was just you
know festering with a whole bunch of
stuff and some water splashed up yeah
and you know and with that and with that
your liver is literally destroying that
Invader so it's using everything it can
everything it
can I told you this was going to be
intense all right let's cruise along we
got so much to cover it's
ridiculous because the liver is already
putting out like I said there tremendous
number of resources to trying to do what
exactly what I just said it's doing
protect things from entering into the
portal vein a portal he hepatic artery
all of that and if you don't know what
that is that's just you know that's
veins coming off of your intestinal
tract
lining that's veins and they all funnel
to the liver into a main Highway hepatic
portal
Highway same thing with arteries the
artery all the blood vessels all to a
main artery a a
highway so that's what the body is doing
is trying to kill those off these are
the immune defenses of the liver the
liver's personalized immune system
that's what this show is about it's a
highly Advanced information for warning
anybody who just tuned in and listen to
the show over again you got to listen to
the show over again I think you know
honestly it's it's it's a shame when
someone just Tunes in halfway in the
show doesn't hear the first half I know
we're all busy but this is about your
health loved ones and everything else
and it's about knowing some important
information much of the sophistication
of the liver's immune system is still
unknown like I said to Medical
communities research and science it's
why you don't hear about it every day in
the world that's the whole
point almost all of it's not known and
that's how it
works and and it's unknown to medical
science and research that your liver's
immune system is made up ready of six
main units your liver immune system is
made up of six main
units I'll give you three of them right
off the top the hepatic vessel white
blood cells okay hepatic portal vein
white blood cells science of research
doesn't know about this has no clue
these aren't even not even on the radar
not even in any study not even in
anywhere it's Advanced information for
warning you hepatic artery white blood
cells those are three of those units I
just said just now they're the soldiers
that stand watch they stand watch as the
blood enters the liver research and
science just thinks there's some white
blood cells floating around inside the
liver that's about
it that's about it and there's a reason
I really think there's a reason money's
not going there and I really think
there's a reason why it's understudied
like everything else in chronic illness
but I think with this one I think
there's a big reason because once again
it leads to the fact that the liver is
filled with viruses and and then virus
Es are the cause for all the chronic
illnesses and guess what it's not
genetics it's not genetics it never was
genetics that why people are sick with
chronic illness it's not the body
attacking itself it's a it's a
liver filled with a load of viruses try
to bleep myself and not
swear cuz this stuff will just you know
it'll it'll make you get emotional and
the whole point is is that you know that
we're not supposed to know about like
how viruses make us all sick we're
supposed to kind of stay stupid and then
we get an answer or diagnosis we're like
what our body's attacking itself our
body is actually attacking itself so my
body's own immune system is destroying
my thyroid or my body's own immune
system is destroying my skin or
destroying my kidney or my body's own
immune system is making me sick is okay
and and it's genetic oh wait wait
there's information out there now you're
telling me that Epstein bar kind of
plays a role but it's not the cause it's
just a trigger that's another screw up
just look out for all that you see all
these you know these studies and in the
medical medium Community will actually
post them and be like hey look aw was
right Anthony William was right it is
Epstein bar but when you read the study
they still don't want the truth they're
trying to derail you and trick you
that's the whole thing I talked about
that on a Facebook live they they're
doing that because of what we did we
spent years getting the truth out there
and it became a storm it it's raging
through the country alone never mind
globally of the truth that's causing
chronic illness because of the medical
medium book series so then they put out
the bogus studies saying oh well epsteen
bar oh it cause of Hashim Motors cause
of this cause no it's not the thing you
read the article or the or or the
article or you read the study it has
nothing to do with the cause they say
it's genetics and the body's attacking
itself and they say that it's just
linked it's it's a trigger they think
unbelievable they do that on purpose
that's all done on purpose don't get
fooled by that the truth still isn't
still isn't they they don't want you to
know the truth it's the way it works and
the liver has so much to do so much to
do with it so research research and
science is behind with the liver for a
couple of reasons because it's the
incubation place where all the viruses
go and a lot of viruses are manufactured
going all the way
back and they've somehow
escaped many of them stealth viruses
many of the different varieties and the
mutation somehow escaped out some lab
whoa I don't know how they end up in
people but they
do and they incubate inside everybody's
liver no one's taking care of the liver
and then oh the big the big trendy the
trendy guys out there the big fancy
doctors whatever they put out their
books whatever and they want to hang
their hat on something it's all on a
high fat this and a high fat that or a
high protein this and you can see some
of them are trying to back down that
that little bit and they're like
lowering that bringing in more juices
bringing in more fruits and vegetables
oh when did you learn that last year how
about 30 years ago when I was getting
people out of bed that were out of
wheelchairs it's important to know what
you need to do it's so critical so
sarcastic today I'm sorry guys I hope
that doesn't turn you off and make you
want to hang up from the
podcast here's the
deal you just got to you just got to
remember I'm silly too a lot so just
just just bear with me when you're doing
this for like your whole life since Age
4 you just you got to remember the
medical information that came to me at
age 4567 is the same thing you're
reading in these Advanced books it's 50
years 30 years 20 years 10 years ahead
of its time at age 5 6 7 8 I was getting
the
information that's why there's this
picture of me in the book age four years
old sitting in there there's a reason I
was getting the information that early
it was no fun so there's these six six
main units of our liver's immune system
so here's how it works like the padic
portal vein that's the main Highway vein
I was talking about it comes off of the
intestinal tract so as viruses and
bacteria are funneling up into the liver
those white blood cells in the hepatic
portal vein that's one of the highways
those white blood cells monitor the
portal vein itself this is the main
Highway into the liver this is past the
point of any more off ramps or on ramps
actually on ramps sorry about that
there's no more exits this highway ends
up heading did you ever did you ever get
in traffic did you ever drive and you're
like crap I should have gotten off of
that you should have got off in in La
especially in La it's like I should have
gotten off that exit oh my God what did
I do why am I stuck in this for the next
45 minutes now for the next hour and a
half I should have got off that exit or
in New York or wherever I mean it's just
crazy or anywhere in the country so so
there's no getting off that that that
that blood is heading up into the liver
through that hepatic portal portal vein
so these white blood cells
they stay they actually act like TSA TSA
at the airport that's what they do as
blood's coming through the hepatic
portal vein it's filled with nutrients
right you know that part I think our
blood is filled with nutrients I think
you guys probably know that there blood
going into the liers filled with
nutrients and poisons lots of poisons
it's filled with both and this is a hot
spot for any kind of troublemakers
trying to make their way inside the
liver like
viruses so they try to actually go in
through that way and the more poison you
have coming in the more your white blood
cells this one part of the six main
units of your immune system can get
derailed as an EBV a new
EBV is is heading up through the hepatic
portal vein exactly ready to give
somebody a good chronic fatigue syndrome
I mean you know so right when it's
heading up there your white blood cells
so that's one of the troublemakers there
right so it's a troublemaker that virus
very common Troublemaker unbelievable so
it heads up and it comes and here's the
thing so all this blood coming through
is coming from your digestive tract it's
unfiltered it's unfiltered the liver has
to filter it so whatever you're eating
whatever you're eating if you're eating
a high high fat diet which people don't
know they are but they really are they
really are vegans too vegans plant-based
people eating such high fat diets
unbeliev able it's like everything has
just lots of fat in it nut fat in there
whatever kind of fat in there it's it's
incredible vegetarians are really on
high fat diets they're eating eggs
vegetarians are eating
eggs I mean it's unbelievable and so
they're eating all that high fat
everything else around it and and you
know a lot of Keto diets now based based
with eggs and then avocados and then and
they're vegan you know or or or you know
they kind of borderline vegan or
whatever it is they get vegan keto diets
it's just all fat the thing is you can't
be on the vegan keto diet can't exist
because an avocado has sugar in it it's
different when you go on a animal
protein keto diet that is an actual real
keto diet if you if you there's no such
thing as going on a vegan keto diet you
can't they're sugar and nuts they're
sugar and nuts you can't be on a keto
diet all you can be on is just a high
fat diet when when you're vegan fancy
that see that
information so because avocados it's 25%
sugar I mean you can't you can't nuts
there's a percentage of sugar in there
so you really can't go
keto um on a vegan diet you just go high
fat with still some sugar so this you
don't get the ketosis Factor you just
high fat diet and you're cutting down
your carbs that's about
it and then the animal
protein if you're doing avocados along
with your animal prote proteins you're
still not even really doing keto anymore
anyway either you're just doing high fat
so the whole keto thing is a bomb it's
not even understood right and then you
got these experts teaching it I don't
even know how it works it's the craziest
thing ever it's crazy it's like whoa
it's amazing it's a wild west you can do
anything you can do anything now in
alternative medicine and diets in the
diet world you can do anything can put a
bunny rabbit in your hat and then just
and do a funny dance with a cane and
then show up another trendy diet in one
second boom here's another one oh I'm an
expert and then someone's you know on
another diet and oh I'm Doctor whatever
do little and this is this is what I got
now I used to be you know a doctor and I
used to be this and this and this at you
know Prestige prestigious medical school
and everything else now I'm into health
and yeah the keto diet's the way to go
you lose a little weight lower your
carbs what about everybody that's dying
of chronic illness and all the viruses
that are eating up their bodies and
their livers and their immune systems
and they can't function and they can't
even do anything they can't can't work
they lose everything they lose
everything in their lives and and that
diet ain't going to help got to have the
you got to have the truth in your hand
so you can
heal so you know these six main units
one of them is there is waiting at the
portal gate right there it's waiting a
stomp on a bacteria and a virus that's
creating all the illness that's going on
out there but there's so much poison and
there's so many nutrients all combined
coming up that highway from your
intestinal tract unfiltered that can get
derailed pretty easy so that's how it
works and that's that's really a
difficult
situation and then there's hepatic
artery white blood cells that's a whole
another kind so that's your that's
another group hepatic
artery white blood cells okay so they're
in these these artery white blood cells
this is where blood is coming in with
high oxygen level so you have to know
the difference so with the hepatic
portal vein blood coming in from the
digestive tract there's no oxygen in it
I mean there's a little bit in there not
a lot and and then you got and the
stream is slow it's like
slow the stream is not fast at all it's
slow so the hepatic the hepatic artery
those white blood cells they're
stationed at the C circulatory entrance
to the liver this is hepatic artery this
is different this blood is coming to the
heart coming from the heart it is higher
levels of oxygen it's holding and then
the blood that enters from the hepatic
portal vein it's traveling at a higher
velocity than than that I mean you have
to know this this is the big difference
right here if I'm if I'm trying to
trying to remember trying to
remember so it's hepatic artery white
blood cells they're different they're
adapted to a whole different situation
cuz you remember high levels of oxygen
pouring into the
liver that blood's being pumped from the
heart this isn't blood coming from the
digestive tract being sucked in through
the veins up into the liver I was
talking about before this is high
flushing ratio pumping blood coming from
the heart entering into the
liver okay and these white blood cells
they're adapted to high oxygen levels in
High Extreme blood
flow whereas hepatic portal vein white
blood cells
they can't they can't they they can
survive they can survive in other ways
with lack of oxygen they're different
there's there's two different buggies
they're not buggies two different immune
cells two different immune
cells one can survive high oxygen and
high blood flow another one can survive
low oxygen and lots of
poison that's the difference that's the
difference right there research in
science I don't know 40 years from now
on this one although they'll still be
studying genetics I forgot and they'll
still be you know make you know wanting
everybody to do a genetic test on you
know TV commercials and all that so
looking for your heritage and stuff
they'll still be wanting to do that so
they can collect all your
DNA it's unbelievable so they just play
with it more and more until they like
clone people down the road said they
don't even care about chronic illness
telling you science and research doesn't
even care about chronic illness they
just don't the people working for them
do they do but they're they're they have
bosses they're all under they're all
under direction or they they're out of a
job so the bottom line
is this is how it works so that that
group of of that group of immune cells
that sit in that artery area with high
oxygen highspeed blood flow coming
through
okay they know how to swim
aggressively
they know how to swim aggressively they
can handle it under a microscope if
these immune study if these immune cells
were ever on the radar of science and
research if they were ever on the radar
if they were ever of even interest in
today's world of
medicine they they first of all science
researcher probably think they're all
the same at first but there's subtle
differences that mean everything and
that would take years of
study so just the three I'm talking
about the three the three main units I'm
even talking about out of the six main
units right now they're they're
different they're subtly different in so
many
ways that's how it works all three of
these white blood cell types are
incredible swimmers they all can
swim they can even go against the
currents with a rare ability to go
against these currents in such a way to
pursue guess what pathogen the very
thing that's keeping everybody sick
that's giving everybody everything from
acne to ECMO psoriasis to oh my God to
Everything Under the Sun that to all the
different diseases and illnesses that
are listed in the liver rescue book to
everything else in the medical medium
series that's listed in there thyroid
problems and then all the different all
the other different stuff that's in
there athletes to the highest degree
these immune cells
are they have a special
shape that science and research hasn't
even yet to discover that allows them to
hover in an area of rushing blood like a
grizzly bear waiting against dangerous
Rapids to snatch a migrating
salmon I mean come on that's how that's
how powerful our body is it's incredible
and when a pathogen escapes from these
Secret Service agents cuz that's what
they're like these secret Ser servant AG
when a pathogen actually escapes at the
liver's entry entryways where they are
they find themselves up against the
liver's next Defence which I'm going
into and these are the other three of
the six if I think I covered them all
they're say you know what I hope I
covered them all already you got to get
the live rescue book I can't do it all
in the show this D this show is a little
bit you know about having fun too we got
we have to have fun why we're doing it I
guess it's a little hard to get it all
done so the next defense are these lobu
white liver lobu cells these are immune
cells they're personalized
guards so these
protect parts of the inside of the liver
so these lobu white blood cells they
border the capillaries and other blood
vessels within the liver on the lookout
for Invaders like Epstein bar that
escaped and by the way Epstein bar is
respons responsible for Hepatitis A
Hepatitis B hepatitis C hepatitis D
Hepatitis
E just for the
record as well as also a zillion
undiscovered autoimmune conditions of
the liver I know there's not a zillion
of them I know that but that's what it's
that's what it's turning out to be
something
close so that's that's one that's one
variety of the immune system right there
sitting inside the liver so look grade
viral infections inside the liver that
go undetected by medical communities
these white blood cells I was just
talking about this one this one set of
our our immune system out of the six
main units these white blood cells have
a license to
kill their job is more difficult than
the white blood cells that were guarding
the liver's entryways so this liver L
this liver lob white blood cell that
sits inside the
liver it has a much more
difficult
job than the ones that guarded the
hepatic portal Highway the veins both
the veins and the arteries that I was
talking about
before so this is an entirely different
blood cell white blood cell it has a
license to kill anything that escapes
and enters the liver this one's way more
aggressive
too because your liver here's how it
works your liver is your body's
filter so it can be filled with any
number of toxins that get in the way of
white blood cells work so when these
white blood cells have to do their work
these toxins get in the way all the time
these blood cells have to be stronger
and even
better it's like the soldiers on the
Battleground unable to see clearly from
the smoke of burning buildings because
there's so much going on and there's
heavy metal runoff inside our liver
there's viral and bacterial waste waste
from Epstein bar sitting in the liver
for 20 years just built up and built up
and built up there's junk in there
there's all kinds of stuff there's old
pesticides even DDT is in all of our
livers you better believe it's there
it's still in all the eagles DDT is
still in every single Eagle every single
Eagle on the planet in the US has DDT in
it the eagle eggs still have DDT in it
we don't have any DDT in us oh no we
don't have any DDT in US of course
every single Eagle does but we
don't no of course not why would we have
any in
us so DDT and other
troublemakers they muck up the liver
that's how it works so these these white
blood cells these
lobu white blood
cells have to really figure out how to
attack these
pathogens it's why keeping the liver
clean like in Liver Rescue this this
book Liver Rescue is so healthy and so
critical it's part of protecting
yourself from
disease it's not just about liver
disease forget that it's about every
single illness you get it's about Lyme
disease that's liver
related it's about all these
things it's about all the these things
and by the way I've been saying this
just not just from book one medical
medium the series Lyme disease every
single person with Lyme disease has
Epstein
bar I wonder why I wonder why there
there neurological lime symptoms maybe
it's Epstein bar it
is because bacteria doesn't create
neurological symptoms when is the when
is the medical community is going to
wake up to that fact alone and if that
made you mad about Lyme disease I say
this every show if I say something about
Lyme disease because I've been I've been
whiplashed from it so bad over the years
if that made you upset get book one read
the lime chapter learn the truth about
Lyme disease don't don't stay in denial
it's important it's important if you
need need to bring a torch and try to
burn my apartment down I bring bring
bring a pitchfork bring a bring shovels
and bring baseball bats and torches if
you want because I because I said the
truth about Lyme disease if that's what
you want to
do okay so it's it's so this is how it's
so important that these these white
blood cells really help so bio
production is one of the top functions
of your
liver bod duct white blood cells are
unknown to research and science and
they're assigned to watch over the bile
duct system there's an immune cell
that's protecting your bile duct these
cells are the only part of the immune
system that could withstand B's harshest
harsh nature it's an immune white blood
cell that's not discovered or studied by
science and research it has a sheath
over it a membrane that could handle the
harsh nature of
bile it's got a protective C cover
undiscovered by research and science it
acts as a shield like a hazmat suit or a
firefighter's gear the bod duct white
blood cell looks for passer buyers in
bile that may cause infection of the
liver and gallbladder and dadum and
intestinal tra that this white blood
cell can travel upward and invade the
stomach it can travel upward and NAB a
pathogen that slips by that gets out of
that bile duct it can even travel white
blood cell will launch itself kamakazi
attack you got a white blood cell that
will kill
itself it'll die for you is what it'll
do it'll launch itself out of the bile
duct into Uncharted Territory into your
gut knowing it's eventually going to be
destroyed and and its Shield is going to
burn off its Shield is going to burn off
and it's going to be annihilated but
it's trying to stop a pathogen before it
gets killed off and burned up by too
much bile overtime and hydrochloric
acid and it knows it can't find itself
back or find its way back once it goes
into the gut it's going to die
eventually or get eliminated out of your
stool or wherever it's going to go
so this so that's how it works you got a
ComiCon you literally got you literally
got a white blood cell that will kill
itself for
you and it'll Follow The Invader as far
as it can to try to stop
it by the end of this journey the path
basically dest ultimately destroys and
kills the bile duct white blood cell I'm
talking about by burning away its
protective
cover it's suicide mission
was for pursuing the
pathogen which is that incredible that's
your liver so do we still want to hurt
our liver do we still want to you know I
mean look we're not educated about
eating right I get that that's not what
I'm up with that you know what I don't
care I don't care if someone is eating
fast food and they're not educated about
their liver or they're not educated
about what diet they can do they're not
educated what they should be doing to
protect themselves in the liver's immune
system I don't hold anybody I don't
judge anybody on that on any level I
don't judge anybody on that you better
believe it you better believe it life is
hard you're trying to survive you're
going to fast food restaurant or you're
eating wherever at a friend's house or
you're trying to get your next meal and
you're trying to just whatever you got
to do and if you if you're eating if
you're eating donuts and you're drinking
whatever and you're doing whatever
you're doing I I totally get it you know
what pisses me off is when you're this
Elite SL doctors slash trying to be
public figure slash writing books and
articles slash doing whatever and then
telling people fruit will hurt your
liver and stay on a high fat High trendy
high protein diet oh bring in celery
juice by the way where' that come from
that came from here we know that medical
medium that's that's one of those
jewels and and that bothers me because
then people get really misdirected and
now they're on these other diets
thinking they're still doing something
for the liver yeah it's a little better
than it was than if they were doing
processed foods but let me tell you
something it's it's not enough we have
to protect your liver learn how to eat
you're allowed to have some fats you're
allowed to have some animal protein
you're allowed to have some fats but you
got to be cautious and you got to try to
be careful on that protein tag that
protein tag will keep you sick and take
10 years off your life down the road and
does that matter it matters when you're
70 and you want it to live to be 80 I'll
tell you that much it matters greatly it
matters when you lose 15 years off your
life when you want it to be 80 and you
you lose lose it at
65 you want it to be 100 but you tanked
at
80 I don't know it matters and if you're
chronically ill and you wanted to make
it to 60 but you made it to 40 it
matters so it all
matters so the bottom line is your liver
has this unbelievable immune system we
have to take care of
it and then finally there's this other
part of the liver's immune system the
lymphocytes they Patrol the outer region
of the liver these white blood cells
tend to stay on the outside of the
liver and they're like wa they're in the
Watchtower positions and around the
lymphatic fil these are the guys that
are trying to stop all that strep that's
pounding out of the liver that's coming
out of the liver and going into up up up
beneath the Derma and getting every
teenager in trouble with all the
different acne and the cystic acne and
all the and everybody just everybody
with acne that's a strep and so these
lymphatic white blood cells these
outside ones that are part of the
liver's immune system that research and
science aren't aware of yet they're
trying to actually stop that kind of
thing including like Epstein bar getting
into the tonsils and causing tonsilitis
mono and strep and all that other stuff
that happens I love when someone says I
just got a casol laringitis it's not you
know not when they I'm not saying they
have tonsilitis any when they have
laryngitis I love that yeah no I just
got laryngitis it's she's going away she
been a couple of weeks I went to the
doctor and gave me an antibiotic or she
gave me an
antibiotic and they get laryngitis you
got laryngitis that's strep or mono or
both or
one yep it's a little bit out of strep
Rano are both bottom line anyway so
there's these lymphocytes it's part of
the liver's immune system it tries to
stop Invaders on the outside going into
lymphatic vessels heading in there where
these other lymphocytes are that science
and research are aware of but those
aren't part of the liver's immune system
you got your lymphocytes that you
already have the science research
already knows about they got them tagged
they got them they're on the blood work
they're on there you can you can learn
about them they're no big deal they're
your lympo your lymphatic lymphocytes
they're the ones that actually sit
around your thyroid trying to protect
you from Epstein bar there entering into
it I talk about this in thyroid healing
get the thyroid healing book I got 100
condition
and symptoms in there that you wouldn't
believe that that that are part of the
whole thing with epscene bar and the
thyroid and everything you want to be
Epstein bar expert get the thyroid
healing book honestly that that book is
that book is unbelievable for that but
anyway the bottom line is the
lymphocytes that are around the liver
though those ones are different it's
part of the six main units I'm talking
about this whole time and those aren't
discovered yet and those are there to
try to stop strep or anything else from
going further out and getting out and
getting to the the point of causing
tonsilitis getting to the point of
causing acne getting to the point of
causing some weird sore throat that just
burns getting to the point of causing
all the different fatigue getting to the
point of causing all the brain fog
getting to the point of causing UTI
utti chronic UTI getting to the point of
stopping all of
that so we cover the liver's immune
system not in its entirety I can't get
it all done Liver Rescue has way more
information about it I think I even
missed one for you out of all of those
we don't have the time and I even missed
a whole bunch of other stuff about the
liver's immune system because I can't
cover all of that it's in the pages of
Liver Rescue pick one up if you get a
chance whatever go to the bookstore you
can't pick one up cuz you can't budget
it right now with financially or
anything just go to the library and get
one and take care of yourself for me if
you can't do it for yourself can you do
it for me me can you do it for me okay
that's a lot to ask I know I know all
right can you do it for yourself all
right can you do it for your loved ones
yeah I feel like a loved one right mean
meaning like I love you and I care and I
do I've seen enough suffering in my day
and I still see it every day it breaks
my heart and it's um it's really hard
the amount of people dealing with
everything from you know gut rated liver
problems s too everything under the sun
is really difficult stay strong for me
the best you can I know so many of you
that have actually been just you know
you're fighting your way through it all
and you're trying to get through the
misinformation out there and you don't
you don't know where to go and all kinds
of stuff and you've been struggling just
stay strong for me and hang in there
saturate yourself in the medical medium
books and the information the answers
are there it's Timeless it's actually
there and it's ahead of research and
science try not to get fused confused
with the the the M you know the dis
information out there misinformation
everything else try to be careful
because it'll okay we we I've seen this
over and over again for decades people
have come to me that were sick for
decades they got help and they were
finally free Don't Let it wait that long
I love you guys take one day at a time
bless your heart take care I'll see you
next show this is this is going to be
great all right love you bye