and that recipe you guys might already
have it
right it's in the medical medium new
edition revised and expanded making the
loaded potato hash gonna talk about lyme
disease
lyme symptoms lime triggers i'm going to
talk about some other stuff about the
body how it
loves you unconditionally and it doesn't
attack you or turn against you
i want to cover a little bit on that too
i just want to get the onion in the pan
the pan's getting hot
you guys getting on here right now i'm
excited we're live youtube
live facebook and um
yeah we're we're doing it right now
so i'm gonna put some onion in here this
potato hash
a little bit of onion going glad you
guys are coming on great to see you
live on youtube and live on facebook
right now at the same time
guys i'm making the loaded potato hash
the recipe in medical medium new edition
book one i hope you got it there's
deanna everybody's coming on
hope you guys got the book i mean if you
don't you know
lorraine l i see that
got some onions going in here
do you guys like onion greetings from
vermont
great place to be thanks for being here
patty
hi from the uk pia amazing
love the uk incredible
wonderful wonderful lot of people from
all over the world
i know
[Music]
aw thank you for everything you do it's
an honor honor for you guys to be here
very happy you're here
got some onions frying in the pan right
now
this is a loaded potato hash um you'll
see some broccoli i got asparagus right
here
i don't know if you guys are doing any
asparagus these days but
asparagus is so great um got some spices
got potatoes
some nice potatoes there we go throwing
everything in the air
anything i grab i throw in the air i
don't know if it's a bad habit or
or what some onions here
put a little water on here
i'm going to chop up some potatoes get
these potatoes and these are beautiful
russet potatoes right here they're just
gorgeous
going to cube them up these nice little
cubes
i'm going to talk about lyme disease you
guys going to talk about different
triggers you know i've been talking
about
uh the blood draw right when you go and
get your blood tests i've been talking
about how it takes out the
the immune system and when it comes down
to lyme disease
they just take so much blood and so much
blood and then you go to another
specialist then you go to another
specialist they're taking more blood
then you lose your immune system and
nobody knows it
and then the whole reason behind lyme
disease which they're unaware of unless
they know medical medium information
is it's viral and then viral issues get
worse
love your ideas in the kitchen
from florida amazing love the state of
florida
sunshine state
aloha from hawaii glad you guys are all
coming on going to talk about some cool
stuff tonight
dot medical medium in front of me right
here the medical medium book if you guys
checked it out the new edition
um i talk about chronic fatigue syndrome
fibromyalgia
multiple sclerosis lyme disease chapter
right
depression chapter ptsd chapter candida
chapter
shingles that's right trigeminal
neuralgia colitis
sciatic pain the shingles people
you know frozen shoulder all that right
and so many other things in this book
hashimoto's thyroiditis hyperthyroidism
rhonda renee was drinking lemon water
every morning and
caused lots of heartburn stopped and it
went away
is it too acidic for me lemon water
if you've got a if you have a dirty
gallbladder
okay you have a dirty gallbladder
got sludgy over the years very sludgy
okay that lemon water is gonna purge
your gallbladder
once it purges it a little bit some
junk's going to come flying out
and you're going to end up with a little
bit of heartburn sometimes for some
people do
less do less
do just a little squeeze of lemon
you can reduce the amount of water too
and build yourself
back up and see how it goes along the
way that's a sludgy
dirty gallbladder seen that so many
people
making the potato hash the loaded potato
hash that's what i would do if it was
happening to me
that's what i would do
[Music]
you guys i'm cooking some onions can you
see it i got some potato in here now i
got to put some broccoli in there too
okay there we go it's cooking up nice
it's actually cooking up nice and quick
um let's get some broccoli in there
your book arrives on tuesday yay
incredible can't wait
i cover so many different conditions in
that book i'll run them all by
lupus multiple sclerosis hashimoto's
hypothyroidism
diabetes adrenal fatigue chapter
migraines okay i mean
just so much good information tingles
and numbness tinnitus vertigo
this book has saved so many lives and
then
it's not the same book now though i
added a whole book's worth
to it it's on amazon.com
um and this book will blow your
mind i expanded on the meditations
chapter expanded on the angels chapter
and
it's a spiritual book also it's a
medical book
it's a medical book and a spiritual book
both combined that's what it is
getting my broccoli pieces in here
in my broccoli pieces in here no sound
right now
you guys getting any sound can you hear
me okay
someone said no sound getting the rest
of this broccoli in
is the book in stores now frederick i
think it's in stores now yes ask your
local bookstore
uh barnes and noble absolutely
get it on line two
so i'm making the loaded potato hash
and i'm in medical medium new edition
right here guys don't mind if i cook a
little bit before we start talking about
all the cool stuff
i hope that's okay i just want to get
this started
i want to get this going this is the
loaded potato hash i want to get it
cooking up
that's what i'm doing um
so i put in some broccoli i put in some
potatoes
right you guys saw that put in some
onions
right and um
and i'm looking for the recipe as we
speak it's coming right up here
so we're going to talk about lyme
disease today we're going to talk about
how the body doesn't attack itself
all these things are critical and
important that's what it looks like
right there i just wanted you guys to
see what it looks like in the book
so there's the loaded potato hash right
there there's the recipe
there it is so i'm going to put a little
lid on here too
cook it a little quicker
i put it right in the middle that's what
i like to do
got some asparagus i'm also gonna chop
up
that's gonna go in here beautiful
asparagus look at that
right are you guys eating asparagus this
is really powerful healing food
is there a lot of information on
hashimoto's in your book is there ever
it's packed with information about
hashimoto's
it's in the f steam bar section too
there's actually a the
thyroid chapter so
really really packed with information
i'm actually cutting through the book
right now a little bit um
so the epstein-barr virus is behind
hashimoto's that's one thing you'll
learn in here how it works
if you want to heal hashimoto's you have
to you have to know how it works with
epsilon bar
i got a hypothyroidism and other thyroid
disorders right here it's on page 37
and i talk about epstein-barr getting
into the thyroid
that's what causes hashimoto's
thyroiditis so there's a whole
hashimoto's section so hypothyroidism
and other thyroid disorders
hashimoto's is just more of an advanced
version of hypothyroidism that's what
hashimoto's is
i'm going to chop up some asparagus i
just wanted to get this cooking a little
bit before we go into a lot of heavy
duty stuff
so i just want to get everything in the
pan
putting a little asparagus in here
what kind of cooking where do you use go
to medicalmedium.com on my uh
medical medium.com on my directory
and um you'll see the kitchenware go to
kitchenware
you'll see that
okay
putting some asparagus in here
getting it in so
last little pieces here so what i have
in here is potato i got broccoli
i got onion
and um this is the loaded potato hash
which i really like i'm about to put the
red bell pepper in there in a little bit
but i want to get that cooking
a little bit more
great to have you guys on here
all right i got that cooking got some
red bell peppers i may as well get them
ready
and um are you guys eating potatoes
lately
i got some beautiful russet potatoes
right here
so what i do with the red bell pepper is
i just cut it like this
right i take out the center right here
and that's it you're done i know a lot
of people they wrestle with the red bell
peppers
and there's no wrestling it was just as
simple as that and i got this
i took the stem toss the stem and i have
that and that so
there we go that's it not really red and
beautiful
right i'm going to chop up these pieces
you just ordered cleanse the heal last
night love your cooking show
glad you're here um cleans the heel
this one's on sale on amazon.com us
right now
51 off but um this is a medical textbook
incredible medical textbooks already
healed so many people there's already i
think
over 10 000 reviews on amazon
for with this book so many healing
stories so many people getting their
lives back
cheryl you love this shirt the green
shirt this is the shirt i think i wore
during the
uh one of the tick tock videos recently
you guys the reason why
this is a fat free recipe right here so
keep that in mind
that this is a fat free recipe
so radical fats i call them radical fats
that everybody's eating
because everybody's on fat they're all
eating fat they're
fatting themselves to death and i talk
about this all the time look i mean
everybody's being told eat lots of fat
eat lots of fat and there's foods that
are high in fat right you got your
milk cheese butter eggs you got your
dairy products all the different dairy
products
right okay got your coconut oil yeah
it's a healthy fat
of course it is you got your avocado
it's still a healthy fat got your olive
oil
you got your you got you know there's
still a healthy fat
and all the different fats out there you
got soy that's high in fat right
soy milk high in fat oat milk nut milks
um like almond milk okay and people put
all their peanut butter
on their food and then they also have
their chicken they also have their meat
every day
everybody's eating fat that's what
everybody's doing
okay and then if that's not bad all on
its own because everybody's just tanking
the fat tank and the fat every day
it's it's part of everybody's diet every
single day sometimes all day long right
it's good to take a fat break out of
your diet so you don't kill your liver
kill your gallbladder so you don't you
you don't kill your kidneys
the fats hurt the kidneys over time the
people end up getting kidney disease
later on because
the fats help to actually speed that up
help to promote that that condition and
all that plaque that fat plaque that
gets in the arteries of the heart
gets into the valves um that's from
a lifetime of eating fat so i like what
i like to do is i like to
make dishes that don't have the fats in
hopes that you guys
eat one dish a day or one smoothie a day
or
you know where you're not getting all
that fat in your in your in your meals
right
the whole reason why intermittent
fasting even though it's not a great
idea because it's not done right out
there
the whole reason it's even helping
people to some degree because they're
removing the fats in the morning
they're getting they're getting rid of
all that fat they're getting rid of the
peanut butter they're getting rid of the
eggs they're getting rid of the bacon
whatever it is they did in the morning
they're getting rid of
and that's why they start to get better
or
lose a little bit of weight because they
stopped
bombarding their liver they don't know
that's why nobody knows why
intermittent fasting so-called experts
don't know that's why
because the fat is missing and if they
do know now it's because of the medical
medium information
but i'm trying to get the radical fats
out of your diet a little bit here and
there
because that's the key that's the key
debra said
loaded potato hash from the new book
absolutely that's what i'm making right
here and i'm talking about the heart a
little bit you guys
there's a new book new edition you guys
it's coming out tuesday officially
coming out on tuesday but many of you
guys got the copy now i think right
renee says i've always been very thin
for one year i've eaten mm and minimal
fats and i am at the healthiest weight
i've ever been so happy because you're
recovering your liver
your liver keeps everything in check
you're getting glucose to all your
muscles
that's why you're doing the mm stuff and
amazing so glad you guys are on here
thank you for sharing that that's so
important is shrimp high in fat yeah
it is it doesn't mean dr phan good to
see you it doesn't mean you can't have
shrimp
right if that's what you love
but i'm just trying you know what book
should i carol says what book should we
start with
for fatigue sleep all night and wake up
so tired you poor thing that's awful
you know you just wake up tired every
day you're tired all the time
um the new addition chronic fatigue
syndrome
it you know deals with fatigue all of
this this is one option
i love the i love to put that book i
mean honestly these two books i want to
talk to you guys about the heart
hopefully the heart doesn't
doesn't get into my my dish right
the cleanser heel book right and these
two
what a powerhouse these two are what a
powerhouse you know
and instead of breaking them up in
programs and selling programs for three
thousand dollars a piece
i wanted to give you guys books that
just caught cost like
a few dollars basically in the end of it
all you know it's like
the medical medium new edition is on
sale right now you guys it's on sale on
amazon.com right now
us it's on sale which is unbelievable
before the book even is released it's on
sale right
and this one's on sale 51 off and
instead of like breaking these up and
expensive programs and making everybody
sign up and
cutting off my youtubes and stopping all
my lives and making it so you guys have
to
sign up and pay money to actually hear
me talk and stuff i never wanted to do
that to you guys so
i wanted to just get these powerful
medical books out for you that you can
get free at the library
once the books come out right get free
at the library if you want or you can
just buy them now on sale
and i just want you guys to get a chance
to heal bottom line
like have every opportunity
so i'm making the potato hash it's
actually cooking up really nice right
now
can put the red bell pepper in there
soon
i'm trying to keep you guys off the
radical fats a little bit because the
health gurus of today will literally
cause you guys to have heart problems
down the road
they'll tell you healthy fat healthy fat
healthy fat and guess where healthy fat
ends up
in your arteries and your veins all fat
ends up in your arteries and your veins
down the road
you end up getting the stints you end up
getting the blood clots you end up
getting
the blood vessels you end up getting the
aneurysms you end up getting it all
the embolisms aneurysms blood clots you
got to get the stint you got to get the
shunts
all that stuff and and the thing is the
problem is with fat
is fat's so addictive it's addictive
because it triggers the adrenaline
right you eat that avocado and i don't
mind if you guys eat avocado i don't
mind if you guys eat some healthy fats
and
if you guys like animal protein and you
want like you know salmon or anything
but
what it is is there's so much of it and
there's so
too much of it in the diet and then all
the health gurus are like
you know more fat fats good for you you
need fat for your brain
and they don't realize it but the more
fat you eat
your brain atrophies down the road so
you end up getting your brain start to
shrink and shrink and shrink
this is cooking actually really good and
really quick
um so this is going really good right
now
it's still it's it's it's going nice and
good i'm gonna pop a lid on here for for
a second
so um the whole point is that fat builds
up with plaque
sits on the inside of the heart sits on
the inside of the arteries
sits on the inside of blood vessels so
as we're doing the fats and we don't
stop and it's every single day
and it's not just that if you did all
that bacon in the past
it's it's it built up a fine layer
inside the arteries and veins
you can't get that out unless you go low
fat unless you drop the radical fats
once in a while unless you start to have
a meal
that's fat free once in a while doreen
says i feel so much better fat free for
a few months lost 40 pounds
that i needed off during right isn't
that incredible
so amy said can't wait for the book yeah
that's amazing like 40 pounds
and what people don't realize is they
all have a layer of fat inside their
veins and arteries
they all do it's from the bacon the eggs
the milk cheese
the butter in your coffee whatever it is
it's just all from the fats
you know brandy i've always had trouble
keeping weight
and since liver rescue and cleanse the
heal protocols i am the healthiest
ever super grateful i'm grateful that
you're reading the books looking into
the information knowing how to heal
learning how to heal
grateful for that so so so happy
so that's why people say well why isn't
he using any fats he's anti-fat that's
not it that's not true
right that's not true at all i mean if
you want to cook up some
if you want to cook up some fats
you can do it but i'm trying to get you
guys to be
look you can be fat free for months you
can be fat free for it radical fat free
for a year
you can be radical fat free the rest of
your life
because there's fat in everything
there's fat and the broccoli i just
threw in here there's fat and the potato
i just threw in here there's fat and the
asparagus i just threw in here
there's there's omegas in every single
fruit vegetable herb wild food just
the 4-1-1 on that just letting you know
about that right there
and there's fat in these red bell
peppers right
and it's in here okay
you can be fat free your whole life
you can go radical fat free for a
hundred years
cindy as an athlete i cut out i cut out
all of the man-made crap
amazing protein powders amazing
right eggs etc i have more muscle
and i'm leaner healthier since following
mm for the last 15 months
cindy blown away blown
away
blown away right there incredible
blown away okay that that
is amazing i'm gonna get some red bell
pepper in here for now in a second
get that cooking a little bit more got
my little heart in here
on here and um here's what happens when
you keep on eating all that fat
i'm not saying you guys like i said
can't have some tahini and can't have
some
uh hemp seeds all right sesame seeds
right
okay can't have some sunflower seeds
can't do some pumpkin seeds you know
um i'm not saying that you can't have
all that
or have your favorite animal protein
right
but what i'm saying is that's why
everybody's brains
atrophy everybody's brain's atrophy
because the fat stops the brain from
getting
fed glycogen glucose
the fats stop the glucose from getting
into the brain
the brain atrophies year after year now
you're 40 years old brain shrinks a
little bit now you're 50 years old
the brain shrinks a little bit brain
brain brain shrinks ring shrinks that's
what happens
and then the heart at the same time
fills up with all that lining all that
fat all your blood vessels your veins
your arteries and guess what everybody
who's been telling you to do as much
fat because you need it you need those
fats make sure you're on all those fats
they don't pay the price meaning they
don't care about you
20 years from now after they gave you
all that bad
information all that misinformation
who cares hey gurus health coaches
trainers whoever they are you know
doctors podcast doctors
let them keep on giving you
misinformation over and over again
and then in the end who cares you guys
end up
you end up with problems it's not their
problem
it's your problem it's no one's problem
but yours
that i actually care i don't want you to
be in a position down the road
where we could have probably got got
some you know
fix-its going so you can avoid all that
i'm doing some red bell pepper in this
now
i do the red bell pepper a little bit
later
tends to cook quicker i also like my red
bell pepper
a certain way not so
soft putting my red bell pepper in here
this is the loaded potato hash
i got right here i'm going to cut this
circle working on a new podcast
episode couple of new podcast episodes
medical meme podcast at apple podcast
check it out catch up on the other 17
new episodes too
so i'm about to read something out of
book right now i'm going to talk about
lyme disease
truth about lyme disease gina since
starting mm two and a half years ago
i've been able to get get off of anxiety
medication
caffeine and i've lost 30 pounds so
grateful to you aw and soc
just so you know that's that healing
story right you just told me
would be heralded as god in the media
if i if it was if it was like
things that were happening out there in
in medicine
like if that was happening in regular
medicine
a functional medicine doctor you know
has one of those in a year one
patient in a year
he treat it like god he's treated like
god or she's treated like god
medical mean information has helped
millions get to that point
over all these years um
sarah says how old am i i'm old
i'm older older than people know
i've been doing this for over 30 plus
years
um just re up until recently everybody
thought i was 28 years old and
that's kind of funny i don't look 28.
anyway look i got the lime disease
chapter right here i want to read a
quote
for you in the moment
so much information to cover
it really is there's just so much good
information to cover so
thanks to the readers who went into
action
with the information here this book has
prompted
medical research and science to
re-categorize
lyme disease while labeling lyme
as autoimmune still does not represent a
full understanding of lyme symptoms
this re-categorization is a way
for medical research and science to
admit we don't
understand this as well as we thought we
did
and that's a major shift towards
progress
it's testament to the people who read
here in medical medium that lyme disease
is
viral not bacterial who brought that
information to their doctors and who
applied the healing protocols here and
got results
it's also thanks to the doctors who have
educated themselves with this material
as they work to help patients many
doctors
have even applied the healing protocols
in their own lives
so i'm talking about lyme disease and
if you're someone who doesn't have lyme
disease you weren't diagnosed with lyme
disease you might want to hang around
for this
um because it applies to so many
different conditions okay
that's fatigue that's fibromyalgia
that's
ms because in the end they all can get a
lyme diagnosis tomorrow if you go to a
lyme doctor
if you got cfs if you got lupus just go
to a lyme doctor you'll get a lime that
you'll get a lyme disease diagnosis
and if you don't get one from that lyme
doctor go to another lyme doctor you'll
get one
you will get a lyme diagnosis if you go
lyme disease doctor shopping so it
applies to all you guys
that includes hashimoto's thyroid
problems that includes lupus that
includes ra
it includes just symptoms like tingles
and numbness aches and pains tightness
in the chest
even anxiety you go to a lyme doctor
you're gonna walk out of there with a
stamp on your back
boom that's gonna be the stamp on your
back saying lyme disease that's what
it's going to say
right when you walk out of there um
that's how it works this
this potato hash is cooking up really
nice right now
hey uh sigrid um the tick tock green
shirt video was so funny i laughed and
could not
sleep
[Laughter]
that tick-tock video with with the rat
running
up over the uh counter and the roaches
running over the counter
there's no editing on that that's one
straight
minute of me pulling that off it's
actually really funny
cooking this up right now
it's going to lyme disease
so if you've got a condition and you've
got symptoms whether it's ticks and
spasms whether it's leg cramps whether
it's restless leg syndrome whether it's
burning skin whether you've got
uh thrush whatever it is if you go to a
lyme doctor
lyme specialist you'll end up with that
lime stamp
that's just what's going to happen
you're not going to go to a lyme disease
doctor
and leave there without a lyme diagnosis
if you do go to another and you'll leave
there with the lyme diagnosis
because so really what happens is that
neurological lyme
is basically neurological everything
caused by epstein-barr virus
okay and shingles sometimes hhv-6
simplex 1 2 as well the cold sore virus
all right and sedimental virus can cause
some trouble too these are viruses
that release neurotoxin the epstein-barr
virus
releases a neurotoxin that neurotoxin
is what creates neurological symptoms
tingles and numbness aches and pains
burning skin pain in the jaw pain
everywhere
okay neck pain back pain migraines
neurotoxins just so you know
and neurotoxins don't come from bacteria
they don't come from bacteria bacteria
bartonella the hybrid but vibesia
borrelia they don't release
neurotoxins you can't get neurological
symptoms from those
you can't but yet you have any
neurological symptoms
all you have to do is go to lyme doctor
they'll stamp you with a lyme diagnosis
out the door it's like the broom
salesman it's gonna
doesn't matter what size broom it is
you're just gonna get a broom as you're
leaving that store
right babisia bartonella borrelia are
not
super bugs they are not
super bugs news flash
they are not super bugs okay
they can get killed off really easily
with one dose of a mild antibiotic
they don't even cause neurological lyme
they don't cause neurological problems
they're harmless bacteria
and a harmless parasitical hybrid of
bacteria
as far as babisia goes it's really
and um mrsa
mercy is a superbug so mersa is a
superbug i'm in lyme disease if you just
get
got on here it's a new edition medical
medium merce is a superbug right
a superbug it's one of the superbugs
antibiotic resistant and
they need less antibiotics and not even
the harshest antibiotics
and the success rate for mrsa is
unbelievable
it's incredible really a success rate
right
but for some reason you got neurological
lyme
so-called borrelia and bartonella and
babisia and you're sick for
years they can bombard you with the most
aggressive antibiotics
and you just get sicker and sicker and
sicker
and then would it what happens there
will you get the
neurotoxin shock you know and
people think it's herxheimer so you're
getting bombarded with heavy heavy
antibiotics
and and you're getting a reaction from
these heavy antibiotics you're not
getting a reaction from die off
and that's a confusion with lyme disease
right there so it's not that you
get die off
you know from the antibiotics you get
agitated
nerves from the antibiotics the nervous
system because it's so hypersensitive
from all those neurotoxins
can't handle all that harsh antibiotic
so now you're getting sicker you're
getting more neurological symptoms and
your lyme doctors like and this is what
happened for
years your lime doctor's like that's
herxheimer that's herxheimer keep up the
antibiotics that's herxheimer or we'll
back down the antibiotics so that you
can get a little bit better from your
herxheimer and then we'll bring the
antibiotics back in bringing the
antibiotics back in
it's misinformation it's actually the
wrong direction
so yeah i'm just cooking up this right
now
but of course if your doctor wants you
to do antibiotics you do antibiotics i
mean if that's
you know if you're happy with your
doctor you listen to your doctor you do
and i'm just talking about experience
from
from thousands and thousands of cases
over the years
now this book teaches how it's not
bacterial for lyme disease this book
teaches how it's viral
and that's what the real cause of lyme
disease is
so i'm giving you the rundown on the
bacterial aspect
so what happens is viruses such as
epstein-barr like i was talking about
before
cytomegalovirus simplex 1 and shingles
and hhv6
the viruses that i was speaking about
earlier those viruses create neurotoxins
neurotoxins inflame the nerves
when they inflame the nerves you get the
neurological symptoms
the tingles and numbness the aches and
pains the body pain the neck pain
the jaw pain ticks and spasms
and these are just some things right
there so
you you end up getting all those
different neurological symptoms from
neurotoxins
from viruses right so anyway you guys
this is cut this is coming along right
here
bacteria doesn't release neurotoxins as
i was saying before
bacteria can't release a neurotoxin it
doesn't produce a neurotoxin so bacteria
doesn't cause neurological symptoms
unless it's a bacterial infection that
causes a really extremely high fever and
then you can have temporary neurological
symptoms
but that's because of a really really
high fever but that's a whole different
story
talked about that over the years this is
an entirely different issue altogether
so i'm going to add some spices to this
right here
[Music]
put a little red bell pepper not red
bell hot chili flakes right here
dr faun md do people believe that only
doctors can heal others
i have thousands of patients who weren't
cured or healed by doctors and
specialists
i mean it's interesting you know i mean
there's i think
people need to be sick long enough
seen enough doctors to realize whoa wait
a minute we don't have enough
information out there i just put
red hot chili flakes in there we don't
have enough information
out there i'm putting a little garlic
powder in here you can do fresh garlic
i'm putting
a little bit of garlic powder in here
i'm putting a little thyme in here okay
doing that little time
so we're still talking about lyme but
listen it pertains to everything
pertains to everything neurotoxins
caused by viruses such as epstein-barr
giving people a whole range of symptoms
and conditions vertigo
dizziness feeling of like being on the
boat on a boat
anxiety your chest feels like it's
tightened up you can't even breathe
um you're going to the er constantly
because you think you're having a heart
attack
i mean it pertains to so many different
conditions
insomnia other conditions like that so
you guys um
this is coming together really nice
about to put some fresh cilantro on top
of it in a little bit
i don't know if you can see that in
there
i'm just going to give you a little flip
to look can you guys see
so when it comes down to lyme disease
hundreds of thousands of mostly women
were injured from the mistakes made
with lyme disease their bodies were
bombarded with
intense amounts of antibiotics some of
the harshest antibiotics
it led to them becoming sicker and
sicker and sicker
it led to doctor shopping forever
and it it really really hurt a lot of
people
tens of thousands lost their lives
throughout the process
um sandy was watering used to cook this
instead a little bit of water right off
the running
so i've been seeing so you guys you know
one of the things that have helped so
many people
heal is the heavy metal detox smoothie
the medical medium heavy metal detox
movie
and then um
and then you know what happens is a lot
of people look doctors weren't trying to
hurt people it was just because
you had to remember that with lyme
disease doctors were never trying to
hurt people that's not it at all
doctors are always compassionate their
hearts in it they want to heal people
and you know and that's important to
understand it's just that mistakes are
made
in the industries in the medical
industry and misinformation has
definitely sent people the wrong
direction for healing it's made things
very difficult over the years
heavy metal detox smoothie saved my life
christy amazing
look out look out for that zeolite stuff
that's going around don't i i don't
recommend that at all
i'm noticing what happens when here's
the thing the medical medium community
has healed more people
than anywhere else in all the
communities and so
all these old things these old trendy
things
try to come back into the medical meme
community you know like the alkaline
ionizer water machine it tries
tries to come back in to sell it to
people that have already healed
and the same thing with zeolite i don't
recommend zeolite at all so if someone
thinks hey
um you know you know i used to
i used to i used to recommend
a very gentle zeolite a long time ago
i don't anymore though and it was only
because
there wasn't a lot of dolls to be found
there wasn't a lot of atlantic dolls to
be found
and that was one of the reasons why i
did and it was really
and it was really just to help
try to get a little bit of metal out of
the intestinal tract okay
and but it still wasn't enough zeolite
just doesn't work good it just
doesn't work and right now there's a
whole bunch of mlm stuff going on a
whole bunch of pyramid scheme stuff
going on everybody's trying to sell
something in the medical medium
community and what happens is
what happens is with the medical medium
community is because it's the only
community where that many people are
healing
and they're healing like like no one's
ever seen
it's easy to bring things in that never
fixed anybody from the past
and resell them in the medical medium
community right
that's how it's done in 2000 like that
in the mid 2000s
like the alkaline alkaline ionizer water
machines they were practically dead on
arrival because
for the last 30 years they never got
anybody better and
they were then all of a sudden rebirth
in the medical medium community because
when you rebirth
something in a community that's already
healing like no one's ever seen before
it's easy to say oh
you want to do medical medium which got
you better and add this
you want to do medical medium and add
zeola you want to do medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie
and add zeolite and i don't want to hurt
anybody's feelings out there but like
like somebody said in the youtube
comments a little while ago someone said
that i'm not a people pleaser and i
remembered that and read that
and i was like that's true you know i'm
not
it's not about people pleasing it's
about
life saving right that's what it's about
and it's about making sure that you have
what you need
so you don't get in trouble down the
road with your condition
so you have every opportunity to heal so
the heavy metal detox smoothie
is healing people and it has a track
record of healing people right
so then old you know old dogs come in
with like things that never got anybody
better
like zeolite zeolite never got people
better throughout the years it just
it's been around for a long time and it
never got anybody
better it doesn't have that history of
thousands and thousands of people
getting better it just doesn't have that
in fact it died
along the way you couldn't even revive
zeolite
now people are trying to revive zeolite
and say well you need your heavy metal
detox smoothie
with zeolite too you know and it's like
no you don't
um there's a reason why i don't
recommend zeolite here's a couple of
reasons too
the ones on the market don't do what
they're supposed to do i don't care
what which one where how when
i've looked at them all they don't do
what they do
so that's important to know the other
thing is the zeolites
they take your electrolytes away so
and yeah be careful bad zeolites
take your electrolytes away so
it's not something you're just supposed
to be pounding down or taken every day
because
it will drain your electrolytes that's
one thing
and also zeolites tend to they tend to
dehydrate the body so your cells get
dehydrated from zeolites so you get the
zeolites that
they dehydrate and they also take away
electrolytes
right it's what you don't want to do
it's why i don't recommend it it's why
i'm not recommending one now
and you don't you don't need a zeolite
to get out toxic heavy metals
there's no zeolite that can leave your
intestinal tract
travel through your bloodstream and get
to your brain
just so you know there's no zeolite that
can travel in your bloodstream and get
to your brain
and remove metal these zeolites
all of them they just died along the way
no one cared anymore because they never
fixed anybody they never did anything
so what happens is you know the heavy
metal detox smoothie blew up around the
world right
so it saved lives around the world
because it gets metals out it's
life-changing and when you have a
community
that has life-changing results that no
one's ever seen before in all the other
communities
you you can sneak in something on the
sly
and be like wow i gotta get my zeolite
in there and start marketing in there i
gotta get my
water machine in the medical media
community start marketing in there
i gotta get my colostrum in the medical
medium community i gotta get my
collagen in the medical medium community
because everybody's healing in there so
all you have to do is get all these
people that are healing
get all my get all my admins and people
working on it get all the people that
work for advertising for the company and
get them in there commenting 24 7. like
hey
try the zeolite hey try the zeolite hey
try this college and try this collagen
come combine that with medical medium
you can take yourself all the way
and that's the game being played and
it's really a sad situation really
because you take something that's
working and healing somebody
healing millions really around the world
because millions of books
have gotten around the world and and
that's what that gold emblem right there
um says and what happens is that then
you can slip in these things so hey
let's slip in some charcoal next things
that don't really work
let's slip in corella you know and get
corella
rebirthed again you know let's get let's
get zeolite rebirthed again and we can
do it with the medical medium community
because medical medium community they're
all you know they're they're all healing
there
and that's that's how it works
um so i don't recommend zeolites just
letting you know
um and what happens is you can do
something that's not helpful
but the mm stuff is keeping you afloat
right
you're doing your celery juice you're
doing a heavy metal detox smoothie right
you're lowering your fats you're doing
all kinds of you know you're doing your
healing broth you're doing your spinach
soups right
you're working on healing but then
you're doing zeolite
and it's working against you right
it's working against you you're doing
nutritional yeast it's working against
you
you're doing um you know you're doing
your cruella it's working against you
you're doing your protein powders it's
working against you
see and and but eventually those
unhealthy things those unhelpful things
catch up to you
and they start to tip the balance
because you might be like
do like look you might be doing less of
your celery juice or less of some
medical medium stuff and it's not now
keeping you afloat and now you're doing
the zeolite and the zeolite's
dehydrating you
it's dropping down your electrolytes
okay and then you're doing other stuff
and that's not helping eventually that
stuff catches up
and then you start going down for the
count a few years later
and then you think it's mm when it's
really the zeolite
i'm only one voice for medical medium
right you see what these companies do
they got like 30 people
hacking away they're working for them
and then when it's mlmlm they have
another 50 people and then everybody's
trying to sell it and everybody's trying
to sell it
that's hard to keep up with like they're
all they got everybody working on it
chipping away money's being made
money's being made off the medical meme
community they got something hot going
on
and they got p i'm one voice i'm one
voice is sitting on here right
and it's hard to battle that when they
got like 30 admin and
they got all the stuff going on and
they're trying to they're trying to
infiltrate the group
the medical medium groups do this deal
like do the seal like that in the heavy
metal detox movie is what you do and
it's it's really unbelievable i don't
have 30
40 50 admins i don't have 30 40 50
people
working for me that are on there trying
to
clean up messes and and do whatever what
it is it's just it's it's incredible
really
um suzanne does the new book talk about
gut issues there's a gut health chapter
in here
it's it's really a great one um so yeah
you might want to check it out
in the new book for sure so
the whole point is is i can try to i can
only look out for you guys as much as i
can
okay i mean honestly and it's hard to
battle every single kind of trickery
that's happening
zeolite died it died it has a history of
20 years of nobody getting better from
it
but when you have a community that's
healing
actually healing like the medical medium
human community and that's never been
seen before
in our history you can revive old dead
staples
like zeolite you can revive it and trick
out people because
i you know because i got the word out
there that people are
they're filled with toxic heavy metals i
got that word out there
so hey it's perfect well zeolite could
clean that up let's add that in there
let's revive something that died a long
time ago that very few people even used
anymore
let's bring it back in and try to say
you could do
that within you know i don't want to
hurt anybody's feelings there's some
really good people that are actually
good-hearted people that are actually um
you know trying to push these things and
and
their hearts in it and i'm not saying
anything bad about that i'm just letting
you know christine says oh my god i got
to tell you mr w
i had dry skin for decades and following
the protocols i've got
nicer skin than ever thank you that's
amazing
that's so special that's so special um
i'm going to put this on a plate right
here i'm going to plate this we're still
talking you guys
actually i'm going to plate it and put
some fresh cilantro on top
hello how much different is this new
addition a lot different leslie
a lot only recipes a few extra tidbits
nope
i have all your other books okay you're
answering now
laugh out loud anything else i've
ignored my line so here's the thing
um this book right here i get it you're
gonna think it's a new edition
so maybe there's just a few tidbits
thrown in and a few you know a few
colorful recipes right
but i went against the standard in
publishing
okay and i think i got my publisher
upset
probably i put a whole book in here
so there's a whole books worth in here
is what i did and that's why this book
is
one heavy and big book do you remember
the old one
the old one was light as a feather and
yeah it was a great book it's saved
millions of lives around the world with
what it had in there
this thing is a beast and uh
it's got a whole book added to it
entirely different situation
um and when people realize that when
they start reading it they're gonna be
like oh my god
i'm gonna plate this up real quick for
you guys
so um you guys
do you guys like when i'm doing the
cooking
i mean i i like it because it's it's my
dinner plus it's fun to do with you guys
because i have you guys in my kitchen
which is actually really fun um
but uh this is just really fun
i'm gonna plate this up i'm going to put
a little fresh cilantro on top too if
you guys don't mind
okay i'm plating some of this up
balancing female hormones there's a
menopause chapter in the new edition
you might want to check that out it's
really really interesting
yeah hormones get out of balance
absolutely they do but there's more to
why
you get symptoms right it's not because
a lot of the symptoms aren't because
hormones are not balanced
that's not the symptoms so when you get
heart palpitations that's something
else that's not hormones hot flashes
that's a stagnant sluggish liver that's
not hormones that's a stagnant sluggish
liver
but what happens is all these symptoms
get passed off as menopause symptoms or
hormonal symptoms when really they're
not
guys i'm just putting a little fresh
fresh parsley
a little bit on top of this like this
just a little bit
there you go nice little fresh so that's
the plate right there
that's the loaded potato hash i'm
actually really excited it's got red
bell peppers potatoes in there broccoli
some asparagus it smells so good and
there's no fat in there
so it's like no artery building heart
attack fat
that you know that that gets everybody
in the end right
yeah without fats not saying you can't
eat fats i'm just saying maybe try
not eating fats for a day right maybe
try not eating fats for a week get
better
some people are just commenting earlier
they've been off that for a while and
they lost 30 40 pounds
yeah so if you're really sensitive with
your digestive tract your sensitive
things that you're eating and all that
try the mono cleanse and cleanse the
heal
so the mono cleanses and cleanse the
heel right here try that when you get a
chance these are medical textbooks
there's so much information in here it's
just it's
it's it's unreal really uh
tamara says love cleanse the heal it's
my bible incredible
really is guys i just made this dish i
want you guys to see it i'm gonna move
this heart
out of the way so
the good thing about this food is
there's no oil
put into this think about that a little
bit there's no oil
drenched in this meal there's
there's no fat in this meal right think
about that okay
and what you're doing is you're getting
glucose
because of that to your brain to your
heart you're getting glucose to your
liver when you have all that fat
drenched in
soaking in your meals and in your food
you don't get
glucose to your brain easy it doesn't
get there the fat
blocks it and you can't get it there the
way it needs to be
so that's important there too so you
guys talking about a few things we
covered lyme disease lyme disease is
viral i talk about in the book and if
you're like oh well he just did the
spoiler on that
it's it's viral don't need to get the
book that's not true the lyme disease
chapter
is quite a read tremendous amounts of
information in there
so take a look if you know somebody
that's got lyme symptoms lyme disease
but it's not just about that
neurological symptoms of any kind
this book is the book for that and you
know
it's from you know anxiety depression
everything
so tracy says so what's the base it's
water the base is water and not
oil you don't have to have an oil base
tandy says that looks fabulous doesn't
it look good it looks really good right
this i'm going to move this heart away
move it over
okay that's the dish there you guys
yeah so anyway you guys just want to
give you a quick reminder medical medium
podcast at apple podcast check it out
if you haven't check out the meditations
i'm heading over to ig
and tiktok um so i'm excited come on
over to
instagram live and tick tock live with
me i'm heading over there in about 10
minutes
so courtney my daughter's eating i just
saw that and
then it went up there sorry i couldn't
read the rest of it sometimes that this
they just fly up um and it's hard for me
to control it
isabelle i had horrible hot flashes
before i started following his
recommendations it took about one year
for me to heal
i went full plant based and never look
back incredible and look you guys
medical medium can be plant-based and
vegan
right it can also be animal protein it
could still heal
so whatever if you if you're plant-based
and vegan and that's
what you feel compelled to go to and go
that direction mm
do it absolutely be plant-based be vegan
absolutely okay
and then all right if you want to stay
animal protein
then we do it right and you can do mm
while doing animal protein okay because
medical medium is not just plant-based
it's for animal protein
or plant-based it's for either ore and
you can pick the side you want to be on
you want to be plant-based and do it
that way heck yeah we can do it all the
way
you want to do with some animal protein
still can do it okay
and because people who are plant-based
still get sick
unless they're doing it right unless
they're learning how to heal plant-based
and people who are animal protein still
get sick
unless they learn how to do it right
doing the animal protein way check out
the moon meditation deb thank you for
reminding me
the moon meditation it's that medical
medium podcast at apple podcast that's
the uncentred version
make sure you take a look effie says
looks delicious doesn't it
i can't wait to eat it tonight but the
thing is is i can't eat this yet
i have to go to tick-tock live and ig
live and make another one
um claudia i was really sick from birth
i've been on mm for five years
lost 40 pounds thus last year
be patient it works god bless you
incredible
you guys i'm heading over to tick tock
live instagram live i'm gonna make the
food all over again
maybe i can eat after but i'll have a
lot of food courtney doesn't look yummy
thanks for being here i just saw someone
did the moon meditation last night
love you guys