been a long day but I got a treat it's
healing foods Cafe Gratitude right here
medical medium Healing Foods on the menu
there but I got like a major spread
right here that's insane take a look at
this right so just to start with green
papaya and Kel noodles that salad is
incredible I've had this so many times
can't get sick of it it's too good I'm
excited about eating it again tonight
really excited if I take a look at here
vegetable Sushi look at this right here
tell me that is not insane this is
beautiful not just beautiful so healing
so healthy and it's not high in fat high
in oils got all kinds of crazy stuff in
it that's not good for you this is pure
a pure check that out the vegetable
sushi right there the dipping sauce the
ginger let's get into this one right
here the massage kale salad look at the
avocado right there on the side if
you're somebody into avocado you got
some avocado right here and then look
radishes you got the kale you got the
dressing this is so beautiful you got
the cherry tomatoes in here you got the
um cucumbers all of it this is a
beautiful dish but it tastes so
incredible so I'm really pumped about
that one what else do we got here yep
that's
right burrito bowl right there it's got
the potatoes the potato bowl which is
the burrito bowl you got the actual the
um beans right here which is so spicy
and so delicious got a little avocado if
you want to use it to cut that hot spice
I don't know if you guys like spices but
this is spicy but delicious a little bit
of salsa look at this greens leafy
greens right here okay this is insane
and I am pumped to eat it let's see what
else we have like right in here we got
some take a look oh I love that a little
bit of a dressing coupled with a rugula
right there I'm going to sprinkle a
little bit of that on there so let's
take a look at the other things too that
I got from Cafe Gratitude that are
medical medium on the venue right there
the heavy metal detox smooth at Cafe
Gratitude there it is can't get enough
of those I just can't the antioxidant
smoothie which is the cherries look at
that smoothie right there cherry and the
wild blueberry the antioxidant smoothie
love that one so good and then well
inness reset right here I'm I might
actually eat while I'm showing you these
right here I might actually do that oh
wow these I'm going to have one without
the sauce to start
[Music]
with m
those are so good and then you think
you're not eating something healthy
because it's so good you got to stop for
a second be like wait a
minute the thing is it's just so good
for you and that's the thing about the
medical medium menu at Cafe gratitud
what do we got here this is the wellness
reset tell me you're not going to do any
healing with this okay if you pre-order
this Wellness reset by the way I make 0
on it so not like I'm trying to sell you
this thing so I can make money this is
so people can get the best food on the
planet a Cafe Gratitude the best options
this is to get the menu there so people
can do some healing celery juice right
there it's part of it how cool is that
that's a big deal spice squash soup I'm
pretty sure that's that one oh yeah who
yeah that one right there is so good oh
my God what is this the um healing broth
soup right there it's a little tightly
in there nice for
protection look at that the healing
broth soup this is a cleanse a cleanse
you can do so much healing you want to
lose weight you want to actually feed
your nervous system strengthen your
immune system like rebuild like that get
toxins out this is a cleanse wow and
then we got the heavy metal detox right
here in the wellness reset there it is
and it tastes incredible getting Metals
out of the body doing some healing brain
Soother juice is in the back here can
you believe this you can actually
pre-order this Wellness cleanse if
you're in the area just do do it for
your health do it for yourself that's
the brain Soother juice right there what
is this right here dream shifter shot
look at that baby are you into dreams
are you into healing through your dreams
do the dream shifter shot it's a whole
different experience and that's in the
cleanse who puts that in a cleanse like
this oh Spirit of compassion wants that
in there for the cleanse boom craving
shifter because you might be craving
something else because you've just left
the land of all that processed food or
you left the land of all this heavy duty
food that might not have been you know
serving you while you're trying to
cleanse there it is right there craving
shifter right there that's to help to
take the edge off while you're enjoying
all these nutrients and your all these
toxins and poisons are spewing out of
your body all these old emotions that
have been in you for years dozens of
years from just hardships and different
things and adrenaline all coming out of
you you're actually really resetting
with this this actually is something so
special that they have this right here
and I have it right here I'm going to be
Downing this I'm going to start in the
morning but right now I'm really hungry
and these are cleansing and these are
healing right here and I'm like hungry
so I'm actually going to get started
right let me just open up the sauce
right here
here
nice there isn't Just Junk in here isn't
just crazy MSG all kinds of different
bad stuff people don't know about added
sugar from Bad sources like all of that
[Music]
okay
mhm after the day I
had you guys don't mind if I talk while
I'm chewing or got a mouth full Wasabi's
right there did you ever get a Wasabi
hit
did you ever get that experience you
take a little bit of the Wasabi right
I'm not going to do a lot but you put a
little bit on there cuz I don't
recommend doing a lot because it can
give you a freeze like quite a hit it's
not like a freeze freeze but it can hit
you hard so I got a big hunk of Wasabi
on
there godspeed
man that Wasabi hit
it goes right into the sinuses oh my God
it's like a
rush did you ever do
that if you haven't done Wasabi before
take it easy it's not it's the
horseradish it's not just spicy it's got
an edge to it where you got to be
careful you don't do a big hunk of it
you got to just do a little bit of it
and that's how you do
[Music]
it that one was a taser m
okay I'm going to try the potato bowl a
little
bit guys don't mind so there's a potato
right
there all right just so you know if you
like spicy that dish right there is
something you might want to do if you
like
spicy look at this kale right
here so good and you got some beans in
here
too so so
good that's edgy it's spicy but
delicious and it hits a
spot so what I'm going to do is I'm
going to hit the um I'm going to hit
these right here if you don't mind these
are the kelp noodles the Green
Papaya so that's green
papaya
right and mixed with kelp noodles the
flavors out of this
[Music]
world so
good I can't tell you all
right what this is here I'm put the
dressing on this one if you guys don't
mind my
apologies but it was a day and I was
working really really
hard so I'd like to pop the dressing on
this
[Music]
nice nice nice if you don't mind I'm
going to grab this one this is at Cafe
Gratitude by the way I know I said it
before but I can't even believe it
myself that this is at Cafe Gratitude
the medical
medium menu is insane there okay so let
me just see what I can get
here yeah this is the the massage kale
salad
my
God
flavors across the board so many of them
when you experience this you're just
going to be like oh my God like I need
this every day you should come into Cafe
Gratitude you should get one of these
every day or two of these every day or
every other day or once a week whatever
you can do because whenever you can get
there and the wellness reset experience
that because that's a whole another
level of cleansing as the wellness reset
so anyway you guys I'm going to tank
this I don't mean to be rude or anything
like that or obnoxious here but I'm
actually going to take my Chopsticks and
I'm going to relax I'm going to kick
back and I'm just going to have a really
nice dinner with all of this um I don't
know if I could eat it all in one shot
but I'm definitely going to have those
they're going to be down I'm going to
have a little bit of that probably most
of that that I'm going to maybe have
twice tonight a little bit and then a
little bit later um and I got to put the
UTA on there I saw that over there
anyway you guys are you uh coming to
cafeic gratitude because check this out
I love you guys take care of yourselves
[Music]
a