we're making nut butters
we're making nut milk
we're making wheat grass we're making
baby food puree food right
and we're making salsa
with this machine so this is going to be
really fun you guys i'm actually excited
about this is the mm 1500 everybody was
always asking me well
what about baby food and what about nut
butters and what about nut milks i'm
like you know what
let's do it all let's do it all it's the
mm-1500 and that's what it does 80 off
and you know what's incredible about
this right now
it's 80 off and you get a free cleanse
to heal book with it which is really
cool so i'm excited about that all on
its own so if you got the mm-900 that's
great i use it every single day
but we're talking about nut butters
we're talking about nut milks we're
talking about salsa we're talking about
other things we're gonna be doing
wheatgrass we're gonna be doing baby
puree food baby food or anything
you name it we're going to be doing it
banana ice cream so we'll be doing all
that so that's a whole nother level it's
a whole other thing so
anyway it's the mm 1500
it's 80 off which is actually insane
because the price is incredible right
now for this thing and you get a free
medical medium cleanse the heal book
which is awesome too
so you guys i'm glad we're here i've
been i've been really pumped up about
this in the last couple days for real
because i can't wait to show you guys
how this machine
works
it's insane so it's good to see you guys
come on so let's get started
let's do it so to begin with i'm going
to make some ice cream that's what we're
gonna do so we're gonna start with that
in a second too but i'm just gonna run
run by you guys
what i'm gonna be doing overall okay so
i'm gonna be making a fresh salsa which
is really awesome so fresh salsa here's
the machine right here can you guys see
it get a good view right there we're
live by the way on tick tock we're live
on telegram youtube rumble
facebook
we're just we're just live and
but i wanted to show you guys what i
have going on here so i'm going to make
a salsa and i want to just give you a
little window on to what i'm going to be
doing here so i want to show you this on
a close-up just to do a little close-up
test right here see what it looks like
how beautiful it is
so
that's the ingredients right there for a
homemade fresh salsa i'm going to make
with this machine which i'm really
excited about i'm also going to be doing
puree too so i'm going to be doing baby
food so take a look at that right there
these are some beautiful yams these are
already steamed so i can't wait to show
you that
that's going to be exciting right there
right going to make some banana ice
cream i'm also going to be me can you
guys see all this right here we're going
to make some wheatgrass too with this as
well so we're going to make some
wheatgrass there you go we've got some
wheatgrass sitting here
so
this is this is really going to be fun
so this is the mm 1500 good to see you
guys here we're live
christy says can't wait i'm really
excited about this seriously this is
really exciting so let's let's talk
about ice cream now you can do
ice cream in this which i love so this
machine is totally rich so you got all
these little pieces here
and so this machine does something
different and and it's really sturdy
this machine is really sturdy i love how
this thing is designed lorraine l good
to see it looks great yeah thank you
it's a snazzy machine this is gonna be
fun if anything you guys are just fun to
watch you know fun to watch fun to hang
out and do this and that's what's really
cool i've been having a lot of fun with
this machine
so for a while now i've been i've been
playing with this machine getting to
know it really good having fun with it
people requested this is why i went to
this direction because i was getting all
these dms and the dms were
well what about you know a machine that
does ice cream what about a machine that
does something else about machine that
does baby food that was a big request
right so i was like okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay the mm-1500 the mm-1500
is born now it's born some people are
like i want how can we make nut milks
how can we do this without going like
the hard real okay okay
we got to figure this out and everybody
was throwing that at me right yeah i got
the mm-900 i'm doing the celery juice
i'm saving all this money doing the
celery juice and
the mm-900 well this does celery juice
too by the way and it has the celery
juice end cap and all that but this does
all these other things everybody was
like the baby food and the nut butter
and like nut butter like
to make nut butter i'm like yeah so
we're doing it so this is the
nutritional center right nutritional
system free shipping on this it's 80 off
free shipping right now and you get the
free
cleanse to heal book right here
free cleanse the heel book let's make
some banana ice cream excited you guys
okay we got some frozen bananas right
here look at that
give you a little close-up right here
when you freeze your bananas
what i like to do just a little tip on
this freezing banana thing i like to
kind of keep them whole when i can so i
like to keep them whole like this you
know when you freeze them and not freeze
them in tiny little pieces you freeze
them in tiny little pieces they might
brown a little quicker here we go there
you if you if it's tiny little pieces
but you can't help it that's just going
to happen when you're peeling back
bananas you're just going to throw
whatever you got in there but i just try
to like peel them you know the larger
pieces you know and throw them in there
freeze them you put of course you can
use any piece of the banana it's great
but that's just a little tip
it keeps them from going
so brown in the freezer long term when
they're sitting in the freezer for a
long time you know okay so let's start
making this
all right
i'm excited
so i want to show you
the way to do the banana ice cream
okay i have it set for ice cream fruit
ice cream sorbets banana ice cream right
so that's what i have it set for right
now okay
so i'm popping some banana in here right
now so there it goes
now i gotta tell you guys this thing is
so
awesome
i don't even know what to say it comes
out with this gorgeous swirl
mean seriously
are you serious
like for real
i mean
like this isn't a magic trick right here
i'm making this banana ice cream you
guys should see what happens when you
use like frozen cherries and stuff and
use like frozen mango it's it's it's
like insane it's insane what you can do
with this now
i'll put a little bit more in here
see how it's twisting too
like
it's just so awesome
a little bit more let's let's get this
thing to the top
look at that
ice cream that won't kill you what about
that huh ice cream that won't feed your
bugs
ice cream that won't feed your
streptococcus and all your little
critters that everybody carries around
ice cream that won't feed the cold sore
virus look at that
i'm gonna shut this machine down if you
guys don't mind
this is ice cream
right there
let's take a look all right now you can
do what you want with it that is i'm
actually really impressed
and i'm laughing because that came out
really good oh my gosh meaning meaning
like you know you can pick whatever size
you want for a glass or anything like
that now look
you can do with this you can take a
spoon
and you can just also decorate or
whatever but i'm not doing that but i'm
saying you can do different things i
don't want to do that because this is
just so wicked cool right now so let me
just take a little
bit of a bite if you guys don't mind so
let's take a look
so i'm doing some banana ice cream right
here
it's nice and frozen nice and good
oh
yeah
that is good
put a nice little spoon in there there
you go all right
the thing is like this right there's no
machine out there
that i have seen
in the world that can do like a really
good ice cream sorbet
fruit sorbet
and that's dairy free i mean how
incredible right it really is
yeah so yvonne says do you freeze
bananas with the peel on off no i
actually take them out of the peel
i mean of course you could freeze your
bananas with the peel but i take them
out of the peel and i i put them i
freeze them like that right
so
so you guys this is the banana ice cream
but we have more to do we're gonna have
more fun is what we're gonna do
and let's do it and there's no
commercials no commercials nothing like
that right now we're just doing it and
we're live how cool is that because
usually be like okay heading off to the
commercial you guys we're gonna we're
gonna do the next one
watch 10 commercials no way
commercial free love it all right so
that's the ice cream now
okay
we're gonna do
some baby food
or puree
how about that
that's next
so let's let's get that going next okay
so here we go
now i got these steamed yams right here
which is really exciting
take a look
you guys look if you guys just got on
here
you're watching
this really really cool machine right
here the mm 1500 people dm'd and dm and
said what about baby food what about nut
butters what about nut milk and i'm like
are you kidding we're going to do a full
nutritional center
this thing is going to be
incredible right now it's 80
off
which
i got to tell you 80 off right now is
incredible and they give you a free
medical medium cleanse to heal
medical textbook right there so you get
it free with the juicer just letting it
up
so let's make some baby food or puree
to do that someone's meant to i know
everybody goes to dentists offices all
the time
you know i got a dental friend and
dental friend's like yeah all around the
globe everybody's just getting their
teeth just yanked out and pulled all
around the world
meat-eaters vegans everybody in the sun
they're getting all kinds of teeth
problems and then you run at this
problem where they need some puree
they just had five root canals
and all that stuff so many people in the
dentist chairs you know having problems
because they're not taking care of
themselves they don't know how to have
the trace minerals in their diet with
all their foods they're not doing celery
juice they're not doing things to
protect her teeth they're not getting
the metals out with heavy metal detox so
they're not doing that there's a whole
bunch of people in the world that you
know that aren't doing that and they're
just getting their teeth yanked out left
and right
and so hey
you got some puree for that right there
with baby food too but let's just do
this
let's do it so
here's the next thing we're going to do
let's go i'm going to turn the machine
on
and
we'll roll
it's a little bit of ice cream left in
there i mean you could always take that
out if you want but i'm gonna leave it
there
so i'm gonna run some steamed
i'm gonna actually grab that there we go
i'm gonna run some steamed
yams through here take a look
so this is for
babies and
this machine is incredible really it
really is
you know i've been using it lately and
i'm just like
it's the best part of my day
because i'm having so much fun
so
i just love it do you have the end cap
on now i don't have the celery end cap
on now so this nutritional center has so
many different setups but i don't have
that one on there i have the puree
and baby food set up right now
that's what i have
so that's which one i'm doing
so
you guys if you just if you came on just
now you just missed the ice cream so i'm
just letting you know you just missed
the beautiful banana ice cream i just
made
if you just came on now so you watch
this from the beginning if you want to
see that
all right so there we go
grab a little spoon
so we got the puree right here
incredible i'm going to shut the machine
down for a second you guys
so that is the puree
baby food yams you could do carrots you
can do other other you know other
vegetables too the whole bit
so that's just gorgeous right there
so um okay so if you guys just came on
here i'm showing you the mm 1500 comes
with the free cleanse the heel book
and you know what happens is
that you know people are like i wish i
had something that could make a nut
butter or nut milk or
also do a wheat grass or also do some
purees or ice cream or sorbets or fruit
sorbets or whatever and i'm like okay
just
your wish
is my command i'm here
so anyway
all right so let's go on to the next one
we're gonna move on you guys let's have
some more fun
so i'm gonna run a little bit of
wheatgrass juice now
it's incredible
so you guys just got here it's the mm
okay doing some wheatgrass juice the
whole bit
i'm excited we just made some ice cream
just made some yams
we just some steamed yams some some
incredible puree i'll show you if you
just got on here right now so check this
out
see more people coming on so i want to
show you they did what's incredible ice
cream right there banana ice cream dairy
free i got the baby food and puree right
there
you can do so much with this machine
it's it's insane so i'm excited come to
the free cleanse to heal book it's 80
off you've got to check it out
maybe down the road grab one whatever on
another sale some some day in the future
so
i'm gonna do some wheatgrass right now
so i have right here
the
end cap for the wheatgrass
which is incredible so let's start
running some through
now i like wheatgrass
sat says can you talk a little bit about
wheatgrass juice benefits
absolutely you know how everybody's
trying to get chlorophyll
and they're taking chlorophyll
supplements well that's a great mistake
when you separate chlorophyll
you can't gain anything from it it's
destroyed did you guys know that so if
you see people doing chlorophyll
tinctures it's a sad thing
they're being totally taken
you cannot separate chlorophyll
anything anybody ever said chlorophyll
is good for you can't receive when you
separate and extract chlorophyll from
something and then put it in a tincture
very important to know this or put it in
a bottle
so there's all these people out there
that are getting ripped off with the
chlorophyll
they think it's like great they're
making green water they're putting it in
the water but it's so sad you you guys
because
you cannot separate and isolate
chlorophyll because chlorophyll is
useless when it's isolated because it
has to have
other
chemical compounds in there so anything
you hear chlorophyll is good for
you can get it from wheatgrass
that's how it works
so
now the mm
900 is known to save you money that's a
different juicer right the 900 this is
the 1500 it's known to save you money
because it's got that celery end cap
well i'm using that end cap right here
on the 1500 so i'm juicing really
extracting from this wheatgrass
other juicers can't extract from the
wheatgrass like this juicer can the
mm-1500 so this is important to know
like you can't
you can't extract this kind of um
wheatgrass juice from other juicers i
know i've seen it out there
and and so this is yeah
so back to chlorophyll if you want to
know benefits in wheatgrass
it's everything
they say chlorophyll is good for but you
can't get any of the benefits when you
take chlorophyll by itself you can't get
the benefits it's not going to happen
they destroy chlorophyll when they
extract it
and so everybody's taken for a ride i
thought wheatgrass was bad for you kathy
got together no i never said wheatgrass
so bad for you
i i said wheat's bad for you
yeah wheat's bad for you
so all right so i'm making a wheatgrass
shot right now so i'm dropping some
wheatgrass in here
[Applause]
so what i'll i'll show you how this
works a little bit i probably have
plenty
for a shot right now but i'm just
running a little bit more through
so you guys just got on here i'm making
some wheatgrass i'm using the mm-1500
okay i'm using i'm doing the wheatgrass
part of it this tractor wait till i show
you what i have right here i can't wait
to show you how this works this is
what's incredible about the 1500
okay
so
maybe i'll run a little bit more through
now other machines won't extract as much
juice in my opinion they just won't
okay
yep
the pulp is dry
now i just want to tell you guys the
pulp is dry
do a little bit more
a little bit at a time i'm not trying to
shove it all in in one shot so
letting it take its time here we go
does this model extract more celery
juice it extracts just as much celery
juice
as the 900 so yeah so that's what's
incredible
all right so here i want to show you
guys this all right this is really cool
so we'll get a close-up on this
you're looking at the pulp in here
you're looking at how dry the pulp is
the wheatgrass pulp right
other juicers they don't do that
from what i've i've looked for and tried
and so when you're dealing with the mm
1500 or like the other mm-900 that's the
whole thing because
it would have taken so much more
wheatgrass i'm showing you the
wheatgrass in this bowl it would have
taken all that plus way more to just
make what's right there when you're
using a lot of juicers out there so
that's incredible so you're looking at
dry pulp right here
and and that's what's incredible about
that right there so this is the wheat
grass part of it if you guys just got on
here i just did the ice cream part i
just did the yams the um puree part
which is really cool i did that too and
i'll show you guys everything if you
stay on this is just a fun live right
here
and so and
look
if you stay on there's going to be more
because i'm doing more so i'm excited
about this all right
so that's the pulp right there
and there's more fun info
i'm going to show you as we go along
so you guys this if you just got on here
this is the mm1500 this is an incredible
moment right here i'm actually really
excited about this okay because i'm
making wheatgrass which is incredible
i'm making
ice cream
all right which is banana ice cream
dairy free which is really really
exciting right there if you can see it
back here right you see that i got the
puree going i'm gonna make nut milk
which i'm pumped up about i'm going to
make nut butter which i'm really pumped
up about everybody's eating nut butters
out there i mean they just eat the nut
butters
they'll have their peanut butter their
other nut butters the whole bit i'm
going to make walnut butter which i'm
really excited about so let's just get
this into a shot glass
let's go it's got its own little
strainer on top of it i'll show you this
which is incredible about the juicer the
mm-1500 it's got its own little strainer
goes right over that which is really
cool
let's get a shot glass of wheatgrass
going here
this is going to be good
okay
so let's pour this in
yeah
can do we can make it a little higher
that's some strong stuff right there
uh-huh
that's definitely some strong stuff
got some wheatgrass
i might have to take a little shot right
here
if you guys if you've ever done
wheatgrass
it's like it tastes salty and sweet and
then it kicks you
and then it kicks you at the same time
right you're just like what
oh yeah this is salty and sweet yeah
mark james says do you cook the yams
first yes you steam them
i steam the yams first okay
so that's my wheatgrass shot right there
the machine squeezes
the crap
out of that grass okay you guys just got
on here
i'm talking about wheatgrass i'm not
talking about the other grass think
about wheatgrass
right
so that's it nice and dry the pulp
i was just showing you that's what the
mm-15 it's already drying up that fast
right now that's what the mm 1500 that's
what it does it's got the celery end cap
it's got that killer end cap on it
that's the end cap right here i'm
showing you guys that's it
and
this look how dry that is
it's just it's incredible really and
then i'm squeezing every last bit out of
that wheat grass right there you guys
see on tic tac
that's my wheatgrass shot right there
wheatgrass is really powerful it's
incredible now this is a bigger machine
it's capable of doing a lot this is not
like the 900 the 900 is a celery juicer
you can put other stuff like some leafy
greens through there and everything like
i've showed you
but the mm-900 which is incredible isn't
a nutritional system of nut butters and
nut milks and
and baby food and ice cream
that's an entirely different situation
so this is the mm-1500 but the mm-1500
does celery too
it also does the celery too which is
really incredible and then it does the
wheatgrass the celery and it really
squeezes it dry which is cool
here's the thing
a lot of people requested this this is
what they requested so so yeah i want to
deliver here's the thing to understand
about why i like bmm 1500 and 900 right
food costs are going up we know that
we know food costs are going up
so
if you're going to use a weapon to heal
like you know this is like a medical
machine i've called i've called these
juicers the mm1500 the mm-900 have
called those
that's what they are medical device
right because that's what they are
i'd rather be on this medical device
here than hooked up at like in the
hospital like feed
me
me nurse
b
nurse my medication
i'd rather be
on this machine right here so
and so what i like about this machine it
saves me money every time i run
something through it because it squeezes
the hell out of it when you're running
stuff through it like for instance like
the wheatgrass
so you get more out of there and i like
that i like knowing i'm saving when
you know things are happening so
sounds like we should have waited for
the 1500 robin actually no the the 1500
1500 is for like all that other stuff
right
the 900 yeah i mean you got the 900 i
got the 900 i use the knife i take the
900 out but then i'm like you know what
i want to make a sorbet i want to make
an ice cream
so then boom i bring the 1500 out but
yeah the 1500's got so much going on
but you know it takes time for like
developments like to to make things
better and better it's not that it's
better than the 900 it's not it just
offers other things
which is really cool offers other things
it's a whole complete nutritional system
which is great
all right so
what are we doing next we're going to
make a restaurant style salsa that's
coming up now so let's do it
very excited about this
you guys like salsa
what i really love too is i'm going to
tell you right now which is really cool
about
which is really cool is people eat salsa
all the time right and when they eat
salsa all the time
they're eating the kind of salsa that
has vinegar in it so that's the sauce
that they're eating they're eating the
vinegar salsa is what they're doing and
the thing is with that is that
how much vinegar can you eat it's really
bad you lose your teeth down the road
because of the vinegar that happens all
the time so i'm not a big salsa out of a
jar unless it's vinegar free you know
what i mean so i'm not a big salsa out
of the jar kind of person at all so i
got my salsa
little clip in here all right
and that's next
let's do it
so
a couple of ways you can do salsa which
is really cool tara appleman he's not
against animal protein correct just
providing the information needed to heal
whether you eat animal protein or not
it's so true it's it's why a big part of
the vegan community hates medical medium
like hates on medical medium it doesn't
matter how many people heal from medical
medium doesn't matter how many people
get their lives back does it matter if
i'm a chronic illness for 35 years
doesn't matter if i teach doctors in
some of the biggest most prestigious
clinics around the country and around
the world about about things like what
causes all these diseases and symptoms
none of that matters to some of the
vegans which you know i we have vegans
here too in the medical meme community
but there's a lot of vegans that hate on
medical medium because
i won't do this whole protest
this big protest against animal
people who eat animal protein like i
won't hate on people who eat animal
protein so i guess there's a big part of
the vegan community that wants me
to join in and start like throwing
daggers at people who eat animal protein
and hurt their feelings and tell them
how they're doing terrible things and
there's a big part of the vegan
community that wants me to do that and
because
because i don't they'll say oh he's just
a fruit and vegetable guy or he doesn't
know anything meanwhile people are
walking out of their wheelchairs because
of medical medium information so yeah so
absolutely i support people who eat
animal protein 100 and animal protein
isn't isn't necessarily the thing that
holds people back from healing if you
want to eat animal protein you can be
vegan too and plant-based i love
plant-based foods i love plant-based the
plant-based
angle and people on plant-based all of
it everybody knows that okay so let's go
we're going to make some salsa here
let's go
so
we're going to do a little bit of salsa
here
there we go
i think i just should get that all
squared away
so what i'm gonna do is drop some
tomatoes in here
so i'm making a salsa right now if you
guys want to know now what's really cool
about the salsa
just so you know
is this salsa
is vinegar free
this salsa is raw too
so it's a raw salsa
which is great
so i'm dropping tomato in right now okay
now this is a restaurant style salsa
first of all
if you taste this salsa
without vinegar
and all that heavy duty salt like
basically they just throw a ton of road
salt in salsa
and they just vinegar it to death
and
that's not the kind of salsa that i like
it just isn't you know
so i'm doing is
i'm dropping some onion in here the link
is in the description this is the 1500
i'm making a homemade salsa but a
restaurant style
is what i'm doing i'm dropping some
onion in here i don't know if you guys
like onion
this is kind of like the sweet onion
that's what i really like right
okay so i'm dropping tomato in here i
put
a lime in here too you guys i just threw
a lime in there you know without the
peel so i just threw a lime in there
without the peel
right
i got a little bit of cilantro i'm gonna
throw in here too i'm gonna pop that in
right now a little bit of cilantro
putting that in
so i'm just really excited about this
i'm gonna drop in some more tomato
and i'll show you how i do this this is
so great
there we go
onion fan
lorraine you're an onion fan
who would have known
there's a lot of people that don't like
onion people like no i can't eat that
like why it's got an onion in it
so i'm dropping some jalapeno in there
now that's what i'm doing so i just
dropped a little bit of some jalapeno in
there
some more onion
some more tomato
right
there we go
so this is great what you do is you'll
scoop off off the top a little bit
because you'll
the tomato juice is all on the top there
so you gotta kind of give it a little
chance to get down there moving right
which is great
there you go
incredible
now
what i love about making my own salsa
is obviously eating it afterwards
so what you do is you take this part
here you mix it in here like
this and now i'm going to mix it up
and i get it
a nice presentation of it so what i'm
doing is i'm mixing this up right here
there we go
gonna get it in a nice pretty bowl you
guys
right
if you guys can see this i hope so there
you go amazing
this sauce is incredible
now this sauce is extra hot i got a nice
big piece of jalapeno
in there nice big one okay
so that's the salsa right here i'm gonna
get some chips over here
got some chips for the salsa
there you go got the salsa
okay so
see if you guys can get a close-up this
way you guys can see the chips this way
too oh there we are
and here's a salsa right here incredible
you dip your chip in
and you got this incredible salsa you
just take a look right here
this one's a little hotter
so i don't know some of you guys might
want like a really hot hot fired up
fired up
salsa like you know super hot this one
is kind of like pretty edgy it was like
a half a jalapeno pepper
it was definitely a real edgy
salsa right there and you can put some
different chips in there different ones
that you guys like or anything like that
you can do that you can you don't even
need chips if you don't want chips in
there too so keep that in mind what
machine are you using luanne asks
it's the mm-1500 link is in the
description
so the 1500 mm 1500 and it's on sale
it's 80
off
it's at omegajuicers.com
it's making salsa it's making fresh
puree it's making baby food it's making
ice cream
it's making
salsa i think i said it already
wheatgrass and guess what we're gonna be
making now nut butter
and that's coming next i think so let me
take a look so anyway we got some
incredible salsa there so let's
let's make some walnut milk you guys
now we're talking
some walnut walnut milk man now we're
talking
this is gonna get crazy now
all right
so let's do that
looking good looking good
so it's nut milk time because some many
you guys do nut milks and everything and
that's this is actually one of the
things that
that spurred this whole mm 1500 it was
the amount of requests i got about nut
milks
and even though i say to people look you
know like beezy on the nuts and be easy
on the you know that any kind of heavy
fats or oils and stuff like that and
here's what's really cool right i can't
wait to show you the nut butter part and
what bomb i'm gonna drop about the nut
butter which will blow your mind because
i can't wait to talk about that um but
the nut milks like if you're going to do
nut butters all the time
you got to do them the right way i'll
show you because there's a way to do it
that's so much different than when you
buy a store bought nut butter
and you can't miss this this is actually
health-related information really
important okay so if you just got here
this is the sale that's on you get a
free cleanse to heal book with the
juicer at megajuicers.com the link is in
the description it's 80 off cmm 1500 it
does everything it's insane so
making some walnut milk right here
so here's here's how here's what i'm
going to do right i got this beautiful
thing of walnut so let's take a look
right here
so i've got this beautiful thing walnuts
okay
and what i'm going to do is add water in
here because this is such an incredible
way to do it
so i'm going to have a little bit of
water in here
now these are soaked walnuts just so you
know so these are actually soaked so if
you take a look on the camera there they
are soaked
they're not like dry just your walnuts
these are actually soaked overnight so i
want you to know so i'm making
they're soaked and drained
so that's what i do when i make a nut
milk
soak and i drain it right and then i
have the walnuts they look like they're
dry walnuts but they're actually they're
actually damp they're actually moist and
then i put water in here again right so
now we're going to make some nut milk
someone turn on the machine let's get
going
i'm excited about this wait till i show
you the nut butter
and wait till i drop the bomb on the nut
butter thing that's interesting that i
don't know if a lot of people know some
people might know some people might not
know
no one knows i don't know actually
with that
i know a lot of people don't know so now
i'm adding in
some walnuts
right
so what i'm doing is i'm making a walnut
milk right now
so that's what i'm doing if you guys see
this here
this is what i love about the mm 1500
because i'm making a walnut milk
i'm not buying the walnut milk at the
store
i'm not doing that where i'm all of a
sudden buying you know the walnut milk
in a store or anything like that
so i'm making it right here with the
machine
so this is how i'm doing it
you like black walnuts i just saw
somebody say my walnuts are the best
the nuts are soaked
then overnight yes that's what i like to
do when i'm making a nut milk because i
like this i like to soak them overnight
right
and when you soak them overnight
they almost start to sprout so you have
to know that even if you don't see a
sprout
they're actually
getting to that edge of practically
sprouting when you soak them overnight
in fact they really do
so here we go it's coming together how
you guys on telegram are you guys doing
okay on telegram you guys doing okay on
tick tock
making a walmart walnut milk as we speak
right here
the mm 1500
i'm showing you the machine
80 off right now megajuicers.com
i mean it can do so many things it's a
complete nutritional center i'm making
ice cream i'm making sorbets like i'm
going to make a lot of stuff like i'm
probably going to try to do another live
and show you all these other different
things i can do with it which are really
really cool
like
there's so many combinations and so many
things you can do you can make a cashew
butter you can make an almond butter i
mean you can you can do a lot of
different things you can make an almond
milk
i mean you can just do a lot
with it
really incredible
i'm actually gonna
try it out for an oat milk sometime so
going to try to make my own oat milk
with it and i'm going to show you guys
one day on that one too that will
eventually come up
so i'm making some nice walnut milk
there we go
incredible
so
i'm moving this out of the way right now
okay
now this machine really pulverizes
really really really really pulverizes
just so you know i mean that's what it
that's what it really does it's so good
at that now that little bit coming out
that cream you can actually put into
your because that's what that is right
there it's a little bit of that cream
you can use back in the milk and that's
what you can do
and that's what's incredible this cream
is not nut butter and this is a nut milk
but you can actually take this the froth
over here and you can actually take that
off
i'm making a mess because i don't have a
lot of room right here with what i'm
working on but you can take that
and put it in there
just like this
so i'm gonna mix this up
clean up a little bit here so i'm not
making too much of a mess
so this is an incredible walnut milk
right here so you do a little bit of a
mix to it
like that
and then you can pour it into
the glass right here
so i'm going to do that
that's it incredible walnut milk right
there
which is amazing
so that's what's incredible about this
machine you can actually do that with it
it's really amazing so there it is right
there
so i want to show you if you guys just
got here
right
and you're like what is he doing i'm
using the mm 1500 it's on sale right now
it's 80 off comes with a free cleanse to
heal book
right
here it is
you guys know i work with omega
everybody is requesting a juicer that
did something beyond like a juicer that
did something beyond because they're
requesting so many things here's a puree
right here
for baby food i'll show you that there's
the
baby food puree right there
incredible
there's the walnut milk right here
which you can do other nut milks i mean
that's this is so incredible here's the
banana ice cream now this has been
defrosting for quite a while now but
that's the banana ice cream it's still
icy cold though do you guys like when
your ice cream starts to melt on the
sides and then you're you're getting all
that cold like ice cream that melted on
the sides and everything like that but
you still have that really icy cold
middle so you still get that brain
freeze
you still get the brain freeze because
it's still so cold in the middle right
i also did some wheatgrass too so here's
the wheatgrass shot i want to show you
guys right here okay
so that's something right there and i
want to show you the salsa as well so if
i'm just making a little room here i
mean this is incredible
so we're talking about we got the walnut
milk right here we got the banana ice
cream you could do sorbets with this
thing you've got the puree baby food
right there how incredible you've got
the wheatgrass juice shot
amazing which i showed you how dry the
pulp was and everything and then you got
of course the homemade salsa the
restaurants actually restaurant style
salsa how incredible is that so here we
go
so let's make a nut butter which i'm
pumped up about
okay everybody likes throwing nut
butters they like meaning like they like
their their type of nut butter like
which night is it almond butter i said
some other kind is it peanut butter
which is not technically enough we know
that right
but still they're like they're peanut
butter right
so what i'm making now is some walnut
butter
let's do that so that's
that's what we're making now is the
walnut butter
all right so on the walnut butter
which is gonna be fun i'm gonna use
these walnuts right here
all right
now if you guys just came on here we're
we're crushing it with some great stuff
this is so cool this is really cool
we're having a great time all right
so i'm gonna drop
some walnuts in here right now
so what i'm doing right now is i'm
making a walnut butter
there we go
now let's get a close-up on this
that'll be incredible here
look at that
so this is a walnut butter now walnuts
aren't notorious they're not notorious
for being
like
creamy that's but but that's just the
nature of the beast it's still an
incredible walnut butter in fact it's
better like this i can't wait to show
you what's going on here
so i'm dropping the walnuts in here
so making this amazing walnut butter
link is in the description you guys
right it's the mm 1500
it's also a celery juicer too
but it does all these other things which
are incredible
so what i want to show you here
is i just made
right there a walnut butter
it's like sticks of butter
but walnut butter which is incredible if
you guys take a look on tik tok you guys
can see this
i know you guys don't have that probably
that camera close up telegram you guys
see this
right so this is a walnut butter right
there
now i want to drop a bomb this is going
to be good right here this is
interesting
okay
here's what happens when you buy your
nut butters out there here's what
happens when you buy all the different
nut butters the peanut butter the almond
butter the cashew butter the tahini the
pumpkin seed butter hemp seed butter
they add oil
that's what they do
so what you're doing is you're getting a
jar
of oil
they add it into it
that's what they do
so they add it into it so that's
important to know now here's the
difference right here
this nut butter
someone didn't remove
half of the nut butter
and then added
a quart of oil
even though it's not a quart of oil
right
in a jar obviously you know that
but that's what they do you get less nut
butter
and then they add all this oil into it
that's the game that's the nature of the
game with all the nut butters still you
can buy your nut butter of course you
buy your almond butter and all these
others definitely
right
now
the walnuts were not soaked i didn't
soak them overnight to make the nut
butter
you don't have to soak them overnight
you can rinse them though so you can
give them a rinse
when you make your nut butter you could
rinse your walnuts you can rinse your
cashews you can rinse your almonds right
you can rinse them okay
but i i didn't soak them but you can
give them a rinse to get like the dust
off and stuff like that you can do that
it's a great idea and but this is a nut
butter right here so i'm gonna put it in
a little jar
so i'm putting these pieces in a jar
right here
now you can you can shape this in any
way you want you can pack it down right
you can do what you want with this nut
butter but what's incredible about
walnuts don't they're they're always
just like this in the sense where you
know when you cashews it'll be a little
bit more creamier but cashew butter you
buy
they add a ton of oil like that's that's
real like what they do it's crazy but no
one talks about it yeah they'll add
cashew oil they'll add walnut oil
they'll add almond oil but they're
adding all this oil is what they do
right
so that's how it's done
okay
so you can pack down your nut butter in
here in a nice little jar if you want
right and then get the rest of it in
here
so what happens is you get kind of
ripped off they put all this oil in it's
all oily
it's not actually good for you that way
when there's that much oil in it
right
if you soak the nuts they'll get a
little softer but i'd say rinsing them
is great too
but you don't want it when you're making
nut butters you don't want to soak the
nuts long because it makes your nut
butters go bad later you don't want them
like that you just want to give them a
quick rinse or you can go with them dry
i like giving it one rinse but not
soaking it so that's a jar of walnut
butter right there and you can see where
that moisture is there where like
there is that oil there that's naturally
in that walnut butter you see how it's
starting to get that like creamy like
see that creamy
but but just so you know
there wasn't four ounces of oil added
into this and put into the big jar so
you go to the store you buy the jar and
you're buying a hunk of oil that was
added after the fact which is actually
kind of a little bit scary you know when
i think about it so that's why i like
making my own right there
this is raw too this is not roasted nut
butter and yes you can you can throw
your almonds or walnuts or anything in
the oven you can toast them and roast
them and then throw them into the
mm-1500 roasted after they've been
cooled or something you can do that
that's fine but that's your walnut
butter right there
and you can put a cap on it put it in
the fridge and you're good you got your
you got your walnut butter right there
and you can put a nice little cap on it
and then it goes right in the fridge
incredible
so you guys if you just came on here
i'll give you a rundown on everything i
just made which is really incredible
it's fun it's exciting
i made a salsa which is really awesome
right there
i'm going to try that salsa right now
that's hot
that jalapeno
that was a hot pepper that's incredible
that's amazing actually and then you got
the puree you got the baby food right
there
right that's the yams
that's a salsa you guys already see the
walnut butter you guys already got that
down
right
you guys on tick tock see that telegram
and see the walnut butter
i got the wheatgrass g shot
right there
that stuff is powerful
right
like i was saying before you don't want
to separate the chlorophyll
you want the wheatgrass chlorophyll in
its complete chemical composition you
isolate chlorophyll and it dies
it can't do anything because your body
will see it and be like i don't know who
you are
your body
when when you isolate chlorophyll from
any fruit vegetable not fruit any
vegetable or leafy green or wheatgrass
if you isolate chlorophyll or barley
grass shoots power if you isolate it and
it goes in the body isolated your body
seems like i don't know what you are
you're missing everything else to tell
me what you are
so that's why
i don't like the chlorophyll drops they
don't work they never did i've been
saying that for 30 years
okay
we got the wheatgrass juice shot and
then we got the ice cream right here
so which is great got that nice banana
ice cream you can make purees you can
make anything you want there that's
that's awesome and then
we're talking about nut milks from this
machine too we got the walnut milk
right here
so that's right there too incredible you
guys see that on tick tock see it on
telegram you got the nut milk right
there let's get that in the window i
think that was what we made
we got it all going on here we go
there it is you guys are looking at it
all close up you guys on tick tock do
you see it telegram do you see it
mm-1500 right here people requested all
these things this is also a celery
juicer you can run celery through this
it's got the celery end cap
and which is which is incredible
because it's that dry pulp right there
see that wheatgrass pulp that dry
wheatgrass pulp right there
that's what saves the money with the
mm-900 and the mm-1500
which is incredible so you got the
that's the pulp i just showed you
you guys incredible so link is in the
description check it out 80 off edie has
a question how long does the butter
last in the refrigerator
he don't last a long time i mean
a month it'll last a month it's not
going to oxidize if it's in the fridge
it'll definitely last 30 days in the
fridge for sure there's no question
probably longer
which is amazing anyway you guys
i'm gonna go live again i'm gonna put
tick tock back on i'm gonna put telegram
back on i'm gonna put ig on
and we're gonna go live in a little
while i'm really excited we're gonna do
it again
and have some fun exciting incredible
guys
check it out when you get a chance you
get a free cleansing heel book it's the
mm 1500
right the link is in the description
it's 80
off
how much is the machine with the 80 off
take a look go and check it out you'll
see all the information in the details
go to megajuicers.com so you can see all
the details
and then you'll see in there anyway you
guys i love you greatly i am going live
again in a little while hope you guys
join me we're going to have