on youtube live on facebook live live
live live live
we're live because that's
the way i like to do it um anyway i'm
making
mango salsa romaine boats i'm talking
about
death by a thousand cuts because it's
critical and there's a lot of different
aspects of it
that i missed okay that's another thing
too we're also
gonna be you know what i love about live
there's a coat hanging right here in
this coat hanger
all right there's a coat hanger up here
i just saw it
because we're live that's why anyway
death by a thousand cuts
really important to know how we're
getting cut
what's happening i got some cuts over
here you don't see them maybe
i got some cuts over here i'm gonna pull
them out got cuts all kinds of places
right
because that's how it works with chronic
illness you get cut you get cut you get
cut cut then 995 cuts in and boom boom
gonna listen i got the mangoes here red
onions i got
i'm gonna talk about triggers too you
guys triggers
romaine uh lettuce right here tomatoes
limes cilantro i got the wyman's wild
blueberry juice because everybody's now
asking me about the shots
you know how do you do the shots how do
you do the shots how do you do the shots
that's what everybody's saying
so i'm going to show you how to do this
shot it's really simple
but i take the while the wild blueberry
shot every single day like every single
morning
i take it sometimes earlier in the
morning then i sometimes take it later
in the morning
and um but you guys know that um working
with these guys
okay and because i want to make sure we
don't lose
this precious resource scares me because
it's one of these things where anyone
brave enough to make
this quality this quality and a wild
wild
blueberry juice it's not easy to make
that's not a joke so
i want that product around for people i
consider that a medical medium tool
and i'm working with them i endorse them
just wholeheartedly officially endorse
them
uh anyway i'm just letting you guys know
what's up so anyway i'm gonna do the
wild blueberry shot in a little bit too
so you guys if you guys just came on
here making the mango
salsa romaine boats i'm talking about
death by a thousand cuts i'm talking
about triggers
that's a big deal triggers okay so
covering that too
i'm glad you guys are with me uh you
seem fine to me is here chris
you're here austin austin good to see
you
ashley kevin good to see you glad you
guys are coming on
this is great i'm anthony i went to the
doctor yesterday and
asked for half vials and the doctor
looked at me
and said we don't do half [ __ ] but yet
but yet
you know what's crazy austin is there's
a lot of people saying they're asking
their doctors can can you do half
vials and they're saying no problem and
a lot of phlebotomists now are saying
hey no problem
and it's really difficult when they do
that because yeah of course you can do
half files right
of course there's the half files out
there of course in
because if anybody just got on here
right
this you know this episode that the
episode is medical mean podcast at apple
podcast i talk about blood draw
bloodletting and vampirism and
i talk about too much blood is taken
which you lose
your cbc cbc you were good to me
but now bye bye bb see you later cbc
gone gone
and that's what they do they remove
remove remove they remove
um and and when they remove
you're you're losing that immune system
a little bit a little bit a little bit a
little bit and then a lot more of it a
lot more of it and the bone marrow has
to kill itself
to actually try to restore and recreate
and recreate um uh
the you know recreate the immune system
and then we get in trouble
so the bottom line is um you know
i in the episode if you guys want to
know i talk about how you ask your
doctor for half files ask your
phlebotomist do have files
the lab will take quarter vials we've
had rns on instagram
come on and say that yeah we take
quarter vials
at our lab you know we'll take half
files um
so yeah it's really important to know
the stuff uh
so we're making mango salsa remain boats
all right and we're talking about what
you know austin asked for half files
it's it's not easy you know it's not
easy when that happens i i've
i've deborah hi anthony not feeling my
best today
so if the doctor doesn't take look if
it's if it was me right
listen to your doctor always listen to
your doctor all you guys but if it was
me
like me what i would do is be like okay
well you take full vials you don't take
half files
all right well then you know i'm gonna
give you two to three vials
that's what i would do um i'll give you
two to three vials if you only take full
vials i'll give you two full vials
uh three full vials the most um
listen to the podcast and all that for
sure
deborah hi anthony not feeling my best
today oh no
no you know i mean that's not good
that's not good
deborah you having one of those days
yeah yeah you know it's three steps up
two steps back down right so three steps
up
and then two steps back down right
but what happens is when you start
feeling a little better
on your three steps up you start doing
more
and what spirit of compassion has always
told me is when
and then people start doing a little bit
more than they normally do but they
but but you know it's hard to tell but
you do a little bit more and
then you feel like you get kicked back
down again and
but then you're down again down again
for a little bit and then you go back up
but then you go back up a step a little
higher
and you know and there's this process
you're climbing a slaughter you're
three steps up two steps back
right three steps up and that's how
healing works in the body and there's
nothing more
there's nothing more you know as far as
like
feels disappointing when you feel like
you're going back a little bit
or you're having one of those days or a
few days where you're like i just don't
feel good
you know i don't feel good and it's
really hard endeavor just
just hang in there hang in there because
when
when you're when you're when you're
working on your healing process your
body loves you
it loves you unconditionally it knows
you're working with it our bodies know
their
our bodies know that we're working as a
team with our body and our body loves us
for it and is looking out for us
so just hang in there okay
um anthony how do we take the shots
let's talk about it
um so here's what i do okay
i mean in the morning if if i don't get
my celery juice done yet
you know i mean it happens things are
going crazy
because the celery juice is a powerful
healing tool we know that right
but i'm using for my friends and family
the wild blueberry juice is a powerful
tool too so it's one you know it's one
of those things i just love tools
you know and it matters so what i do is
um
in the morning if if for some reason i
didn't have my
celery juice yet right and i'm in a
place where
um where the the morning's coming on
it's getting late you know it's getting
late in the morning late in the day and
i'm like whoa
or lately we're late morning now i'll
make sure i get a couple of shots in
um sometimes i'll do them early in the
morning too
right so what i do is
i actually get in touch with the energy
here with what's in here so that's how
i do it right and i didn't tell you guys
because
um i had i i've had moments in my life
right
that i've been blessed to sit in a wild
blueberry field and it's something that
i can't even tell you right because the
plants are
thousands of years old and thousands of
years old
and they've been doing their thing every
single year they come up out of the
ground you can't kill these things
they're
they're so potent and powerful in my
opinion it's like adaptogenic times 10
right
and so i've had the experience of
knowing what it's like to cut to lay in
the field and meditate
to meditate in wild blueberry fields
where i'm just
laying in them and you can feel the
energy you've got
the earth and the blueberries are all
around you and they're coming up
around your arms and it's it's
incredible yeah you turn
blue and you got to pick the clothes you
want to wear that day if you do it
because
those things are going to be blue
they're just going to be blue right
and uh because you're laying on those
berries you're crushing those berries
right
and i've been there and you don't have
to have that experience right
because it's in the bottle
what we're not that's how i think about
it you know it's in the bottle
and so i do this little meditation
around
um the wild blueberry juice is what i do
and it's
i sit i sit quietly for a moment right
and you can lay down
too but i sit quietly in a spot and i
close my eyes or i'll lean back in a
nice comfy chair
um or lay down on the floor or on the
couch or something
and i'll think about the power these
wild blueberry plants have being around
for thousands of years and
how they feed all the animals they feed
the deer
they feed the moose they feed the bears
they feed the foxes right and i think
about all that and i think about
like all the hungry animals that when
these blueberries start coming up these
wild blueberries this isn't
this isn't cultivated blueberry the wild
blueberries when they're coming up
in the fields i think about the foxes
going through the field right
and they're hungry because it's not easy
to get food for for wild animals it's
not easy at all
the foxes will just sit in the field and
they'll eat and i'll remember this and
i'll be thinking about this right
and if you haven't experienced it it's
okay you can just think about it and
and so what happens is that um that's
how i get in touch
with the wild blueberry the energy of it
and that's part of
how i take the shots okay uh which is
really
really big part of it so then of course
i open up the bottle
right and i think about the color
and i'm there's you can't juice
a cultivated blueberry and get that
color
it's not gonna happen you know and from
what i've seen in my opinion and what
i've seen and what i believe because
i've
juiced myself so like regular cultivated
blueberries have juiced everything right
and so i think about the color and
where's that what
what is that color like what that's
the power color right that's what that
is
so i connect like my mind and body
to what the reality is of what i'm
seeing
so that my immune system so everything
in my body is starting to like
resonate to be like whoa are we gonna
receive
that color those pigments like are we
going to receive those pigments
so that's what i do you guys can do
something different if you like and you
can do
any you don't have to do any of this you
can just take your shot
but i'm just saying so and then i pour
the shot
with all of this in mind so i connect my
body to what this really is
and you know and i and i really kind of
sing a blessing is what i do because i'm
like well
you know how how is it possible when i
was younger
and i think about those blueberries in
the field that they're so
hard to harvest and to
bring to a market as it is never mind
actually
having that juice and this is all part
of how i take the shots you know and
then i
send it down like a tequila but i've
never had tequila
so anyway as i do a shot every single
day
some days i'll take two shots and there
are days where i take three shots and
i'm like
you know but because
huh hello
what's going on huh
um how come wyman's isn't organic
do they use pesticides so i can answer
that
okay so wyman's is a wild food it's a
wild food
and so wild blueberries they take care
of themselves
for almost all of of what they need they
take care of themselves
and a cultivated blueberry you have to
whether it's organic a cultivated
blueberry whether it's organic
or it's conventional it has to be
sprayed
three times a week so the organic water
the organic blueberries
they have to be sprayed the organic
the cultivated organic blueberries have
to be sprayed spray spray
the cultivated blueberry whether it's
conventional
it has to be sprayed spray spray right
so and the thing is with sprays and you
have to realize
that sprays are a catch-22 so the
organic sprays are a catch-22 and i
talked about
how what's in those things but what
wyman's does is because the crops take
care of themselves
they can pick and choose where they they
spray and they don't use pollinator
killers
and so it's only a part of a crop
certain time of year or one year and a
year to go by and they don't do it all
another year could go by and they don't
don't do it all
and they're barry's got the zero
pesticide residue
because of this because a wild food
sustains itself and takes care of itself
the thing is with wild foods that
are really important wild foods like the
wild blueberries are better than
um organic so that's another thing too
so wild food is better than organic so
that keep that in mind
and so it's incredible about this food
is because
the plants protect themselves to such a
degree
they that you don't have to be spraying
spraying spraying spraying spring
springs brain because that's it
and that's what's incredible about it so
if you get like a fly that comes from
south america and it's once every couple
of years and it gets bad at
one little area of a crop or something
and then they got to spray but they
don't use the
pollinator killers and now vegetables
are different
the conventional vegetable conventional
vegetables conventional fruits
they get sprayed three four times a week
with pollinator killers
and really bad sprays just three four
times a week
whole entire different thing and uh but
anyway
some info there how do you get it
um so you can go to shop.wymans.com so
shop.wymanswymans.com
so that's where you can go making a
mango salsa romaine
boats so that's a little bit on how i
take my shots
and we're in this we got the mangoes we
got the tomatoes we got the lettuce
we're gonna do this we're talking about
death by a thousand cuts
and so and what i love about death by a
thousand cuts is there's things you can
do
to slow down the cuts or stop the cuts
or reverse the cuts
you know and that's important too
because we're doing all these things
that aren't so good okay we're doing our
colognes and perfumes right
we got our colognes we got our perfumes
and that one that one's just brutal
right there
you guys that one's bad too i mean this
stuff is so harsh but this stuff lowers
the immune system so clones perfumes
lowers the immune system that's a cut
you just got cut that's how it works
right so you got that right there maybe
you're doing tuna
in a can right you got the metal from
the can you got the merkur from tuna
the mercury that's a couple of cuts
right there okay
and that's important too um
yeah and that you know it's it's
important to know
right so we got that and wondering what
other cuts are you doing right
are you doing some eggs yeah death by a
thousand cuts
it's no joke because what happens with
eggs is they feed all the bugs that keep
people sick
you're sick with a symptom you got
different symptoms you got different
conditions
i talk about the pathogens involved for
those symptoms and conditions and then
we're eating eggs and then eggs
so i didn't ruin anybody's eggs they
were ruined before
really important to know so um
these are all just a couple of cuts
right here
right then you got your you're drinking
out of your cans
throughout your life you're drinking out
here soda cans you drink even your
healthier
beverages and soft drinks like i'm at
the store and
hey this one says organic and it's in a
can this one says
you know no no no bad stuff in here and
it's in a can
right this one's you know blah blah blah
but what happens is that
you're doing the aluminum that's another
cut but they add up and they add up and
they add up and they add up and they add
up
and that's what happens lunella says
foraging for wild foods
should be should be the new grocery
shopping that would be incredible it'd
be absolutely amazing
anyway you guys with the wild wyman's
blueberry juice shop
s-h-o-p dot wyman's w-y-m-a-n-s
dot com so that's important and then
there's other
cuts too right when you get your blood
tested
right they take a lot they'll take 60
milliliters 70 milliliters 100
milliliters 150 milliliters
100 you know 170 milliliters 220
milliliters 380
400 milliliters of blood and then
they're removing your immune system
that's a huge
trigger and then you go backwards
backwards backwards backwards listen to
the podcast episode
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
blood draw blood letting
are really important to know and i
because i talk about how to rebuild how
to protect yourself before you go into
your blood tests and blood
uh draws um susanna said 12 bottles of
wyman's are on their way
to me april 19th incredible
incredible i'm supporting these guys i'm
trying to get the word out there
that's what i'm doing so i'm doing
everything i can to get the word out
there for these guys because
um like i said when i just don't want
this to go away that's
my my thing where i just don't want it
to go away so i told him i'll work with
you guys
i'll start working with you guys i'll
endorse you guys i'll i'm in it i'm in
it
i don't want that stuff disappearing
because you know and and because it's so
potent it's so so good and i talked
about how how i believe
therapeutically and i use it
therapeutically for my family my friends
that's just what i do anyway let me
start making a little food we'll talk
about some stuff
um i got some mangoes here now this
that one might be i mean these could be
over ripe i got to see what i got in
here i got a bunch of different mangoes
here
so i'll see what i have
i'm cutting a mango right now
that mango looks pretty good
all right so you guys
gonna read a little bit about triggers
for you too so i'm just
so i just cut these like this and i'm
going to scoop them out
danielle says not sure i agree with the
eggs lots of health people
nutritionists etc recommend eggs to
healthy protein
it's so frustrating when all the
information is so conflicting
uh yeah no i
hello yeah yeah
now i heard what danielle said uh-huh i
get it because everybody's talking eggs
yeah they thought lots of things were
healthy throughout the years
uh-huh they thought lobotomies were
healthy yeah
every health professional every
dietitian every doctor
every professional every psychiatrist
every therapist believe
that removing the front of the
brain from a young girl because she had
anxiety
was the best way to fix her yeah yeah
it was it was it was always like that
hundreds of thousands of of girls
young women their the front of the brain
was
torn off yeah they had a probe go up
their nostril
right to the front of brain
yeah this isn't funny because
it happened and it's real every health
professional
thought it was the correct protocol and
procedure
yeah exactly for sure
i know people protect their eggs because
every health professional believes that
they're good for us
but i i think what people don't realize
is that
so i think what people don't realize
is that sorry guys hold on a second
sorry i think that people they don't
realize a couple of things here that
basically what happens is that here's
how it works with eggs okay
don't worry i hold on there's a call
coming in
oh i'm in between calls right here hold
on hold on
hello yeah i work at the egg factory
uh-huh what do you mean on my watch
there's missing eggs uh
two months ago eggs were taken from my
watch
i was on the watch i punched my card i
did my
you didn't hear anything no no you
didn't hear anything
yeah i took a sick day today yeah am i
really home
yeah i'm really home i am i didn't take
the eggs
you're gonna fire me i've been working
at the egg factory for a long time
[ __ ] guys guys be quiet guys be quiet
no no i was just talking to a friend of
mine yeah dropped me off some chicken
soup
i mean dropping off some some soup
yeah no anyway no i didn't steal the
eggs
okay so just kind of leave me alone all
right i got another call on the other
line
hello well see what you don't know
is that everybody that's sick with
chronic fatigue syndrome and
fibromyalgia and multiple sclerosis and
so many other different diseases and
conditions
have bugs one of the bugs is called
epstein-barr
it was raised in the labs inside the
eggs so what they did was
they cut the top of the egg and they put
the epstein bars
and all the different pathogens in the
egg and
that's what they did and then we eat the
eggs
and we feed any bugs that are inside of
us
and that's how it works so the worst
thing you could ever do is offer eggs
for
women with pcos and endometriosis it
makes it worse
if you have if you tell women with pcos
to eat more eggs
their androgen is going to get out of
control it's not going to be fixable
eggs are that that harmful
for women when they're sick with chronic
illness
one of the medical medium tools was to
remove eggs
so that women can have a chance to heal
different conditions
so i get it i know that every health
professional says that
but just so you know that the lobotomies
is just one out of hundreds of examples
i can use
where every health professional in the
world agreed with it
uh-huh yep now i got to put these guys
down they're starting to get
starting to get a little out of control
oh okay
i'll see you guys later i got to put
these guys back
all right we got to stop fooling around
we we need to
make these mango boats before it gets
late
kelly says doubtful it works like that
you mean at the egg factory
or or do you mean eggs
actually it does work like that very
important
to know okay so i'm going to use another
mango
um it you got to listen to the egg pot
podcast
so what happened was all the different
pathogens that we have today
were raised in eggs okay and
i'm going to give you a little 4-1-1
about how it works
the chronic illness is as bad as it is
today because of this
so there was no other food that would
proliferate a pathogen in a controlled
environment right
so you couldn't inject a pathogen
in an animal and then have control over
it
because the animal's immune system deer
first flying everywhere so i'm gonna
have deer for
in my food but you can't control the
environment so
what happens with the medical industry
the reason why they didn't use animals
as the proliferator okay is because and
i see a medical doctor's on too
and you guys there's a lot of medical
doctors that leave
comments and just so you know they're
blocked not by me
but by facebook and instagram i'm
letting you know okay
um we've we've we've learned that
recently
that there are dozens and dozens of
doctors
and nurses that hey i'm a doctor and
everything else and i never
see their comment but i now have some
friends
that are going to be screen shooting
them and all that stuff so they don't
feel like
i'm actually not answering their
questions they always let dr fawn in
which is amazing only eggs okay
are eggplants amazing so um so here's
the difference
in they have to use the egg because the
egg doesn't have its own immune system
it doesn't so they used it as a living a
living creature basically
to in to inject pathogens so they can
proliferate but the egg
the reason why they proliferate in the
egg because the egg doesn't have its own
immune system and the proteins are
undeveloped
really important to know and that's the
difference between surviving when you
put a pathogen
in an animal versus thriving they needed
it to survive
to thrive is what they needed it because
when they injected them to animals
the animal's immune system would take
control over the pathogen and they would
lose control over the pathogen you see
how it works
so what they do is they raise the
pathogens in eggs
then they injected those pathogens into
animals for experimental
hello why am i not making the mango
salsa
boats yet i don't know just kind of
fooling around
put down the deer all right
all right guys that's the medical
industry they don't want me
talking about the pathogens inside the
eggs and how everybody gets sick
and uh huh it's ahead of the medical
industry
they want me to put the deer down and
stop talking about what they do
they want me to just make they want me
to just be a food dummy
mm-hmm yeah did you just say food dummy
they want to be want me to be a food
dummy you know like they just want me to
talk about the health benefits of a
tomato
but only the science-based ones
not even the real ones yeah they want me
to just they want me to
play around with food only and not tell
you guys the truth about anything
are you done i don't know how they got
this number
dr sherry green
yep cruella dr sherry green good to see
you
amazing yeah all
i'm right make some mangoes right here i
got listen to the podcast the egg
podcast seriously
if you guys have any doubts listen to it
medical mean podcasts at applecop
podcast
please listen to it if you can so i'm
what i'm gonna do
is i'm gonna um i'm making some mangoes
mango pieces in here making a mango
salsa and it's gonna be good
okay
teresa or the virus if it's in us
and the eggs cooked would it be active
well yeah the eggs could be cooked it's
still an under
underdeveloped protein and the
underdeveloped protein is what the eggs
was what sorry the pathogens know
exist like that's what they've been feed
on pathogens are
a pathogen that's been raised
never gets killed off right
it gets in the people and then when it
passes on to more people
it still has all the information of how
it was raised to begin with so it
already knows that it eats eggs so
and um yeah it's just what happens is
i'm not
i'm not anti-animal protein i'm not
anti-vegan and plant-based you guys you
guys
aren't in uh you guys aren't at a vegan
channel right now this is important to
know you're not at a vegan channel where
i'm gonna throw this vegan propaganda at
you and you're not
you're not at an animal protein channel
or i'm just gonna throw all this vegan
produce
this bad vegan you know the the animal
protein people
tell all the mommies that they're
starving their children feeding them
lettuce
and the you know the vegans and the
plant-based people telling all the
animal protein people that you
you're soulless because you're killing
animals and animals have souls and all
this
stuff i'm not into that i'm i'm into
tools you're right
i'm into tools like that's a tool right
i'm into
the three steps up two steps back three
steps up then you're healed boom gone
i'm into this everybody gets sick animal
protein people get sick plant-based
people get sick they both get sick
and they both don't know what to do okay
if your plant-based stay plant-based
that's what i recommend if you're animal
protein-based and that's what you love
in all that you stay
protein base you can you know but but
you know it's important to know where
you are right here someone might be like
all right all right he's he's okay he's
gonna
he's all about just it's all vegan or
something no
but i i recommend if you're sick and you
got symptoms and conditions i recommend
as a
animal protein person to avoid eggs and
i recommend
as a plant-based person to avoid
going back to eggs because guess what
plant-based people do
here's what plant-based people do
hello huh you've been plant-based
really for what a year okay
let's go how's it working for you you
what's what's wrong
you're all sudden got fatigued and your
teeth are starting to have problems
really you think it's really the
plant-based thing
you do you're eating eggs now and fish
you're eating eggs and salmon
so you went back to eggs okay all right
i know a lot of vegan people run back to
eggs a lot of plant-based people run
back to eggs the first thing they run
back to it's why a lot of plant-based
people don't make fun of eggs
they know it's a comfort food and they
run back to it i know i know
but are you sure it's the plant-based
diet doing it or are you doing the
plant-based diet
wrong for what you need in your
condition because that's what happens to
animal protein people
keto people run from this ray run for
their lives from keto
animal protein people who are eating all
clean they all of a sudden get sick they
don't know why they got sick and they
get scared and they think they need to
go vegan
everybody's running across to the other
side all the time i think
it's more about tools it's more about
tools
yeah um yeah
so there you go
all right guys i gotta still make this
mango salsa
mango salsa coming our way
um
it's gonna be good knowing the cause of
why you're sick is critical
right that's critical that's the big one
right there
it's critical to know why you're sick
i'm just telling you right now you guys
that's a big piece of it
knowing why you're sick okay
and um so i am in the cleanse of heal
book real quick
spirit of compassion has always said to
me throughout the years of helping so
many people heal that knowing the true
cause knowing the true cause of
why you're sick is half the battle one
if you don't know the true cause of why
you're sick we're gonna be in trouble
i'll say it again if you don't if you
don't know
why you're sick we're gonna be throwing
darts at barns
guessing games running around trying to
heal
trying to fl this doctor that doctor we
don't know what's going on that's what's
gonna happen
knowing why you're sick is critical or
you're guessing games are happening and
guess what happens to guessing games
you might get a little better because
you're cleaning up your diet
right taking a few different random
sorted supplements that maybe a
practitioner has given you right
but you end up sick again and again
and again as time goes on then you're
confused at 10 more doctor's offices
that because unless you know why you're
sick
are you going to be able to do what you
need to do and medical meme
information is about a thousand
protocols i call it basically instead of
a thousand cuts
it's a thousand ways to heal not a
thousand ways to die
right and so spirit of compassion has
always said to me throughout the years
helping so many people knowing the true
cause of why you're sick is half the
battle one you ready for this one
ready for this one okay knowing what to
do
knowing what tools to do right
celery juice you know what a heavy metal
detox smoothie
right wild blueberries right knowing
what tools to do
what to take and how to apply those
tools is the other half battle one
because
that's how you get better and that's why
medical medium information has helped
more people in chronic illness than
anywhere else in in our history yet
yeah sure you can go keto if you're not
that sick and get some results drop a
little weight and then you're on it for
a while yeah but man
you get sick sick you get sick
and then and i'm talking about vegan
keto too and you get sick sick
then it's just like everybody's freaking
you know and
and so it's important and medical medium
information is about advanced
information so you know why you're
sick knowing the true cost all that's
critical
that's and you guys uh that's cleanse
the heel but i'm in medical medium
the new edition letting you know if you
haven't seen it already making the
mango salsa romaine boats if you guys
don't know the book it's mind-blowing
be open-hearted hey how you doing
guessing games for years exhausting
the phone's ringing
be open-hearted i didn't hear the phone
ring either
yeah guessing games for years
i can only imagine like seriously like
all kids decide about everything
like i get it because
people don't get it like the financial
stress
with guessing games right the time
involved
and then your heart gets set on
something is this going to help
is this going to help and then you feel
let down
and you crash right and it's an
emotional rollercoaster ride and people
don't get it
and then it's the people that don't
really understand why you're sick just
go to the doctor
right like be open-hearted you know
right go to you go just go to the doctor
you'll be fixed yeah
and you get people that say that right
you get people that say
what's wrong with you you're sick just
go to the doctor people that
don't know what it's like to be in your
shoes right and they don't like they
don't know what it's like to be
anybody's shoes and they're just like
well all you got to do
why aren't you at the doctor's it's just
getting fixed like be done with it
like what do you mean you saw four
doctors oh i don't want to hear it
that's what people say
like what do you mean you saw all these
doctors
so you know and and and i get it just
just the guessing games and the years
going by
and just knowing that i'm with you man
it's not with you okay
um
guys just know i'm with you sisters and
brothers okay
i just got to cut open one more mango
here
be open-hearted i i understand and
um you're amazing for
all that you've been through
for actually persevering persevering and
hanging in there
so i'm just i'm just finishing up this
mango
salad here well mango salsa and i'm
going to actually put it on some nice
leaves here dr faun
he would say get the heavy metals out
and use antiviral protocols in his books
genetic illnesses are not what you think
they are conventional medicine
has no treatment other than treat
symptoms it's coming from an incredible
medical doctor by the way
yeah like
very wise words dr font
um you guys have just uh
doing a little bit more mango and then
we're good there you go
so i got my mango salsa in the works i'm
very happy about this
they blame they blame it on your body
they tell you it's genetic
they tell you your body's your body's
immune system is attacking yourself
it's attacking your organs your glands
you've got if you've got thyroiditis
you've got hashimoto's or anything well
then that's your body
the best thing they can come up with is
that your body attacking the thyroid
right but that's not really what it is
that's not what it is uh oh the onion
i know i'm gonna pay for this um
they don't they don't talk about all the
radiation exposure we have the toxic
heavy metals the cloned perfumes that
actually poison us
they don't teach us about clones and
perfumes i mean people who are sick
they're they're they're going downhill
after spraying their perfumes on them
on themselves no one teaches anybody
about this stuff
it's really sad so i'm doing some onion
is what i'm doing right here
inside this salsa
okay a third of a cup of finely chopped
onion is all you need
so i'm just doing a little bit of onion
for this
so this this dish is
just such a light incredible dish you
can eat this dish all day long you can
make a big bowl of it what i do
just so you guys know is i make a huge
bowl of this one right
and i just put it on lettuce all day
long like i have it sitting there in the
kitchen right
sitting there just waiting for me you
know just starting to put it together
now
um and it's just so it's so amazing to
have
lunell trolls don't bother to first
learn the information
course not thank god for that because
there's so much of it
that's how you know they're trolls sick
people learn
all of it it's wise words loon
and i know you i know you've been
through a lot
you know i know like many of you guys i
mean
all of you been through a lot
i mean it's not easy when you've been
sick you know and
why isn't science fixed it why hasn't
science fixed it did you guys see the
tick tock
um tick tock um what is it
not episode what do you call it tick
tock post i did
today check it out if you can if you
don't have tick tock don't worry
but check it out right and it's it's
like why didn't
science aren't they supposed to have all
the answers right then some troll throws
a scientific study at you
right here's a scientific study eggs are
good for you it's the last thing you
need to hear
here you are sick and you'll be told
eggs are good for you
maybe you're getting out maybe you're
lacking protein how stupid is that one
for so long now
meanwhile science science also says that
eggs are high in cholesterol and give
you strokes and heart attack
isn't that funny so who's right who's
wrong
what's science why are health
professionals saying eggs are so good
for you when science is actually saying
they give you strokes and heart attack
right
and then science will come up out of
nowhere and be like you know what
actually you know eggs are good it's a
good protein
it's like which way you're gonna go man
which way
right
doing some tomatoes in the salsa gonna
do a little bit more
i think the bottom line is when you get
sick right
all bets are off all bets are off
that's it it's like man
it's just about getting the information
and getting better
right isn't it amazing that you think
people think that
if you don't have a letter after your
name
anthony williams dsbb
yes
phd md whatever i mean they think that
if you don't have something after your
name health coach whatever if you don't
have something after your name right
then don't listen to that person right
it doesn't matter how much experience
they have how many doctors they
they've helped over the years doesn't
matter
it doesn't matter of anything right
doesn't matter the most powerful people
in the world
have reached out to you for the last 30
years because they've had access to
every single doctor there is
and all the money in the world to go to
every place fly around the world but yet
they're
at the medical mediums door right but
that doesn't matter because i don't have
any letters after
after my name gotta have letters right
letters mean everything like i couldn't
have got some letters after my name
well i couldn't have gone to medical
school
chose not to dr sherry green m
d exactly all bets are off when it takes
you
down and traditional docs have no answer
dr sherry green a medical
amazing medical doctor amazing medical
doctor
um okay so we're coming along now let's
get some cilantro in here
i don't need a lot of cilantro but yet i
put a lot of cilantro in
healing tulle oh well wait a minute
didn't we know cilantro was good for us
so
wrong anthony wrong aw uh
that's no healing tool because we
already knew cilantro is good for you
but what people don't realize is i'm
talking about eating cilantro as a leafy
green
and that's a medical medium tool nobody
knew that like eat it as a leafy green
like
have this even more anyway guys making
this real quick
[Music]
there we go
just squeeze some lime in here put a
teaspoon of
uh cumin in here
that was give or take a little bit you
know cayenne don't you don't have to put
too much i like cayenne
i put a lot i also put a lot by accident
but then i end up
liking the fact that i did that i'm
gonna squeeze some lime on here you guys
there we go
yep that's a spoon
someone said to me for a guy that
doesn't like toxic heavy metals you eat
with all that silverware and
again guess what i take more atomy than
goes in
more out of me than what goes in i do
the heavy metal detox smoothie i use the
vimergy products
that's the bemergy spirulina the vimergy
barley grass juice powder
so v is in victor i am ergy i'm not
sponsored by
the energy but it's the best stuff there
is spirulina
that's a healing tool right that's a
healing tool
and so i get more metal out of me then
goes in
so i'm like yeah i'll use it i'll use a
spoon yeah i'll use a spoon
healing tools you're knowing what to do
what to take that's why i talk about the
right stuff
christy kristy kramer i talked to my
doctors about anthony
at my visits dot dot dot looking for
them to say
no but they agree
i'm deeply honored
okay guys i just made the salsa the
mango salsa
right there it is okay looks beautiful
isn't it beautiful in a
in a bowl too let's do this
okay let's make a little bit here
guys i love having you in my kitchen
it's an honor
to have you guys in my kitchen like
meaning like
i'm beyond grateful and honored that
you're here and that you even want to be
in my kitchen
right so
truly like it's special to me it really
is
so i got some romaine now what you can
do i have small romaine lettuce leaves
right
there's really big ones there's you know
there's there's big ones
that's a small one right there so there
you go on a romaine lettuce leaf see
that
now what i do when they're small like
this i'll take a few leaves
right that's a nice actually that's a
big one right there it's a big one let
me move this one over
that's a pretty big one that's a big you
know these are actually pretty big you
guys
maybe i called that shot wrong
right maybe i called that shot wrong
think i did i have some decent sized
ones here
okay so what i'm gonna do is put
some of the stuff you guys watching here
i'm filling up the boats right now
i just love the smell of fresh tomato
fresh ripe tomato
okay
incredible incredible okay i got my
mango
salsa romaine boats i got some romaine
lettuce i put them in there and then you
just eat them like that right
incredible that's what we have here
knowledge is power and the details
matter don't forget it
when it comes down to healing the
details
matter a reminder that's the wyman's
wild blueberry juice okay
so shop s-h-o-p dot lyman's
w-w-y-m-a-n-s
link is in description dot com uh link
is in the description that's a while
blueberry just talked about the shots
but i'm all about healing tools also
special things right
if you look in here in the medical
medium new edition you're going to see a
section
triggers and i talk about the different
triggers very powerful section of the
book for chronic illness that's
important
now you guys um mm
info isn't just about making a little
bit of food it's about
knowing what to take what to do dosages
what supplements to try
you know what to stay away from like
what to stay away from in supplements
right
well you know there's no natural flavors
in the wyman's wild blueberry juice
there's a reason for that there's
nothing else in there
just and it's not from concentrate but
the whole point in knowing the true
causes these are just all examples right
it all adds up so details matter details
matter details but i'm going to ig
and tick tock so i'm going to instagram
the medical medium instagram page the
main page and then i'm going to
tick-tock then after that
i'm going to 369 cleanse page on ig
and then tiktok again letting you know
where i'm heading but it's going to
medical medium
and tick tock i love you guys and uh
i'll see you soon