okay a couple things to cover i'm gonna
be talking about blood again
what happens when you get your blood
drawn i didn't cover
certain aspects of it like i did you
know when i was talking about it the
other day
and if you missed me talking about it
before the other day you're gonna want
to listen to
today all right so we're going to talk
about what happens when you get the
blood draw okay when you get the blood
test and it's important to know because
something happens when you get your
blood test that can be
really really really difficult on your
body so there's a way to do it in a
certain way that could be helpful
especially if you're dealing with a
chronic illness sickness of any kind
it's really important i see everybody
coming on so it's one thing we're going
to talk about i'm also making a mango
salad so i got the mangoes right here
okay
i hope these mangoes are good i've got a
bunch of them
i had these mangoes for a while they got
real ripe i you know i don't know the
condition they're in but i'm hoping
they're yummy
got some cauliflower here it's part of
the mango salad letting you guys know
and answer some questions too try to be
helpful where i can
i'm gonna be making salad got some
butter leaf lettuce how much butter leaf
lettuce did you guys have
lately have you been eating it have you
been having lettuce lately have you been
doing
cilantro as a leafy green have you been
doing butter leaf lettuce are you doing
parsley
are you doing romaine lettuce are you
doing red leaf green leaf lettuce what
are you guys doing these days
hey david's here good to see you amazing
everybody's coming on um
yeah i want to cut open these mangoes i
want to see what i got going on so if
you guys just came on here we're talking
about blood
getting your blood drawn getting your
blood tested and how to protect yourself
in the best way possible so we're going
to cover that a little bit
uh we're going to talk about your immune
system why when you get your blood drawn
does your immune system drop
nobody knew that this is important to
know and how people get sicker and
sicker and their blood is being vamped
out of them so i'm going to talk about
that pretty soon and
you guys um doesn't make it the mango
salad we're going to talk about medical
medium it's out
it is out people are getting their
medical medium book they're getting it
in the uk
they're getting it in germany i hear
they're getting it
in all kinds of places the revised and
expanded
medical medium new addition this book
is incredible and i can't wait for you
guys to see it it talks about the
tingles and numbness the tinnitus
the vertigo ticks and spasms the body
pain
adhd right autism
pms menopause lyme disease baby
lyme disease the book of lyme disease
truth that
changed the world with lyme disease and
saving lives um
gut health we got that covered in here
migraines
a guide to supplements protocols
meditations essential
angels in here 28-day cleanse 45
recipes epstein-barr chronic fatigue
syndrome
fibromyalgia lupus multiple sclerosis
hashimoto's thyroiditis
hyperthyroidism diabetes adrenal issues
can i say more candida migraines
what else did i say migraines shingles
tmj
trigeminal neuralgia colitis neuropathy
i mean
what what more right so uh you guys i'm
excited revised
and expanded it's out i'm going to read
a little
bit in here we're going to talk about
blood draw i'm also going to talk about
other controversial stuff like i always
do because i'm excited
i'm gonna make the mango salad
so yeah you have romaine terry great
great great
incredible i'm glad romaine's remains
amazing
there's nothing wrong with that at all
it's really good so uh
you guys i'm live on youtube right now
and
i'm live on facebook as well so i want
to read a quote to you guys
before we get started talking about
blood and everything else
um readers continue
to introduce more and more healthcare
providers to this
book and it has prompted
a new movement to look for the deeper
causes of chronic illness and to take
epstein-barr
virus seriously prior to the publication
of medical medium
the first edition right ebv
epstein-barr virus was practically a
non-concern
medical communities didn't understand
what the virus could do
because for example medical research and
science were unaware
that epstein-barr virus creates symptoms
that led to neurological problems you
guys
neurological problems caused by
epstein-barr
medical medium was ahead of the curve
there not one single doctor
on planet earth nor did medical research
and science know
that epstein-barr led to a neurological
symptom
and medical medium book one brought that
truth out
um very special okay
now epstein-barr virus testing and
awareness are becoming
every day at the doctor's office because
of little
me well spirit of compassion really i
can't take credit
research and science are finally
starting to find a link
between epstein-barr virus and dozens of
conditions
after the publication years after
research and science are finding a link
so when someone says where's your
science where's your science
where's your science medical medium
where's your study well how about this
medical research and science is taking
all my information and using it
they take it after medical medium
publishes a book and then medical
research and science a couple years
later
takes it and plagiarizes the information
so stop saying
where's your science because really
where's their science well it's here
they're taking it from here and using it
anyway it's just fun
and that's the truth medical medium new
edition it's out you guys i'm making
mango salad i'm gonna talk about blood
draw link is in the description and
michelle l said that's right aw it's soc
laugh out loud it really is
because it's either i'm a genius which i
know i'm not
because the doctor said that to me many
times a doctor friend of mine says
you got to be a genius you have to be
in order to write medical books that
research in science
steals after the fact you have to be a
genius and i'm like
i ain't no genius it's spirit of
compassion
um anyway you guys i'm gonna make mango
salad
all right and i'm gonna read a little
something to you in a little bit too
let's talk about blood draw
for a couple of minutes let's make some
food too i got some mangoes
look at these green onions right
no right yeah okay look at these
do you guys like green onions scallions
okay
love love love scallions um
scary scary
tomatoes hurt me tomatoes are bad
everybody tells me it's a nightshade
tomatoes aren't good for me
um they say tomatoes got lectins um
get those tomatoes away it's scary
and just so you know it's all
misinformation leslie
why onions and tomatoes cause swelling
of tongue
throat etc all right so here's the thing
there's always a food that gives
somebody a swelling in their mouth some
people swell
when they eat um anything doesn't matter
what it is whether they eat a carrot
okay you talk to people someone's always
gonna say i'm i can't eat a carrot i
either get swelling in the mouth or
something happens or
someone's gonna have a problem with a
celery stick someone's gonna have a
problem with a zucchini
someone has a problem with apple you
would think apples
anybody can eat an apple everybody can
eat an apple there's always someone
that's like
my mouth something happens in my mouth
or my throat when i eat an apple right
the one out of a hundred thousand people
or whatever it is
it's like that and there's people i eat
a piece of cheese and i get a swelling
in my mouth
i eat an egg and then my face blows up i
eat you know i hear this all the time
it's every single food
on the planet someone's gonna have
something to it right
but when they have a little problem with
the tomato it's because of tomatoes a
nightshade and it's a really bad tomato
you know tomatoes are really bad but
they're not bad and that swelling may
stop someday and you may not have a
reaction but you but i'm going to give
i'm going to help you to be your own
private detective right
is it to is it a tomato by itself
is it a fresh ripe organic tomato
by itself right that does it
that's one question right there and if
you're getting a swelling don't eat them
don't eat them
um so that's one thing to know or is it
tomato
sauce mixed with canola oil is it some
treat that's got natural flavoring in it
is it
is it tomato with cheese is it tomato
cheese some kind of parmesan is it
lasagna and it's the tomato
like whatever it is is it ketchup
and you're having this problem or don't
or you don't have the problem with
ketchup so
all these things are just questions to
kind of look at right there so that's
number one
do you swell with any other food that's
another question ask yourself to be your
own detective and i tell this for
everybody
like anybody who swells want to eat a
carrot because i i've run into that all
the time people like i can't touch
carrots i can't touch carrot juice
my mouth swells up it is it is it
you know that's so is it any other food
no other food swells up your mouth on
any level
not one other food you can eat anything
doesn't matter pork fish
chicken you know eggs whatever you can
glam
uh you know milk cheese butter not just
that
any vegetable anything there is right
any fruit the only thing that makes you
swell is tomatoes that's the next thing
you kind of kind of kind of
kind of got to look at and be your own
detective i say this for everyone who
swells to something i see people who
have a problem eating cauliflower
i see people who can't touch a lemon i
see people have you know it's all that
kind of stuff so
check out all those different things so
what i would do if i was swelling and it
was
tomato and i had a mouth swell from
tomato itself
i would get rid of other things in my
that i was eating i would get rid of
milk cheese
butter gluten eggs gone i would look out
to make sure i was doing no msg no
natural flavors in anything
no apple cider vinegar no nutritional
yeast and no caffeine
get rid of all that then and i would
even probably get rid of chocolate and
then
after about a month being free from all
that you try a piece of tomato
if you want or your doctor wants you to
you ask your doctor what's right for you
but that's what i would do if it was for
me
that's what i would do because what
happens is tomatoes
are anti-viral and for some people
they do some serious viral like
cleansing
even viral killing and when that happens
you could have an h pylori in your gut
and the reason why you're getting
swelling
is because the tomatoes starting to
whack that h pylori you can have a
little streptococcus in your gut
e coli and that tomatoes whacking that
strep and that e coli
so i just want to cover it's a really
good topic i love when someone brings it
up so i can help other people
awesome okay you guys let's start making
some stuff we'll talk about blood draw
too
so um when it comes down to blood draw
all right you have to know that they
take
too much blood for what they're looking
for
they throw all the blood away they take
a little bit of blood
they draw a nice tube of it and they
take a little bit of blood and they
throw it they discard it
at least you think they're throwing it
away
what if they're not throwing it away i
was talking to someone the other day
because they heard me talking about this
and they're like well you know aw what
if they're not throwing it away
i said yeah they could be using that
stuff for genetic testing meaning
genetic messing
playing with genes they can be using
that stuff for a lot of reasons
absolutely because why else would they
ask this why else aw would they be
drawing so much blood they don't need to
draw
why would they do that if they weren't
using it for something that was somebody
asking me that question right
i was like hey hey who knows who knows
okay that's right no one does anything
dirty and horrible out there oh that's
right
science of research never did anything
wrong oh that's right they're angels
everybody who works for them is angels
the people at the top they're all angels
anyway
let's talk about blood draw okay
everything else is rotten in the world
there's corruption everywhere but not
there
let's talk about this now we'll go to
page 197 right here so
it's all interesting stuff you know it
makes you think really and that's that's
that's something too kind of giving you
i'm in the new book right now if you
just got here all right
so i'm in a new book
and we're having some fun so
i'm in page 197 on the medical medium
new edition
just so you guys know i'm talking about
blood draw information
and it's important to know that that
when you get
your blood test ask your doctor for less
blood go in there more frequently or go
to the to the blood lab place more
frequently
um and be cautious to how much now if i
was gonna get blood work
you know i wouldn't let more than three
vials
out the gate that's that's for for you
know what i would do
and i would even do two vials so you
tell your doctor get what you can get
out of two vials
get what you can get out of three vials
right
and then i'll come back another day
because what happens is
your white count is in that blood
your white count is keeping all of your
autoimmune in check because everybody's
going to be diagnosed with autoimmune
everybody out there i don't care who it
is
eventually mark my words every
single human on this planet is going to
get an autoimmune diagnosis
as the years go by just telling you
right now
some earlier than later some later than
earlier
all depends so i want to show you some
stuff here so
anyway this is
um a white blood cell okay that's your
white blood cell
so it's floating around in your
bloodstream that's a virus
okay the viruses they
mainly stay inside your organs and i
know that some people will say
wait a minute if you're getting your
blood drawn out and your white
count your killer cells are all being
taken out
because you're taking 5 7 10 12 14 vials
and it's being taken out right well the
viruses that are in your bloodstream
they're going to be taken out too with
it so it's kind of one for one tip for a
tat right or equal ground
you're taking just as much white count
out as you're taking viruses out
so you end up with less viruses you end
up with less immune system
we're okay cancels out each other not
how it works
not how it works at all the viruses they
live inside your liver
they live inside your organs they live
inside your spleen
they live inside your pancreas they live
inside the intestinal
linings they live inside
tissue all through the body okay
and they live on nerves they even live
on nerves
vagus neurophrenic nerve all kinds of
nerves right
but and your white count is swimming
around
making sure making sure
that that virus doesn't get out of the
gate
so when the virus wants to peek its head
out of your out of your liver
and it wants to make a run for it to
then
blow up and explode meaning blow up and
and and proliferate and start to spread
what it does your white count is keeping
all that in check
so the white counts going through your
bloodstream hey you want to peek out of
the liver today you're not gonna
just just starts to tear apart that
virus the virus wants to pop out
of your spleen the white count is
swimming around in your bloodstream
finds it tears it down keeps it down
your viruses because everybody's got
viruses inside of them
know that there's an armed guard always
in the bloodstream floating around
floating around and there's things that
drop our immune system
lots of things there's betrayal broken
trust broken heart
hardship emotional abuse emotional
hardship all of that knocks down
the immune system adrenaline fight or
flight caffeine
really hits the immune system hard right
so there's all this stuff that hits the
immune system and then we're not eating
foods that build up our immune system
right
and then then the worst of all
the blood tests that's when they take
your immune system
out of your body and then it takes weeks
and sometimes
months to get your immune system back up
to par they pull all that blood out
right they pull all that blood out which
is your white count
and then the viruses they got free game
and then that means a couple of months
later my lupus is worse or i just got
diagnosed with lupus and i never had it
before
or now my hashimoto's is going to a new
level
and i want to talk about this in regards
to cancer
this is important when it comes down to
cancer okay
getting large blood draws constantly
because of cancer
it's a nightmare a nightmare
and i mean i have a you know family
friend
family friend right say like you know
what do we do what do we do like you get
small
you know this is you you do what your
doctor tells you okay whatever your
doctor tells you it's what you do but
this is what i told family friend
small blood vials periodically
versus larger ones you know at one time
because when it comes down to cancer you
need your white count
you need it to be strong and you need it
to be actually keeping things in check
and under control
really important really important so i'm
going to read just a little bit out of
medical medium right
here for a second
okay you guys and um
when you have autoimmune when you have
autoimmune
um of any kind
eczema psoriasis hashimoto's thyroiditis
ra lupus
ms lyme disease lyme disease now now is
autoimmune it's not bacterial
thanks to this book right here if you
guys just came on here this book has
changed how they view lyme disease now
medical research and science took the
cue from the book
took the information and now lyme
disease is in the autoimmune category
which means viral
which isn't bacterial anymore and
so any kind of condition you get
diagnosed with
and say you're not diagnosed with a
condition you guys say you're not
there's no diagnoses
tingles and numbness you got a little
vertigo dizziness
focus and concentration maybe you can't
see good you know
something's going on there whatever it
is that's happening in your
life whatever it is okay whatever
symptoms migraines
body aches and pains a little bit
fatigue all can worsen
all of it anxiety i've seen people get
too much blood drawn
and their anxiety becomes from from
level 1
to level 10 and now they're crippled
crippled with anxiety because
when you remove your immune system
it takes time to rebuild it over again
and there's not a lot of quick ways to
do it
because no one's going to be doing
medical medium to the 100th degree
a lot of people dabble in it a lot of
people dabble in medical medium they're
playing with it they do the celery juice
they do a little this they do a little
that and then they're doing apple cider
vinegar nutritional yeast charcoal
colostrum
collagen they're doing all the stuff
that breaks down the immune system
they're doing caffeine but they're
saying they're doing mm
so in order to build that blood up quick
you got to really
stick to mm stuff for sure but the
bottom line is
you know it doesn't happen really like
that it takes
time takes time to actually rebuild your
immune system and so
and that's the problem there um so
what i would do is small amounts it's
not about
fear it's not about never get a blood
test it's not about being scared
it's either i watch your back and and
help you so you can have a choice to
protect yourself
or you know or i become a people pleaser
you guys want me
to be a people pleaser you you want me
just to people please like all the other
podcast doctors do
because what they do is it's always
about just always about
you know people pleasing a little bit
and this and that right
it's all about that and it's not about
here it is how can we protect you how
can we can make
make sure how can we make your make make
sure that you have every opportunity to
protect yourself your family your
children and your life and
heal because what happens is what i've
seen
for for over 30 plus years 35 years
really
i've seen people recovering recovering
recovering they're getting there to the
finish line
they're recovering from multiple
sclerosis and they're making it
and then boom they had a 14 vial blood
draw
back in the saddle again back in the
saddle again
now we got to go to recovering
recovering
recovering recovering seven vial blood
draw boom
kick back notch even if it comes two
months later three months later five
months later
boom kicked back recovering recovering
having a harder time recovering now
because the body just went what the heck
recovering
another five vials another 10 vials
it's it's horrifying and no doctor
realizes it
no doctor knows about it then unless
they've learned from medical medium
and you know it's really it's really sad
this is why it's so important so
tanya says what does it mean when the
test comes back
and they say there was too much white
blood cell in the blood
first of all when you get a blood test
and something's
something's high in your your white
count say your white counts hot
whatever they can average your white
count the basophils neutrophils
you know lymphocytes whatever they want
to do right monocytes whatever they want
to average
out with your white with your white
count right
killer cells however they want to
average it some doctors average it
differently some look at it differently
i've seen virologists look at blood work
differently right
and but when the white counts up
that means low-grade viral infection
that's what that means low-grade viral
infection that's what i've always taught
doctors through the years
it's the number one question i've had
doctors ask me throughout the years you
know
it's like you know what's going on with
this white count you know what can we
see what could we not see and what
happens is in a lot of people that have
their elevated white count
they got some viruses inside the liver
they got that happening
where they got the bugs inside the liver
a little bit of an elevation of
low-grade viral infection
or their white count is in the process
of destroying an epstein-barr virus
epstein-barr virus is the number one
reason why people get that elevated
white count
important to know shingles can do it too
and and simplex one the cold sore
cold sore people go few my cold sore
went away it's just a cold sore well
what happens what people don't know
is it's still in your system and then it
causes some trouble so it's good to be
anti-viral and that's the thing about
the medical medium new edition
it's an anti-viral book in its greatest
sense
and and so important to know it really
is
good question michelle what about what
about um what about low white count
same thing low grade viral infections
with low white count
because the because the white count was
maxed at one point
and then it lost some steam and then it
maxes and loses some steam and the thing
is with blood work anyway
any given day it could change so he gets
your blood test
one time one month two months later you
get it tested again
it's different than what it would have
been a day later or three days later or
five days later it's always changing and
ebbing and flowing for a lot of people
but low white count
low weight count what that is is usually
a little extra toxic heavy metals which
actually
lowers the red blood cells too so it
lowers those babies
and and the thing is is you know red
blood cells you get your blood drawn
you get trouble with the red blood cells
you get the trouble with the
white blood cells right and below
white count is is indicative to the
whole thing if it was
high at one point and then it got
drained the immune the immune system got
low it got lower it got lower it's
getting drained because it's battling
low-grade viral infections
you ask your doctor about you know take
the medical medium books to the doctor
you ask them all the questions you want
to ask them show them the book that's
what happened with this one it was shown
to doctors around the world
for the last six and a half seven years
however it is
um so anyway you guys i'm here i'm
making a mango salad but haven't started
yet talking about blood draw
how serious it is when you get your
blood test um
and here's here's why i'm talking about
it so much today okay
so here's one reason why i'm bringing
this up for someone reading some
questions
vivian says what about if the celery
causes high blood pressure what can i do
to stop the blood pressure from going up
um that's you be your own detective is
it really the celery causing high blood
pressure
um nothing else caused it you never had
high blood pressure before
um what happens when you don't do celery
at all do you ever have high blood
pressure
um if i had high blood pressure uh
because celery juice lowers high blood
pressure right
so but and that's what it's that's what
it's proven to do out there but what
i would do if i had high blood pressure
is i would lower fats
i would make sure there's no milk cheese
butter and eggs in there if you're
eating animal protein only eat it once a
day
if you're eating plant fats like avocado
nuts seeds nut butters nut milks
lower them i would lower them so your
blood isn't so
thick and stagnant and the liver gets a
break and then you start healing the
liver and then blood pressure problems
that are mysterious
go away ask your doctor take
take take the book to your doctor go to
library if you don't want to buy it it's
going to come out in the library i'm
sure eventually
get the la get it in the library for
free and and take it to your doctor
ask them about your high blood pressure
show them the book um
ask him any questions you find any any
you know things that you find in here
that you want to ask
so anyway you guys allison said you said
two or three tubes yes sometimes the
tubes are larger sometimes you're
smaller you don't know which one you're
gonna get you don't know which one
they're gonna take
sometimes they'll surprise you they'll
take the large ones sometimes surprise
you they'll take
more of a smaller tube but i'd say two
to three tubes
that's what i would do for max but
really if you're sensitive two to three
tubes
that's my recommendation ask your doctor
do what's right for you
you know with your doctor um and i would
even ask for
half tubes so the phlebotomist said it'd
be like oh half tubes
can we do half tubes and i would ask
your doctor can i get
half tubes now the blood labs would be
like we don't want half tubes but they
but but they're fine with it when it
does go through
and one doctor says okay let's do half
half tubes
so instead of eight you know full
tubes we do really at equals to four
food full tubes
instead of eight because you're getting
half tubes right and it goes to the
blood lab
and the blood lab is fine and runs it so
when you hear about the blood lab won't
let it they won't let it go
they're they're just they're being
ridiculous because they're only using a
smidgen
and they're throwing it all away
smidging and they're throwing it all
away
now look you guys why would i take this
serious
like why would i want to talk about this
because
it can mean life or death for a lot of
very sick people that are chronically
ill fighting their way back
from hell and they mean lyme disease
really bad ms
lupus or you're somebody that just gets
headaches you're sensitive
because you've got a low grade shingles
without knowing it you've got something
else without knowing and say you got
sibo
you don't know it you're walking around
sibo and h h pylori and streptococcus in
your gut
and you got some sibo and stuff and and
you know the blood draw
affects us and here's the thing you have
to know
one of the most important things what
you're going to hear from functional
medicine doctors what you're going to
hear from podcast doctors
what you're going to hear from
nutritionists now
you're going to hear parroting right
it's like a parrot
you know and the parrot says
your immune system is all in your gut
that's where your immune system is
that's what you're going to hear from
the podcast doctors the functional
medicine doctors
you're going to hear that now for
chinese medicine doctors you're just
going to hear it the immune system is
all in your gut
that's where your immune system is wrong
boom
wrong another ridiculous trend and
theory and thought
in the system which sends everybody you
know in the wrong direction
your immune system is not all in your
gut that's not where most of your immune
system is
completely 100 inaccurate and wrong
bottom line okay you know where your
immune system is
it's in your bloodstream that's where
your immune system is
it's in your bloodstream
that's where it is that's where they
test for it that's where it is
it's in your bloodstream so you don't
get
blood poisoning i'll say it again
okay it's not in your gut it's in your
bloodstream
so you don't get blood poisoning
so another ridiculous trend but here's
the thing
they're allowed to make ridiculous
trends over and over again and as they
keep on bombing or hurting people or
bombing or hurting people or being
useless
no one pays the price it's all like oh
move on something else five years ago oh
let's move on to something else so let's
change our tune once again let's do
another ridiculous trend let's talk
about lectins now
that's the new one what's coffee animus
let's talk coffee enemas
oh wait a minute here let's do some cold
plunging into ice
and shock our body so that we live less
longer
let's you know because the body gets
injured over time from the shock
let's do all kinds of things and that's
what happens the ridiculous trends come
flying in and and should people just you
know and they don't do it
you know before medical medium
information you guys came around before
medical medium information got in the
books too
before that everybody swam in all those
ridiculous trends misinformation and
theories right
they didn't have mm info to pull them
out but now it's mixing up
it's mixing they're taking medical
medium information they're sticking it
in with all those
while doing all that other useless stuff
and then people get a little bit better
and it's the mm celery juice it's it's
the m it's lowering the fats
intermittent fasting is lowering the
fats that's making sure you don't do
fats in the morning
that alone is helping people a little
bit even though it's not quite right
done
but the bottom line is and then the
epstein-barr reactivation of epsom bars
medical medium information
it was in this book first so i want to
read a little
bit about the blood draw when a larger
number of blood vials are
drawn it could be stressful on the
immune system
because the very immune defenses that
are keeping the viruses behind lyme
symptoms at bay
and other chronic illness symptoms at
bay are being drawn
out of the body with the blood that's
taken
your white count gets drawn out you get
sicker as you go along down the road
and yeah you're young doesn't feel
there's no problems you're you know
young and you're you feel indestructible
but you only got some acne and
maybe a little you're a little tired a
little brain fog
but it's gonna hurt you when it's done
wrong and they keep on vamping that
blood
out of you okay so
larger blood draws
tend to take away a substantial portion
of a person's immune system
that day yeah and it sometimes takes
weeks and even longer to rebuild those
portions of the immune system
within those weeks that the full power
of the immune system is not present to
monitor the blood in organs
right not present viruses can get
in a window get a window to strengthen
and proliferate
infections can travel from organ to
organ with ease
because they're not being corralled by
your immune system anymore
and that can lead to a flare up of
symptoms whether a week later a few
weeks later months later
or even a year later i recommend doing
smaller blood draws
over more visits if you're struggling
with lyme symptoms
ra focus and concentration migraines
anxiety
depression whatever you're struggling
with eczema psoriasis
i recommend no more than four vials of
blood at a time
and even consider fewer if you're very
sensitive a mistake made by well-meaning
doctors is to draw a large number of
blood vials with sensitive people
even ask for half blood vials anyway
i'm reading medical medium new edition
you guys the book is out there
amazon.com
barnes get a copy if you want to protect
yourself learn how to protect your
family
a whole bit so more to go i want to
start the mango salad right now
there's more stuff to read some cool
stuff you guys
coming up all right gonna make some
salad link is in the description
just so you know
[Music]
so i'm gonna make a salad i'm not gonna
have the leaves really big in this
but i'm not gonna dice it either okay
what i'm doing is i'm cutting the
lettuce
to um you know these nice these nice
good sizes
so this information is very important
this guy is full of okay sure
that's great
how many lives have you saved in your
lifetime
i wonder how many doctors are using your
information
how many people have gone from being
deathly sick in their beds and got their
lives back and they're running
five miles a day now 10 miles a day
how many people did you help in your
life i wonder
thanks for being on here though i
appreciate it eileen
i guess we don't get the answer about
donating blood
yeah i'll talk about it i'll talk about
it
um first of all
if you're sensitive you got chronic
illness you got any kind of epstein-barr
related
symptoms and conditions
um if you're somebody with fatigue
eczema
aches and pains um
somebody with you know with high anxiety
depression
anything somebody with an autoimmune
diagnosis or maybe just a rosacea
dermatitis um you know anything like
that
maybe you've had symptoms before tinkles
and numbness
whatever it is you want to be cautious
about donating blood because you get rid
of a lot of blood
you get rid of your immune system and
then you can become a sick person
a real sick person who's going to need
someone to donate blood to
and so kind of think about that and be
cautious because
if you get too much blood drawn and too
much blood drawn
and you're sick you can end up really
release it because i've seen it happen
and um and then now you're now you're
you're needing blood
yourself absolutely it's one thing to
think about
i'm going to talk more about it though
jenny love you detox smoothie really
helping my son with autism incredible
jenny
amazing it really is so i got some
lettuce in here
right another thing is too um yeah you
can donate blood
absolutely it's it's a noble thing to do
it's a great thing to do
um maybe you can donate smaller batches
maybe you can find out about that and
look into it smaller batches
also be really proactive when you donate
blood
be careful don't don't push yourself
hard for a week afterwards
make sure you're taking good care of
yourself staying hydrated
make sure um make sure you're doing some
zinc
ask your doctor if that's right for you
okay but i would if i was donating blood
i'd be on zinc
um and the right kind of zinc of course
lunel medical medium is the only hundred
accurate info out there i am reversing
autoimmune
with his info only people who haven't
dealt with chronic illness could reject
this info
without inquiring deeper i'm really
proud of you loon
and loon you actually know a lot too
like
you're you're seasoned and
you know a lot because you've tried a
lot of things out there
because i've read your comments like you
tried everything out there like you
know everything in the field and
you're you're really really seasoned so
that's that's i'm honored i'm honored
doctor and fun md it's great that some
people
won't listen to him it makes me look
like a genius when they get to me
you are a genius he's an amazing doctor
you guys
an amazing doctor i always say look for
medical medium
friendly doctors mds um
right there right there there he is
uh julianne medical medium has helped me
his methods work incredible incredible
cutting up some some cauliflower right
here right now
putting that in here i'm cutting the
pieces not so small not so big
that's how i got lime from a blood
transfusion shannon bentley that's how i
got lime from blood transfusion
um my concern is when you donate blood
and you have that reactivated
epstein-barr and they don't know you
have reactivated epstein-barr then you
donate blood then that reactivated
epstein-barr goes into somebody else but
yet we need people to donate blood
because of critical situations
surgeries heart surgeries and all kinds
of different stuff and i completely
understand that
but if you're donating blood maybe
donate less maybe
really take care of yourself for a week
or two after
i if okay this is a good way of doing it
say i was gonna donate blood all right
well what i would do is make sure i
wasn't eating any
of these right here any time before
like a month before and anytime after i
would not eat these eggs right here
okay that i would not do no eggs no milk
cheese no butter
i would keep that away i would keep
gluten away at least keep those foods
away if you're going to donate blood
that's something to consider right there
and i suggest never eating those at all
eggs for for sure i suggest never eating
those anyway
cutting up some florets some cauliflower
right here
it's one thing i do i make sure i would
be taking zinc
i would be taking some goldenseal i'd be
taking the vimorji stuff personally
that's what i would be doing
um i'd be taking lemon balm that's what
i'd be doing i'd be taking antivirals
vitamin c i'd be taking a lot of vitamin
c so if i
try to donate blood at least i had a lot
of vitamin c in me
that was feeding what was left of my
immune system
so here i'm going to donate some blood
they're taking it out
right and meanwhile i took vitamin c
that morning because i want to make sure
whatever white counts left in me it's
able to gobble down and gobble down and
gobble down vitamin c
which i think i put it over there but
that's what i would do
i mean definitely what i do um
yeah i don't know where my vitamin c is
so yeah so i put some cauliflower in the
salad
now i'm going to start doing some mango
maybe some tomato in a little bit
let's see what these mangoes look like i
don't know if they look good if they're
not good i don't know what's going on
we're gonna see
but you know you guys
you know it's like this okay
all right i have a this mango does look
good it's not not so bad at all wasn't
sure what i had today
i'm not trying to put fear in anybody
but i know a lot of people that were
happy they got this
information throughout the years when i
taught it
one-on-one a lot of people were happy
it protected a lot of people so they can
be safe
they got smaller blood draws their
immune system was preserved
and they kept fighting forward healing
instead of getting vamped
instead of it all being taken out of
them vampires
okay i've done a lot of lectures about
it throughout the years
all of that so and i figured you know
what
i don't talk about it enough i've talked
about it before
but i don't talk about it enough with
you guys and i'm like wait a minute i
better jump on this because
i gotta look out for you guys that's
just the bottom line
you know so
making some mango salad i got some mango
i'm just gonna
take i take a spoon i just cut it i cut
it like that and these little
you know squares in there and i take a
spoon and i'm just dropping
the pieces down in here right
this is the way i'm doing it a piece
just went on the floor landed on my foot
so let me get some of this going
um mango is a really powerful healing
food
i talk about it i think the detox was
too much for my adrenals which caused my
blood pressure to rise and i became
really weak i crashed i had to quit
celery juice and doing better
um
nancy uh so
are you doing any antivirals are you
doing what kind of what kind of
protocols are you doing
um when someone's really toxic or really
really
viral you know that they can have
all kinds of things can happen when
you're healing and flushing the stuff
out of your system
um but celery juice is really really
gentle it's gentle very very gentle
um why don't you i mean you don't have
look ask your doctor what's right for
you
that's what i would do why don't you ask
your doctor but if it was me i'd go down
to four ounces of celery juice
i mean that's what i would do but ask
your doctor what you what you should do
so
cutting some more mangoes here we'll see
if we get some more good ones that's a
really nice one right there
if it was up to me i would work up the
dosage that's what i would do
trying to pay attention so i don't cut
my hand of course got another mango here
i would work up start with four ounces
start working my way up
another thing too if you're detoxing
okay what else are you doing and what
else are you eating are you eating
enough
could have nothing to do with the celery
juice are you eating enough
did you go without food too much are you
on so little calories
are your calories enough
because really it sounds to me like not
enough calories going on
might have been eating smaller portions
of something or not eating enough
frequently enough especially if you have
adrenal issues
especially if you're adrenal sensitive
um i'm putting some more mango in here
okay i got my mango pieces in the salad
which is coming along really nice
got the mango in here all right let's do
some green onion
you guys okay if i do some green onion
some people say i don't like green
onions some people like it i still got
radishes to go that's a healing food
radishes are antiviral green onions are
antiviral
so i'm gonna cut these green onions
right now
now i don't want them too small and i
don't want them too big
so i'm just going to do this here
put these on top
can you guys see this i'll show you the
salad in a second
got a little bit of that so we're
working on it we've got the mango
cauliflower butter leaf lettuce
underneath there we've got the scallions
as well let's
do some radishes let's not lose that
radish
because i like to throw things in the
air
the habit i picked up throughout the
years anybody
hands me something i throw it in the air
i don't think that's a great thing
some thinly slicing these
that's how i'm doing it with the with
with this radish right here
because do you guys eat enough radishes
do you ever have them
it's something that a lot of people
don't really think about it's like nah
radishes isn't something i want to get
at the store you know i'm going to cut
these radish
slices in half in one half okay like
this
that's what i'm going to do
guys we're live on youtube and facebook
at the same time link is in the
description on the medical medium new
edition
it's a life-saving book it's already has
a track record of saving lives
that's what's that's what's incredible
about it
i can't say that about a lot of books
um so in the medical medium book i talk
about the tingles and numbness
how to heal that of course the vertigo
aches and pains it takes the spasms the
body pain the fatigue chronic fatigue
syndrome fibromyalgia adhd
lyme disease menopause symptoms i mean
the list goes on depression
ptsd diabetes 28-day cleanse i have in
there meditations
oh my god pms i talked about right i
told you about the lyme disease gut
health issues migraines
lupus candida i mean seriously i mean
what i cover in there is just
it's just unbelievable beth buck i'm
very grateful i wish i would have known
i had 15 vials and it makes me sad and
cry to think
they harmed me well here it is they're
not doing it on purpose
it's just that science research is
behind on a lot of information
and now you know how to protect yourself
what you do is you ask your doctor can
you do less can you do seven vials
if it's if you know can you do half
vials i mean
i would i would do i would do
if i'm sick and i have any kind of
condition if i had any kind of symptom
or
aches and pains or condition i would
personally do two to three vials
at a time i'd say to my doctor what can
you get out of three vials because
that's what i'm that's what i'm going to
give you
i think we okay well we'll schedule they
just here's what it is
they want it all all at once they don't
want to have to think
that you know the doctor doesn't want to
have to think what he has to divide the
test
in it's a hassle right so you become
anybody becomes like either you take the
hit
because the doctor doesn't want the
hassle that's all so
let me get it all done in one boom out
the door
instead of doctor being like okay let me
divide this let me check out your
thyroid
right check out some of your white count
we'll do smack 27
let's check out your white count let's
check out say your liver enzymes let's
check out your thyroid that should be
enough let's do a few vials
and then we'll come back and we'll check
out hormones we'll check out this we'll
check out that we'll check cortisol out
we'll do that at another day we'll do
another three vials that day
now you're protected but yet it's a
hassle for the doctor you see
to do that to break it up
suzanne doctors all told me i need to
kill my thyroid with radioactive iodine
i was feeling horrible had tried
everything in the world
it wasn't until i incorporated mm advice
that i have turned a corner
and now my thyroid is normal range and i
still have my thyroid thank god
and i'm not dependent on synthetic
hormones thanks anthony i'm really proud
of you
the medical medium information saved a
lot a lot of thyroids
so you know mm info has saved a lot of
thyroids a lot of people did not have to
kill off the thyroid did the
radioactive iodine and a lot of people
who did the radioactive iodine
were able still to bring some of the
thyroid back and and sometimes totally
back with mm
info too which has really been special
i'm going to do some tomatoes i did some
radishes you guys were cutting through
this i want to read a little something
out of medical medium to the new edition
if you guys have the patience if you can
hang in there
you know anyway so i'm going to cut this
tomato up real quick throw some slices
in
we got a really pretty salad we're
making right now i'm going to make a
quick dressing too
throw some tomato slices in here
you know it's one thing if you get a
bunch of vials taken out 14 vials
it's another if they keep on doing it to
you every few months or
every month or every six months and
that's the thing it's it's always great
to
to be able to to actually now look out
for the future
i have bell's palsy what can i do to
help recover i talk about
balls bell's palsy in
um in the book can bring the book to
your doctor and show them
how i um
how i talk about shingles being the true
cause so you can actually take the book
to your doctor
you can show your doctor hey anthony
william okay
talks about how shingles is bell's palsy
here and
there's a protocol in here for me to do
and you ask your doctor can i do it is
it okay for me to do his protocol or
help me with this protocol
that's when the shingles virus gets the
trigeminal nerve
fasciae nerves
salads coming along good gonna make the
dressing right now you guys
let me do that get a little bit of a
bowl here
or something make the dressing in
so i'm gonna put some honey in here
i'm gonna put some lemon let me start
with some lemon let me do that
and i have
matt robinson don't forget to hit the
like button hey
thanks i never asked i never try to
bother you guys about anything you know
like i just don't you know
i just want to be like guys can you well
i do like to bother you about going to
medical medium podcasts at apple podcast
i do ask you guys to go there because
it's a free resource to really help you
heal
and so i do i do always ask you guys you
guys should listen to the podcast
episodes
they're so healing there's so much
information there if you want i mean if
you want but um
anyway that's the mango salad right
there that i'm making and finishing up
with the dressing
is what we're doing dressing right one
tablespoon of lemon juice
one tablespoon of pure maple syrup
always can use honey as an option
so i'm gonna do half teaspoon of mustard
so i'm actually in the book right now
and let's get a tablespoon of lemon
going
love the smell of lemons can't get
enough of them
can you use organic frozen mangoes yeah
andrea definitely totally can
janice does does anyone feel very hungry
on the diet what can i bulk up on we'll
pass it on
which diet are you on are you on the
mono eating
are you on the 369 advance or the 369
simplified or 369 original
are you on the 28 day cleanse in the new
book
um what what diet are you on
that's something to know and you can add
in a little bit more steamed potato
or some winter steamed winter squash how
about adding in a little bit more
steamed winter squash what about that
you can get a little bit more calories
more bananas more papayas
but what what diet are you on like what
version
medical medium has a lot of protocols so
people can get better for a lot of
reasons
and are you eating enough leafy greens
squeeze a little bit more lemon out of
here you're eating enough leafy greens
right
because if you're not doing enough of
those mineral salts you're getting the
spinach soup in you
are you getting 32 ounces of celery
juice are you talking
about cleanse the heal with all all like
the different cleanses here are you
doing 32 ounces of celery juice
every single morning you're doing some
coconut water in and out of the day
there's a lot of things you can do i'm
trying to help you out so you could be
your own detective
isn't this fun got some honey right here
you guys
let's get a little bit of honey going
all right
so we're gonna add a little bit of honey
to this dressing
i'm gonna add a little bit of mustard
powder right
got that yeah jackie celery shortage
yep kentucky
yeah i'm just gonna say this i can't
help myself
i can't okay more people are drinking
celery juice around the world than
anything else
in the healing arts anything there's
nothing else
in the healing arts that people are
doing more than drinking celery juice
stores run out thousands and thousands
of farms are growing it
hundreds of thousands of farms around
the world are growing it it's the
largest crop in every farm but guess
what
everybody pretends it doesn't exist
because guess why
medical mediums the originator all the
influencers keep it quiet why they drink
it now
they don't want to talk about it
meanwhile they're all drinking it you
can even see it i have people tell me
all the day
that people are getting caught drinking
it in their youtubes and they're not
saying they are but they're caught
drinking it every morning like
it's crazy right it is the number one
healing tool in the world right now and
the media doesn't want to touch it
they don't even want to talk about it
because too many people are healing from
it it's too powerful the movement's too
powerful it's too big
and yeah there's a shortage and they're
growing it in truckloads like never
before in history
it's actually just crazy really i think
the influencers don't talk about it as
much
and youtubers don't talk about it as
much because they can't make
money off of it you can't make money off
of it it's like
you juice it you drink it you can't say
hey check out the code the 10 off in the
code down there make sure you go and
click that so
you know you can't like you can't it
just doesn't do it
um kim can you speak about menopause in
this book here
there's a menopause chapter
it's a really special one it's a great
chapter in here
really has all the information about
menopause that's the revised
and expanded so make sure you know that
new edition
link is in the description i'm gonna mix
up this
right here a little mustard powder in
here
i got some honey i could do maple syrup
i love maple syrup
love it it's just that i'm out of maple
syrup right now so i'm doing a little
honey
which i love too absolutely so i'm just
mixing it up little lemon juice a little
honey
i mean how great is that
honey antiviral lemon juice antiviral
okay going on the salad right now you
love greena
lorraine loreno you love green onions
incredible lorraine your comments on
youtube cracked me up
you guys i if i don't respond on youtube
or anything it doesn't mean i'm not
reading all the comments i read them all
it's just that i i i got so many moving
parts right now
between this new book coming out
and the tick tock and the in the um
medical meeting podcast episodes i got
to work on
and a whole bunch of other stuff i'm
working on too
for for you guys that i haven't
disclosed or anything a whole bunch of
cool stuff
but um i haven't told you about but
anyway but i read the comments i do
so i just want you to know that and you
guys are really incredible
that's the salad right there you guys
uh bitty how can i heal how how can i
know it
if i have ebv
you know anybody that's ever asked me
that
okay you can take the book to your
doctor and you can show your doctor the
book right
when you read the book you can match up
symptoms to know
and learn and that's the other thing too
the symptoms
matching them up to knowing about the
virus all the different symptoms and
conditions and that's you know how you
can know
about learning anyway you guys
and get the book at the library if you
need to okay just so you know
mango salad now i'm taking off now to
tick-tock
going to tick-tock i'm going to
instagram live i'll be there in probably
like 10-15 minutes or something like
that
and i can't wait to have this right here
i'm actually really excited
um
dressing's amazing
i don't know about you guys but i love
mango
what their what is there not to love
about all right you guys
i'm heading off i'm seeing tick tock
instagram love you guys