marijuana about it it's going to be a
big deal we're talking about a lot of
stuff people don't know about marijuana
like it's high and toxic heavy metals
that's right I called that shot first a
long time ago it's documented and then
they're starting to look into it seems
to be kind of high and toxic heavy
metals what that's right so we're going
to talk about what's up with that how
that works what's going on we're going
to talk about weed we're talking about
weed but yeah at the same time what
happens when people smoke weed they love
mac and
cheese anybody who smokes weed loves Mac
and Cheese man
yo bring on the mac and cheese man salad
no I don't want no salad not what I'm
high man I want mac and cheese but guess
what we're making a salad with fresh
dressing French Fresh dressing let's
correct but um is that because I'm high
right now Hey listen check this out
right to bake mac and cheese but I'm not
high because you guys know the mm
doesn't smoke the stuff no way nor does
the medical medium eat it doesn't do
Edibles it's like yeah go to a party and
there's a big bowl of Edibles there it's
like siloc cybin T whatever what you
name it just no I don't do it I'm not
judging anybody that does no way life is
hard I understand not judging anybody
who smokes weed 80% of people who are on
the internet probably smoke weed 80% you
go on Tik Tok you go wherever you go
right and everybody's commenting
probably like 75 80% of the entire
internet is on weed right I'm not
judging
anybody but we're going to talk about
weed and all about it and then we're
going to talk about making some mac and
cheese cuz I got everything in front of
me to do so with a salad too how many
people get stoned and they're like yeah
give me that salad of greens yeah man
give me that salad of greens you got a
tomato in there yeah I want a tomato
yeah man I love tomatoes when I get a
high give me a fresh onion and a fresh
tomato and a fresh Leaf piece of lettuce
now I'll take that and maybe a squeeze
of lemon no no one does that no freaking
way instead they're just like bags of
chips and garbage and whatever else or
they they're in a diner and they're
doing like sausage eggs bacon pancakes
whatever hash browns a whole bit with
all that oil and all that grease but we
got a lot to talk about first I want to
give you an introduction I want to
introduce you to my friends my friends
right here you got fresh baby arugula
beautiful herb you got cucumbers you got
lemons if you could see those you got
some green onions there some scallions
you got lettuce is a lot of this stuff
from the garden you got heirloom
tomatoes now that I can get high on
right there I can totally trip out on
these right here with without a doubt
your loom Tomatoes you guys know what
they're like it's an experience beyond
all other and I don't need to be high on
weed to know that those are that good
and then I got some mangoes here I got
some red bell peppers over there I got
some all kinds of different stuff from
me some spices and everything else and
some other things too and yeah got the
food processor ready we're going to make
pasta because pasta is how you make mac
and cheese that's a big part of it you
have I I think so I think that's what
you got to do you got to make pasta in
order to make mac and cheese right yes
yes all right let's talk about the
marijuana stuff let's get into it we
might even do little demo stuff with my
dummy right about how when weed goes
into you and goes into your system
what's going on okay and let's get into
it
so
marijuana is toxic for a lot of reasons
one of the big reasons is it's it's high
in toxic heavy
metals high in toxic heavy metals toxic
Metals overall just high in it why is
that how does it work for one weed
growers marijuana growers they cut
Corners they cut Corners all bets are
off no regulations know anything I'm
talking about some of the most
respectable weed
Growers out there in the world they cut
Corners so they need their weed to grow
they need the buds to be
big they need their weed to grow and
they need their buds to be big that's
what they need in order to make those
big buds they need
fertilizer without
fertilizer you don't get the big
buds you need fertilizer for the big
buds but Growers are
cheap cheapos in the worst way that's
notoriously how they are they don't want
to spend the money on the good
fertilizer and fertilizer is real priced
up so right now weed is going to be even
higher in toxic heavy metals in the
coming next couple of years like we're
talking like you smoke weed you're
filling your tank with toxic heavy
metals so let's get into the fertilizer
thing what goes on with that first of
all they need the cheap way out they
don't want to buy
fertilizers and they don't want to buy
the resources to make their own
fertilizers the good stuff they don't
want to buy
seaweeds they don't want you know
manures from reputable
places they get manures in massive boat
loads from guess where you know it the
industrial cow center of the world
industrialized Cow Patties that's what
they use and begin with just so you know
industrialized cows are filled with
drugs they're filled with antibiotics
they're filled with all kinds of
different Pharmaceuticals they're shot
up left and right with antibiotics and
pharmaceuticals and antifungals
antifungal just for the record are
really high in toxic heavy metals and
other toxins and poison
okay so the Manu that marijuana growers
use are loaded with antifungal
medications keep this in mind right here
how this works that manure is also
loaded in
antibiotic
medications these are just two another
thing too is conventional cows get
inflammation to the point where they
swell so if you go to an industrialized
you know uh ranch right they're kind
they're all caged up they're all locked
up you're talking about industrial meat
right the real thing okay the cows are
swollen their legs are swelling their
organs are swelling they don't last long
before they get butchered they can't
hang long they get too sick organs are
swelling so they pump them with
anti-inflammatories so all that
anti-inflammatory goes into the cow pad
you guys get what I'm saying into the
cow manure that's the cow manure weed
grow weed growers actually use it's a c
manure from the industrial center of the
world of
cows and then that manure right there
filled with antifungals
anti-inflammatories
antibiotics and other medications and
other
Pharmaceuticals is in that manure and
high in that manure the other thing is
the feed right all the feed that's being
used highly sprayed sprayed feed just
for the record here this is critical to
know that weed growers don't use
organic like organic everything like no
high like high quality highly reputable
organic manur and fertilizers they don't
do that they use the lowest of the
lowest of the lowest they even concoct
and make their own and we're going into
that next part in a minute because you
can't miss out on this some good stuff
let's get into it a little bit
so maners are a big part of how weed the
buds are loaded with toxic heavy
metals because of the antifungals and
the antibiotics and the
anti-inflammatories but that's just one
place and then it's the feed for the
cows that are laced in the pesticides
and the rodenticides and everything else
the weed killer and everything else
that's in the grain that's fed to those
cows
and then the
manure is highly toxic highly loaded
with metals and that manure is
purchased for very little money like
dirt cheap and a lot of times weed
growers make deals where they're
actually bartering with weed for cow
manure and they get the lowest grade
bulk crap cow manure there is on the
planet and they barter with weed for Cal
manure that's a practice that does
happen out there you might be saying not
my weed grower not mine in my state not
my you know whatever my weed grower
never does that they tell me they got
the best care for it they do this they
do that but I'm sorry but I highly
doubted it's highly unlikely maybe some
Homespun weed grower somewhere some
little Homespun weed weed grower that's
actually growing some weed for
themselves or something or trying to
start up a business legally or whatever
right
and they're starting out and they want
the best for the best for their plants
but once you get into it for a little
bit and you look at the bottom line and
you're watching your Dollar Bottom uh-uh
it all changes fast and then you hear
about practices that the weed growers
are doing the big weed growers are doing
and those practice is are the only way
to survive it's a big part of how the
weed industry works so you get a bud bud
looks great but it's toxic very toxic
just go into something a little bit
deeper on this people who smoke weed are
already high and toxic heavy metals
there's very few people who are smoking
weed they have a need for weed if they
have a need for weed they're high in
toxic heavy metals because toxic heavy
metals Mercury aluminum copper all of
that lead everything that's inside our
brains when we have too much of it
patched out in different areas too much
of it in different places in the brain
what happens we start getting depression
we start getting the depersonalization
we start getting the anxiety attacks and
you yes you can have pathogens involved
pathogens love metals and you can have a
combination of both but what I'm trying
to tell you is is the bipolar the
schizophrenia the depression the sadness
the all of the above and
more okay emotional not feeling good
feeling bad not feel feeling unwell
feeling sick in any way plus people who
are suffering too in different ways not
just emotionally and mentally but in
physically and they smoke weed to try to
curve everything curve the emotional
pain curve the mental pain and physical
pain to some degree they're high in
toxic heavy metals people who smoke weed
are already really high in toxic heavy
metals so then they're smoking or using
weed or eating weed or however you know
some new way of taking weed comes into
town whatever it is they're adding on to
their heavy metals so the metals that
they're getting from their weed is
actually going into the metals is mixing
into the metals that are in their brain
and it's adding to it so they're smoking
weed and it's kind of dumbing down their
pain and sorrow and then the weed wears
off and then boom they're back to square
one you got to smoke the weed again
dumbs down the pain and sorrow back to
square one when it wears off boom you
got to do it again dumbs down the pain
and sorrow wears off boom you're back to
doing it again right the Vicious Cycle
of weed the Vicious Cycle of marijuana
use it's you just and I'm not judging
anybody on this at all that's not what
this
is that's not what this is at all right
but you you have this thing where
everybody goes up and down it becomes a
vicious cycle and that vicious cycle is
hard to break out of because people feel
like they need the weed to calm things
down emotionally what's happening
instead is what they do not know is
they're dealing with toxic heavy metals
inside themselves in their liver in
their brain in their body in their
organs mostly in their brain creating a
problem which leads them to a place
where they want weed to begin with it
leads them to to a place where hey I
need to smoke
marijuana but the problem here with
marijuana is it's really high in toxic
heavy metals and it's really high
intoxic heavy metals adding to their
problem slowly over time but adding to
their problem slowly over time so let's
get into fertilizer a little bit
fertilizer might be
a boring ass topic but when it comes
down to weed it's not
boring so what most weed growers do
the we grower near
you is they use their own urine to
fertilize now before you B at the old
your own urine to fertilize thing I'm
not ripping that up totally back to the
Landers have used
urine for their
fertilizer
for dozens and dozens and dozens of
years however you want to say it urine
has been a fertilizer a staple for
people who are trying to survive grow
their own food food and they use
urine to feed their food their growing
food the nitrogen from their own
urine can actually help support your
garden now that's your own urine right
that's
yours the weeds you're
smoking is a whole bunch of other
people's
urine people that you probably wouldn't
want to ever meet
someday probably the people that you
would probably not want to run across
someday they're uring so what they do is
they contain it so in weed operations
everybody who has to take a leak is not
allowed to go take a leak on the edge of
the the marijuana field they're not
allowed to take a leak on the edge of
the woods they're not allowed to use the
bathroom when it comes down to
urination so they can't just go into a
bathroom and urinate most weed growers
have a rule the rule is it's got to go
into a vet or a jug it's got to be
stored and everybody's urine gets stored
for the weed growth
process
now sure you got your own little farm
Farmstead Homestead you got your little
you're back to the land you're growing
your garden and you want to use your
urine for your own plants you want to
know how to use it you mix it with water
you thin it out a little bit you got
your your fertilizer you got your
nitrogen I'm not ranking on that idea or
that concept I understand it well and I
know it
well problem is with the weed rowing
situation the industry is it's urine fed
that's what it is now what I don't like
about that for the weed industry is ur
in fed from people that are highly
toxic people that aren't eating good
people that actually are in high in
toxic heavy metals people that are
drinking energy drinks out of cans all
day while they're harvesting weed while
they're growing the weed while they're
nurturing their weed and they're
drinking out of they're just drinking
energy drinks out of aluminum cans and
all kinds of toxins and everything
else and even with all that they're
exposed to Metals in so many other ways
we can't even imagine I've taught about
this for years toxic heavy metal
exposure and how that
works
so the urine fertilizer that basically
runs the gamma of the weed
industry is highly toxic and filled with
toxic heavy metals it's not just filled
with some syphilis here and there it's
not just filled with some Epstein bar
here and there it's not just filled with
a little gonorrhea it's not just filled
with a little chyia it's not just filled
with some shingles and it's not just
filled with some strep it's not just
filled with some staff or some some
serious antibiotic resistant Mera and
strep and Seed if it's not just filled
with that that goes into those Vats
because that's what the urine all has in
it and that all goes into the ground
there to grow your weed it's not just
that it's filled with toxic heavy
metals and so many other different
toxins and
poisons and so that's how the weed
industry Works each Farm has their own
dog Day
rules you work there you learn pretty
quick doesn't matter how kind of
hippie-ish or kind of homegrown the
people are how nice the people are they
got their rules and a lot of their rules
are is this is what we're going to use
for fertilizer we're going to use the
urine we're going to use the cheapest
comve you've ever seen on this planet it
doesn't matter grow those buds no one
gives a freak it doesn't matter who
smokes it whatever as long as that boom
that content is there as long as that
bud is powerful as long as that Gene of
that plant is strong it doesn't matter
it's where it's at so let's go into
another realm of why toxic heavy metals
are in in weed and I've been talking
about this years versus anything else
they can't use weed
killer to dumb down the
weeds I don't know if you guys get my
drift on this at
all they can't just take a weed killer
and spray the field because even
marijuana resistant weed killers
or so forth where they don't kill
marijuana still damage marijuana so they
can't really so they have to rely on
other means of keeping the weeds down
and that means row covers so people
don't realize is a lot of Road a lot of
row covers are loaded with toxins
poisons they're loaded with Metals
they're loaded with plastics that are
unstable so I got to tell you something
about row covers row covers have a
different form of plastic they have one
where it's actually really unstable
breaks down really fast and and so
marijuana growers can't really keep the
weeds under control underneath their
marijuana plants because you can't kill
those weeds with those weed killers cuz
you're going to end up killing your weed
and so they have to go with other means
of dealing with and controlling their
weed growth with their crops I know it's
confusing I'm talking about weeds versus
marijuana so the row covers go down
that's one thing another thing is they
use aluminum container ERS so we Growers
most of the time use aluminum containers
to Harbor their plants the roots of the
plants go up against aluminum containers
they're really high in
aluminum it's another thing that happens
too all these things matter when it
comes down to farming and it's all part
of why the toxic heavy metals are so
high in weed and
marijuana medical mum information called
the shot first talked about it for
years
years about how weed is loaded with
toxic heavy metals but nobody knew it
and it was never tested just recently
they started testing some weed and they
found it's high in toxic heavy metals
and everybody's got like a question mark
above their head and they're like what
how what
why I wasn't testing it I wasn't
starting a scientific study it comes
with Spirit of compassion and constantly
Spirit of compassion is proven right
proven right proven right so many times
to make your head been we have hundreds
now hundreds documented of s so's
information first and then someone
taking the idea from s so like whoa it
does have toxines let's what does have
the metals Let's test weed now and see
what it has in
it so let's dig a little deeper into
weed for a second but let's just do a
little check right here on what we have
going
on
so another thing too is there there the
whole thing it's not just about testing
weed it's going to be
testing it's not going to be about
testing weed it's going to be about
testing other things too like
people so that's the next thing like why
are people who smoke weed higher in
toxic heavy metals why is that happening
what's going on they're going to put two
and two together and they're still not
going to know why until they hear this
live so when someone hears this
live or here's a video that I put out
with this information on it or however
they're going to start testing people
and start testing people and as they're
testing
people they're going to find they in
their high in toxic heavy
metals so yeah interesting all on its
own all right so I just want to talk
about what we're making real quick you
guys just got on here we're making baked
mac and cheese we're having a really
good talk as well now there's no no
judgment on anybody who smokes weed
there's no judgment on anybody who
actually um smokes
marijuana but we're making some baked
mac and cheese in a little bit we're
making a salad as well I think I might
start heading there as we speak or we're
going to cover a little bit more
information on
this so if you want to grow your own
chickens in the backyard and you want
your chickens like really
pure really clean really organic you got
your chickens out there free-ranging it
and they're picking out bugs and they're
picking out things in the grass right
they're picking at things in the pen you
let them go if you got a little bit of
land and you let you let those chickens
roll those chickens will be picking off
stuff left and right right they're
getting this incredible diet of wild
food so your chickens your free range
chickens are actually getting all that
wild
food that's what's going on so when you
go and you go eat your chicken you're
like well I know the food I fed my
chicken chicken the problem is like with
weed it's not like organic farming and
even that can get questionable sometimes
but it's not like organic farming when
you got organic lettuce or you got
organic food that you just purchased
there's regulations that are really
strict with that even though there's
still fine lines and nuances and
everything else but there's still a lot
of strictness to
that so but when it comes down to the
whole weed thing it really doesn't work
like that so you can't take a group
group of every group of people that
work at a weed farm you can't Coral them
up in a pen and make them eat organic
food only make them eat this make them
eat that make them do this you know
they're not allowed to take any
Pharmaceuticals they're not allowed to
do this you can't Corral a whole ton of
people you can't go around the country
and around the world round up all the
farmers that grow weed and all their
workers and tell them that they're just
going to be going out in that field and
they're just going to be picking away at
Wild foods and wild bugs and they're
going to have this diet that's super
clean and no Pharmaceuticals and no and
no energy drinks or whatever else you
can't do that to
people so then all their urine that's
going into the
fertilizers are not like monitored that
urine is not monitored so when you go
and you consume that weed or eat it or
smoke it or whatever there was really
nothing there
to create a boundary of protection
instead you know when you got your own
chickens you know what you're feeding
your
chickens you don't want to go to
somebody else's house and they kill a
chicken in their backyard and they tell
you well here's what we feed our
chickens guess what we feed our chickens
we feed our chickens a whole bunch of
crap like a whole bunch of toxic stuff
and everything else here you are eating
their chicken and you're just like uh I
don't want to eat this
chicken I want a chicken in a controlled
enough environment where that chicken is
actually eating wild bugs eating seeds
eating anything else it can find in that
dirt that keeps it healthy that keeps it
pure at its purest form there's always
going to be tox heavy metals everywhere
they fall out of the sky but even beyond
that I'm just saying the cleanest you
can get with what this Earth
offers with what's happening with this
Earth so this isn't like an insult to
people who use weed medicinally
medically where they use it because they
feel like they need it they use it for
things they need it's not about that at
all this is just
about the mere understanding of how it
goes what's going on and maybe this talk
changes the system over time and maybe
down the road people who are actually
consuming weed will consume weed that's
not high in toxic heavy metals and how
about that wouldn't that be
great and maybe we actually have care
about it if people really believe in
their weed and use their weed they
actually the system can change a little
bit as it goes along where that stuff is
clean already there's people out there
like it's the miracle it's the miracle
medicine weed's the miracle medicine
it's the greatest stuff there is there's
nothing better than that it can fix
anything it can cure anything we cure
anything you know the people say that
stuff they say that stuff all the time
and they do that whole thing CBD CBD
weed weed weed CBD weed whatever and
everybody's just freaking out like no
it's the miracle hemp hemp hemp it's the
miracle
medicines meanwhile it's loaded with
toxic stuff highly toxic which adds to
the problem to begin with of why
somebody's even suffering to begin with
so it's almost like what how does that
work so maybe the system will change
someday they're already taking an
interest in looking into weed having
toxic heavy metals because of mm info
now they're going to be looking into how
people are you know are they highend
metals that actually smoke weed and and
they're going to start and maybe down
the road they're going to start looking
at growing practices and find out really
why everything's so cheap skated
everything's so Cheapo and then to the
point where people are just dumping
their own urine into the crops because
they're just trying to create a bud no
matter what high water or hell and it
gets done and that's it so let's start
making some
food and there's plenty more to talk
about talk about weed than that plenty
more about how it's not good for the
brain actually it's actually bad for the
brain something that's very important to
know I'm going to drop some pasta in
here if you guys don't
mind so this is 3 lbs I'm probably going
to just leave a half a pound out maybe
I'll do
that me I might be able to do all three
pounds in here let's take a
look there we
go I'm going to add a little bit more
for it there you don't want to overcook
your pasta when you're doing this so
keep that in mind you don't want to
overcook your pasta that's one thing
that's really really important because
if you overcook your pasta then you're
going to have just kind of like mush
it's not going to be firm it's not going
to hold itself up and that is going to
be a problem all on its own so kind of
just a reminder for people who
actually I mean but unless you like your
pasta mushy and and if that's the case
that's awesome totally awesome if you
want to do that why not a lot of
people a lot of people um like their
pasta overdone
overcooked this is going to cook fast
I'm going to remind myself every couple
of minutes I'm just going to double
check let's get that
going
okay all
right now I know when you talk negative
in any way any way with marijuana you
just get like hit like it's like people
just get so upset they're highly
protected they're like pites they're
like Watchdogs over it and they're
highly protected protective over it but
by no means is this an insult towards it
it's just information that I think that
everybody should know I mean I think
it's everybody's right to
know yeah a question right there what
kind of pasta are you using check out
medical me.com go to my
directory and you'll see what kind of
pasta I'm using
I mean we're going to make some killer
mac and
cheese so what I'm going to do is make
some cheese sauce if you guys are okay
with
that I'm just going to get a couple of
potatoes out if you don't
mind these potatoes are really really
hot right here I'm going to move this
okay I'm going to get the skins off of
here too now these are already
steamed they're already
preheated these are
warm the oven's preheated the 400 right
now let's go find a nice spot here there
we are look at that how much room we
have today on The Cutting Board let's
just go here now I take the skin off the
potato because you don't want the skin
on there because you're making your this
is the base of your cheese sauce and you
guys know I just made this pretty
recently okay so that's one I just
peeled out peeled back let's see another
one
here yep and I'm just taking the skin
off of course you can leave the skin but
you might have a different color cheese
in the end you you want to have that
authentic looking Cheese look let's
check this pasta cuz I don't want this
biting me in the
butt cuz that pasta will
cook no joke I already pre preheated the
oven at
400 okay so let's take the skins off of
this
one there you go and I might put one
more potato there Karen Spence says is
there a reason to take the skin off
after cooking and not
before well I know when you're taking
the skin off before you can do that you
can totally do it but then you might get
kind of a tougher outside the skin kind
of becomes the the place where the skin
becomes the protective sheath that get
takes the heat becomes kind of
like um beat up from it now I got this
just is all going to be kind of creamed
up easy in the food processor so that's
kind of why I do it if you skin it first
and you cook the potatoes the outside of
the potatoes that you cook cook you get
a little tougher and now this is all
just right there to that that part I'm
going to get one more
potato just in case I got one with a
little piece missing right
here yep so I want to talk about
marijuana a little bit more if you guys
are open to it I want to go into an area
where I actually was starting to go into
and I kind of got derailed a little bit
so Mar lot of plants get a lot of fungus
they get a white they get a white fungus
is what they
get so they use a lot of
fungicides on marijuana to try to get
rid of this white fungus so the plants
turn white and when they start turning
white they get a white film going all
the way up the trunk of the plant all
the way on the stems it eventually can
get to the buds
too and this is a big problem for
Growers out there and so what they use
is they use a lot of
fungicides on their plants now this is
going to be a decent amount of cheese
here for
sure they get a lot of pests too and see
what they do for pest control with
marijuana is they use outdated they they
there's auctions out there for outdated
pesticide in aerosol cans so the kind
one you go to the store whatever store
you go to hardware store whatever Big
Box store you go in there and what
happens is
that they sell aerosol cans that are Bug
Killers it's like kill spiders kill kill
ants ant killer right wasp killer right
let's make sure this doesn't get
overcooked no still got a couple more
M nice
wo all
right I might make two batches of cheese
real
quick we'll see so I'm going to take
some carrots that I steamed earlier I'm
over here you guys see the carrots here
they're going to go in here now I don't
like putting so many carrots in here
where you got so
many
I'll show you guys like this right I
don't like putting so many carrots in
here where it's tastes like carrot
cheese if you keep the carrots down a
little bit it won't taste like carrot
cheese it'll taste like cheese it's
crazy when you put all the spices and
everything else in
there all
right I'm going with
this
let's see if I can get this in
here all right you guys this is going to
get a little crazy just bear with
me kind of
uh kind of run it around over
here I want to get to the bug killer
stuff that's what I want to do want to
get to the bug killer
things all
right let's go you know how the medical
medium cooking show
rolls sometimes it goes real smooth and
sometimes it could be like a little bit
of a [__] show
right all
right feeling good about that that's the
pasta right there let's get this cheese
cooking right now I don't want this
pasta like drying up in there all
right let's
go all right guys that's my pasta I'm
going to move move this over a little
bit so what Growers like to do is they
like to buy outdated auctioned
10-year-old aerosol cans of bug killer
and then the workers at weed Farms take
the can and they just spray it directly
on the plant it's not M it's not like
regulated it's not like you know diluted
there's nothing like that going
on
and and so basically what's happening is
people are smoking weed with the blood
of that going
on
we're making the cheese right now but I
got to add the
spices I'm
nervous why am I
nervous but I
am all
right wrong
spice garlic
powder okay freak
up
nice let's go onion
powder all
right go little bit of chili
powder
Cayenne let's get this
going cheese is coming
together I'm adding a little bit of
water in here but I need some
lemon
we're going to add some lemon in here
too it's going to be
great we're going to talk more about
marijuana in a second we're just going
to add lemon in here what pasta is this
I see a question check medical meme.com
check out the
directory that's the pasta I'm
using all
right we're serious about this right
here you got the
munchies this is going to do it right
here let's look at
consistency
right Trisha Marie says I love your
telegram messages I'm honored that is
incredible right
there that is an amazing
cheese okay spiced up it's looking good
I'm going to move this
over
yeah
boom few sound effects right there let's
just see okay so what you want to do is
this pasta is perfect right now it's not
overcooked I want to show you let's take
a
look if we can
you guys see this past up
close what you want make sure you do is
you don't overcook it if you overcook
it it'll all start sticking together
because you're not adding oil this is a
fat-free dish you're not adding oil
where's all the oil you're not going to
have oil that's the whole point this is
a mac and cheese that doesn't kill your
pancreas I mean how how incredible is
that
I'm going to mix this cheese up with it
take a
look you guys looking at this let's hope
we're not so overloaded that I'm in
trouble in this bow
size actually getting
nervous
yeah let's hope that that's
okay now let's mix this up see what I'm
doing you
guys so this is going to go in the oven
in a minute take a look does that look
insane that looks
insane
aw I think you did
it all
right
so I mean if if you got a bunch of pot
heads at your home we don't have Poe
heads here but I'm just saying if I know
that people do a lot if you got a bunch
of potheads at your home man and you
make this do you think they'll actually
eat
it or you think they're just going to
order some crazy pizza at some like
really greasy Pizza
chain or most likely somebody's
urinating in the dough
anyway I don't know about that
all
right just you hear stories you hear
stories over the years okay so I'm just
mixing this up take a look you guys like
it I just want to get that cheese in
there as good as possible I'm going to
add a little bit more cheese I hope you
guys are okay with this but but there's
still some left and I'm kind of like
partial to this tastes so good check
this
out
there we
go look at
that I think that actually really does
it now you'll see here it's not o like
there's not I didn't use so many carrots
don't get me wrong you like carrots you
can do more carrots but I didn't use so
many carrots that it's like a you know
like a more of a darker orange cheese I
like it like this you can't taste the
carrots I love carrots but you can't
taste them
okay so the key is you want to mix it
pretty good and I'm I'm saying this
because you don't want an
unhappy person who's eating in your
house and you don't want somebody that's
unhappy because they got a little
section there that doesn't have a lot of
cheese in it you don't want anybody
like
complaining you want everybody happy I
think that's getting pretty good let's
let's pan it man let's pan
it
yeah I think we can pan that
baby boom let's take a
look I have a pan here you know I'm just
trying something different and's going
to bite me in the ass but I put a little
parchment paper on the bottom you don't
have
to go that
route let me show you also the recipe in
the book are you guys seeing
this you guys are even allow gloud to
see it cuz I know it's hard to find the
medical medium there we go you guys see
this I'm trying to lower this down to
the camera look at that all right there
we
go all right let's get this
down I think what I'm going to do is I'm
going
to maybe I'm not going to parch some
paper this one I'm going to put it plain
old in here that's what I'm going to do
right in the
pan
okay this one this is a heavy Bowl right
here doesn't look heavy that's a heavy
bowl and I'm just trying
to yeah yeah yeah yeah that's right I
got to try to get it this way you guys
got you guys locked out of that
one
let's get this in
here equally
distributed if you can just like you
see like
that here we go that's cheesy that's
good I've actually I think I've moved
that around just
right all right you guys in the oven it
goes I got the oven set for
400 let me give you a little bit of what
it looks like right there to the
close-up camera you see
that and then right there on IG can you
see that you guys let me not drop it
there you go in the oven it
goes let's do it oven's on oven's hot
I'm not putting anything on the
top let me put my aluminum foil on the
top no I'm not no aluminum foil talking
about toxic metals and and and
everything and PC Rivera says the sauce
looks so much like cheese only it's not
and it's healthy not only that here's
the real screwed up piece about it all
like here's what's really crazy about it
right it tastes like cheese it tastes
like cheese I didn't put salt in this
one you want to put a little bit of salt
in yours put a little bit of salt in
yours right and then you got that salty
cheese
flavor unlocking Infinity says what
about marijuana's effect on the
emotional body because I have seen huge
benefits not with constant use but
occasionally with subtle energy Fields
doesn't seem cut and
dry so you see what you're saying right
um look everybody that smokes weed that
loves to smoke weed they'll they'll
they'll say the same thing they're not
going to say it's bad like it's it's
hurting them I mean there should if they
try weed and they like weed and it feels
good and they like to do that they're
going to continue to do that ask them
ask them how it's working for them
they'll tell you how great it's working
for them like I said I told this story
over time and I hope my friend doesn't
kill me
but you know my friend is still sitting
on his couch smoking weed
and he's he's up there in age and uh his
wife left
left them years ago and she couldn't
take it anymore right great guy
incredible guy
but you know she first got into the
relationship and she was smoking weed
with him and they were both weed smokers
and they were happy and they were
smoking and then eventually she was like
I can't do this anymore no matter how it
makes me feel or how I can't do this
anymore and she felt like it was time
for her to um leave the weed smoking
world and so so when she did that he was
really upset and he didn't want to
change for her so he didn't want to
change he was like no I'm not going to
change for you we've been married all
these years and I don't want to change
for you and so that's what he told her
over and over again for years she quit
smoking weed and then and then she had
to smell it every day in the house and
she had to smell it in the living room
and she really kind of got to a place
where she was like just one morning he
woke
up and there was a in the kitchen and it
said I have to leave I'm gone and he was
like what and instead of him pulling his
crap together and like and really
working it out with her and be like all
right I'll back down on my weed smoking
I'll try to like I'll try to you know do
I'll try to work with you on this
instead of that it just he just didn't
didn't pursue and it's really sad treia
said that's what broke up my last
relationship on YouTube right there um
this is just it it happens it happens
really difficult for a lot of people and
my ex became addicted it was constant
every day so much so he changed his
attitude his priorities I could not
stand it I could not stand it exactly
and so I've seen this happen to a friend
and you know friend's a good guy and
everything but that's what he does it's
just it happens Jor
said weed gave me a panic attack never
worked for my symptoms a lot of people
say this so many people there's two
kinds of people in the world there's
people that smoke
weed and there's people that tried weed
and it gave them panic
attacks that's a big one right there so
many people that tried weed and it gave
them panic attacks it made them not feel
good in so many ways it's like either
weed two kind of people in the world
people that like weed people that
don't right that's pretty much what it
is in the end if you really kind of
break it down as far as weed goes but by
no means is this like
you know bashing weed smokers or
anything like that it would
never ever do that
because you know I know how life works
it's called A Hard freaking world we
live in and there's a reason why someone
started smoking it it's a reason why it
took on a habit it's a reason why it
took on addiction it's a reason why
they're trapped in it there's a reason
why they're doing it and there's a
reason why there are thousands and
thousands and thousands of people
homeless on
drugs everywhere right now all over the
streets or wherever and it's it's crazy
like and I'm not saying we did that
that's not at all what I'm saying I'm
not ignorant like that or I'm not like
naive or anything like that that's not
how it works I'm just saying though that
it it's gotten a lot of people and
there's people that say I can control it
I can control it I can control it like I
got it under control I do just parties
weekends and all that I respect that
whatever
and I'm not against anybody who's even
doing it but here's what I always say
whatever Vice you have or whatever
you're using that you feel is helping
you medically or however it is and I'm
not not dissing the whole medical
marijuana thing people you use it for
pain relief no way am I dissing that at
all like I said there's so many people
that use it for so many reasons it's
really hard it's hard and there
situations are really difficult I'm just
saying that you might be somebody that's
like whoo I didn't know about this and
maybe I can do this and maybe there is
some maybe I can get the metals out of
my brain instead so I don't need weed
people say that they test weed for toxic
heavy metals before it's sold people say
that all the time uh
sure sure sure sure and people saying
there's organic weed and it's free of
toxic heavy metals just like tat two ink
is free of toxic heavy metals heard that
over and over again and my tattoo to
Salon we use ink that is metal free
heard that over and over again over
again but that's not true that's not
reality that's not how it works okay
keep that in mind right there it's very
important to know tattoo ink is loaded
with metals because that's how you get
the pop remember how I always told you
guys I tell you guys all the time that's
mm info by the way out there once again
now they're talking about it like wait a
minute did you know vegan ink and has
Metals in it you know it came from mm
info but in medical medum books and
everything but the point is is that yeah
sure you know my organic weed you know
grower you know whatever there's nothing
toxic in here it's all clean uh-uh uh-uh
no way no way in fact it's the opposite
in fact they're testing weed now in fact
they're actually finding its high in
metals in fact it's going to probably
change the way weed growing works out
there because people are on to it now
because of mm info but they're on to it
and so it's going to change as time goes
on and like I said before the people who
actually are farming and using it are
still not going to stop their practices
their practices are like grow the
biggest
bud makeshift your fertilizer use your
aerosol canned bug spray that's the
rules that's how it works people always
ask if they're
urinating and cucumbers and other
produce no they're not they're not using
they're not using urine in the process
of organic farming I'm talking about
people use urine for their own backyard
growing their own little farm that
they're doing their own garden people
use their own urine they store the urine
they mix it with water they find a ratio
some even test it a little bit test
their own urine to try to find ratios
for nitrogen that's really difficult
really that's not really what they do
but some people are trying to do that
really what happens is they're just
mixing urine with water and they're just
trying to find the right batch and then
they go and spread it on their
Garden but with organic farming and the
organic produce and everything like that
you're not getting human urine as your
fertilizer for that so it doesn't work
like that I'm going to make a salad
circuit and working on that um if the
worker pees once in a while on produce
field that's much different than what
we're talking about here so if you got
an organic farm and worker runs off to
the edge of the field and pees somewhere
that that's not what we're talking about
here so if you're if you just got on
here watch this whole thing for the
beginning
yep let's start making a salad we're
still talking about weed and marijuana
something else is going to come to mind
too I did want to finish those thoughts
though about like spraying down the
plants they spray them down with the
aerosol cans as I was saying before but
you have to know that um there isn't
it's not like there's all these rules
big rules and regulations with weed
growing even states that are completely
open to it it's not like somebody's
coming in inspectors are coming in every
minute and they're like you can't use
this you can't use that you can't do
this you can't do that they they don't
have that going on yet it's pretty wild
west and another thing too is the fields
the very few Growers that are at
adhering to anything that doesn't
constitute the rest of the 95 97% of all
the other Growers including for sure all
the other growers in different countries
so that's a whole another level too of
understanding there no regulations to
anything the stuff is high in toxic
stuff stuff is high in plastic stuff is
high in metals it's high in it's high in
actually
everything um that you don't want
dioxins is a whole another one all on
its own let's let's start making a salad
we'll cover some
more why does weed give so many people
panic attacks and anxiety it's toxic to
the brain I talk about like a lot of the
brain obviously in the brains saer books
there's a Brain saer book right there
here's the brain saver protocols right
here I'm going to do a whole show on
like weed what it does to the brain and
everything else too so I'm going to go
into that
just having a coffee right now to try to
keep myself awake so I'm doing this you
know coffee but you guys know it's not a
coffee no way medical medium doesn't
drink
coffee I don't like
caffeine I know too much about
it and this isn't apple cider vinegar
this is apple cider so I'm drinking
apple
cider drink apple cider in the health
realm 10 years ago oh you're going to be
like you're going to be frowned
upon drink anything Apple now and you're
like wo apples are good for you 10 years
ago you can only have a green apple I
don't know if you guys remember that
fruit fear and we destroyed fruit fear
now everything's accepted in Fruit World
amazing all right let's make a
salad baked macaroni and
cheese it's cooking up
nicely all right
so I'm going to get the salad bowl
out I like the salad bowl looks pretty
cool
okay can I spin it nice I like that all
right F over there on on YouTube I
started I started smoking when I was 15
trying to stop all my
life first after I started M info I
was I was trying to stop and I'm so
happy feeling the world now I was able
to stop so you're doing okay I was just
looking
there so fja so what you're doing now as
you start to smoke when you were 15 and
you you really hooked on it and then
with all your life struggling with it
and then medical meme information helped
you stop that's
incredible um aw you're forever grateful
forever grateful that's amazing I'm so
proud of you truly all right I'm going
to do a rugula now I got lettuce here
you can do lettuces here um we can do
that I'm going to do an arugula salad if
you guys are okay with that I have this
fresh incredible arugula right here take
a look at that if you
want nice it's a rugula rugula is a
herb it's an
herb all
right I'm going to get get some Rubble
in
here it's an
herb okay look at that what an
incredible that's just starting it out
let's get some fixings on
it move on
over let got a few fixings
going tomato
heirloom
tomato okay I'm going to cut out the top
a little bit here a look guys I'm
cutting the top out right
here there we
go I want to cover the aerosol talk a
little bit more too we're going to do
that let me just do that while I'm
chopping stuff
up there we
are all right right so this is an
heirloom tomato by the
way nice here we
go and I'm going to cut these little
tomato
slices now you don't want to like you
want a tomato to look like a tomato in
the bowl so I'm going to try to achieve
that I'm not going to put them in there
that big I'm going to do one slice down
the
center that big actually
yeah okay I'm I'm proving been wrong
here the
moment we're going to put these
beautiful tomatoes like
this I would say one of the biggest
reasons
why why weed is so toxic with Metals one
of the biggest reasons is probably the
canned bug
spray used Direct ly on the
plants I'm going to do another heirloom
tomato here cuz I want a decent amount
of tomato on
here look at this one whoa you guys see
this one right
there oh nice nice let's cut out the
core you guys see this on IG you see
this ear Loom
tomato yep you you could put anything on
your salad come on you guys know that
you could put anything on your salad you
can do what you want Bo McGee this is
hard to watch because I know it is true
and my fiance thinks he can stop but
won't try to give him celery juice and
brain shots and offer compassion but
it's but it's very hard yeah it's very
hard it's very hard it is it is it's
hard
um yeah it's not an easy thing to do and
I'm trying to make a happy show here I'm
trying to make a happy
show
right I'm trying not to be a downer you
know like right I'm not trying to be but
seriously it's it's pretty bad stuff out
there it's pretty bad
stuff you guys this is really cool I got
the salad right here you can see it
partially and I'm going to even try to
get this tomato in the right there can
you see that yeah it's pretty
cool no yeah no all right let's get a
few more tomatoes on here you want
tomatoes in your Sal so when you mix it
up you want it to look nice and tomatoey
I'm just going to get a couple of these
pieces in here all right let's get it
cucumber
skinned all right and let's
get some of this tomato juice off of
here you want to you want to actually
avoid cutting yourself so easily make
sure your board is dry all that tomato
juice makes things slippery and when
things get slippery your whatever slides
out from underneath you and then you're
in
trouble all right I take the skin off
you see that skin right there you know
what's on that skin I don't care if it's
organic I don't care if it's the most
organic unless it's in your backyard
unless you raise it yourself unless you
Gro yourself even if it's organic farm
like organic farm cucumbers they're
sprayed with wax and MSG and nicotine
and caffeine all on the outside of the
um of the Cucumbers but if you and I'm
getting all that off that's why I take
the green off of the Cucumber you
guys would the world change if everybody
who smoked weed just smoked cucumbers
would that change
anything dry dehydrated cucumbers and
they just smoke
that now it's not just cucumber they do
that but cucumber's a big one they do
that with it's but that's not just
cucumber but cucumber's a big one right
there so I got most of that off feeling
pretty good about
that all
right but I'm just talking about organic
produce in general you know how it's
organic produce is sprayed with waxes
and all that filming stuff conventional
produce too but but we still we need our
organic produce we need our produce
whether it's conventional we need to eat
are you know herbs and wild foods and
fruits and vegetables and everything
else and leafy greens we have to eat
those so I'm just saying that one of the
things you do is with cucumbers unless
you grow them in your own backyard you
just want to peel the skin off if you
don't peel the skin off you eat it that
way so be it it's not the end of the
world I'm just saying that you do want
to do that now I'm going to cut this in
half and make like half cucumber
slices from what the recipe kind of
calls for
here all right so I'm going to do is I'm
going to knock some of these down like
this you don't want them too thick oh
wait you might want them thick you can
put them on your salad any way you like
I'm putting them a little bit thinner so
that you're not like stuck eating a huge
piece of cucumber while you're trying to
enjoy your salad so
the let's check that mac and
cheese dang that mac and cheese is just
about done that ain't no joke that stuff
is just about done
just about
done another thing too you know when
they use those aerosol bug spray cans
for all the crops for all the marijuana
crops you know as the workers are doing
it the workers are breathing it in
they're not hating suiting themselves
and they don't they're not wearing masks
they're just breathing it all in and
then they
urinate afterwards with all that bug
spray in their bloodstream and they
create urine that's even higher in toxic
heavy metals and all kinds of different
pesticides and they use that as
fertilizer wizer it's just it's like a
vicious cycle it just goes on and it
goes on and goes on how crazy is
that and in the end I know nobody really
probably
cares if you're sitting on your couch or
something or you're at a party or
something you're eating Edibles and
you're smoking weed and that's just what
you do you're not going to be thinking
about any of
this boom but I got to tell you
guys that's looking good
I'm getting this mac and cheese out of
the
oven any
second yeah that's going to come
out I'm going to get this out
now why am I clapping cuz I'm
excited I'm clapping cuz I'm
excited dang let's not burn hand or
anything
are you kidding
me I'll give you a little real quick
here hi IG you guys see
this whoa look at
that
boom
yeah that's right all right let's get a
dress
together
dressing I'm too Stone dressing man not
kidding you guys know the only thing I'm
high on right now is apple
juice the only thing I'm high on right
now is apple juice and your
company good all right let's get a
dressing
going
okay all right
guys I'm going to move this over a
little bit cuz I'm going to make a well
actually I could keep it this here
probably and make this dressing so let's
do this
whoa come on you guys right is that mac
and cheese look
insane or
what okay
okay let's go let's make this up we got
to dice up um a mango so I am going to
use
this I am going to move
this you're with
meing thing's
hot all right let's get one diced mango
one cup of diced mango I'm going to look
for a good mango here look at this this
looks actually really good let's
go oh yeah I'm liking
this look at that um let's get that dice
mango in this dressing
here just do a little bit of this here
carefully
so
um I'm going to have fun eating this I'm
going to try to open up two mangoes I
want one that's a little bit softer
too what's this one here this one
actually feels pretty soft is it
overwrite that's trouble you know what
happens is
that trouble meaning overwrite
you don't want overripe mango it's going
to have a flavor to it you don't
want
fermented all right so that's my mango
right there going to go with one cup
roughly
around
and let's go with that this is going to
get Blended up so I'm just going to kind
of I diced it so you can kind of measure
it a little bit you can make your
dressing you know like you can go
hardcore and you can just put whatever
you want in
there
y let's go pretty
great this is a good mango I'll take
it that's roughly going to be one cup
for
sure going in the
blender
all
right what else we got half2 cup chopped
red yellow bell pepper I got red bell
peppers
here you know what my addiction
is I'm going to show you how what I do I
cut cut the pepper like this you know
what my addiction is you guys show you
how I cut this right I just go like this
and then I take out the stem right there
and see how I got this little rent
ring my addiction
is throwing
fruit vegetables in the air I'm going to
take this out like
that done look at
that that you can take it out like
this what happens is though things end
up on the floor when I do it though
that's the only problem the addiction is
is am I going to be able to catch it am
I not going to be able to catch it am I
going to miss it am I going to miss it
in front of
everybody is it going to be
embarrassing you just get addicted to
that right okay so half cup of
chopped pepper
here am I going to screw up let me just
take a chance I can't help
it if I drop something on the floor and
I look really bad then that's just
what's going to have to happen I'm going
to have to get over
it that's just the way the story
goes it's half cup I'm going to put
about a little bit over like that that's
actually good nice goes
in love this what's next garlic
clove where are you
garlic
garlic clove you can put a small garlic
clove you can put a um a larger garlic
clove
in all right you ready remember you're
ever going to crush it like this want to
make sure the knife's out you guys I've
talked about it a billion times but you
got to make sure the knife is is going
that direction not towards you can't
tell you how many people make a mistake
all right let's put a clove of garlic in
there what next need lots of tablespoons
of lots of tablespoons of Lemon Let's
get the lemons
out
cruising
cruising you know what I do I like smell
stuff not because I just want to smell
it because it's like delicious and
invigorating and and vitalizing that's
not why I smell stuff that that's part
of it right I smell it in case you know
you got a bad lemon and you're about to
ruin your entire meal you imagine making
this gorgeous salad and then you've got
kind of like a rotten lemon you didn't
know and it's it's like fermented or
something it's been sitting on the
counter too long and you got company and
you all of a sudden
don't realize
it you got a bad lemon that bad lemon
destroys your whole salad and
everybody's like eating it and you can
kind of like taste something funny I
just don't want that to happen so what I
do is I'll
smell there we
go we're looking
good okay
that's that's some nice lemon juice
right there I didn't show you guys that
one I probably should
have all
right let's get some other stuff in here
too we got that we got tomato paste
let's crack it
open
tomato paste there's nothing in this
tomato paste that's
bad we're going to do 3 tablespoons of
tomato paste so I'm going to usually
gauge that to be about
this
nice
ready all
right maple syrup two tablespoons of
maple
syrup been pouring maple syrup my whole
life I'm going to gauge
that was that two tablespoons very much
well could have been this is a French
dressing okay and it's the finest French
Michelin star festar restaurant they
make this do they half teaspoon of
Mustard Seed
powder
boom half teaspoon of onion
powder boom and some
dolls right here it's Atlantic dolls
I'll show you up close up right there
I'll take a look at this dolls you guys
I'm going to dampen this then throw it
in watch what I'm going to do just hang
on I'm going to get a little bit of
water in here I'm going to mix it around
in the water a little bit like this and
then I'm going to squeeze the water out
not to get rid of flavor or anything
like that because I I want it to be
softened up a little bit there we go you
don't need much a little bit goes a long
way in this dressing so I'm going to
stop it
there let's blend it
up guys I feel like I'm on today a
little bit right like I feel like I'm
I'm on a little bit better today right
[Music]
you know like I feel like
I'm pulling it off
today let's go let's try to turn this
on salad
dressing you guys I feel pressure I got
a whole bunch of pothead friends waiting
at the door for mac and
[Music]
PE
all right we blend
in
all
right let's do
it so I'm going to put this in a uh
Bowl let's find a
bowl I pour in
here
okay
yep okay let's take a look at this let's
get a closeup bow on
this there we
go that's the
dressing all right guys I'm here okay
I'm going to put this in here like
that let's let's get this stuff ready
I'm freaking hungry man I'm like
starving I'm
starving
okay first things
first mac and cheese is going on
here okay let's
go
this is too hot to hold yeah it's a
little too hot to hold
still all right now you can you can do
this in many different ways okay I want
to show you right you can do this in
many different ways so first of all okay
um you can just take a spoon and just
whatever you can do it anything any way
you want I'm going to kind of like I'll
cut it in like what I think is almost
like a square I'll give it a try I'll
show you
here so
this macaroni and cheese looks actually
insane
okay I mean right or no
no
no um sorry but I want a big piece a
really big
serving yeah that's what I'm talking
about I'm sorry about that that's like
yeah that's insane you guys see this on
IG
right yeah you guys see that
now I mean I might put a little
more just around the side here cuz I
can't help it just a I'm a little mac
and cheese
greedy I can't help it that's the mac
and cheese right here on this plate let
me move this
let's get some salad plated
up
salad all right now I'm going to toss
this salad really
quick I might just scoop I'm just going
to scoop and put it here
yep yeah yeah yeah it's a rugal salad
right here just don't get me wrong just
get me right uhhuh there we
go that's what I'm talking about this a
rugala salad this time this is a rugala
salad that's the difference here and you
know what you guys I just saw an onion
in the back there I'm going to grab it
cut it open real quick if you guys don't
mind
whoa right oh
yeah
okay
yep
I'm going to get an onion out really
quick I found one some reason it was
hiding
Yep this onion was hiding back here this
is a sweeter type of
onion Erica says where are you getting
this recipe what huh is this the
Twilight Zone Erica am I in the Twilight
Zone mind in the Twilight
Zone
right this is the protocols book The
Brain
books and the French resting salad one
is in here too like
what I mean I me come
on like that's
insane all right okay I just want to
chop up this onion really
quick no no onion
today talking to myself all right you
guys um you can do anything with the
salad you can do anything with it
seriously but let's drizzle on some
dressing okay let's get it on
here let's go what do you guys think I'm
just going to put a little bit on
here okay yeah that's
insane now you can you can put as much
as you want on like you don't have to do
it like I do it you can put as much as
you want on there we go you don't want
it like you just want to do what you
want that's perfect it it'll actually
settle in there and do its
thing that
is baked macaroni and cheese you guys on
IG baked macaroni and cheese you guys on
Rumble
YouTube
Facebook there you go and that's the
salad too with the French
dressing right
there now I'm sure if like a French chef
was here they'd be like that's not we we
we mour that's not a French
dressing but no it actually is it is you
guys I'm going to take a look at a
fork
I got a fork right
here and if you guys don't mind I'm
going to try just a little
bit this is so good I actually you know
when it's so good you you just want to
dig in but you're
like like that
right yeah insane
insan I'm going to eat it with my
hand right out of my
hand when you're over a guest's
house and somebody actually hosts a
party dinner party and they invite you
and they invite you over
right if you want to impress them and
you're sitting down at a nice dinner
table and everybody's sitting around you
want to really impress them what you do
is you take some of your food and you
put it in your hand in front of of them
at the table and you just eat out of
your hand like this with a fork if you
want to impress guests not guests
hosts and they'll be really impressed I
promise they'll be so impressed they'll
think you have the best maners
ever you guys thank you wait wait wait
sorry
salad with the dressing
nice dude that's got no oil in
it that's got no natural flavors in it
no junk no anything this mac and cheese
is just
insane this this salad is
insane all
right I told you guys about mindful
meditation chewing you know you sit
there and you take in your food and take
your time and you have your bowl of food
and a little bit at a time and you chew
carefully and you mindfully eat I can't
do it right
now unfortunately that's how I eat no
Dairy no gluten no radical fats in this
meal no radical fats in this meal oh
yeah
if I was somebody and I was high on weed
or coming down off of weed this would be
the greatest
thing
ever Ronda says it always amazes me how
tasty your recipes
are I'm going to have this cucumber and
this arugula this Garden tomato is so
good it's actually like you think that
like why is this this
good
seriously
guys Co white spring you're
laughing I'm laughing too I'm laughing
too I appreciate your
comments hey guys can you give me a
thumbs up or whatever you do I don't
even know what it
is like whatever platform you guys are
watching this time can you give me a
thumbs up or whatever you call it can
you
subscribe and um can you like the video
if you don't like the
video it won't hold a
grudge not at all I'll have the utmost
respect
mhm hands down that is insane so insane
I'm going to celebrate with
a green scallion from my
garden you guys the medical medium
bulletin comes out tomorrow make sure
you subscribe to my newsletter so you
can see the bulletin come out medical
medium.com subscribe look at the link in
the profile in
description and anything else too
telegram messages I'm leaving telegram
messages did you actually hear the one
say the word
light from Spirit of compassion did you
guys
actually listen to my telegram message
say the word
Light Spirit of compassion
had me actually talk about what happens
when you say the word light how to do it
how to say the word light and um I left
that on my telegram have you found that
yet Spirit of compassion has to like
kick me in
gear you know I joke around too much I
fo around too much Spirit of compassion
says no you have to just listen for the
moment try to
listen pay attention and then
and then show them to say the word
light Anthony you are eating loud oh
yeah dang right I eat
loud two things you want to do when
you're invited over to
a a dinner
party what if you were invited over to
somebody's Mansion right at a dinner
party and they had like Butlers and
[__] and then you just you were there
you know for some reason you got invited
cuz it just that happens people get
invited and you're there what you do is
you want to chew as loud as you
can yes um um
Dutchess lady Duchess thei
um I don't even know if there's such
thing I got to tell you a story on my
pig farm versus a pig and was rolling
and [__] and rolling and [__] and
everybody was laughing
I'm that was so good so
good you guys by the way cold and
flu cold and
flu is coming our way new flu
strains blah blah BL blah blah but it's
true new flu strains and new bug strain
strains are all on their
way it's like they put them out there on
purpose just in time for the holidays so
everybody's coughing their brains out
and [__] their brains out during the
holiday season because that's what they
do
um anyway in this section right here in
Chapter 2 in brain saver
protocols
you got the golden rules of supplements
right so important to know I mean
they're really it's really important to
know that information and then over here
okay I got two pages stuck together
might be some mac and chees between
those pages of the book got the medical
medium shock therapies for Cold and
Flu important to understand this is an
incredible
book and um page 655 in medical me and
protocols page
65 cold and flu and coid supplements for
cold flu and coid for adults and it's
got children it's got the whole
different dosages all of it so I'm just
showing you right
here incredible information ask your
doctor what's right for
you
for all ages ask your doctors what's
right for you show them this book show
them the protocols and the dosages and
everything ask them if it's okay or not
do what's right by your doctors okay for
all ages the
protocols okay so they're for different
ages all right I'm saying that reminding
everybody because everybody's going to
be coughing and everybody's going to
be you know fed up you'll see it out
there you'll see different and stuff
it's like you're supposed to go
somewhere and the friend's like I'm sick
I can't
come
yep and you guys know about the uh by
the way you guys know about the vimergy
sale right now for this weekend which is
insane if you get up to $200 of vimergy
supplements they give you like a barn
basically
they give you three free products I
think they give you the D3 I think they
give you the golden seal and I think
they give you the lemon
balm three free
products the vergy sale right now vi.com
I endorse that company because of things
like that that's just one out of a 100
things company's just too good too
good I so it was just mac and
cheese Med medical medium mukbang didn't
want you guys to miss out on the Great
Deals that's why I'm mentioning it tell
everybody you know because it's your
chance to get a hunk of free supplements
I mean what I don't see companies doing
that out there I just don't I'm
sorry so yeah so check it out they give
you a free
D3 bottle of
D3 the best one on the market
for sure in my opinion they give you the
they give you a free lemon
balm and they give you a free golden
seal that's the lemon bomb I happen to
just have out here I don't have the
golden seal behind me right now but
that's the lemon bomb they give you
three free things for just up to
$200 for your
order freaking
insane like I don't even get it all
right I'm just enjoying this I'm going
to see you guys later I'm going to have
some more food um I just want to tell
you guys get a chance if you do get a
chance because I'm leaving
powerful messages on telegram I'm going
to leave another one pretty soon so kind
of look out for that so go to telegram
make sure you subscribe and so I can
leave you know you guys a message check
out the say the word light message and
check out the PMP messages pride and
preice messages and if you already
watched Pride and
Prejudice and you enjoyed it it was
soothing it was healing cuz I talked
about why it is listen to those messages
so you know why it's so healing and
soothing it's really an entirely
different situation it's that one that
situation that one film not other
versions so I'm just letting you know
check out the PMP information Pride and
Prejudice information on telegram all
the different past
audios like if you get a
chance Felicia and IG says I just did
the kids protocols for Cold and Flu from
that book 24 hours later the kids were
better so just did the the cold and flu
protocols right here from this book and
the kids 24 hours or better 24 hours
later and that's why so does this with
the information and that's why I am the
Messenger to deliver the information out
there love you
guys I'm going to enjoy the rest of my
dinner and aw's Bar and Grill looks
amazing
today thank
you
I wish Dr nesbet was here I'll see you
guys later