potato cauliflower mash we're live
youtube we're live facebook
potato cauliflower mash i'm gonna make
that i got some cauliflower here
and this is right out of medical medium
recipe you guys got that recipe now
because you have the book now right
so we're good we got the recipe got some
beautiful potatoes russet potatoes we've
got some cauliflower got some parsley
right here and i got some water
a boiling pretty excited about this you
guys
pumped up gonna be steaming
is what i'm gonna be doing steaming
elena hi
good that you're here ashley kevin good
that you're here
you guys you know i was like this do i
take a day off
do i um so listen i got a tiny bit of
water in the pan
tiny bit of water in the pan and i have
it steaming and i'm about to throw
potatoes in here
cauliflower in here i'm gonna make the
potato cauliflower hash
i mean do i take a day off do i just
stop working today
what do i do right and i'm like you know
what we got to talk about blood
draw a little bit because i'm telling
you
i don't think a lot of people get it man
i don't think i think they're all just
going to get the blood sucked right out
of them
and they're not going to get better and
they're going to do just just they're
just going to do some things that aren't
going to be great
good that you guys are coming on all
right happy easter
uh even that yeah happy easter it is
this means
it's incredible easter is basically here
um hey megan hey everybody
theresa tara sherry
whew guys are all here diana
um i'm peeling these potatoes this is
the cauliflower mash i'm peeling these
potatoes here
um
okay so that's what i'm doing
um making the potato cauliflower mash
doing this right now how do we find out
what is wrong with us
without blood draw no i want you to get
your blood tested
absolutely did you listen to the podcast
you gotta listen to the podcast i can
explain it all
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
link is in the description
blood draw bloodletting and vampirism
right i'm going to talk about lyme
disease as well today
i think lyme disease i'm also going to
talk about neurological symptoms tingles
fatigue numbness vertigo burning skin
aches and pains neck pain back pain what
i'm doing is i'm peeling the potatoes a
little bit
okay so that's what i'm doing i'm making
the potato cauliflower
mash it's not about how do we how to not
getting blood work i want you guys to
get blood work you guys got good doctors
you go to your doctor
but i talk all about how to do it to
protect yourself it's critical actually
because they're taking too much blood
from everybody that's what they do
and you know what when you're sick i
mean it can take you down a real wrong
direction
and really hurt a lot of people it has
it's actually killed a lot of people too
because they stay chronically ill
chronically ill and they get drained and
guess what the worst part
about the blood draw is the one of the
worst parts
is deficiencies they take from you then
they take from you more and you get a
deficiency now you're getting more
deficiencies you can get
deficient from all that blood work this
is so scary
um gene why don't you use
why don't you use the potato i always
use potato skins it's just that this
recipe
is a different recipe it's the potato
cauliflower mash and i'm not using the
skins i'll show you the recipe in a
second so i got some water steaming a
little bit in the pan right here you
guys
and i'm just just taking some skins off
real quick
right we're almost there and
i'll show you how how we do this so
there we go
it's another potato got that
got some cauliflower too it's potato
cauliflower mash
you know it's it's friday it's a great
day for this tara galloway amazing
podcast love it incredible did you
share it with anybody to help protect
them so they have the information
elena when i go fat free i feel fatigue
are you getting enough calories number
one first of all there's a couple of
reasons for that
when you're doing the fats it stimulates
adrenaline
so um fats cause the adrenals to
actually
flood so what happens is there you can
actually get addicted to fats you can
get addicted to
oils and avocados and nut butters and um
and you can get addicted to
cheeseburgers
and because the reason why an ice cream
because fats
they make the adrenals run because your
adrenals are trying to thin out your
blood
so that your heart doesn't have to deal
with all that fat in your bloodstream
right so the minute
you take away those fats your adrenals
you save your adrenals but here's what's
gonna happen
you're gonna get your adrenals nice and
strong any day you're fat
free you're going to get your adrenals
nice and strong to the point where your
adrenals are finally better and there is
no fatigue
another thing too is did you ever feel
fatigued before
is that this the first time it's like or
is fatigue one of your symptoms you've
been dealing with all this time right
so think about that trying to be your
own detective right there so i'm peeling
these potatoes you guys
um keep your you know keep your fats a
little low if you want
on the lower side you can do some great
healing but make sure you get enough
calories though
if you take away fats because fats are
so high in calorie
that's another reason why you might feel
some fatigue you take fats away
they're so high in calories it's why
everybody gets fat
they get stagnant sluggish livers and
they gain all this weight from fat
fat all the fat they're eating right
once you take that away you better have
some calories are you doing enough fruit
are you
you're also getting fat from every food
i mean fats are in every
single food anyway but those are just
more radical fats more radical fats when
you're doing too many of those so let's
do this
so i got a pan going right now
so i'm going to steam some potatoes i'm
going to steam these up for the
cauliflower mash
it's what we're doing cutting them in
little pieces here
rosie says i have i have lime
time four times i had lime four times
and i've had vertigo and
ra so here's how it works with
rheumatoid arthritis
that's caused by epstein-barr i talk
about that in medical medium books
vertigo is caused by epstein-barr okay
lyme disease is caused by epstein-barr
you see how it works
lyme disease is just an inflammation
marker
they don't actually find your lyme
bacteria
they just they're testing for
inflammation
and then they place the name of the
bacteria on the test
it's criminal but that's what they do
so what happens is but your real
symptoms are epstein-barr
i talk about in the book new edition do
you have the new edition medical medium
new edition the one that i was just
showing earlier
so you can actually learn all about your
lyme disease and how to heal
melinda you've healed me from so many of
my symptoms i am forever grateful
for uns so see linda thank you for being
here
thank you for working hard on your
healing process awesome i'm so happy to
hear that
trust me that means everything to me
because that's the whole point if you're
getting your life back then that that's
what gives
meaning in my life that gives me
like that's the meaning in my life right
there you get your life back
like to me that's what matters
so i'm gonna steam some cauliflower in
here too you guys
place it in here get this going
so i'm steaming cauliflower and some
potato talking about blood draw talking
about lyme disease and neurological
symptoms
season interesting neurological symptoms
are all caused by the epstein-barr virus
and the shingles virus right
okay think about this okay and what
happens is
you get all the vertigo and you get all
the vagus nerve stuff
and you can get some anxiety too and
tingles and numbness on your body and
tinnitus and all this stuff right and
then you go to a lyme doctor they'll
just say you got lyme disease i'll tell
you one thing about lime and we'll talk
about in a minute
about how it works so okay this is
getting steamed up
get the lid back on
get that cooking cauliflower potato hash
got five potatoes in there so that's
good
um
all right so i got some potatoes in here
steaming up good
um maybe i'll throw one more little one
in here why that that's getting hot
jane robinson what treatment do you
suggest for
uh him necrosis my friend gets one pint
of blood drawn every month and i'm now
realizing that doesn't sound good after
listening to you
well look that's a viral issue so what
happens is
um when viruses
um when viruses uh get into the spleen
okay and they get into the liver and
they even get into the bone
marrow when viruses get in in there we
can get that condition
and then what they do is they try to you
know they drain a pint
continuously to try to deal with it but
all the deficiencies happen all these
other things so
it's a matter of like how do we also
help with the deficiencies how do we go
after the viral issue and get that
better so
we get better and um and that's that's a
big part of it there it's about
going after the real problem that's a
band-aid you know they try to
keep things in check by doing that but i
mean look
the doctor knows best for what's going
on right there but what i would
recommend
if it was a family member or a friend of
mine if it was happening to me
it was happening to me i'd be getting
the books i'd be learning about the
viral conditions and then once you start
eating the right foods for the for the
viral issues once you start taking the
right supplements for the viral issues
then all of a sudden that starts getting
better and better and better and then
when it gets better
then they don't have to drain the pint
during the pint train the pipe
pine you know so anyway here is potato
cauliflower
mash right here that's what i'm making i
don't know if you guys can see it
so i'm excited this is medical medium
book one
with all the lyme disease neurological
symptoms and information
so what you'll find out there is
is people anybody can get diagnosed with
lyme disease anybody just need a
neurological symptom just go to a lyme
doctor and you'll get diagnosed with
lyme disease that's how it works
all you need is lyme doctor and some
neurological symptoms
you walk into the lyme doctor's office
we i'm getting kind of weakness in the
limb right here
a little weak in the limb um boom you
got lyme disease
you walk into the doctor's office i got
some tingles and numbness up the side of
my neck
side of my head i got a little pain here
that comes and goes
feel kind of fatigue you've got lyme
disease you go into a lime doctor's
office boom you leave with a lime stamp
on your back
seven ways to sundae got that lime stamp
that's how it works um so
but really all those symptoms if you go
into a multiple sclerosis doctor you'll
get
a mess tag most likely you go into just
an autoimmune specialist
right with autoimmune they'll say you
got ra
maybe they'll say you got something else
right but they'll say you got something
because they'll be like and they'll pick
an autoimmune disease that you have
it doesn't mean if the label is right or
not maybe they'll just say autoimmune
but any kind of neurological symptoms
now you just get tagged autoimmune
tagged
you know multiple sclerosis tagged lupus
cf you know cfs tagged lyme disease but
you go into a lime doctor's office boom
you got lyme
that's it you can go to 30 doctors and
end up at a lyme doctor and you got lime
you know lyme was this thing where
we finally know what's wrong with
everybody we figured it out we finally
know
we know why everybody's sick and that's
what it's about it's like
it's like we finally know it's wrong
it's that tick right there
that's what's wrong with everybody it's
the tick it's the tick
and you know so um you know and i want
to read a little bit about lyme disease
right here
but that's that's that's how it works
big blood draw
lead to vitiligo uh leanne
wow you had the big blood draws man you
get the big blood draws
and now you're sick sicker if you're
already sick
now you're sicker and then you're sicker
you need another big blood draw and now
you're sicker and now you're sicker and
that's how it works
i mean it's it's it's listen you gotta
hear the podcast though look i could sit
here and do a dance
for you guys all day long but you gotta
hear the podcast medical meeting podcast
at apple
podcast please listen to it share it
with other people it's the blood draw
bloodletting vampire vampirism episode
you can't miss it it's critical critical
you know um sicilies has any info on
endometriosis i got it in the books
my god true cause what to do supplements
to take dosages
right here and cleanse the heal it's
right here
and you can take the book to your doctor
ask him he's okay
or her it's okay what are blood draws
christine
blood draws are i'm getting a blood test
at the doctor's office he's gonna take
seven vials
five vials ten vials fourteen vials if
you're sick or got problems
he's going to take blood right and i
talk about in the podcast episode
too much blood and it all gets thrown
away why does it matter
that's your immune system that's your
immune system right there there's a
white blood cell your cbc goes out the
window
okay and when you lose your white count
now you get sicker and sicker and sicker
you know
and i'm noticing blood draws are causing
problem
problems with women that already dealing
with immune
problems they got symptoms issues they
got
maybe they got chronic eti's bladder
infections interstitial cystitis
maybe they got other issues chronic
sinusitis migraines
um uh weakness in limbs or just fatigue
anxiety depression and the body's immune
system is already under stress we're
already under stress and then
we get all this blood drawn when they
don't have to draw that much they can
draw
half vials they can draw less and then
separate the tests but you got to hear
the podcast episode
and then the immune system goes out the
window out the window out the window
your cvc goes out the window and then
your bones have to
go into overload and hopefully in three
four weeks you get your immune system
back
by the time it comes back you're already
not feeling that good so now you're
going to another doctor and then they
take blood again
and then the vicious cycle keeps on
going and going going
unless it usually takes months to
recover your blood back
your bone marrow takes time to actually
recover recover takes a long time
so very important to know i'm reading
the
lyme disease book right here so i'm
looking at it
and lyme disease book medical medium
new edition okay talking about lime in
here i got potatoes cauliflower steaming
we're talking about blood draws talking
about lyme disease talking about
neurological symptoms a little bit too
laura says the bloodletting show wow
that in chemtrails
that chemtrail show so disturbing but
grateful to know
what can i do to help my son is on a
regular
blood draw schedule he believes it's
necessary
because doctor says so you can still be
on a regular blood draw schedule
absolutely great doctor do the blood
work
but will he learn what to ask the doctor
because you can get your doctor to work
with you on that instead of taking seven
vials
full vials maybe you can talk to the
doctor and the doctor will take
three and a half full vials or
seven half vials so the podcast explains
all about it
um and no you lori you heard the podcast
you totally get it
well listen it's his doctor he just does
what the doctor tells him
you know listen to the doctor totally
get it but if i
was getting regular blood draws which
i'm not but if i
was that's what i would do i would i
would
you know listen i would definitely do
what's in the the podcast myself
personally
so i i got the lyme disease chapter open
you guys i got the book right here
we're steaming up some food i'm going to
make you a dish
uh marie marie uh
posa when i had tubal pregnancy
i had to have blood draw every day
that's what they do
that's what they do they do that so
we'll talk about pregnancy right now for
a second
so i want to talk about that
so here you are a mommy and you got a
baby
right and
you're getting your blood drawn every
single day okay
now if we're all supposed to be about
energy um vibrations frequency
frequencies
um sensitivities
if we're also worried about
subtle energies different variables in
life
and blood is being drawn from mommy
continuously or even partially just
maybe sometimes right when you're
pregnant
and i have known a lot of pregnant women
that get a lot of blood drawn
a lot and what happens is that no one
realizes
but it's stressful on the baby
okay because the baby can sense
everything that's happening inside mommy
everything every word mommy says okay
everything mommy does everything daddy
does
all right the baby picks up on voices
the baby picks up on energy
the baby picks up on stress so if mom is
stressed out
the baby picks up on it so when mom gets
a needle jammed in her
and mom's adrenals are flooding they're
just like
because you got the needle the baby
picks up on all that adrenaline surge
that adrenaline surge
if mom's in a bad mood and had a really
bad day
or there's a disagreement somewhere
something's happening
confrontation the baby's gonna pick that
up all that energy right
so what happens is with the blood draw
they take way too much blood from
pregnant women
they think pregnant women have plenty to
spare lots more blood
and lots of spare i think that's
probably one of the big
big biggest mistakes with everything
especially in blood draw
it just shows you that research in
science is so far behind and antiquated
and there's broken pieces of it in the
system you know
broken broken aspects of it and this is
a big one right here when it comes down
to
pregnancies first of all
a mommy's immune system is already
looking after the baby
because the baby doesn't have the baby's
own immune system yet
very important to know so mommy's immune
system has to look
after the baby so when mommy's getting
blood draw all the time when pregnant
that's mommy's immune system but that's
the baby's immune system disappearing
baby's immune system is disappearing
because mommy's immune system is the
baby's immune system
and um and it just doesn't recuperate
instantly like the the mommy's immune
system doesn't just all of a sudden oh
it's fixed it's great it's all set
now we're fine that's that's not reality
that's not how it works
so the baby feels all this so really
what they should be doing now here's the
problem you might be thinking well hey
what a bad guy i am because i'm trying
to tell
pregnant women not to get blood tests
and the system no that's not at all
i want pregnant women to get their blood
tested if that's what the doctor wants
totally on board but they throw all the
blood away so as i showed you guys and
demonstrated
a drop of blood is all they use in each
test
they throw all that blood away so why
are they putting mommy under stress
removing her immune system a big part of
her immune system
risking the baby's life with these blood
draws
and the in the protecting the baby when
they're throwing away all the blood
when you think about that this is really
scary
right um
talking about lyme disease talking about
other stuff too that's no point but
listen to the podcast episode you guys
you guys listen i i don't ask much of
you guys
i'm always at your service like i always
tell you
okay but please share the episode
help other people protect themselves it
makes a difference
so the medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast the uncensored version
listen to the blood draw episode but
please
share it with everybody you know and ask
them to share it
this isn't just about hey it's a cool
episode let me listen to it i picked up
some tips
hey it's coffee talk he's got some
guests on
he's talking about some cool stuff he's
talking about some aliens and
spacecrafts he's talking about
5g now this is this is like really
important this episode like
share it with everybody you know so we
can actually protect people
so important um
the bambi is a deer responsible for lyme
disease
well talking about lyme disease
now i'm going to tell you something
this little critter right here everybody
thinks causes lyme disease and
there's the little tick right here so
that little tick on the
bambi right there that must be why
everybody's sick with lyme disease right
but that's not why everybody's sick with
lyme disease i'm going to talk about in
a minute
the slime tick is going to get into the
deer's eye it's terrible spot for a
tick by the way and we are going to read
a little bit about lyme disease now
what else should i do on a friday should
i take care of myself should i go take a
run
should i take a bath i mean what should
i do no i want to
i want to give you guys information
because it matters and i'm hoping you
guys hear the podcast episode to protect
yourself
seriously it's that important let's
travel back in time for a moment to
november 1975 when multiple children and
young adults were developing
symptoms which alerted doctors to launch
an investigation in the area around lyme
connecticut
that gave lyme disease its name lime
first let's remind ourselves of the
technology
back then rotary phones
let's go there rotary phones
so they knew the causal lime back then
in 1975
when they didn't know what causes any
chronic illness but they knew what
caused
lyme disease interesting well okay
think about the technology back then uh
uh
there's a fire there's a fire
okay there's a fire
all right hang on uh let's see
9-1-1 didn't exist back then but
we got to hurry up there's a there's a
fire
technology is so really it's so good
back then
technology is so good all right wait
hang on oh
oh my finger slipped oh i gotta start
again the fire is getting worse
um hold on okay seven all right
seven okay seven okay
four that was a quick one because that's
a short number
four two that's a quick one oh nine
nine uh nine again and an eight
uh huh okay
i'm waiting here we got a fire
technology so great in 1975 but they
know why lyme disease is lyme disease
back then when they don't even know why
lyme disease is lyme disease now
i'm waiting here oh yeah um can you send
a fire truck
uh what you can't hear me okay
fire truck okay my address
uh okay well okay you're coming
okay okay bye
i mean that was technology at that time
right
right to get all these kids sick
medical research and science didn't know
what was wrong with anybody with chronic
illness and they still
don't know now what's wrong with
everybody with chronic illness they
still don't know
now right
but they had all the answers back then
okay first let's remind ourselves of
technology back then
i'm in medical medium book one please if
you
can go to the library get it for free or
go to amazon.com
and pick up a revised and expanded
edition new edition
on sale at amazon.com
first let's remind ourselves the
technology back then rotary phones on
the kitchen wall
no such thing as voicemail right and
sony was releasing the first
vcr guys remember the vcr the tapes were
this big
they were like this big you put the tape
in so i'm gonna watch
honey i shrunk the kids
or what am i gonna watch right what were
the movies back then
not even i mean we're talking a long
time ago i'm thinking in 1975
oh we're gonna put nine to five in uh
nine to five what's that movie now
that's even wait a minute that's even
later this is 1975. what's 1975.
we're gonna put in uh i don't know what
dog day afternoon al pacino what do
what was the movies back that 1975. i
don't even know
so anyway in the medical world kids were
getting their tonsils plucked out like
they were apples and they don't they
didn't know why
kids tonsils were swelling they still
don't know why now but wait a minute
technology was so advanced back then we
might have to make
another phone call okay uh uh
i don't feel good and i got to get 9-1-1
wait there is no 9-1-1
this is 1975. i gotta get to the
hospital what's the host honey what's
the hospital's number
what did you find it in the book the
telephone book what page are you on
what what page are you on in the
telephone book okay what's the number of
the hospital
okay six five three okay oh hold on
six five three
nine nine four seven nine
nine i don't feel good though
four seven four well my finger slipped
i gotta start over again what was it
i mean that's that's what we're looking
at
let's keep on going
even today there's no clinical
understanding of what's behind
tonsillitis technology
has made leaps and bounds yeah right
your phone's better
but everybody's still sick everybody's
still
sick you mean to tell me signs of
research didn't fix everybody in the
last 40 years
uh rose theresa we had 9-1-1 in 1975
really because not
i think everywhere in the united states
had it
um but i'm glad you told me
rose thanks for being here awesome
um well it looked maybe we did have
9-1-1 on there
out there in 1975. i just remember
i think in 1981 i think is when
where i live we had 9-1-1 it was in the
80s
early 80s anyway there's no clinical
understanding of what's behind
tonsillitis while technology has made
leaps and bounds
we still don't know why everybody's sick
and they still don't know why
everybody's sick today
there we are nope we did not have 9-1-1
katherine i i i didn't think we did
um yeah we didn't have tammy says we
didn't have 9-1-1 no we didn't
okay we're sim i don't even know if we
had it in 1981-911 maybe i'm wrong but
it could have been like 1989
were symptoms that have been seen okay
so there were symptoms that were seen
for decades before the lyme symptoms
appeared you guys
all right and somehow in this area
the illness was treated as something new
and recognizable
it most likely because of compassionate
doctors they were trying to get to the
bottom of a problem
okay so all around the world
everybody was suffering from these same
symptoms but they for some reason
thought these symptoms started
in lime right
so townspeople began looking for a
culprit and they landed on the deer tick
deer tick you guys right the deer tick
okay
so the deer tick
um but back then wait we had 9-1-1
back in 97 i would probably say not in
the entire country very small areas if
there ever was
i mean i didn't have 9-1-1 and 75 no way
um so it landed on the deer tick because
one of the patients reported seeing a
tick a few
weeks before he fell ill
that's like a train derailing for
reasons unknown and a passenger
mentioning a deer he saw grazing 50
miles back the clues didn't add up
so so you had a few people that were
sick they had some fatigue
a few you know and uh jerry says 9-1-1
started 1976 but only for 17
of the country right yeah i mean 1975
it wasn't there right but 76 it started
i don't think it got to
i don't think it got to we're up you
know where i was until
a long time so yeah
see you guys the whole thing with the
tick comes down to this
right so a deer tick
right was seen a few weeks
before okay someone got some lyme
symptoms right
during the summer right and
but that's that's not enough evidence
it's just not enough evidence
a deer tick is not enough evidence so
the culprit became all the deer
and that's what everybody focused on it
was all
sharon said connecticut 9-1-1 1981
so andrea says the nation's first 9-1-1
call was placed on february 16 1968
and haleyville alabama california state
statewide system initially launched in
but wasn't fully completed until 1985.
yeah
i i remember most people getting like
911 by like 1989
somewhere around that yeah
yeah and in connecticut was 1981 yeah
it's 1975 right just this wasn't around
it's it's isn't it interesting all
that's interesting
so the deer was blamed for lyme disease
okay no proof
they never found the bacteria in a tick
ever
just so you know i'm letting you guys
know they never found bacteria in a tick
they never found the borrelia
never found the bartonella in a tick
ever never did
never did but um
diana loves the visuals it helps right
you guys i'm steaming up potatoes
cauliflower making the
potato cauliflower mash so
the point all of this is and i'm gonna
keep on going here
karen says crazy that they name the
cause of lime from deer tick
how did how scientific is that haha
exactly that's how it works
so get back to this a little bit
going back a little bit more okay 1981 a
doctor announced he discovered the
missing link a bacterium named
borrelia that the ticks passed along to
humans through their bites
they never found the tick that had the
borrelia
never found that but it was a theory is
what it was
he was lauded for his discovery which
led to a series of bacteria focused
tested treatments for lyme disease
which started the process of destroying
a lot of lives
it was the perfect out for the medical
authorities no one liked
ticks anyway do you guys like ticks no
one likes ticks
everybody hates ticks molly what do you
take tests why do
ticks test positive but then when they
say they're positive with lyme
they're not tested positive with
borrelia or bartonella
um not at all they're te if people are
tested
for inflammation that's how it's worked
so
your blood gets removed and that blood
gets tested with inflammation markers
kind of like the a
a anti-nuclear antigen test if you if
you show an elevation of inflammation
the the lyme lab puts the bacteria name
along with
it they don't find the bacteria in your
blood
they never did isn't that sad and
when you learn the truth about lyme
disease might really get you upset
because you wonder why is there so many
devious sinister
corrupt situations in chronic illness
why there just is for a lot of reasons
one was to sell billions of dollars of
antibiotics actually more than billions
of dollars antibiotics now so we got 50
years
of lyme disease for whatever it is now
40 years 40 plus years of lyme disease
and with that 40 plus years of lyme
disease they've sold a lot of
antibiotics
and that's a big part of why it's done
it was a perfect doubt
metal meta the medical authorities no
one liked
ticks anyway and the theory of a
tick-borne illness fed into the fear of
nature already present in society
medical authorities felt they could give
up on digging for an answer
so let's not dig for an answer anymore
let's stop looking
let's stop looking it must have been
that tick
meanwhile the world was suffering from
the same symptoms
and much of the world all the people
weren't around ticks ticks were only in
certain areas of the world
but yet there were lots of areas of the
world where there were no ticks no one
saw a tick
no one ever had a tick bite in their
life their family members never had to
take bite in their life but they were
sick with these symptoms see how it
works
it's interesting unfortunately all these
tick
discoveries were wrong this is what you
won't hear
anywhere else lyme disease is not caused
by ticks
and lyme disease is not caused by
borrelia
and this broke lyme disease the world of
lyme disease is back
is this book doctors are now treating
lyme disease differently
they're treating lyme disease with cat's
claw
right anti-viral treating lyme disease
with cat's cloth
now doctors check for reactivated
epstein-barr when they're
searching for lyme disease so they all
test patients now for epstein-barr
because of this book
so now doctors are checking for
epstein-barr
when they're looking for lime that's why
you hear uh yeah i got diagnosed with
lime and epstein barr
i got diagnosed with lyme and
epstein-barr
i got diagnosed with lyme disease at
everybody gets diagnosed now with ebv
now
doctors never thought epstein-barr did
anything besides gave you motto and went
away but the book
taught on how it's reactivated so this
is the first book in the world that
taught everybody that epstein-barr
gets reactivated and causes real
symptoms
because they used to think epstein-barr
just went away now we've changed the
world of lyme disease including adding
cat's claw into the
regimen which is really amazing
so does anything happen when you're
bitten by a tick yes
good call good question let's talk about
that for a second
all right so i'm sitting here minding my
own business right
and that tick gets you and it gets on
your neck
and you're like what the heck what is
this
honey is that a tick take a look in the
mirror
is that a tick that's a tick right get
the tweezers wait
you're not supposed to squeeze it right
you're not supposed to squeeze it with
the tweezers you're supposed to try to
pluck it out so you don't squeeze the
bacteria back into you right so you're
not supposed to squeeze the bacteria
back into you right
um okay we'll just try to get a careful
ow
ow you got the tick oh no the legs are
left in me
i think the head of the ticks left in my
neck
ow ow and what happens is
when anything's left in you from an
insect
your body goes crazy you get the
bull's-eye
it's called the bite it happens when a
bee's
stinger stays in you if you don't take
the bee
stinger out and you leave that bee
stinger in you
you're gonna have one hell of a swollen
uh migraines rash heck of
one like you're gonna have that bull's
eye
is what you're gonna have spider bite
if the venom's in you or a little bit of
particles
proteins from the spider's venom there's
venom still in you
you got the bullseye you get
bit by something like a tick and a leg
is still in you the little bit of the
head you're going to get a bull's eye
yeah you can get an infection if it's
not cleaned up and addressed and a lot
of people the head of the tick stays in
turns into an infection but that's a
staph infection
that's a staph infection
that's not borrelia that's a staph
infection right there
that head of the tick stays in your neck
that tick gets pulled out
that's a staph infection
so many holes in the lyme disease thing
it's so sad
it's so sad so let's keep on talking
book explains all this you guys got to
read the lime chapter
it explains all the triggers okay and
i'll go over the triggers a little bit
with you too
in a second
so let's go just a little bit
when the research was taking place in
the 1970s and 1980s you'd suppose
researchers would have realized the
problem was happening nationwide and
globally
and today you think someone would would
have wake up and realize that hundreds
of thousands of people who have never
been near a deer tick receive lyme
disease diagnosis right
so think about science and research for
a minute just think about this you guys
i'm serious okay
this is serious right a few kids
came down with aches and pains
fatigue right think about this
some compassionate doctors wanted to
know what's going on
okay research in science
did not pick up the phone
and call other states to see if kids
were dealing with the same thing
i'm going to say it again how screwed up
is this
famous research and science
godly research and science top doctors
of harvard
top doctors of yale doctor top best
doctors on the planet
research in science didn't pick up the
god damn phone
[Laughter]
right a friend of mine's grandmother
said that the other day
she said are you going to be talking
about lyme disease
and then she said those damn tics
i said i said there's not the ticks
it's like 92. i said it's not the ticks
all right they could have picked up the
phone
and called anybody else in this
any state in in the country they could
have
called overseas but that's right
technology i don't think you could make
an overseas phone call
with this could you i highly doubt it
what someone lives in the uk
uh never gonna talk to him ever because
this thing's not gonna get there well it
is probably it probably would reach him
the point is though is that they could
have called anybody
anywhere around the world and said are
you
having problems is there any kids
entering your hospital with fatigue and
aches and pains
how about your town how about your city
but that
shows you research and science is so bad
and was so bad then and guess what you
think they fixed it
you think research and science was fixed
like it's fixed right
it's fixed the only thing they fixed it
with now
is research in science focuses on the
matcha tea
that's it that's it they focus on matcha
tea
women are laying in their beds can't
function can't drive cars
crippling anxiety aches and pains total
sickness every there's all the different
conditions we have
and they're focused on machete once
again that's what research of science
did
they first of all they tried to help out
three kids back then in 1975
said well it must be lyme disease that's
what they said
right they never found a bacteria in a
tick they came out with a theory
but completely bombarded hundreds of
thousands of women and children with
antibiotics ruining their lives all
through the late 70s
80s 90s 2000s and all they had to do was
make a phone call and realize
that if everywhere around the world they
were suffering from the same symptoms
that maybe
it wasn't a tick
it's actually sick demented
when you think about it so that's how it
works
yeah so anyway i'm just giving you guys
the rundown
um all right uh elena says i found a
tick of my apartment about six months
ago my god i freaked out
so bad we called exterminator
sprayed all this stuff all over
poor thing didn't even die so we sprayed
again
um if it was me i would not
do the sprays i wouldn't do the sprays
they won't kill really the bugs the bugs
will keep on coming back and all you do
is you're just spraying yourself
so of course you can spray if you like
to
i'm not trying to tell you different i'm
not trying to take i'm just saying if it
was me
i just would i don't think i'd be doing
all that spraying
pesticides herbicides fungicides a whole
bit
so
hooking up some stuff you guys
all right a little bit more
it's not bad for a friday afternoon
right we're just trying to have a little
fun
but you guys if you just got on here i'm
talking about neurological symptoms it's
not just lyme disease
here's i'm talking about lyme disease in
the moment talking about deer ticks
talking about that
got a meal i'm making right here which
is really great
but just so you know if you haven't
listened to medical medium podcasts at
apple podcast
please listen to the episode i'm not
just trying to get you guys to listen to
an episode
you know like hey i want i need them to
listen to this episode like i need them
to listen to some episodes like
i like why would i even care it's like i
got no advertisers on there in
commercials
like i'm not gonna make any money if you
listen to the episode like the other
podcasters do it's just
i just i do that purposely i i just i
want you to listen to the blood draw
okay blood draw bloodletting vampirism
episode
to really protect you okay lard
large blood draws
can trigger lyme it can trigger every
symptom to lyme
it can trigger every symptom to any
neurological symptom here it's a
condition you've ever had or symptom
you can trigger a symptom to a symptom
to a symptom you had years ago
it can trigger everything so the large
blood draws and that's what they're
doing they're taking they're taking
these large blood draws
and they're just going to set everybody
back and set everybody back and somebody
said the other day
anthony anthony anthony william why
didn't you tell us about this before
why'd you let all these years go by and
not tell us i did tell you guys
told you guys a bunch of times that no
one listens they're all like
my doctor knows best of course i'm like
okay your doctor knows best i gotta i
gotta bow down
i gotta bow down i can't step up your
doctor's best i'm sorry i told you about
the blood draws because they'll kill you
they'll kill you with those blood draws
but i get it i get it doctor knows best
knows he knows best i shouldn't be
helping i shouldn't be sticking my nose
where it shouldn't be
but i'm watching a lot of people get
sick so i decided to make it all about
the platform for now and like if i got
this little platform then let me
make sure you guys can just i gotta just
scream
i gotta scream scream to top my lungs so
i can try to protect you guys with
everything i got because i've been
telling you about the blood draws but
i don't think everybody's been hearing
it
all right lyme disease symptoms the
confusion about lyme disease symptoms is
vast
vast at this point every autoimmune
disease or mystery illness in this book
and in existence has symptoms that have
been linked to lyme disease
every single autoimmune symptom out
there can be linked to lyme disease
and lyme disease is not bacteria and i'm
going to talk about that
lyme disease is viral so it's viral
that's the difference so
here's a bacteria okay
here's a virus bacteria
virus bacteria doesn't
pee and poop out a neurotoxin
okay viruses
release a neurotoxin neurological lyme
and every other neurological symptom
people deal with
is caused by viruses releasing a
neurotoxin
bacteria doesn't lyme is not bacteria
just not
autoimmune is viral and you can get a
lyme diagnosis if you're autoimmune in a
heartbeat go to a lyme doctor you got
your lyme diagnosis
and guess what he's going to be testing
for epstein-barr because of medical
medium
millions of books going around thousands
of doctors
with the books they're testing for
epstein-barr now
they say lyme because the blind the lyme
lab won't let go
the lime lab they won't let go they
don't want to say they were wrong
they don't because if they say they were
wrong
all this time they're going to look
really bad so they have to keep
what they're doing even though it's
viral
why do blood draws kill over time
because severe deficiencies too much
blood being drawn
and when you're sick with lyme disease
like neurological lyme you're fighting a
virus
and as your immune system gets pulled
out of you and pulled out of you pulled
out of you you get weaker and weaker and
weaker
a lot of women have died with chronic
illness
because they lost their immune system
over time they lost the battle to
viruses
because their blood kept on being drawn
drawn drawn now i want you to go to the
doctor and get your blood drawn
absolutely but listen to the podcast so
you can learn what you can ask for and
do it right
and learn the information
tandy says i listen to the podcast it
made me so angry
all of the bs happened to me 15 years
ago
i'm so glad to have found you i just
bought three of your books including the
new
and revised edition new edition thank
you tandy
it matters this information you know you
know who knows about this information
i saw dr faun here he's here tonight
incredible dr
sherry green another incredible doctor
dr vaughn dr green
two mds incredible mds
look nobody knew about the blood draw
thing it's medical medium had to
you know get the cannonball out
uh dr faun per mm the tick doesn't have
the virus
the bite triggers the ebb thank you for
clarifying that
thank you thank you thank you so
the tick doesn't carry the epstein-barr
virus or the shingles virus or the hhv
six of the side of that megalovirus the
tick
right bites you right take bites you
whatever
the tick bites you and then you get
triggered because
the tick bite can lower the immune
system especially if a little bit of
a little bit of the proteins from
the bite or the tick's head really the
tick's head
pieces of the tick's head get lodged in
everybody that's how it's done
and that lowers the immune system
mc says i'm not a doctor but i'm here
i'm glad you're here darlene says what's
happening in that frying pan so let's
talk about that now
and rightfully so
let's find out because i you know
okay potatoes are done so here's what's
happening in this frying pan
i'm going to shut this frying pan off is
what i'm going to
okay you guys shut the frying pan off
for a second all right
is that okay and i'm gonna get a bowl
like this
and i'm gonna put these potatoes in this
bowl
so i'm gonna put these potatoes in here
these are definitely cooked
now i'm going to put the cauliflower in
here too so i'm just going to do this
for a minute if you guys don't mind
and
look bed bug bites michelle l bed bed
bugs
yeah that could be a trigger too just
bug bites can be triggers for a lot of
people that are sensitive and immune
systems down
just triggers that's how it works
spider bites so i want to get this all
in here you guys
just training a little bit of the water
here right i did a steaming in the pan
now you can use a steamer
right like there's all kinds of
different steamers you can get
i got some medicalmedium.com i got
kitchen stuff
at medicalmedium.com the directory if
you ever look for stuff
right now i was just doing it this way
it seemed to be just a kind of a fun
easy way to do it right now
so i'm getting all these potatoes and
cauliflower in this pan
um
the reason why i'm talking about lyme
disease today
is because by the way we're live youtube
live facebook right now
i talk i'm talking about it because i
think the people with
lyme and anybody autoimmune with
neurological symptoms they suffer the
worst
when it comes down to blood draws but
you gotta catch that episode but here's
the thing you think you're healthy you
think you're fine you think you have
nothing to worry about hey nothing to
worry about at all who cares
um you know i got i don't have lyme
disease i don't have neurological
symptoms i don't have these problems
i don't need to i don't need to worry
about it i can get my blood drawn any
old time anytime i want to but even five
vials full vials
done when you're healthy still sets you
back you start getting deficiencies
deficiencies lead to a lot of problems
and then we just get in trouble
could you add onions to the potato
cauliflower absolutely
you know what if you eat this meal
because it's a fat-free meal
okay the recipe is in here but if you if
the recipe is in this medical medium new
edition
but if you eat a fat-free meal
because this is a fat-free meal and you
want to put onions in here i'm fine
just don't put oil in there don't put
butter don't put
don't put oil butter don't put avocado
in here this is a fat
free meal for a reason because
everybody's inundated
they're fatting themselves to death
that's what they're doing everybody's
eating so much
fat you know what's funny you guys you
know like my friends they're like
when are you gonna give me a little
attention my friends are saying right
they're like
when are you gonna make me a meal you've
been cooking
for your other friends so all my friends
are starting to get mad at me hey cindy
lou
good to see you glad you're here i know
you leave a lot of comments on the
youtube
afterwards and i'm honored you're doing
that
michelle sweet and sour stir fry
so i'm just mashing this up there we go
okay and now i'm gonna mix a whole bunch
of stuff in here too you guys
let me do that two teaspoons of garlic
powder
so let me go into the recipe
so i'm in the recipe here that's
that's the cauliflower mash right there
so so i'm reading the recipe two
teaspoons of
garlic powder so we're gonna do about
two teaspoons of garlic powder
so my friends are like when are you
gonna spend time with me
that's what they're all saying like huh
i said you're spending time with all
your other friends
even on fridays and friday nights almost
every single day every other day
and then you're working between that so
you're not spending any time
with us you're spending every time all
your time
with them so my friends are jealous
about you guys
so it's like like well you know
so now this is going to go in another
bowl
the difference is i told my friends look
i got my other friends they're sick
they got like a lot of symptoms they
don't feel good they're working on their
healing process
you know and i just want to be
supportive i need them to heal i need
them to get better and all these
different demos and demonstrations and
everything count
sarah and blood draws weaken your immune
system is that what you just said
yes they weaken your immune system
terribly and it takes time for your
immune system to come back
and especially if you're already sick
you got fibro don't feel good you got
lupus you've got multiple sclerosis
you've got lyme disease you've got some
other condition a whole bit listen to
the podcast episode for sure
but we get our immune system removed
that's your white blood count that's
your white blood count that's your white
blood count
it gets removed then you get sicker then
they draw more blood then you're out of
specialists he draws he
he or she draws a whole bunch another
blood i mean it's just it's the endless
endless endless hell and they just
weaken you weaken you i mean it's just
people pass out all of them they just
say chalk it up
chalk it up is what you got to do you
know um
it's really incredible how it works
looking for another bowl here and
so i'm gonna make a nice now i made
a nice serving here for a whole bunch of
people
when you donate blood they draw a lot
what about that
they draw a pint okay
they draw a pint so i'm gonna put this
and serve it in a nice serving bowl here
and i want you to listen to the podcast
episode
i would like you to listen i mean if you
can
they draw a pint and there's ways to
protect yourself if you want to be
a blood donor okay i recommend
friends that i have that aren't well and
they're working on their healing process
they're finally working on some medical
medium tools
i got friends that they like they just
don't want to do anything they just want
to
drink champagne and dance all night
and they don't want to they want to eat
pizza when they want to eat pizza they
don't
want to eat parsley and then when they
finally get too sick
they end up calling me up and they're
like hey
what do i do listen to the podcast
medical me and podcast at apple podcast
it's important so
okay i'm gonna chop up some parsley
you don't need much you can put a little
more parsley if you want
okay or parsley i use it as a leafy
green
i like to teach about using these herbs
as leafy greens
that's how you get better too using
these herbs as leafy greens
you get better when you use these herbs
as leafy greens you start getting better
tandy says the podcast is amazing
it's a life-saving podcast what it's
going to do for people
it's just it's unbelievable and you
think nobody
nobody needs that podcast episode yeah
they do
they need that podcast episode the world
needs that podcast episode
a little parsley on top okay just a
little parsley you don't need a lot
and i'm gonna put a little sprinkle of
paprika on top too
so just bear with me for a second a
little sprinkle of this on top too
looks beautiful
so that's it right there that's the
potato cauliflower
mash potato cauliflower is all mashed up
in there it's got the garlic powder it's
got the onion powder
a little parsley on top too you could
put more parsley
you can put more um jessica says where
can i find the podcast medical mean
podcast at apple podcast link is in the
description
check it out it's life saving life
protecting
you won't be disappointed when you hear
it you're just going to be so pissed off
when you hear that podcast episode
you're just going to be so pissed off
because truth when you when you realize
you've been screwed over
when we realize we've been screwed over
and you hear it and know what is going
wrong and you're like
what is go how what what
sherry dr sherry green amazing md
every doc on this planet needs that
podcast episode i mean
sherry right it's that important right
look you know i want you guys
to have like these opportunities you
know i want you to have these
these like this information and
knowledge it doesn't help me
that you guys have this knowledge you
know to put out like
a cannonball like that
this is not gonna be fun for me but it's
like
if you know what i mean but what i love
is knowing that you guys are going to be
able to protect your friends your family
your children
and you know that means everything so
lyme disease
protocols let's head into the lyme
disease protocols a little bit i just
made this beautiful meal
i'm excited about that meal go back to
lime for a little bit i have the lyme
disease protocols in here you can check
out these protocols
so i just want to give you a rundown
real quick show it to you and then
there it is lyme disease boom
balabi hi mm what are your thoughts on
ticks carrying a parasite that lives
inside
the lime well my thoughts are this
okay i can tell you this okay a parasite
in a tick is not the same thing as
borrelia in a tick
and lyme disease neurological symptoms
so that's important too
another thing too is there's no
tick-borne illness that ever caused
neurological symptoms
the only tick-borne illness we've ever
had in the united states or
somewhere else globally has been a
fever but not neurological sickness
chronic long term so that doesn't exist
and parasites don't cause chronic
illness
parasites don't cause chronic symptoms
when you get a parasite in your
intestinal tract you either win the
battle
or you lose the battle there's no in
between
so when you get a foodborne pathogen
that's parasitical
your body throws it up craps it out
throws it up craps it out throws it up
craps it out throws it up craps it out
you're in agony pain you're in the
hospital you're on painkillers you throw
it up you crap it out then they drug you
with more painkillers until you win the
battle
and in many cases foodborne illness from
eating some chicken in a restaurant has
killed a lot of people and you lose the
battle
there's no in between your body won't
live with a parasite inside
the gut worms are different though your
body will live with a worm and you can
have worms in your liver you can have
worms in your body
but the worms don't cause neurological
symptoms either anyway you guys heading
off to
tick tock heading off to ig going there
now
please check out the podcast when you
can
right really important link is in the
description on the podcast episode don't
miss it share it with somebody
i'm keeping light-hearted about it
tonight but that podcast episode can
save
someone's life long-term short-term
so many people are affected by it it's
unbelievable i'll see you guys in tik
tok
and ig head in there now and then we
might do some more ig's after that
letting you know like
celery juice benefits celery juice heals
we'll see we got
we got some work to do tonight i love
you guys