we speak right now and i want to talk
about why it changes lives like why does
the brain meditation
do what it's doing for people like how
is it possible
and i want to talk about how you can use
it as a sleep aid too you can actually
use it while you can use it to fall
asleep and
it does what it needs to do as you fall
asleep
that's another powerful thing which is
amazing so
like your subconscious mind is still
doing the meditation
as you're sleeping that's what's
incredible about it so talking about the
brain meditation
it was released today and i hope you
guys
you know experienced it already i hear
some people are doing it three times a
day
some people are doing it two times a day
people are crying when they do that has
that happened with you
are you are is it bringing you to tears
because i'll tell you why that happens
what kind of release that occurs
during the brain meditation hi so
i want to talk about all that good
evening so glad you guys are here going
to talk about the brain meditation and
the power it has
and what it's doing for people and i'm
i'm curious to know how it's going for
you guys too so if you want to
let me know how you're feeling with it
and what's happening there yeah the
brain meditation
janet it was it was powerful did you try
that hi you guys
hi michelle um it you know it's really
one of these things where
i had to make sure that you guys
have this tool because here's what goes
on when we go through losses
betrayals broken hearts broken
friendships broken relationships
dorina you fell asleep while listening
so and um
alexandra hi anthony i did the brain
meditation twice today
oh my god incredible i felt nauseous the
first time why
the second i fell asleep afterwards that
was a release
so that's what that was when fear leaves
us
it it it what happens is that nausea
that's the vagus nerve the vagus nerve
is attached to the emotional center of
your brain
the emotional center of your brain is
is holding on to all this fear even if
you don't know
it's holding on to this fear from maybe
a relationship
uh breakup that happened years ago or
confrontation
or a loss or a heartache or broken trust
or a friendship of some kind that may
not any kind of hurt or wounds or maybe
a great loss
and what happens is that fear sits
inside
of us and it it creates a gap
between the soul and our physical brain
so
when that fear leaves and it's leaving
that's why it's important to do the
brain meditation more than once
do it twice or do three times alexandra
i'm really
happy that you did it more than once
because
then it's only gets better because
you're releasing that much fear and that
much fear and then
the bridge comes together the bridge
actually comes together between your
soul
and your physical brain the emotional
center of your physical brain and this
bridge comes together
and it starts to close the gap because
that gap
was filled with fear as we go through
hardships that gap
opens and opens and opens and it gets
filled with fear
and so this powerful brain meditation
releases that fear so the gap gets
filled so
so your soul comes back to the emotional
center of the brain so it starts to
reconnect again
because then we get depersonalization
when fear is sitting in there
we get mild bouts of depression we get
mild
mild issues anxiety all kinds of
different things that happen along the
way
we can't trust anymore so the brain
meditation
is a way to get rid of that fear so that
the soul can come back and
heal and that connection can be made and
it's really powerful
really really powerful and you can fall
asleep during it
which is incredible because it's still
going to have an effect it's still going
to work you can do the brain meditation
as a sleep meditation every single night
what it can do to help you heal can take
you to a whole nother level
okay so i want to tell you where you can
find the meditation the brain meditation
so
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
so that's where you can find it so make
sure you subscribe to the medical medium
podcast at apple podcast
so you can get notified and you get
notified right away as the episode comes
out it already came out today it's a
really exciting time
so many people are getting so much help
and they're doing so good they're
healing from
this brain meditation and i want you to
know that that
i i chose apple podcast to be the
official platform because
it's uncensored for for medical medium
it's uncensored
and you can hear the entire episode now
other platforms i can't guarantee that
and it just it won't be like that it
will upload right you'll be missing
pieces even if the minutes on the
episode are the same
it's not the same those are censored
that's the whole point this is an
uncensored
podcast on apple podcast now if you
don't have an apple device and you have
an
android or some kind of other device and
you're like well how am i going to
listen to this
well go to medicalmedium.com okay look
at the menu you'll see
podcast in the menu at medicalmedium.com
just download the link of the the
podcast and you can hear the episode
it's incredible hey you guys uh marissa
says
i just listened to the podcast the
ending was super trippy
loved it i'm going to listen to it again
tonight as i fall asleep marissa it's
incredible for using to fall asleep
because you can rid
fear out of that out of
your body out of your brain at the
emotional center of your brain as you're
falling asleep you can rid the fear
as you're falling asleep you can because
your subconscious is still
doing the meditation as you're falling
asleep
and it's really powerful like that
elizabeth
says i cried during the entire
meditation it happens a lot most people
are going to cry
and because it's that healing from a
deep level so he cried during the entire
meditation
and felt a deep loss i felt before thank
you for sharing anthony
if you can you do the meditation again
and you do it again and you make sure
any kind of fear that happened during
that deep loss keeps on
leaving so it works more and more jody
said
did brain meditation today extremely
emotional
lots of tears but felt like some weight
was lifted
we'll be doing this every day jody a
weight was
lifted that was trapped fear that
creates this divide between the soul
and your physical brain and body how
does this happen
when you get when things happen to you
in your life trauma or
loss or any kind of ptsd that you've
been suffering with or any kind of
emotional blow that you've ever had
what happens the soul comes out of body
a little bit that's what happens to us
like
you get this news like oh my god what
just happened i just got hurt
i just got hurt emotionally i got a
broken heart now and
you have this out of body experience for
a moment and when that happens
fear fills the gap and but the fear
doesn't go away
it stays there and minute there's other
meditations don't rid that fear
it won't go anywhere this is actually
designed to pull that fear out
so the soul comes together with the
physical part of your body
and it fills that gap and then that
weight is lifted
that weight is lifted it's so important
so um and the link is in the description
okay so link is in the description of
this live
so so the apple podcast link is in the
description
of this live so you can find out how to
go and do this
um
well i appreciate you too tina i'm so
glad that you're here
ivana says looks like i missed the
meditation
where do i find it and what's it called
it's the brain meditation
okay and it's at uh it's medical medium
podcast at
apple podcast and it's the brain
meditation it's the third episode
now i want to give you a forewarning
okay the first episode chemtrails
is a really scary episode okay and it's
shocking okay so i'm just letting you
know this is an uncensored podcast
and in the sense where the the
information is so
powerful and no one's ever heard about
it before and it could be shocking the
information
that kind of uncensored and then there's
the fruit fear episode
and then there's the brain meditation
episode and the details are
in these episodes meaning like when you
hear the chemtrail episode the details
just mind-blowing
because someone might heard of
chemtrails but they really haven't heard
anything
about what was really going on because
that information doesn't exist besides
the medical medium information so when
you hear it it's like oh my god it's
mind-blowing
and you'll connect all the dots when you
hear all the details and then the fruit
fear episode
very groundbreaking and and and in the
shocker too and then
the brain meditation episode is the
third episode
okay powerful meditation that i've had
family and friends do
all through these years like 35 plus
years when spirit of compassion
gave me this meditation now the
meditations medical medium are not
man-made it's not like a guy's idea and
then he got it from this guy's idea and
then
they kind of blended their ideas and now
it became popular down the road and
someone's trying to meditate with this
idea
this is from above so this is not
man-made so because it's not man-made
it's super powerful and it does the job
and that's the key it does the job so if
the spirit of compassion tells me this
reds fear
it's going to rid fear and it does and
it has i've used it for friends and
family that were suffering from ptsd
for many many years and i've used this
to rid that to rid the fear
from trauma and loss and it's really
really powerful but it's emotional too
you may cry
as you're ridding that it could feel
like a weight's been lifted off of you
which
exactly which happens there's just so
much going on there
so we're so sharon says where's the
brain meditation so
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
you'll see the link
in the description of this live look at
the link in the description of this live
okay if you don't have an apple device
and you have an android or something
just go to medicalmedium.com look at the
menu
the podcast menu and and download the
the episode you can't miss it you have
to you're
i just saw a comment the comments are
going up that
um so uh so you're gonna do you're gonna
do it after
after work incredible i hope you do this
and you can do this
when sleeping too when you're when when
you're getting ready to go to bed
and all of this
incredible so i want to tell you guys a
couple of things about how it works when
you do the brain meditation
and i'm going to answer comments too i'm
looking at the monitor to answer
comments
and the brain meditation is unlike
anything out there
and it's life-changing gina says i did
the meditation this morning it really
does
work it it i i've been doing it
and i and i'm the one that did the
medicine you know i'm the one that did
the meditation for you guys to have it
and i do it i use it i use it
it's that powerful it's that powerful
and um so um you can you can listen to
you can listen to this episode at apple
podcast
so medical medium podcast at apple
podcast and you can hear the episode
it's really really powerful so what this
does what the brain meditation does
okay with which nothing else like this
does this
is it reconnects your soul to your
physical body because when you get
delivered
uh jarring news like a loss or
maybe somebody cheated on you or a
friendship didn't work out and you've
been really
hurt or you lost a loved one or you had
a bad experience or a bad emotional
experience
well we have this fear that builds up
between our soul
and our physical brain and the soul
every time we get delivered bad news
we have this out of body shock and our
soul just gets shocked and it gets out
of body for a second it's like a
protection method
but it never realigns back again because
fear fills in the gap
old wounds old emotional wounds from
that fear gets filled into the gap
what this exercise does what this brain
meditation does
is it pulls the fear out of the middle
so that your soul can come close and
reconnect with your physical brain your
neurons in the emotional center of your
brain
up here so in the emotional center of
the brain so it's critical
and then what happens then is you have
this weight lifted off
you start healing you may cry during
this and
you everything starts to just improve
emotionally
mentally clarity the healing that can
happen
and if you're somebody that has a
difficult falling sleep try this as a
sleep meditation too because
or just even if you don't have a
difficulty falling asleep use it as a
sleep meditation
every single night so that when you fall
asleep and the meditation is going
that that subconsciously it's happening
for you so you're doing your healing
share it with people too please do um
okay lou demilla it was very special for
me
i couldn't concentrate first and then i
fell asleep and afterwards i felt
relieved
wanted to repeat it again so we'll do
before bedtime
it's probably one of the best times is
every night before bed
you could do it in the morning you could
do it in the middle of the day you could
do it
before a nap if you have a chance to
ever take a nap for a minute
and i know you guys are so busy many of
you and but before bed
every single night the the
amount of healing that could be done
with a soul
if you do this meditation every single
night
it's just it's unbelievable it's just
epic um the details of how to find this
brain meditation
are in the description of this live so
just so you know and you can also
medical medium podcast that apple
podcast you can go and you know
just right there it's a guided
meditation
so it's a guided meditation so i guide
you through
each step i do the work for you
and then just let you heal so that's
what's so important about this brain
meditation
please know that my job is to do the
work for you
so that you can then access the power of
this meditation
and heal and not be stressed out and not
be
you know working hard because what
happens is if you work hard to try to
meditate
everything gets lost that's not what
happens here this is i'm doing the hard
part
you're you're doing now the healing
you know i hold your hand through this
meditation so you can heal so no matter
what
this happens for you um
haley says does it work if you are angry
yes because the anger
what happens with anger is that anger
usually starts because we get fearful
and fearful
and fear is trapped in us and it's
trapped between our soul and our
emotional brain so our physical
emotional brain so we get we get this
fear that's trapped in us and that can
easily trigger off fear
and anger too in so many ways deep
seated
and it's incredible for that to help rid
that if you feel anger coming on
you can you're welcome to do this and do
this before bedtime too
really important please leave a review
if you guys can too at apple podcast so
other people can
hear it and there's or the other people
can look to see the reviews they go oh
my god i want to try this and please
share
i want to tell you something special i
think it's special anyway and you guys
might think so there's no sponsorships
there's no infomercials there's no
advertisements
you're not going to have an infomercial
in the middle of this podcast you're not
going to have
advertisements before it there's none of
that it's a free resource please share
it for everybody
to everybody and um and and so the brain
meditation is that powerful okay
the reason why it's on apple podcast is
because the official platform
i chose was apple podcast because i can
trust that it's uncensored
and other platforms if you think if you
think you heard one of my old radio
shows
that you listen to on other platforms
i'm going to tell you right now
i've always been censored on all of
those so
um and so what happens with this it's
not it's uncensored so even if it looks
like the same minutes that
you see on another platform and you want
to measure it and be like well it
doesn't look like it looks the same
it's not it's not little pieces
fragments are missing
that's how it's done it's just
unbelievable really
so but um but so much healing can be
done
when you do the sprain meditation i
recommend doing it every single night so
you can heal while falling asleep
you could do it in the morning do it at
night
and so important so fabio says anthony i
am going to share the meditation with
all my siblings bless your heart god
bless you fabi
i thank you for doing that because you
can help them heal
and please do that share it with anybody
you can
that you feel you want to share with of
course
janice says oh my god this is going to
help a lot of people thank you for
sharing your gifts
thank you for being here thank you for
being on this live with me right now
we're live right now and it's so great
to have you guys right here
it really is and just remember though
the three new podcast because that's
what it is it's three podcasts on this
new
medical medium podcast it's it there's
i've already
released three episodes is what i did so
that's that's what i did not three but
three episodes
and the first episode is chemtrails
second episode is fruit fear
both of those really intense not for the
faint of heart
uh mind-blowing information mind-blowing
information if you haven't heard those
episodes yet
and the third episode is the brain
meditation
um so i'm talking about the brain
meditation tonight
what's what i'm doing um so
honey says oh well i only have a cell
phone
i never seem to be able to find podcast
my bad luck
um the link of the podcast honey is in
the description
so see if you can just you know get that
link or go to medicalmedium.com
all right go to medicalmedium.com and
see if you can find the link
on the menu there for the podcast um
so michelle l says i have experience
that out of body during a traumatic
experience michelle
it's i'm sorry that you've even gone
through that and you experienced that
and i'm really sorry about that
and because no one should have to go
through these experiences and these
traumatic experiences
and what happens is when you get that
shock i mean
look you know you know this you know
this i mean it's not like i'm telling
you something you don't know michelle
and when you go through that shock it
just knocks the soul right out of you
and just knocks it right out of you and
it just hovers
the outer body when you get that trauma
when you get that
news when you get that experience it
just knocks it out of you like this
and it's so hard it's so hard and so um
to bring that back and make that
connection to get
those wounds out and that fear out this
brain meditation does this and i'm
honored you're here michelle
thank you for helping so many like you
do thank you for doing all the work that
you do to help so many others
get information i'm just so blown away
every time just so you know
i see your comments and everything and
i'm just always just blown away
but um but so important
um how this works with all of this and
but i want you to know that when you do
the brain meditation
you can do it at night too instagram is
censored yes it is
yep exactly and the other platforms that
my old radio show was on a censored and
if you listen if you find this podcast
on other platforms if you find this
medical media podcast
with the brain meditation and everything
else on other platforms and the
chemtrails
and the fruit fear it's i can't
guarantee it's
not censored so that's why apple podcast
is the is the choice
that i chose um
so and i'm just reading some i'm reading
some comments here
and what you're going to feel you you
might cry so many people cry during this
brain meditation
so that can happen right there um
i'm reading comments right now on the
monitor so it takes a second you guys
thanks for hanging in there with me
and i want to talk about what happens
like i said
with that connection so the brain
meditation
brings the strengthens the bridge and
gets rid of the gaps in the bridge
that's what it is the brain meditation
so the soul and the physical brain can
come together and the fear leaves
it's critical to mend the wounds
in the bridge that's happening there
it's critical to mend those wounds
and the brain meditation is the only is
the only powerful tool
i've ever seen out there from that from
my source or any
source that does this so that you can
have that healing and if you do it every
night what it can do is just
unbelievable um barbara says that
meditation is unbelievable i just said
unbelievable
i cried really hard at the end thank you
anthony
barbara thank you for doing the
meditation because then i know that
that you're taking care of yourself and
you're working on your healing process
and that matters to me because what am i
if you're not doing that
i mean that's the whole point i'm here
so you can have that
chance and do that and heal i i need you
to do those things to help heal
um francine says the chemtrail one
just was so informative such validation
for the contrail versus chemtrail
argument
wasn't it francine is that unbelievable
like the whole thing how the difference
the contrail and the chemtrail that's
episode one of the medical medium
podcast the official medical meeting
podcast
the chemtrail episode um
catherine says anthony anthony i
couldn't stop crying
it it it gets me it gets me when
when when i listen to it you know and
what happens is that
the 35 years of of doing this work
and i've seen so much pain and suffering
for so many years
for so long and i've seen this and
i've lived it with so many i've
experienced it through so many people
with their
losses and their suffering and
everything else that you know i take on
so much and i like the the brain
meditation because i know that
many of you guys take on a lot with
people around you throughout your life
and you take on a lot because
you have this compassionate the good
intentions and the compassions and and
with it
and it's just what happens and it's
that's why this is so good for so many
reasons
it's so good the brain meditation is
that powerful and that good for so many
reasons
um
so i so you can find it i'm i'm reading
through the uh
the comments right now so you can find
it at
uh apple podcast it's the medical
meeting podcast
official podcast at apple podcast okay
that's where you can find it
the link is in the description so you
know of this live right now
okay if you don't have any if you have
an android and you don't have an apple
device
go to medicalmedium.com go to the menu
and in the podcast in the menu and make
sure you download the links
you can listen so important it's a
guided
guided meditation the brain meditation
it's like i
guide you through it personally guide
you through it
so you can do the healing and you can
move forward
thank you for everything you do you guys
are amazing
really are and
it's a lot of a lot of trolls in spam
seems to be on the comments section
tonight so i'm trying to
find some comments
yep it's that apple podcast that's where
it is so
it works there's a question right there
elsie says asks
does it work if you fall asleep while
it's happening i mean elise
sorry yeah elise yes it works
while you while you fall asleep or if
you fall asleep while it's happening the
reason why
is is your subconscious brain your
subconscious mind
is actually hearing the entire episode
when you're sleeping
so and i'm doing the work for you that's
the difference
so i'm doing the work for you so you
have every opportunity
to heal and you do the exercise with me
but if you fall asleep that's fine too
because i'm still
doing that i'm still talking to the
subconscious mind through the episode
through
that powerful brain meditation and so
that
you can still have that healing process
occur
that's how it's that's how it's created
so that you can use this also as a sleep
meditation every single night
and heal because a lot of people don't
even have the time during the day or
they don't have the time in the morning
to do
you just do it before bed and you can
fall asleep with it
wyla green said hello anthony the brain
meditation was incredible cried after
then
fell into a deep sleep what's amazing
about while
is that when you fall asleep after the
brain meditation
the the the amount of healing that
occurs even before that
and then you fall asleep and you're you
have the peace
without the fear and the fear goes away
so important so
you guys i'm so glad that we had a
chance to be on tonight
um this is incredible i'm so glad we're
on today
and so i just want to give you just a
recap real quick
it's about healing the soul it's about
bridging the gap between the soul and
the physical brain
the brain meditation does this because
when we have trauma
we get out of body experiences fear
fills the gap the bridge gets
beaten down it gets broken down it gets
chewed up
and frazzled and this disconnect happens
but we still live our lives
but we still live our lives the
disconnect happens and so forth and so
forth
so really important to know that when
you rid this fear and you do this brain
meditation
and the soul starts to come back
and connect and there's nothing in there
anymore between the fear and all the
chaos and that goes away
then you can make this connection each
time and make it stronger and get rid of
that fear and do so much powerful
incredible healing
and that's the brain meditation
experience it share it
please share it with others tell them
where they can get the uncensored
version
tell them please where they can get the
uncensored version it's at apple podcast
it's medical medium podcast that apple
podcast the uncensored version
please tell them where they can get it
share it or share
share the link you'll see the link in
the description right here of this live
and please leave a review so others can
find their way and be like wow it's that
good it's in you know it's that good
it's that healing and they can find
their way okay
and so but i'm proud of all you guys and
listen to the other episodes there's so
many more
episodes to come so many powerful
episodes to come that are mind-blowing
um so stephanie you shared it too
incredible anyway you guys
bless your heart uh bless your heart god
bless you and
um proud of all of you for all the hard
work you're doing
and i believe in what you're doing i
know you're healing so many of you are
working hard at it this
is a whole nother step of healing the
soul
and that's the big part there and get
rid of that fear so okay so
um hope to see you again all right i
can't wait make sure you
do the brain meditation when you can if
you get a chance and uh
bless your heart bye