best-selling author got cleansed to heal
gonna answer questions
so let's cover as many questions as we
can get done so that would be great i
got my
got my fresh squeezed orange juice right
here which is pretty cool
and the celery juice though i'm working
on that first
so that's what i'm working on as we
speak this is about 30 ounces of celery
juice
are you guys doing your celery juice
it's an important tool therapeutic tool
it's an herbal medicine
and spirit of compassion told me about
this long time ago when i was younger
and
just a great great tool it's helping so
many people
so
um hey guys hey hey everybody there
great great to see you too
good to see you hey good to see you
barbara wonderful and um
glad everybody's here because i want to
answer questions
so yeah there's there's a question there
about mrsa too so i might have to
talk about that in a little bit as well
you know the thing is about with merce
it's all about like getting immune
system
stronger getting your immerse is a bug
and i talk about bugs it's all about
bugs right
and so when you look at cleanse of heal
you see you know the anti-bug cleanse
and everything else but
bugs bugs have similar jobs their
similar jobs
is like bugs similar jobs is to
feed off of food so
bugs love food so bacteria whether it's
super bacteria
they love food so always they always
realize they have to be eating something
they like
something that we have inside of us so
a lot of doctors talk to me about mrsa
it's something that comes up all the
time
and what i tell doctors is um because
because
you guys know i tell you this is i talk
to a good two or three doctors a day
every single day
and they reach out they want to know
information so they can help their
patients out there in the world
and um and what i've always asked about
mercy like
what do you you know what's your take on
mercy and my take is
getting foods out of you out of your
diet that actually
feed mrs that's one that's one edge you
can try to get and i tell doctors so
eggs you don't want to eat eggs because
eggs were
used to raise mrsa
originally so mrsa wasn't this thing
that just appeared
like it appeared mrsa was in a lab
along with all the other bugs a long
time ago and somehow
got out somehow escaped i don't know how
but they did you know you can think of a
lot of different ways they could have
done it
but it escaped and got on the scene and
how was it raised it was
raised in labs eating eggs so using eggs
as the food so you got to remember that
so if you're you know somebody that has
that and you're dealing with that no
eggs look out for that look out for
gluten
look out for different you know for um
milk cheese and butter
don't do anything like that that's
really important to know and then it's
about like
if i had mrsa i'd want to make sure i
had the right zinc
because that's incredible for any kind
of bug issue like in that or anything
you know and i'll make sure i got the
right zinc i make sure i know the right
tools make sure i'm drinking my
celery juice and someone might say oh
he's saying celery just fixes everything
no it's not it it's
celery juice is really supportive for
the immune system
it also is anti-bug so it's all about
how many tools can you bring in
can you get rid of the eggs can you you
know can you um
you know it's all important you know
it's all about that plus uh celery juice
is bioavailable vitamin c it doesn't
have to be converted
so like the celery juice right here that
doesn't have to be converted to vitamin
c
every single vitamin c you take and do
has to be converted by your liver
and celery juice is the only celery has
the only vitamin c that doesn't have to
be converted so it's all these little
tools that count
um so that when you're somewhere if
you're visiting somebody in a hospital
or whatever it is you end up getting
mrsa
or you could you can get it in a public
bathroom
and now you have mrsa and it's like
yeah it's like what what kind of
environment are you
giving mrsa like what kind of
environment is it
allowed to take advantage of so it's all
about
the tools it's all about the zinc it's
all about making sure you're not eating
eggs it's all about keeping your fats
low
if your fats are too high then your
immune system is going to struggle if
your blood fat's high all the time
you're eating too much
avocado nuts and seeds you know almond
butter peanut butter
chicken meat fish whatever it is oils
you know whatever you're doing if you're
eating too much of that you're not
eating enough leafy greens
leafy greens are critical if you're not
doing you know enough of that wild foods
are you doing any well foods and so
it's all this stuff medical medium
information has all that information so
and talks about that it's what it's
always been so yeah
so um delores super low b12
getting weekly shots what can i do to
naturally increase now what i tell
doctors all the time i get asked that
doctors contact me and say i heard
anthony you don't like the b12 shots
the doctors will ask me that i don't
like the b12 shots
um and i i like it orally
so that's what i like using the b12 it
has to be oral b12
i mean my my whole opinion from what i
get from spirit of compassion teaching
me so then i've
i'm obviously going with spirit of
compassion's information so
and i tell doctors to be 12 shots
is that is it a shot is an actual shot
versus in uh inter intravenous
vitamin so that's different i mean you
know i'm pro-intravenous vitamins and
for some things and for some reasons and
for some cases
so i'm pro that but b12 shots i'm not
pro
so i'm not i'm never happy about b12
shots so um
you go to your doctor ask him say hey
what about an oral b12
i feel that when it goes or not feel i
mean i've known through spirit of
compassion and then i've seen it work
when it goes through the digestive tract
so when it goes into the mouth through
the digestive tract it hits the ilium
the ilium is where you produce your own
b12 when it hits the ilium you're
producing your own b12 there
when you get a b12 shot it doesn't hit
the helium and you want the b12
eventually
going down to the helium where you
produce your own b12 and then it pulls
up into the liver
so when you take an oral b12 supplement
it goes to this natural process
it goes down to the ilium where you
create b12 then it gets sucked up to the
hepatoportal highway up into the liver
and then the liver then converts it
converts it better
and when it converts it better it
baptizes it sends it back out and that
makes the b12 really work so
um and if you're plant-based you're not
b12 deficient because you're plant-based
uh animal will be animal based people
they're all b12 deficient
just millions and millions of them
millions so really important to know
so but having a combination of adenosil
cobalamin methocil cabal
methylcobalamin adenosicobalam and it's
really important you can check out my
directory medicalminion.com
you can look into those but a good b12
is important
can i freeze becky can i freeze celery
juice
if you have to yeah and
you know this whole plague that's been
going around everything happening i get
a lot of
questions from friends like can i freeze
the celery juice because i can't get out
and get celery because everything that's
happening and i can't get
what do i do and yeah you can freeze it
you can juice it
and then freeze it don't freeze it in
glass
i don't think you want to freeze in
glass and glass might just blow up and
explode
sunday hi anthony i've been suffering
with eczema and other symptoms
weeping eczema i think i have mold issue
well mold mold is a trigger for anything
else so if you have eczema
then you have something going on and if
you look at the
you know cleanse the heel for example by
the way this you can go to the library
get it for free
just you know sunday go live or get it
for free if you want
your own copy right away amazon.com in
the us selling it 51
off unbelievable sale on this book
specifically 16.99
but you can get it to the library at the
library too but the point is is that
you'll find out the true cause of your
eczema finding out the true cause of
your ex is critical that's a that's a
big
piece right there and what you'll find
in the book unique information you can't
find anywhere that's the one thing about
the medical medium information it's all
unique and original everything else is
not
so everything else floating around has
been the same old for decade after
decade with nobody getting better
unless they take tidbits of original
medical medium information
and they do and they don't cite it back
like a lot of different people all
through the years 35 years of this
have not cited it backs and then someone
thinks it came from somewhere else
um but what you'll find is copper inside
the liver
plus ebv equals eczema weeping eczema
for sure all of it so you need a virus
inside the liver
and i teach doctors this all the time
the virus inside the liver ebv
it feeds off of copper releases a
dermatoxin
it craps out copper the virus actually
craps out copper
when it releases it goes to the bathroom
and that copper comes out
that becomes this dermatoxin and that
floats around through the body and it
surfaces through the skin because the
liver is stagnant and sluggish
and when that happens you end up getting
your eczema so
you'll learn here like what do i do
you'll find out the true cause
what do i do what kind of options do i
have take this to your doctor ask him
about it
you can customize your own protocol to
get you in the direction of
of healing that's the whole point you
can actually customize
your own personal protocol with medical
media information you can take it as far
as you want to go
thousands and thousands and thousands of
people are healing their eczema
psoriasis
i hope i helped in any information
tidbits i can give you on that
the mold is a trigger to lower the
immune system and then yeah anything
else can get worse
but what you want to do is take care of
the what's getting worse the problem
like the eczema get working on that and
so forth
so rachel says
gestational diabetes how do you treat it
so only seven weeks old you know what
happens is with
with um with that and diabetes is that
you know first of all what i've always
told in a
um like doctors and and and
other people have known throughout the
years is you you
definitely get when it comes down to
gestational diabetes
ask around get second opinions get a
third opinion
get a fourth opinion and what you'll
find is when you're getting different
opinions you'll find that
another doctor is going to be a lot
helpful with that more helpful with that
than another doctor that's what i've
always known there's
that that's where i would start is did
you get a second third fourth opinion
because when it comes down to that so
important to get a consensus
between doctors and are they talking to
each other too like are the doctors
talking to each other if you find they
won't talk to each other
and and you and that that that's really
hard and i noticed that
you know getting extra support because
when doctors start talking to each other
so then they can try to figure out a
game plan and how to address it
so
it's a little dry tonight so i better
sip some storage
i've been talking all day so
you know what a lot of times you'll hear
you know one of the what the whole thing
is
looking for some questions here you guys
i'm glad everybody's coming on we're
going to cover a lot
i'm going to get as many questions as i
can answer
so each other day 9 of the advanced 369
cleanse
the advanced 369 cleanse is in cleanse
the heel
that's really helping so many people
around the world right now it's an
unbelievable cleanse
just finished your eighth year so you're
just finished your second
your second celery juice you're on round
eight of 369.
incredible i'm so proud of you it's
amazing it's really amazing
love you too erica
karen r a rheumatoid arthritis so first
thing you want to do is you want to know
what causes it so that's the key go to
the library
don't even buy the book go to the
library get it for free
okay so then you can get the book and
you can look at it and you can see
like the cause of ra and you it's
you can go to the autoimmune because ra
is
called autoimmune that's what the
research and science calls it it's what
doctors will call it it's autoimmune
so if you go in here you'll find it
either in the autoimmune section
that will just be anything that's not
listed in here that's autoimmune you go
into the autoimmune section
unless you find it
sandra says you never answer questions
you just say
buy my book okay good question well
don't buy the book
get it free at the library that's number
one so
another thing too is i'm not just trying
to sell a book if i wanted to do that i
would sell programs
and get rich you know by selling
programs for five thousand dollars
apiece
twenty five hundred dollars a piece
three thousand dollars a piece thousands
of people would buy into the programs
i can do courses and classes i don't and
um
it would be unbelievable really what
would happen so i don't do that choose
not to do that it's my publisher's book
they sell it out there sure i'm trying
to get the book out there too to help
people so people have a resource
but if i was all about just trying to
sell something
then i would be selling courses classes
and
um programs and selling them for
thousands upon thousands of dollars
i would break the book up so no one
would get the information and they would
have to pay for it but i want you to
have the information for free
so i'm here answering questions and
telling you to go to the library
um and what i'm doing is i'm answering
questions as far as
letting you know that you can find the
causes to these conditions and i'm going
to talk about food questions and other
things too
but the causes of these conditions so if
you've got something going on you can
learn the cause
and that's that's really important
it's so you know what to do it's like um
all the information's in this book if i
sit here i can blow an hour away
just on one thing by how much
information i can talk about which in
this book and so
i want to answer as many questions as i
can
but good question
and thank you for asking it
hey arizona i hope from
arizona amazing so
wendy says my name is wendy i have
healed my thyroid
i am so proud of you that is incredible
and that's an accomplishment that's an
incredible
accomplishment it really is it's so
helpful too for other people to know
that
you're doing your celery juice 16 ounces
that's wonderful
um okay so carrie can you talk about
bipolar
so i would love to um bipolar
is a diagnosis for
no one in medical research and science
or anywhere knowing
why how what the cause is what it is
okay so
it's a really silly name for a condition
that's really
hard to live with when someone you know
when you're suffering with it yourself
it's really hard and
so they they don't know what causes it
so they name it bipolar which means
north south up and down so all the
research and science we have
all the technology we have all of the
studies and peer review studies and all
of the stuff that we got going on
the best they can do is you're either up
or you're down that's what they tell
you it's sad i think bipolar is probably
quintessentially
an example of how screwed up the system
is and how screwed up the medical system
is and how screwed up research and
science it is because
they're better off just saying we don't
know why you're going through this we
don't know why you're suffering we don't
know why you're hurting so bad and
you're
you're emotional and you're you're in
agony and you're
in the depression and you're not feeling
good or you're manic and we don't know
why
all that's happening and so
i wish they would be honest and not not
be in denial but what they do
is they will name it something bipolar
which means
nothing it just means they think you're
either
up or you're down it's really sad toxic
heavy metals is the cause of
that term bipolar it's the cause of
somebody being all over the place like
that where they're hurting emotionally
and they're up and they're down and
they're all over the place and it's then
it's you know mercury
big part of it so that's mercury is the
issue behind that so that means
you can go you can go and get a mercury
test at the doctor you can go to your
doctor get a mercury test
um but it may not show up because
mercury
is inside organs and it gets inside our
brain and it gets in center of liver and
it gets inside our organs
and so they won't see that in a blood
test
because it's inside organs and organ
tissue
you can't test for that easily but you
can at least you can ask the doctor and
tell them look
i i think i got some heavy metals i
think i got some mercury
and you can you know you can learn
information on how to you can take
the cleanse of heal book to your doctor
talk to them about
you know toxic heavy metals i have a
heavy metal detox cleanse ask your
doctor if that works for you
and but the bottom line is it's really
sad when they don't have an answer
instead they kind of like basically say
something
they give it a ridiculous name i mean it
just doesn't make any sense
um but the heavy medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse is important they
if they only would give it its real
the real thing like you got mercury and
you know mercury poisoning so that's
what it is
that's what i tell doctors all the time
so they know about it i just want to say
that
your frozen shoulder remedies are spot
on
so cheryl says that cured my husband
in a few weeks while others are having
surgeries
in mua et cetera and suffering for years
thank you well the frozen shoulder thing
is is the shingles
and research in science doesn't know
that and so they look for
they look for um and they look for
tissue connective tissue that's messed
up they look for tears
they look for cartilage issues they look
for spurs
they look for all this by the way i'm
really proud of you i'm proud of your
husband really proud of you
cheryl they look for all this stuff and
then they put people under surgery and
i'm not anti-surgery i'm not anti uh i
mean i know surgeons i've talked to
surgeons there's times when we need it
there's times when we don't but what i
like to do with frozen shoulders i like
to go
this way which is you're inflamed
and we need to give it a chance to heal
before we jump into surgery
and so i'm proud of you and your husband
because you did
protocols you speci you did them
specifically for you you customized it
for you you knew how to use the
information
so that your husband could actually get
the inflammation down
with the information and get it down
and so that you can get the shingles
down because that's what it is the
protocol is designed for frozen shoulder
for
shingles so that somebody cannot be in
pain anymore with their shoulder
and and others yeah other people they
have to go get the surgery they don't
know about the protocol they don't know
about knocking down
the shingles they don't know about all
that so they don't know what to do
i'm really proud of you cheryl really
proud of you and your husband because
sounds to me like you read the book you
opened it you read it
and you're like you know what
a lot of people they just right now in
this day and age
some people are like i don't i want to
just find a video somewhere
and not read a book but it's important
to read it if the information's there
susan do you know anything about
orthostatic tremors
so and when it comes down to tremors
you're talking nervous system
so when you're talking about nervous
system you're talking about a couple of
things there
if you're if you went to your doctors if
you went to your um neurologist and they
did all their tests
they did their mris they did their cat
scans they did everything that they want
to do
and they can't find anything they can't
find a brain tumor they can't find
something else they can't find
and you're in this land of what do i do
and now it's under this label
or the static tremors and what do i do
and when you're in that zone then you
have to realize
well okay then you look at like cleanse
the heel you take it to your doctor
you look at cleanse the heel and you'll
be like okay tremors
and you'll see that that's the central
nervous system and you'll be like whoa
there's an actual reason for this
and when you see there's an actual
reason which is viruses
such as epstein-barr shingles so forth
and and
in other viruses too but viruses such as
epstein-barr and shingles
they release a neurotoxin that
neurotoxin
clings to nerves causes tremors and then
that neurotoxin is also
heavy metal based toxic heavy metal
based so the viruses such as ebv
feeds off of mercury then releases a
mercury byproduct that mercury byproduct
is so highly toxic it causes tremors it
clings to the nerves
clings to the vagus nerve the phrenic
nerves um all the different nerves and
then
you get that tremor and so it's good to
know what's going on so hey if i had
orthostatic tremors what i would be
doing is i'd be like trying to get the
metals out number one
i'd be trying to um i'd be eliminating
foods like eggs
get the eggs out because eggs raised
they raised viruses with eggs
in labs released the viruses over over
the years somehow they got out
and these viruses got into people
throughout the decades and then boom we
got
orthostatic tremors
so okay hi anthony i had breast implants
two years ago
so madolina so breast implants two years
ago since then i've been suffering from
chronic bloating and
vaginal candida my left breast implants
has always been harder than the other do
you think i can recover from these
symptoms without removing implants
i've just i have to say that without
realizing i've been suffering from these
symptoms since i was
little but now it looks like with the
implants they got much worse so
okay for for for one um
like the vaginal candida when you're
when you're candida is
a label for when they don't know what's
really happening underneath things and
not underneath it all
and so i i tell doctors this all the
time they ask me about candida because
candida is really confusing for a lot of
people and
it's never really candida it's
streptococcus and then candida gets the
label
yeast infections get the label when it's
streptococcus so
and then if you read the medical medium
books you'll learn that strep is a
cofactor to ebv so scrap is a cofactor
to epstein-barr
and then breast implant illness is
fatigue in the brain fog
and the nerve pain and all that combined
and that's neurological so then you're
looking at
viral plus viral creating neurological
and then you kind of find your way and
then you realize it's viruses that's why
one one a woman can have breast implants
and not have any problems because
she may not have she doesn't have an
active viral
issue in the moment so what i would do
is go to your doctor say look do i have
any kind of viral stuff going on do i
have any kind of epstein-barr going on
because that
that's what happens and um and it comes
out usually later so women with breast
implant illness
end up finding epstein-barr in their
blood at a doctor's office
two years down the road three years down
the road because it's hard to pick it
off at a lot of times during the blood
test you got to keep on going over time
and so um breast implants can
you know what happens is they can be a
trigger if something's going wrong with
them they can be a trigger but you have
to have something inside of you
that's getting triggered and the epstein
bar will create the brain fog
the fatigue um all kinds of different
symptoms and so forth and that's what's
happening
and that's why it's important like when
i go to cleanse the heal i'm like well
what's the symptom you're dealing with
and it's also why you had symptoms when
you're younger you notice madelina like
you said exactly you know you without
realizing it you were suffering from
these symptoms
since you were little but now it looks
like the implants got that much worse
what were those symptoms when you were a
little fatigued or were they fatigued
brain fog anxiety were they body pain
were they tingles and numbness when you
were little
and then migraines and then the breast
implants
could worsen them because they became
kind of a little bit of a trigger so
okay if if i had breast implants okay
now if i was a woman i would just be
working on
i would be working on the underlying
issue
so i'd be working on that and so i'd
look at the symptoms and find out what
were the symptoms i had when i was
younger obviously you're experiencing
them
that's what i would do and i'd be like
what are those symptoms let me find
those symptoms find out what the real
causes start
there you can talk to your doctor
so that's a good question there cindy
says why is it that you have to go to so
many doctors for every problem
i have to go to many doctors and visit i
have internal medicine doctor it's good
that you have one of those
refers me out to pulmonologists yeah i
know because he probably doesn't do
pulmonology
and then you got the bladder doctor yeah
you got the
you know the bladder doctor urologist
and everything else you got
in the heart doctor right cardiologist
and what happened to the doctor who can
help you with
without so many of the doctors yeah
totally i i completely understand
um you know it's it's like that even in
alternative medicine too
it's it's funny like alternative
alternative medicine you'll get a guy
that only does this
and you'll get somebody that only does
this and it's whatever really what the
doctor likes to focus on like the lyme
doctor just wants to focus online but
what's funny about that
anybody who goes to him will get a lyme
diagnosis so
that's the only problem anyone who goes
to another doctor will get another
diagnosis
it's pretty funny in alternative
medicine if you go to a gut doctor in
alternative medicine they just focus on
say you know microbiome every single
person leaving will be microbiome
microbiome microbiome here's some here's
some probiotics
out the door here's some probiotics out
the door you go to a lime doctor it's
like you got lime
out the door out the door lime trap lime
trap and so it's it's crazy how it works
but
but i get it it's a lot of guys and and
in the business they just want to do
their one specialty but yet you know
they have to send you out for everything
else under the sun
michelle hot flashes from sluggish liver
yeah totally and um absolutely
michelle thanks so much for all the work
you do by the way because i see your
comments out there
and um and they're always spot on
they're they're always just spot on it's
it's amazing how much you know
it's amazing how much medical medium
information you know and
it's it's incredible really and you're
obviously reading the books and you
obviously
know what you're reading and
understanding because these are medical
textbooks so
it's amazing michelle
so dana says if you've had mono
how long can the epstein-barr virus stay
in your system
which book has protocol for this i would
start with cleanse the heel go to the
library
get it for free and
what is your you know what what is your
symptoms too what that's what i would do
i would say what is my symptom and i
would go back into here
there's over 200 symptoms and conditions
if you also want to like
you know keep your immune system strong
and you can look at any number one of
the any
any number of these cleanses but i would
read the book take one page at a time
and get through it and
you can learn so much about that
you know really what happens the medical
media books exploded epstein-barr out
there in the scene in the world
now you're hearing it everywhere out
there that's for millions of copies sold
out there like if you read the little
gold emblem on here millions of the
medical medium series sold out there all
around the world
medical medium book one just went
everywhere
around the globe and millions of people
learned about epstein-barr
and but here's the thing what never
existed out there before was
what epstein-barr causes what symptoms
nobody knew any of that that's all
medical medium information
they only thought epstein-barr caused a
little little bit of fatigue
and a little bit of malaise and a little
fever once in a while that was all they
knew and
medical medium information opened the
door for the first time in medical
history
to actually link epstein-barr to all the
symptoms and conditions and it was
published by medical medium first and
also
i taught it and lectured it to doctors
over the last 35 years
and it's incredible what has happened
and transpired by that
spillings are being helped but the only
problem is it this
it doesn't get cited back to me many of
it doesn't get so people don't know
where to get the
information the protocols more
information about epstein-barr like all
the ins and outs
so yeah
let's see um donna very first time on
with same issue hot flashes how do you
fix
what you definitely want to start with
lowering your fats hot flashes
sluggish liver you got to look at it
that way and you want to
reduce your fats if if your animal
protein okay which i'm pro animal
protein if that's what you like
you you just got to reduce your your
meats and stuff like that i mean i would
get off of dairy products number one
that's what i would do personally if i
had hot flashes
i would get off milk cheese butter kefir
yogurt gone
i would get rid of that and you know and
and i would start with their eggs get
rid of eggs
boom get rid of all that if you're if
you're eating animal protein then i
would lower
the amount of animal protein that i was
eating i would
reduce it so maybe it's only once a day
or once every other day
if you're plant-based i would reduce
okay if you're plant-based i'll make
sure you're gluten-free of course
i would stay away from nutritional yeast
for sure because that would just
ruin the liver and then you know get rid
of that
and then i would reduce the amount of
nuts seeds
nuts seeds avocado i would reduce all
that
oils reduce all that bring that down and
lower your fats there if you got if you
got the hot flashes whether you're
plant-based or
animal product so that's what i would do
because i'm pro
all the diets yeah i'm pro whatever you
want to be but i want to help you
be the best at what you love to do if
you love plant-based
i want to help you do it right if you
love the animal protein based diet
if you're if you're an animal baser i
want to help you do if you're a
plant-baser
i want to help you do it and and make
sure it works for you and
cleaning up that liver and making sure
that liver gets cleaned up
and this is just one part of it right
here a tool for it
[Music]
that was 30 30 ounces of celery juice
and i'm working through it right now
tonight for dinner
but i also have fresh squeezed orange
juice right here
for my dinner
but sluggish liver doesn't just resolve
in one shot
you got to work on it and so i mean do
you have cleanse to heal
are you there yet have you gotten to
cleanse heal are you doing some of the
cleanses you're doing the 369 to really
clean up that liver
but you can get yourself on the way so
it's important to know
so liza love you anthony hey love you
too
i have been on all your books incredible
over a year starting with liver rescue
due to liver methylation issue
incredible i completed 20 day
28 day cleanse 369 and i'm doing 32
ounces of celery juice daily
have many improvements so you got lots
of improvements but hair
still falling out does this mean i
haven't found the root problem
so look i'm not a flying fly on the wall
um at your house and but what's you know
first time it could take a little time
and one thing's for sure that that when
it comes down to the hair still falling
out
hair falls out later later on so what
happens is if you've had a rough couple
of years
or a few years then the hair falls out
later
and i just you know i imagine you're not
on caffeine
but did you do caffeine in the past
because you can have this delayed effect
where hair falls out much later because
of it
did you do the matcha tea did you do the
green tea matcha tea coffee drinks cacao
that's that just makes hair fall out for
women
it's really sad it beats their adrenals
down and you end up losing one of the
adrenaline hormone blends one of the
adrenal hormones
when you lose that just hair continues
to fall out for a long time it can take
a long time to restore
and are you doing supplement protocols
in the books too are you customizing
them for yourself to what's going on
like the hair loss protocol and cleanse
the heel
and that's something right there and you
know and i'm look i'm sure you are you
got the books you're working on i'm
really proud of you
it you know you can get there and i'm
really really proud of you actually
incredible incredible
rebecca says i have both these books do
you consult with people i don't consult
with people i just consult doctors
um that's that's and i've done that for
35 years
the reason reasons why i had so many
people come to me when i used to consult
many many years ago is through doctors
doctors recommendations doctors
recommending people
to talk to me but i still have all those
relationships with hundreds of doctors
over the years plus new ones contacting
me so what i do is
i do help doctors on a daily basis so
they can help their patients
so you can bring any right back you can
bring any of this information in the
book or from
what i'm helping you now with to your
doctor of course so you have both these
books amazing
and you've had two neurologists tell me
i have
anxiety after having an mri eeg
emg and i was cleared so
so you had the eeg you had the mri and
the emg
and you're cleared so they but they say
you have anxiety i have twitching
involuntary movements
jerks vibrations and basically they just
say
uh okay economists
they cannot find anything what direction
to
turn so they say you just have anxiety
um so if you look at the medical medium
books and you look at
cleanse the healing you can take the
information to your doctor and i'm asked
this by doctors
and um this is neurological your
symptoms are neurological
so you look at your symptoms so when you
look at cleanse the heel and you go back
in there and you'll find
twitching you'll find um you'll find
that in there like the
vibrations i talk about that when the
body's humming
buzzing vibrating twitching spasms
you know ticks and spasms twitches all
that stuff you'll find it in the back of
the book
and and you'll learn what the true
causes are and then you'll be like whoa
i found the true cause and you can go
and take that to your doctor or work
with it however you you need to or want
to
but that's that's you can find answers
for that
and and then you can even go into the
anxiety section if you want to but
that's not
if if i had that i would know that
that's not anxiety like if i had the
jerking
and the twitching and the spasms and all
of that
and i was living with that i would know
it's not anxiety because i know it's a
twitch it's a jerk it's a spasm and
that's not anxiety
it's just that anxiety doesn't help it
but anxiety also can happen
simultaneously with it
veronica what do you think about dmso
please i don't like it
i mean i'm not a fan of it i think it's
what happens is when you have nervous
system conditions and your nervous
system is inflamed because of real
like like real causes like viruses and
stuff like that
um and i mean but but
hey look i mean that's just my opinion
i'm not a big fan of dmso
uh only because i find it's a little too
harsh
for people with nervous system issues
that are dealing with
the chronic fatigue syndrome and the
tickles and numbness and like the
twitches and spasms and all that other
stuff
burning skin aches and pains all the
nervous system stuff
i'm not a fan of dms so i just you'll
find look
some of the answers to your questions
will be answered if you read the books
but like he doesn't
recommend dmso he doesn't recommend
nutritional yeast he doesn't recommend
corella he doesn't recommend something
charcoal
and then you'll see well if he's not
talking about it then that's a whole
thing
peter hey peter a.w asking gods
asking god directly for help versus
angels
absolutely you can ask god directly for
help there's no question
um i asked i asked god for help i mean i
i i absolutely and you know it's it's um
but but yes you can you can ask angels
for help too
god's angels you can definitely you can
definitely ask each other you can
ask out loud you know and
and call upon angels you can you can ask
um
the angel of mercy that's an angel that
i've always asked and try to send
prayers at the people i'd ask angel
mercy to help someone
you can definitely talk straight to the
angels and you can talk to god too you
can
you can directly talk to god and ask god
questions
so nancy says i ate an egg tonight what
should i do now
oh you know it's okay if you had an egg
tonight it's all right
it's all right just one day at a time i
mean if you're are you dealing with
symptoms
are you dealing with the condition then
just i wouldn't do any more eggs
if you can um that's all right look it's
it's not an easy time for anybody right
now with what's happening
with the plague that's been around us
and making life so much difficult by the
way is which
which is why i want people to build
their immune systems up it's why i want
them to be
you know taking care of themselves but
it's perfectly fine if that's what you
did
it's all right and honestly nancy the
whole world's eating eggs
the whole world is eating eggs but um
but what i would do is avoid them if you
have a symptom a condition if you have a
concern with your health
just avoid them from here on out and and
do some good things to count i look i
like celery juice to counter
any eggs you know because i know people
that are eating eggs and it's like are
you still doing your celery juice
because at least you're doing something
to counter it all
and it's not that eggs were bad or
are bad for us it's just that because
of what they were used for and i talked
about that before
what they were used for to raise bugs in
the labs years ago and they just
happened to feed bugs but one egg's not
going to do it okay people
one egg's not going to do it all right
i'm not trying to give everybody a
license to just gobble down eggs i'm
just saying that you're gonna be okay
with that egg
delight heart don't worry and um
just try not to have any more if you're
dealing with a symptom or condition it's
okay
it's not gonna hurt
chrissy says can a protocol help
tinnitus well what is the cause of
tinnitus
so what is it apparently science and
research doesn't know
unless you've had decibel damage like
high decibels and
you're in rock concerts for you know
week after week and
sitting next to the speakers and you had
your ears just you know
blown off but other than that i mean if
that didn't happen
all the time and you got and you you
have this tinnitus that's been
developing because that's
viral tinnitus when it develops like
that that's not
damage but it's viral tinnitus that's
when viral issues get into the labyrinth
of the inner ear they inflame
the nerve channel there and then you
start hearing buzzing popping
ringing all kinds of noises and i talk
about this in so many lives i've done
i've done facebook lives all about this
i've done
um i think i did some youtube lives
about this too somewhere but cleanse the
heel
in the back you'll see tinnitus with the
true causes and then you're like wow i
know the true cause and then you can
start working on things to actually help
it heal
get get the book free at the library if
you want there's a sale on amazon.com us
which is unbelievable
it's for this book specifically only for
this book it's 51 percent off
it's it's really amazing right now if
you can't get to a library and you want
to just grab the book
glad everybody's here this is wonderful
so samantha i went to a healing touch
nurse and she directed me to you
on how to treat hsv 2
simplex 2. what do i do um
i mean look if i had that i would be in
here i'd be looking at cleanse to heal
where are you are you overseas book
depository you can find it there library
i heard somebody in australia said you
can get a library in australia
it's incredible but in the us looking at
the library for free you can get at
amazon.com
but um if i would look at the protocol
in the back for herpes simplex
and you know hsv2 hsb1 and i would look
at that and it'll give you some guidance
and then i would embark on a cleanse and
that's what i would do personally
start getting a hold on doll i'm glad
i'm glad i'm glad your practitioner
recommended
the books
so angela i randomly became dizzy one
day
and it won't go away and it feels like
falling
right before bed and been on a boat all
day it's driving me nuts and my heart
will race and my anxiety goes crazy help
well your anxiety's gonna go crazy
because you're
you're feeling like you're on a boat you
know what happens that people deal with
this they feel like they're walking
along and they're going down
and it's just like oh my god it's like
so scary or your your balance is going
one way
and not the other and it's really
difficult it's vertigo so that that's
that's what that is that's just vertigo
and um so
i've talked about this that balanced
feeling and being on a bow and the true
causes to that
now if you've been to your doctors
you've had your mris you've had all your
checkups they looked at everything
they're looking for things and and all
that well you can bring the book to your
doctor too and say look since you can't
find out what's going on
he's got an answer in here he's got the
true cause so you can find it in here
and cleanse the heel in the back and
vertigo that's you'll see the true cause
and what happens when the vagus nerve
gets inflamed
the vagus nerve gets inflamed by a viral
infection that they can't find because
that's how viruses work they're so hard
to find
that viral infection keeps that that
that vertigo going because the vagus
nerve
gets a neurotoxin attached to it
neurotoxin comes from a virus the virus
eliminates the neurotoxin
the vagus nerve swells up and then you
got your boat you're rocking on the boat
you're going see-sawing and you're doing
the room spins you hop in bed and the
room is spinning and that's the type of
vertigo and i talk about i
i've been the only one with spirit of
compassion that that put together
epstein-barr virus and vertigo
um and then you can learn how thousands
of people have healed their vertigo
through the information
and spirit of compassion so i hope that
helps
so you can you get a direction on where
to go so you can start thinking about
what can i do
maybe maybe embark on the mono eating
cleanse
bringing in some celery juice or the
mono eating cleanse and you start
working with that so angela so you can
start getting better
so lisa says please talk about
mysterious rashes
you're welcome so i will talk about it
for a minute the serious rashes
eczema is a mysterious rash so
psoriasis is a mysterious rash um
rosacea is a mysterious rash they don't
know the cause
true cause unknown they just named it
maybe they didn't name your ash but it's
all the same in the sense
meaning all the same in the sense of
they're all mysterious
really important to know this is how the
industry has tricked everybody out
they give a name for something if enough
people have a certain identifiable
relation to a rash
then they put a name on it but they
don't know what causes it so it's
mysterious
mystery illness is every diagnosis
practically
and and every autoimmune diagnosis is
mystery illness every
all of that so some mysterious rashes so
i mean if i had a mysterious rash i
would just be like looking in here and
being like okay
uh first of all he's got the street cred
because thousands upon thousands of
healing stories on rashes and
eczema and psoriasis and all that stuff
and what did they do well they did some
celery juice they
they stayed strong with that they got
rid of eggs and dairy products they got
rid of gluten right
and they started bringing leafy greens
like the spinach soup
they started bringing wild foods like
the wild blueberries
um and they started to learn how to heal
using like the herbal medicine right
here the celery juice
and they started getting minerals they
started learning how to use b12 they
started learning how to do these things
and in the back of the book i talk about
eczema psoriasis and other skin rashes
and stuff
so um
gabrielle hi anthony what about tingling
in my limbs
after every shower thanks very much
tingling and limbs after every shower
what that is is when the shower's
hitting you
it's hitting your nerves this is why
when people have any nerve sensitivities
that
if some people get so so
sick with different neurological stuff
that they can't take a shower the water
hitting them
will make them pass out or make them hit
the floor
or really hurt their nerves or cause
lots of numbness and tingles
you're just having a little tingling
going on so what that just means is you
got a little bit
your phrenic nerves are a little
sensitive that's all that is
i mean you know i i talked to recently a
practitioner who's a
naturopath and this naturopath i mean i
talk to mainly medical doctors
but i do talk to some naturopaths in
between it all um
and i stuck in this naturopath that
reached out to me
and the they were talking about this
very thing about taking a shower
feeling weird sensations feeling tingles
and stuff like that
and i was explaining to this naturopath
that people have a lot of sensitive
nerves they have sensitive
frantic nerves you know all kinds of
different nerves get sensitive and the
shower is
hitting the muscles it's hitting the
muscles and the heat's getting in
and what happens is your nerves are
coming out they're coming
out into muscle in other places the
nerves are going into all kinds of
places
it means they're a little bit
hypersensitive a little extra sensitive
do you have any anxiety along with that
do you have other things going on with
that um
i mean i personally if i was dealing
with that i would be like no gluten no
caffeine never the caffeine
no eggs no dairy products move that
stuff completely out for now
um i bring in a little bit more fruit in
my diet i bring in some leafy greens in
my diet
so i would start doing that maybe do a
little celery juice so i mean that's
what i would do to start with
and and and personally what i would do
if i was going through that i would
bring in some b12 the right kind of b12
to learn about that in medical medium
information but i would bring that in
and that's where i would start if i was
doing that
so
so tanya says literally all these
questions you guys are asking
are in his books if you if you go read
them tim you're amazing
you read the books you're an expert so
that means i bet you're an expert
because you've gotten into the books you
know them well that's where you're like
hey you guys
it's all in there thank you for telling
everybody that
it's so helpful because i want people to
be able to heal and get the information
bless your heart
tanya
okay so there's a question of there's
there's a question of i have all the
books
bought all of them but you don't talk
about durkheam's disease
okay so there's that question right
there and lisa
i'm glad you asked that question okay um
the the fatty lipomas and
and other cis other symptoms that kind
of like go along with it and stuff like
that
but you know the thing is with that is
with
okay first of all fatty lipomas fatty
lipomas i do talk about that in
in these lives many times and what
happens with the fatty lipoma it tends
to grow these
in order for the lipoma to grow it has
to grow the
uh these blood vessels so the blood
vessels grow out of it and those blood
vessels need to be
need to drop food they need to drop
nutrients so
i asked them i get asked about lipomas
all the time
and and like how do you stop them from
growing why are they growing what's
going on
and they grow because they're eating
something
they actually do feed it's the craziest
thing
and i know it sounds crazy but they have
because i talk to surgeons they're like
well we got to kind of cut their roots
when we come when we remove lipomas
we have to kind of like sniff their
little roots and
nobody knows that it's the craziest
thing how nobody knows this information
but
those little roots drop nutrients and if
it feeds the lipoma and what this
lipomas like to eat
they love eggs they love eggs like
homers grow bigger and bigger when you
eat more eggs eggs eggs
that i know and they do also like some
dairy products
they do like that they don't care about
gluten like homers don't care about
gluten i mean
you may not want to be on gluten for
other reasons that i talk about but
lipomas don't care about about gluten
okay but they love
dairy products they love eggs really
important to know
okay right there and and that alone you
can be proactive
and if you're eating a lot of fat in
your diet
okay so fatty tumors
yeah um drop down the fats that's
another thing too
and and that's that's something all on
its own
but really it takes a virus to make a
lipo
and look what i would do is dirkham's
disease it's like what's all the
symptoms of dirkham's disease
what are the symptoms and i would
individually look at the symptoms
because it doesn't mean durkheim's is
the like they name it that but they
don't understand the symptoms in between
it all so you take a look at you
identify the symptoms on their own when
you identify their sense so when you say
look
you talk about all these other things in
the books but you don't talk about that
well no you take the specific symptom
and you take that specific symptom and
you go on the back of the book and you
line it up and then yeah it turns out i
did talk about that
in fact now you know the cause of it so
it's really important
so rene says why is my hashimoto's
thyroiditis affecting me neurologically
really awesome question incredible
question for tonight
my neurologist can't give me an answer
because hashimoto's thyroiditis
is the third stage of epstein-barr
and you'll learn that in the medical
medium books so hashimoto's thyroiditis
is the third stage of epstein-barr so
what happens is
the first stage of epstein-barr is when
you get infected by it so
mononucleosis it's not mononucleosis but
it's pre-mononucleosis you get infected
by it
it sits around in your system a little
bit and then it kind of camps out
and then the second stage of
epstein-barr is
boom mononucleosis it goes into war with
your immune system
so it means you had mono whether you
realized it or not one time in your life
going all the way back
and then the third stage after it sits
in the liver
after mononucleosis it goes and hides
itself in the liver it leaves the liver
in the third stage
and goes to your thyroid so
hashimoto's thyroiditis is epstein-barr
stage
three and and anything thyroid related
hypothyroidism hypothyroidism is
epstein-barr
stage three this isn't research in
science this is a head of research in
science doctors tell me all the time
that medical media book
information is way ahead of research and
science that's why i talk to have to
talk to doctors every day
this is a medical textbook so the
information's in here now
and you can't get that anywhere else
this information doesn't exist it's just
the circuit is how to live longer uh how
to anti-age uh
telomeres um top five foods that are
great
top five foods to help you live longer
uh be at your beth i mean
it's like rhetoric out there between the
plant-based books and
the paleo-based books and the circuit
and the podcast it's like
none of it addresses all this real
information it's only gonna
it's only mm info but they'll take
little pieces out there and sound like
they're really smart and not cited back
to medical medium information it's
actually funny
because i'm discriminated against
because of where i get the info from
um so but the point is is that that
hashimoto's thyroiditis
that's of the epstein-barr viral
infection at stage three epstein-barr
but here's the thing
stage four i've seen bar is it stays in
the thyroid but then it leaves the
thyroid and it starts to aggravate
nerves
so that's epstein-barr so go to your
doctor
talk to your doctor ask them hey um
there's a lot of doctors that use these
books or in the
in their that's the whole point they're
in their doctor's offices then they know
why
um people have hashimoto's thyroiditis
now they know it's epstein-barr
then you can start looking into it what
can you do all this stuff talk to your
doctor about it
so he can learn or she can learn um
let's see lacrecia is there anything you
recommend besides celery juice for
weight loss i
am periodic patient and electric patient
and they push protein
is a vegan diet best i also have cfs and
fibromyalgia well first of all you got
if you have the cfs the chronic fatigue
syndrome and the fibrobiology you
already
are identifying one thing you have going
on so when you look at the true cause
you learn that that's viral so that's
one thing right there okay and yes
you can you can do lots for weight is is
what you can do
you there's lots of information like in
cleanse the heel there's a whole weight
weight loss weight gain weight loss
information it's packed in here there's
a protocol in here for that
there's even in the back um there's a
protocol back there
it's really about lowering fats so
whether you're animal protein
or you're plant-based it's about
lowering fats if you want to be
plant-based yes you can be plant-based
and then you can figure out how to do it
like
if i had that condition like me
personally
anthony william had that condition i
would do like
the mono eating i would go into the mono
eating right here so the cleanse is in
here
and i would get comfortable with one and
see how it's working for me that's what
i would do
i'd probably be doing the potato one
personally for me
or maybe papaya banana one with the
celery juice and the lettuce and so
forth but
that's something i would try a little
bit or you can even do something even
just the morning cleanse which is so
so easy and simple and it reduces your
fats
so that when your fats are down that can
help all
like that all on on its own right there
and then the weight can start going down
so yeah and if you if you want to do
animal proteins
keep keep the fats low keep them down if
you want to be plant-based keep the fats
low
because then the liver can recoup and
you can start losing weight and do your
celery juice and do it all like you're
cleaning up the liver so it's really
important
um
[Music]
sand you gotta inguinal hernia so the
whole thing with that is
it's about reducing that it's it's about
you the thing is
is that don't overeat if i had that i
wouldn't overeat
i just wouldn't that's one of the keys i
talked to doctors all the time about
this they asked me about this
and that's the first thing i would do is
you just don't overeat that's a key
right there
so the muscle wall weakness if you
overeat
and you're doing big meals all at once
you can pop a cork
and that can happen okay you don't want
to pop a cork
and so it's it's you want to keep your
meals like
you know you can do little meals all day
long however you want to do it
um i mean that's that's that's the
safest way to go
not eat like three big meals or one big
meal and stuff yourself because then you
put all this pressure
if you get stuffed you put all this
pressure and then that puts pressure
up against the intestinal tract going
into the stomach wall lining
so um so that that's right there
um so aaliyah what if you have such a
wide range of symptoms that you fall
into so many categories
where do you start what's your more
annoying symptom what's your second
most annoying symptom um aaliyah like i
would go into cleanse to heal
get the book out of the library for free
if you want go back
go back to the symptoms and conditions
section and look for your
like more annoying symptoms and then you
see
that if you address that annoying
symptom
or one of them your second most annoying
your third most annoying symptom kind of
go to those if you want
address them and what you'll find or
address
two symptoms but what you'll find is all
of a sudden as you're addressing that
other symptoms start to disappear and
start to ease off and that's that's how
i would handle it
if that was me
so you guys are amazing um
i'm really proud of you someone's
dealing with multiple sclerosis
which book is best for multiple
sclerosis um cleanse the heal because
you have so many different
options it's really comprehensive i walk
you through cleanses
um has a protocol for multiple sclerosis
you can take it to your doctor
uh ally so really
and you can learn about the cause of it
so you can gain control over your life
which is so important
chota says you're amazing anthony thank
you jody you're amazing too
thank you for all the work you're doing
and out there
you guys are incredible um i hope you're
drinking your celery juice hope you're
taking care of yourself i mean
why not drink it right i got myself got
my orange juice right here for later
yeah so um bless your heart and
keep a light heart you know keep a light
heart okay you're working on your
healing
process three steps up two steps back i
tell people that all the time because as
you're healing
and you're moving forward and you're
getting stronger you're going to do more
without realizing it and then you're
going to feel like you need a day to
recoup
the symptoms could crop up a little and
then boom you're even better and then
you're even better and you keep on going
up the ladder to healing
it happens with a lot of people who are
seriously sick but you take one step at
a time i know many of you guys are on
mattress island and you're struggling
because you spend a lot of time
in bed and all of that and you know i
just want to read one quote out of
cleanse the heel right in the back here
i'm going to cleanse the heels here's a
quote at the end here in the book i'll
show you the quote so you know
right there and it's not survival of the
fittest
it's not that people who haven't been
trapped by chronic symptoms simply
understand the secrets of life
better than those who get sick it's
survival of the ones who come into this
world less
toxic with lots of love support and
resources at the same time
and then happen to stay that way while
here on earth
if you have ever found yourself lying in
bed scrolling through somebody's feet of
waterfalls beaches and smoothie bowls
with peanut butter
wondering where you went wrong to land
yourself on your little mattress island
apart from the world
know this you didn't go wrong you're not
faulty you're not less than
the reality is that outside
circumstances and inherited poisons and
pathogens not internal weaknesses
determine
the challenges we face and someone who
has suffered health challenges can
change their fate what i'm saying is
if you guys are struggling because you
got the pathogens you're dealing with
and just so you know everybody gets sick
people who don't seem like they get sick
now and they're young they're strong
they get sick later everybody gets
symptoms later everybody gets sick but
just know
that you can change your fate when you
know and understand about the different
pathogens that you have
about the different toxins that you have
and then we can turn that around
we can take control over health the key
is to know how prevention and healing
really work
and if you really like this uh the show
and everything give me a thumbs up
give me a like a thumbs up okay
subscribe follow
um that would be amazing supporting
medical medium information
and supporting god's work and uh bless
your heart have the
and please share please share the video
if you can you know it really helps it
helps people out
i look at it this way it's i'm not
looking for clicks i'm looking for
people to heal
so remember that so if you can give me
some support so someone else heals
and someone else gets the information
and they're not in the dark that's a
huge huge thing
uh for a spirit of compassion and i
doing all this work all these years
and remember you know when you're
sleeping at night before you go to bed
at night think about the angels being
there
think about the angels being by your
side know that they're there
you know envision them being there ask
them to be there so they can watch over
you why
while you heal throughout the night okay
and help protect you while you're
healing help your body
with the process that it needs to do for
healing while you're sleeping and
remember your body's looking out for you
your body wants to heal
your body wants to heal it wants to heal
okay it does it does we just have to
give it the right tools
i love you guys bless your heart and
take