Anthony will scoot down a little bit
William the medical medium Kristen
Cassidy okay um Calvin Stebbins right
here two amazing people a healing story
a powerful healing story since rational
means the world to me because they're
family to me and so it really matters so
much and we'll have him here this is
incredible I didn't think I can get into
here but we made it happen it's
incredible so long so I just want to
introduce everybody that this is the
these two people are so precious to me
they've been through a lot and it gets
me choked up I actually because I'll
never forget and it's been it's been
it's been a long time now but we're
gonna we're gonna talk about what
happened we're gonna talk about you know
how serious it was and and Calvin's been
through he's 18 years old now and he was
10 years old at the time and so they
contacted me 10 years the other we're
gonna talk about it all so everybody
just get ready and sit back and get
we got yourself we got yourself reduce
right yeah it's been kind of hectic and
crazy this morning and so anyway we're
here to tell a story talk about a story
that happened and it was not it's eight
years ago now I would say now just a
there's go it's going on ten years ago
yeah and yeah it's been quite some time
so and you were ten years old and you're
starting to happen and everything so so
hey you know you guys see what you want
to you want to start and anymore you
know and I could I could take like I
just know when you guys reached out it
was your mom that reached
is that how it happened originally um
yeah my mom was the one that found you
I'm in a magazine and got this sort of
intuitive hit that this was someone that
could help us and we were at a point
where we were so desperate at that point
when we did find you and this had
started in January Calvin had started
with a just a just a stomach book just
an upper-respiratory thing like every
kid gets a normal cold and and then it
just it was having this abdominal pain
that just continued for months months
and months weeks and months and just
progressed and progressed and we went
through all of this we went through
everything that we could possibly yeah
by the time we had met you we were we
were at a bad place and it's just a very
very desperate desperate I was I was
just at a place of such desperation as a
mother it was just the most challenging
thing to have your child so sick and to
be so hopeless and our whole family you
know Calvin's dad and comes sister who's
a little older too we all you know all
of us together having to go through this
but I every day it was a it was a
full-time job every day to find
something that would work for him every
day I brought you I would bring you two
things you're old for a ten-year-old
that's got to be really hard
I mean I've talked about this for years
too but it's of course with mom goes
through because it's unimaginable to
when that's happening but then when
you're 10 years of age though it's
really confusing I mean and it's like
okay what's wrong here life was normal
and then now I can't really function I
can't do anything and that's you know
you know and I remember being on the
phone with you and you were just
literally in tears but it was more of
was New York I mean it was he couldn't
get up and walk when I was on the phone
was right and and you told me he was his
spirit was so broken you been to the
hospitals you've seen all the doctors
seeing the best doctors around all of
this and
and that's a thing I always tell people
science and research doesn't have
information for people that we think
they do they think we think they have it
all set yeah it all down beat you
quickly fine now that's not true and
that's that I mean and so tell me a
little bit like what you remember were
you in pain because I remember you
wanting excruciating pain yeah I think
the hardest part to is in the medical
industry if they don't know what it is
then they say you have a mental illness
that was the biggest thing that we were
gone for evil that was 10 years old I
had this enormous amount of pain that I
could feel in my body and then mental
state was terrible because everybody was
saying I was crazy you know they wanted
to put me in the loony bin
pretty much unbeliev what people don't
know about back in lolis I've been doing
this for 35 years people think I started
this yesterday meaning doing the work
we're doing on this and this is - going
on ten years with you guys but I think I
stirred this yesterday they think I just
popped out a book or I started some
celery juice thing but they don't know
that back in the back years ago and what
they did was they just told you it was
all in your head now they're teaching
you you're creating it that's the new
thing they're doing they're teaching you
you're gonna be eating it so it's like
your simple and your fault you're
creating it you're not attached to the
universe you're not attached to did some
things whatever and it breaks my heart
but the older days it was like it's in
your head can you imagine telling a 10
year old and and a 10 year olds mom that
he's making it up I mean he's an
absolutely excruciating pain he kills me
this is this yeah this is a stuff that
kept me going every day because it's
like we can't have this happen I mean he
went through a hell yeah I mean yeah
yeah it was hell on earth I mean yeah at
first it was confusing and then when I
got to the point where just before we
met you that was rock bottom
that was rocking like everybody I was
tired everybody would just want to give
up friends some friends and family gave
up on me though you know so as a
ten-year-old that is the hardest thing
is
so yeah it's not just being like
excruciating pain you can't go and you
can't go and you can't play you're ten
years old
ya can't ride your bike you can't have
any fun you're bedridden yeah
a men's family really does in certain
aspects of families not really trusting
in how you're young because they heard
from a professional that well we can't
find anything wrong with him and that's
the thing science research doesn't know
what's wrong with anybody even has a
diagnosis anyway yeah so it's it's this
is exactly what's happening at but I
mean I can't imagine as a little kid and
I remember I mean I was like when I was
on the phone with you and talking to you
and stuff oh yeah when I was hearing how
you guys are being treated ya know with
Indiana medical industry I mean I've
seen it happen before but but when you
see with you know literally I mean you
were so choked up you couldn't even
speak I mean you couldn't even speak
anymore and then yeah you said he can't
even get out of bed Anthony and no one
no one is helping yeah yeah I mean as a
mother like that was and you know
there's all those moments where I'm just
like you know I can't give up can't give
up on your child it's like you have to
do everything within your power and I
had a big bag of tricks like I really
thought I had you know I I was a you
know I was a practicing herbalist for a
really long time so which is incredible
Kalvin which is amazing how it like
lived in the garden and I made all these
things and that's what I treated him
with and so I knew a lot of alternative
healers and they were actually great
they they you know I went from phone
calls to people across the country i
exhausted all attempts of certain
doctors that I had and they could go so
far they went so far to support what
they could but really it was so out of
their sort of you know realm of
[Music]
I used as sort of a last choice but I
mean we went through that whole process
because he was in such pain I mean he
was I'm like we gotta go the ER and get
him comfortable and so we did ER visits
from our town we went to Dartmouth we
had to drive every time we drove him to
the larger medical which was the
Dartmouth Hitchcock in our he's like a
snowstorm I was like why can't they be
either in a snowstorm or something he
did the Scopes we did the blood test we
did heart ever to take your son hard to
take your child to all these different
tests driving around I mean with no
answers sitting here on a wild goose
chase yeah it was it was unbelievable
and they also in some of their bedside
manner was you know like after he did
his Scopes and I came in and then he
started that stomach pain and he was
moaning because it was just a you know
he just moaned all day long and she's
told to be quiet and I thought okay i
wheeled him out of that day in a
wheelchair and he just says mom you know
they're not on our side you know my
moment I said to him you know what no
they're not but but I'm here and I'm not
giving up and I'm gonna do whatever I
can and you know but and it just kept
going and going and going and no answers
I mean get through and it was a
full-time job I had to connect with all
the doctors I actually fired a doctor if
you do that hired someone else's his
primary because they were just not you
do I'm not against doctors never was I
know
I know hundreds of doctors I talked
about some great but you got a fire you
because like we just needed some other
support that just wasn't happening there
that's all well you know it's look
someone may think 10 years ago it's not
a long time ago that's a long time to
welcome kind of times were harder than
chore with being recognized that you
even have something
wrong with you you know but still this
is still happening today regardless but
it happened a lot more back then yeah
but but it's it it's it's tragic in the
sense where because it's it's lingering
afterwards it's like it's the PTSD is
what I know you guys have gone through
you told me about it but it's the it's
the post-traumatic stress syndrome or
pts SS they call PT a
PT so many PTSS right cuz they're they
call it now it's a stress syndrome
version yes you know and but the bottom
line is you guys went through a lot of
that yeah I mean it was pretty much that
was just like a testing dummy for a few
months until I met you going into
doctors doctors are great but when it
comes to something that they don't know
it's a thing people if they if they
don't know something then they tend to
not like it so they tend to not focus on
it yeah and that's kind of what the
doctors did they didn't know what it was
so they didn't focus on it they picked
another excuse for it yeah which was a
hard thing to do it was hard and like
you said the medical was just that there
was I was grateful for all the testing
to show but nothing would show up on his
testing so it was like nothing came in
to this this illness I want to bring it
back so you know you felt ill at first
and we're gonna talk about we're gonna
talk about what happened and along the
way your recovery what I saw we're gonna
go and talk to but wondering what was it
we're gonna cover back in yeah yeah but
like as far as like as you were getting
worse and and and the pain was there I
mean rock-bottom was you were just
laying in bed yeah couldn't walk
couldn't walk yes I couldn't even walk
across the floor it hurts so bad the
vibration that's what you said right
yeah is there any member any harm bring
him anywhere you told me he couldn't be
carried you told me that Dad had to
carry him around yeah we would carry him
you carry yeah yeah right sometimes yeah
yeah and that if you walk the you could
your steps were just even just stepping
was so pain stinky yeah until he
couldn't really scary
yeah and that was when as Calvin said
that rock-bottom to a feeling like you
like you said you think you've got that
there's gotta be someone out there who
knows something like you it's been six
months almost of just everything and
hitting a wall hitting along and having
people in your life like I had some of
my best friends the time show up and say
you know what are you doing to get in
the way of this healing why aren't you
having my license he's gonna end up in a
diaper if you don't and I'm like I can't
go down the road of fear with you I'm
sorry it's uncomfortable to watch this
you can't Ramanan what it's like to live
it I always yeah but I know I'm on there
what you're saying I'll look at
everything you know we could try to
psych her out they wanted to put him on
these meds that I couldn't even believe
you know it's just I got you know it was
just like all right we're gonna do we're
gonna cover everything to the point
where we feel but the biggest thing was
just like everything that we got out of
this and when I got out of it too is
just like I had to follow my gut
instinct I'm like I know that it's not
in his head I know that everyone in
everyone around me was saying you're
doing the wrong thing you're doing the
wrong thing he's gonna end up here and
you're you know you're gonna regret this
what if he what if he dies and you're
gonna regret doing you know and I felt
like every test he got it just didn't
help you know and even worse than
general a ten-year-old just wants to
play yeah be happy yeah and eat
he went to snowboard a ten-year-old boy
doesn't lay in a bed and purposely just
go into a mental state to die yeah it
doesn't happen but but that's and even
in the thing is and I've been talking
about this for years is that you lose
friends you know who your friends are
you know who your friends are and then
you lose them to you you know who you do
have his friends and then you know who
isn't your friend or isn't you know
because they can't put some type of
belief system they can't put that
they put that ahead of you knowing your
son softly yeah and put that ahead of
you you know of your son suffering you
know they do and I think people do that
because it makes them feel better that's
enough that's what yeah it makes them
feel comfortable to whatever they
believe in how science and research has
the answers because you're doubting
science and research and that that makes
them uncomfortable because people want
to feel safe you're not you're not
seeing the chronic illness is growing
exponentially it's it's populating the
population on the planet is basically
suffering at this point I mean because
people are hurting because yeah I mean
it's just the u.s. alone there's so many
people sick I mean in with symptoms but
this was this was grave at the point it
was yeah it was grave it was really
really really hard for you guys but it
look like I said it's it's people want
to feel better notice that that's what
they do so though they'll turn against
you or they won't believe you because it
makes them feel comfortable because
that's another thing it's the most
bizarre thing but it's true it is and I
think a lot of it I just I mean when my
friends came to me I I was just still I
recognized that was just their fear they
were afraid and there was nothing they
could do and I did understand you know
that you know that I said to just you
know I just got to do what feels right
to me even though it was really just a
few people in our lives who were on our
same page yeah just a few everyone else
just all the teachers means that you
know you're just a lot of other family
members I mean in the friends too I mean
they just didn't know they were just
probably as confused but they didn't
live the daily every day that was so
excruciating and to even hear him in
pain and for us to to feel that you know
and have trouble sleeping and it was
just so much I had him watching videos
we were watching Jeff Dunham and even
though I felt it was a little
inappropriate at the time the puppet guy
I just knew that laughter was needed
because it was we were like I just feel
like my spear was breaking and I was
scared of that like I was starting to
head that's when I wasn't even
comfortable going and I couldn't give up
but I was at that moment where yeah I
was I was sitting at the table going
I'm gonna do what I just said I would
never do I'm giving up I have nothing
else to turn to and that was like that's
where I was I was in the it was raining
outside you guys had finally gone to
sleep and I was just crying it like on
the table going I don't know what to do
I've done everything and that and then
you're gone it was like my mother
calling but she was just like I think
you know I found that you know I saw
this guy kind of you know think you
should go check him out and I you know
and then I called him and she said I
gave my plea and they're really busy but
they're gonna they're gonna talk to you
and you know and remember that was what
I was doing consultations they did
decades of consultations you guys know
that I've talked about that before but
but I think that that was yeah my office
got in touch with you and I remember
them they were taking your plea to me
yeah and they were just like no you have
to you know there's working on 50 people
in days it was more until night all the
way till midnight I slept so many hours
some you know all of it but the point
was was I was just like am i yep my the
people to my office was like they were
like no you have done just drop
everything coming back at me and I said
I said okay okay I said okay you got it
and and I think I got on the phone with
you and I was like oh yeah no we have to
take care of us we have to get this
better because um so a week and you know
in anything is is that the thing is is
you guys did what I wanted you to do
that's the thing I'm gonna talk about -
yeah because that's a whole nother thing
you were like I don't care what it is
yes you tell me he's gonna do it and
first of all you know to think that like
what Leah when a professional or doctor
says well your son's making this up or
something yeah right well no that's not
possible when he was literally he wanted
to do anything
you know he he literally wanted to do
anything yeah cuz cuz I said well you're
gonna have to eat like this just you're
gonna have to take all these supplements
yeah you're just like yeah yeah you know
and spirit of compassion who's talking
to me telling me exactly what he needed
to make sure you heal now the
information is now in all the books so
if anybody's out there and they're like
well how do I get how do I get a hold of
Anthony how do I do this now it's
through the books information is in this
I mean I obviously bought all the books
cuz we've just been you know it's our
place after we just got so close because
I mean I was just in such a place that I
was talking to you like every other day
and you were like just hang in there I'm
you know so young in there he's actually
getting the celery juice thing I've
actually given books to my friends too
who are book was this one's great too so
I mean all these are incredible it's
it's just amazing medical books there
are most people don't realize they're
actually medical books they are they're
it's all the information that people
can't get anywhere else
no that's what it's not it's not on the
internet it's not in other books all
that stuff does it doesn't you know take
this do this do your meringue a powder
do your collagen that's not gonna get a
ten year old boy out of hay out of a
crippling illness it just doesn't and
you know and yeah microbiome talk
doesn't get a crippling boy out of
illness it's like all these different
things in fads and trends and candita
theories and all this other stuff isn't
gonna do it you need real answers but
you know I was really I was really happy
about you guys contacting me at the time
because when I when I you know when i
centered myself because I was like with
chicken with a head
oh yeah we have to take care of this now
yeah and I was so happy when you guys
were doing what I needed you to do yeah
you know it was like okay as long as I
know you guys were doing it then we can
move forward and you can get better in
so I want to talk about a little bit
about what happened on my end so so
everybody knows out there so you guys
know so started out with a stomach
problem but nobody knew what it was and
it was like the you thought it was a
cold or something yeah it was just like
a normal first it was just like a normal
sickness people yeah yes a stomach ache
stomach oh yeah yeah okay but he wasn't
dealing with the flu he wasn't dealing
with a stomach flu
it wasn't dealing with anything or
appendicitis or yesterday we went
through everything no you guys went
through everything with the medical
testing routes all of that so what I did
I did a scan okay so I did a reading is
what what I used to do was this what how
it would work and spirit of compassion
would talk to me and tell me what's
going on and give me the vision of the
internal is internal working so I could
see in there as well a whole bunch of
white light comes down many of you
probably know I've talked about this
before I go partially blind and then I'm
able to see inside the person so that's
how it works so what was happening with
him he had a virus viruses I talked
about now viruses I talked about before
they came to me and advanced information
about virology that doesn't exist
anywhere and and so what happens who
that's responsible for chronic illness
and why people suffer and I try to keep
on teaching that there but what happened
was I saw a viral issue inside of him
and it was in the shingles family it was
actually in the shingles family now
children can get the shingles and it
won't rash out that's how it works
they're too young to have it rash out
because it's a different form of
shingles there's over 30 varieties of
shingles right now out there many of
them are non rashing that children get
adults can get non-rational ones too but
this is what variety of virus that
wasn't the problem is with this fire
it creates so much pain now an adult can
have shingles and they know the pain it
creates the outside rash the amount of
nerve pain it creates now when its
internal like this it's it's so
debilitating you can't walk you can't
function you could barely eat you can
barely even move and you won't you felt
kind of almost seized up and pain from
your from your lower abdomen to the top
here right where he was like you know
you're dreaming weird like your dream
remember you said something about your
dreams yeah and I'll talk about why it
wasn't right and then it's interfering
with and so people he just doesn't wanna
do homework I'm like no you know he's
like I can't get my brain so he's gonna
live he's gonna he's gonna he's gonna
lay in a bed and just waste away and die
because he doesn't wanted you home yeah
makes sense right ten years old yeah
yeah you know I didn't want to do any
homework when I was a kid but I would
just throw throw my notebook my homework
[Music]
that was that was how I handle it I know
you would handle the same way he didn't
want really doing you just wouldn't do
it yeah but you did your homework that's
not it you did exactly and all that but
it's unbelievable and so the shingles
virus that herpetic family virus it's in
people have if you think you don't have
the shingles viruses in yeah I got I got
it just give you this wake up called
everybody does think there's different
varieties and they come out at different
times they give people in there Appa
thee to give people jaw pain trigeminal
neuralgia to get people migraines they
give people fatigue they give people a
lot of problems and that's what the
shingles virus does and those are just
some things that it does and and so it's
amazing now it was interfering with
sleep because it releases a neurotoxin
viruses when they're really hyperactive
like that when you come down with an
infection like that like Calvin did it
releases a neuro toxic chemical that
floats around all through the body and
even
to the brain it can disturb sleep it can
create sleeping issues can make dreams
weird it could do all these kinds of
stuff
now it's advanced information you're not
gonna hear this stuff anymore and that's
what other thing is because we're kept
in this weird bubble of no one has
answers I don't care the best the best
authors the best doctor offers the best
whatever all these people out there they
don't have the answers science research
doesn't so we're kept in this bubble of
just try this try that
go get your blood work oh it's this it's
that in and so but this is really
complicated information so just try to
rewatch this again to understand how the
show - works and the bottom line is when
it gets into the lymphatic vessels -
because that's what happened it got into
your lymph glands from your down from
your lower groin and was spreading yeah
yeah it's spreading so what happens is
when it gets in there it then swells up
around the vagus nerve around the
phrenic nerves that run to your chest so
you got the vagus nerve and your phrenic
nerves that run down through your neck
down into your chest right here they get
inflamed from the neurotoxins from the
shingles virus it can seize you up it
could get everything - not only hurt in
severe critical pain but it could get
get your chest tight it could make it so
you can't walk it could cause so many
complications and difficulties and so
and these viruses if you don't when they
get like that and you don't jump on it
and you don't do the right things they
could go like this and be like this
forever I mean for years but we jumped
on this we got it taken care of and he
doesn't have to worry ever again yeah
but this was a shingles virus infection
it got into the lymphatic vessels they
got into nerves and in the thing is with
abdominal nerves are so sensitive that
all you need is a viral infection
touching all those different abdominal
nerves and and it's it's crippling and
for a ten-year-old to pierce that scary
thing you you did an amazing job you
protected your son yeah because because
of how you know you were mindful about
alternative medicine you were mindful
you're you have a yoga studio you still
have a yoga studio now there's Erin into
he's been eating out of the garden you
know when he was in trouble you have the
garden
you guys were organic food right yeah
there's that's a miracle that's why I
don't dislike all of alternative
medicine or alternative thinking you
know now we see the alternative medicine
world still is messed up - just like
conventional but there's so many great
things you guys are even working about
but the thing is is that that was a
blessing because moms out there they
don't have that and they they get stuck
in the conventional way and then what do
you do where do you go from there they
don't they don't take they don't they
don't reach out for something else or
they don't they just stay within the
perimeter of what they have a
conventional system or the thought
process there and then a virus like this
now could get really severe it could
create a problem then the then the
children may get a diagnosis of like ALS
or they may get a child did he make yet
another diagnosis of something else or
some see severe critical multiple
sclerosis or they run you through 20
more tests and they end up injuring you
in those 20 yes I've watched this it's
painful I talk to doctors that have
watches me I've seen some amazing
doctors out there talk about you know
other doctors that have not seen the
signs yeah yeah and so so your your your
motherhood your mother powers were
really on I mean you are really an all
moms powers are on they're all doing the
best they can and don't have
opportunities you know you guys were
able to find me yeah and and and so yeah
I mean but you don't know what you don't
know you know and so that's in like you
said to that even when we found you you
said you were caring for a lot of
children and a lot of them will end up
strapped to a hospital bed which I knew
that that was sort of the mean I just
felt like that was trajectory we're
headed if they were you know everyone's
like just put him on psych meds why
isn't he on psych meds and I just
thought you don't get it
IIIi will lose him
we'll lose him and you know and you said
that that was you know I know I was
harsh no you are you didn't you weren't
her salt what what look this is my what
you said that was I was so worried you
were but no you just said you are right
because I said I know it's not his head
and you said you are right in that
moment it was just to me like okay like
my gut instinct
I mean mom's just that's like the
greatest thing like go with your gut no
matter what people say or do and we had
everyone around us in my world just
doubting every move you are being a
terrible mother I mean I got I got stuff
coming at me and I just thought you know
what I have to keep going I have to keep
going and have to keep sticking to here
because I will lose him if I even think
to do what everyone is telling me to do
so when you just you just stepped in and
said you're right it's not in his head
you're right it's like okay so you kind
of pulled me up from that spirit so I'm
just like you just kind of hang on there
you keep going with us keep going with
this and that's why it was like we
talked a lot and you said put him on
this will do that there was only a
certain amount of food available to we
did a lot of bananas we did a lot of
well you guys were in Vermont I mean I
come from me I know what it's like in
the winter I know it's like when there's
nothing there you know and just it's a
difficult situation and but it was like
okay well what do you have what's there
you know what kind of it was it was sort
of like a mono diet in some way and
you're like no that's fine that he's
having a lot of bananas it's fine and I
drove 45 minutes to an hour every week
to go to Whole Foods so I had more fruit
and possibility and I was making things
that weren't so great for you because
you couldn't have meat and things like
that no because in order to it doesn't
mean you have to be off animal protein
the rest of your life right but what it
is and this is where belief systems can
completely stop somebody from healing
yeah
if someone's book it believes or doctor
believes now the
or protein or a family believes animal
protein is going to be the answer you
can't not eat animal protein in this
situation you wouldn't be here right now
yeah so anybody who's playing bass this
is kudos for you or whatever I mean you
guys are you know because you
plant-based believers or really they're
really strong on their belief system and
they fight a fight you know unless they
get a symptom and then they run back to
animal protein but the point is the
bottom line is is that the reason why we
had to go off the animal protein for you
which is a huge step for a ten-year-old
boy yeah I mean that's a huge step the
reason is because the high fat in the
bloodstream lowers oxygen levels so we
won't have a good chance of healing the
virus your virus is in your blood
it's in nerves it's in organs and then
if the blood fats too high because
you're having chicken fat cuz chicken
lean chicken lean chicken breast without
the skin has all this fat in it if you
have too much of any kind of animal
protein fat or if you have an animal
protein that could feed viruses it's a
whole other thing
and I'm not anti animal protein I'm not
anti being in whatever I'm just giving
you guys the layout is viruses they
think they can't thrive when oxygen
levels are really high in the
bloodstream that's number one okay
number two in order to get medicinals
in your system rapidly and faster you
can't have high blood fat you can't have
chicken fat and I mean I've seen this
over and over again and you got the keto
diet which is a high fat diet meaning
meanwhile you put somebody if a
ten-year-old boy suffering to this
degree has a virus like this so many of
you out there and you put them on a keto
diet we're gonna go downhill from yeah
people don't realize that in I'm
not anti keto diet I'm just saying it's
in this crisis situation we're applying
especially later saying can't have him
on me he will atrophy like I feel when
he's lying down there people that are
blind down thinking I mean all these
people in hospital you know that need
healing are being fed the wrong diet
here's how it works yeah the high fat
when you're when you're bedridden and
you you have the possibility of Astra
Fein and losing muscle and you're eating
the animal proteins you're the high fats
block sugars from getting to your cells
and sugar is how you sustain muscle
laying in bed I've had to help so many
people with severe neurological
disorders or viruses or problems Orange
is chronic illness of some kind it's
like whoa did the high fats have to go
the animal products have to go for a
little while because we need to sustain
your muscle because carbohydrates is how
we keep muscles it's how we keep those
muscles built and kidneys muscles strong
people don't know that so here's how it
works is okay number one you're stuck in
bed you're ten years old you can't use
your muscles so now we're at that now
we're at the mercy of the conventional
system both psychiatrists psychiatry
both the medical system he's 10 years
old they can possibly take him away from
you who knows you know the mindset they
have right you know that's how they do
and here you aren't laying in bed and we
had to say hey wait a minute
we have to make sure you sustain muscles
so spirit of compassion knows this
information nobody knew this information
out there they still don't and so it's
like sustain your muscles number one we
had to lower your fats in your diet so
that viruses can't thrive because here's
how it works
sugars like fruit sugars and potato
sugar and all that doesn't feed viruses
it doesn't at all it feeds your muscles
its antiviral so it's number one
so getting getting the fats down lower
made more oxygen occur in the blood it
allowed supplementation disels to get to
the virus the virus protects itself with
fact that's how it works so if we eat
all these fatty foods and we're sick
then it protects it with all that's the
fat in the bloodstream and does it
matter you know so what happens is we
had to make sure the supplementation got
to the bugs and killed off the bugs so
that's what happened we use
supplementation I talked about in the
books all the time about viruses and
these different things we had to make
sure that that was ample and you're in
your bloodstream we had to make sure
that the diet was really clean we had to
make sure there was no eggs in the diet
because eggs feed viruses and you're on
eggs at the time when I met you guys
yeah okay yeah you're gonna make your
ten-year-old ten-year-old scrambled eggs
of course every mom and makes their
technically not child scrambled eggs and
you know and rightfully so I totally
understand but hey these belief systems
we had to be like wait a minute no and
we had at the pinpoint no guessing games
yeah that's what I've talked about in
the books is there's no guessing games
at the map believe information it comes
from above any of the other information
that's all being thrown around a total
guessing game to how to make sure we'd
save his life and you did you did just
as bunch of a part of the you say I was
you too because all these different
things you did you listened and you know
you're like okay I'm gonna I'm gonna do
that and you were like I mean you just
ate whatever I told you to eat you
talked about what it was like for you he
was in pain yeah and you're really in
pain you're not going to be really happy
about anything no didn't like she would
make me it actually was look like
pudding and I remember thinking god this
tastes really good I think we could only
use raw honey
so it's wrong and pure like cake can our
cocoa and I had to go and I whipped it
up and it was this good and I'm like oh
my god chocolate pudding and he goes
chocolate pudding he takes a couple
bites he goes oh and then he sees the
green in the avocado you go wait
everything yeah
you just know I know I'm like trying to
hide it you know it's sort of like I may
do these like nut burgers and then I
think
I think some other moms - you had me
later justice sort of supports where
there is a support team brother mom
they're just going through this intense
situation and when we cook and where can
we go there is a lot of moms that we
were helping okay because that's what
happens it's just you know moms were
contacting the everyday in with a lot of
moms were stopping to recover their
children and we recover just these
hundreds and even thousands over the
decades and this happened was I was like
okay okay you got to talk to different
moms
we'll get you look at your mom to kill
them that worked on healing your
children the same way yeah move forward
with everything so it was about yet so I
connected you guys with a lot of moms
and make sure that you had support and
you were doing fruit because I remember
I had and right now free to shun its
tion this is something bad it's shown
this something not human I had a lot of
fruit potatoes said he's getting to take
a potato potato burgers and so my hero
he is you're my hero
because you know you just you just did
it you did it you're just like you know
and you just said just whatever I gotta
do I remember her telling me
specifically that you said you said to
me just give me whatever I need I'm
gonna do what I gotta do that's it you
said yeah I mean are you gonna heard you
a few times talking then you're talking
to me so yeah you know brave enough to
be on the phone meaning you know and
mama be talking that you you know I
would you be talking to me
and I gotta say you know if it's just
I'm really proud of you man I'm tracking
you I'm proud of this family because you
know because it you guys are tough yeah
it was a family effort we are all his
dad his sister we all just were like
cool chasity it was a whole effort I
mean we wouldn't be here without you so
you know I know the other thing is that
Calvin when he was going through his
pain and it's just torture to to look at
your child and just not be able to do
anything that was the thing to is I mean
the medical iov to go okay can we just
give him a pain med can we do something
can we whatever nothing touched it a
nerve block they tried every medicine
viral pain there there's no pain meds
for nothing nothing to again unless it's
really mild viral pain and then you know
people can use they can use some meds
for it but but what is it when it yeah
when it's viral pain and it's it's in
it's infectious like the higher
infectious state they listen you're
healthy the thing is is everybody's got
these bugs in them everybody girl boy
doesn't matter who they are they got him
in them so it's not like that's the
whole thing it's just Russian Roulette
basically or whatever it's like musical
chairs to when it's gonna hit yeah it
can hit you at 40 that's when it hits it
hits you at 45 you can go find you can
go through life you can do whatever
you're doing and then it hits you it's
just horrible and and then it can hit
you younger too it just means it's so
it's like we all have these bugs in our
system that's how it works and we all
get these different conditions I mean
you're healthy you're so healthy now
it's ridiculous you're healthier now
then I mean I could go just walk down
the street or I can go in a meeting
somewhere you're healthier than anybody
in there meeting you healthier then I
mean that's the whole thing I mean
you're really rock solid it gave you a
hug when you got here it was kind of
guns you got muscles you got muscles
many times bigger than even arms and in
your back you were all muscle so it was
like if the whole point is it's like
yeah you were like you're healthy with
how you taking care of yourself you
cleaned up that bug early on so it
doesn't sneak up on you down the road
everybody else has sneaks up on that I'm
Dan of getting sick with all these
problems they get the high anxiety they
get the you know the aches and pains
they get the tingles and numbness they
these are the things that happened in
their life and they get that you know
they get all these but you're but you're
really it's you're strong you're healthy
you put this behind you yeah tell me
about like the PTSD factor though
because I'm big on the PTSD because I
mean I even wrote about it I wrote about
it in the books many times and how in
the PTSD for one you've recovered from
something and gone through something
it's like you think if you get a little
cold you're like oh my god yeah yeah you
get a cold if I got anything it was like
what is this gonna be you know you you
overthink everything and then it just
sends you back down the road yeah when I
was super sick so it was it was hard to
actually get through that it took I
don't want to for me it took a couple
years I'd say a couple years yeah yeah I
mean we all sort of our work you know
and when you're in crisis as a family
you're you're also all trying to manage
your own emotions and everything else so
you know everyone has her own story I
was gonna say to I'll talk about the pts
for me to when you were just clearing
member when he was laying down and at
that point you know and I just nothing I
could do for him that's a hard thing I
couldn't take his pain away just give it
to me I'll take it but there's nothing I
could do and he looked at me and said
mom don't worry about it it's gonna be
okay
like you like you were trying to ease my
emotional you know ya breakage of
feeling to you counselor and I'm like
God you were just such a was calling you
my mom you know like my little Buddhist
monk he just was dealing with it and
like it's gonna be okay
you know he said I said that he's gonna
be okay and you know and so we you'll be
got through it become a Buddha it was
really cute first time shaving a saddle
but I mean the thing is for you to even
manage to manage chronic pain I got gosh
I mean you have this newfound compassion
for people that are also experiencing
what you're experiencing out there
you know all of you that are out there
experiencing that you're experiencing
and knowing that you know to be able to
manage that day by day it's such an
intense power within you to just manage
it and you're gonna have days where you
must have just felt like you wanted to
give up I can't yeah yeah yeah you know
just get so broken down that you know
that this information is out there too
you know that just you know like you
said we went through everything
everything served in its own way like
you said that's you know everything
servic but really we couldn't get to a
point where we could actually heal and
here we are there's all these little
tidbits out there there's all this
information the internet there's all
these so-called studies behind it
because everybody's throwing all these
studies the vegans and opinions are
battling each other over food and don't
even know what causes illness and then
you have all this going on and but yet
in the end you get sick you get sick
it's yes really sick where you shrug
them for why me and that's that's that's
what spirit told me when I was a child
and said you have to understand how
important this is cuz when I was your
age when I was 10 years old I wanted to
quit and I remember telling spirit I
don't care about anybody I don't care I
want to live my life was to be a kid I
want to be a kid
yeah that's route said no you don't
understand and there's there's gonna be
a lot of misinformation out there spirit
told me and it's gonna be impossible for
people to take action that really do
need to heal the here and you have to
stay with this as long as you can
post-traumatic stress disorder or so you
know the whole thing with that the PTSD
that's definitely interesting you know
the thing is with that is is it happens
to every I know I haven't see you guys
too all the time you got the chronic
fatigue syndrome you got you got the the
vertigo you got it doesn't you know you
got the anxiety you got the migraines
you got in an off son you're getting a
little better and then you get a little
symptom and if you like you know and I
always say it's still you know healing
is three step when you're doing the
right things have three steps up two
steps back and when you finally get out
of there and you're out of the weeds and
you're out of that
the depth of darkness you know and
you're finally pulled out of that then
you can still have that PTSD for a long
time I mean I've seen people have it for
five years four years you know years
after they've been healed or after
they've healed and so it really is
amazing how it works
yeah I think ours was about the same I
think that I mean I remember a day where
I didn't react with when you got sick I
remember that moment when oh my gosh I
didn't get that feeling in my body so
you were getting harassed it could have
been three years I just remember each
time even all of us you know the whole
family each time there was sort of a
sniffle read sneeze cough or someone's
sick at school and we thought oh gosh
the other thing that Calvin did you
remember is that when you when he in his
healing process and we would start to
transition them to eating more he would
start to get those symptoms again so we
know if we were off track and he'd say
oh gotta go back on that shouldn't eat
that I can't go on back any like you
immediately track back into protocol we
did that you know because you're still
in the early early process of healing
you were healing rapidly and then we're
and then you know you go into the old
ways in the old ways anyway wait a
minute I gotta get back on track until
it's finally all yeah did you have a
basketball hoop in your driveway did I
were dead why am I thinking you had did
you did you have a basketball basketball
yeah I'm saying this because I remember
you telling me he was in the driveway
bouncing a basketball well when you told
me and this was this was literally like
the first warm dad coming up I think or
you're just recovering you're finally
walking around the house yeah you were
feeling good
to it you told me I called up I was like
alright what's going on what's going on
and you're like he's in the driveway
playing basketball right now yeah yeah
because they knew motional II
emotionally you're using your arms
you're getting your strength back you're
bouncing your back that's gonna feel
mentally like you feel past that stage
if oh my god I was dying yeah now you
feel at the stage where no I'm living my
life playing and I knew that was so
powerful you that's the key it's like
you needed to be freed up and be that
child again and just move on with your
life you know when people get pranic
illness you guys know it's like hey wait
a minute I want to move past this I want
to move on with my life I want to get
past all this and you know and and and
so there's nothing better than having
that final chance to do that is to
finally put it behind you and just to go
back to work because so many people have
met them with the medical medium
information they heal and they feel like
they can go back to work they feel like
they go back to do things they feel like
all that stuff when you're a child I
mean it's it's just unimaginable really
because and you have to grow up fast you
have to learn how to grow up fast
because you had a council mom both my
kids are it was a really interesting
experience when he was in that process
of healing
especially when you have people telling
you that it was all sort of secondary
game for some reason and that and the
other thing too with the information
what does that mean
secondary game yeah I mean secondary
gain was what some of the um
professionals were telling us that um
secondary gain means that he was doing
it to get out of school work okay that's
it yeah that's it like that kind of
thing they were saying I'm like this is
not my kid this isn't how he is but
that's that's that's just I know it's oh
you can't no it's awful but you know but
I watch that be literally the thing now
that's what it was out there you got
sick if they couldn't figure it out
which was
millions of people that was all
experiencing that where you think you're
crazy
now it's like this is hope like now
these nations in the books the
information is here and in a live chat
or in any of your you know mediums that
you're out sharing this information is
that I think the number one thing to and
in the process of healing and being a
catalyst for that it's just hope when
you're at a place where your soul feels
so broken so hopeless and so sick that
you start to lose hope that there's
something that can actually be there to
sort of help you and and that was a
really big for me for you to just be
like hang in there hang in there okay
now he has to walk I'm like are you sure
like yeah you got to get him up on you
got to get him on his feet and and
Calvin wanted to get to his sister's
graduation and he forced himself in pain
forced himself on crutches when she was
at school so we could surprise her in
her eighth grade graduation we put him
in the car and it still hurt to go up
there because I'd hit a bump and he's
like wow but he just went through and he
showed up on his crutches and you know
from then on like you said then he
started to get ready oh yes we haven't
had a relapse you know and once that was
healing no relapse yeah I just hope for
people absolutely we got him out I mean
I wish I could have written the books
earlier than 2014-2015 I wish I could
have done that and to get the
information to everybody so they can
have this information yeah but I was
helping out so many the waiting list was
in the millions by the time I was I was
writing the books and there was just no
way to do that had to be through the
books from here on out but this was the
early days and this is this was towards
he you know this was not so early in at
all but it was early it was ten years
ago and it was in it you got me there
you know you got me when I was doing
that but they tell people don't lose
hope just because you can't talk to me
because now I'm doing the books the
books have this information in it if you
if you spend time to read if you can
folks some people they feel so sick they
can't read the book have a friend read
the book to you
just have them read the book to you
can't afford a book go to the library to
where I've taken pictures on my phone
and sent them like a chapter to somebody
yes they could read an or I would send
the protocol and different things that
they could start to Jason you know Scott
Bakula and Chelsea field were here
yesterday they're actually stocking some
libraries right now there's been some
requests and they're actually stocking
some libraries but some books they just
said hey you just let them know what you
know it so she maybe has some pound
we'll try to keep keep an eye on it too
and but you know okay so the
informations out there now but but you
know when the time when you guys you
know the books weren't there and Union
and yet you found me and stuff yeah it
look it's an honor it was an honor to
know you guys through the process and
and help you and be there for you guys
and and it says I've never forgotten I
mean you know we're family now yeah but
yeah yeah that's so amazing when you go
through something like that yeah and it
just it bonds you together you know you
know you can't break that it's just
always going to be there but I mean but
I have to say you know you you were your
fighters yeah
swear to God your fighters and I always
tell people just just find that fight
it's in you find that fun right there is
a place there is a place and I think
that's my this was like the most the
most challenging thing I've had to go
through and I always look at what's my
takeaway that I can share my yoga
students or even people in my life and I
think you know indomitable will it's
it's that like there's something inside
of us that is such a charge and such a
force that's untouchable from anything
else and that we have to find that place
there and I and I want people to find
out what you're doing now you're doing
you got your the other studio going on
it's in Vermont wait tell me what's
going on like how can people even reach
you and even get there and do yoga I
made you guys come down here to
California actually and then off the
plane later like I just barely made the
car yeah
so I yo my Studios in Brattleboro
Vermont I mean it's it's this great
community I just wanted to provide a
sacred space for people to come and
access through yoga just to access a
place you know being in their body in a
way that's accepting really funny the
place we're talking about I just
expanded my studio I can only like about
30 because I love that but people also
talk to me just in general it's freezing
it's freezing cold so I'm here to I'm
here as as a facilitator of getting
people to just label like the eleven
little you have a lot of experience
because when you when you get through
something like you did I mean that's
what I always tell you guys you guys are
experts when you when you literally
you're going through all that that
experience of being sick and going to
doctor and a doctor and making life
about doctors appointments cuz you have
no choice and all these other things you
give to the experience and something
inside you becomes powerful your soul
everything through the whole process and
go I don't want anybody to give up on
any level and then and then so what's
what it is is it's it's that experience
with all its really powerful and healing
and I mean you guys you guys are experts
that's how I see it I mean I see Calvin
is an expert because he knows more about
health than so many people that are
professionals he knows more about health
than any diet
and I met some great ones that know a
lot he knows more about health about
many of the nutritionist I've ever met
he knows more about health that's the
enemy that's the kind of thing it
creates like I'm wiping I'm hoping you
do some kind of health coaching
eventually I know you're young and on
your own but you know I'm hoping you
some health coaching I'm hoping that you
like start something like that because
your experience of what you went through
and how much you know and the knowledge
you have I think is priceless and I'm
hoping you actually start something and
instructing and helping people on that
level Tuesday no they gave no so much so
it's incredible when you I want people
to become experts I want you guys become
experts you know I've only said that
read the books become experts that's
that's when you become an expert too
it's experience you have of what you've
been through then you read the medical
medium book so you know the truth and
then you put that together and then
that's that's that's what happens and I
think what's great too is it empowers
you to take responsibility for your
health and you know like you said
there's only so much we can do but then
we can access the more educated to make
the choices that we may be able to
empower ourselves because research says
there's nothing in it
research doesn't know what's wrong with
people but they'll say celery juice
doesn't work isn't it amazing if you
like this live please subscribe I beg of
you to subscribe if you like but
I don't know anything about tech I don't
know anything I mean so I mean hitting
it with tech but the bottom line is ya
hit the like button right and subscribe
click that belt so you get notifications
or somebody how it works
super easy see I'm a dummy about that
stuff alright anyway I love you guys
this has been an amazing amazing amazing
time thank you guys an honor to be here
with you and with everybody out there
who's watching so really such an honor
and privilege I hope that you all get
some really good information for
yourself to move Florida into more
powerful life for yourself what do you
have a message for moms
well message my moms are really just um
you know - I mean for me it was just
keep on keepin on I keep listening to
your gut that's really everyone really
get as a mom you know we burn our
children were still so connected you
know when Calvin talks about wanting to
stay in California when I go back to
Vermont thinking my umbilical cord
doesn't stretch that far very just so
connected that that mom suggests like
hang in there and really trust yourself
like really be able to find a place
where you can to get calm and to get
centered and really be able to connect
into that deeper source that's within
you because you know you know what's
right for your kid like you really do
you do it doesn't matter what as someone
says and follow that lead to just follow
that lead and there's people like us out
here and other people too are here to to
support you and that to just like help
you when your faith drops when you just
feel like you're gonna you can't go on
but there are people there to help lift
you up and move you forward so I'm gonna
turn this this device off here bless
your heart