lunch so we're here gonna make some
things for you guys
and i'm actually really excited about
this because i'm gonna make the apple
cinnamon smoothie right here and cleanse
the heel if you guys don't have this
book you're missing out
okay so there you go cleanse the heel um
and i'm gonna show you what i'm gonna
make right here
so i'm gonna make the apple cinnamon
smoothie
so check that out right there okay this
is really an incredible smoothie i love
this one
i actually make this all the time uh and
love it
so you guys know i mean if you're up on
the book cleanse to heal
75 recipes in here but it's more than
that this is a healing book
it's not just healing foods like the
recipes
but there's information how to do
protocols for
conditions and symptoms over 200
symptoms and conditions
supplements and dosages i mean
the amount of information in here is
just so much um
but the apple cinnamon smoothie is what
i'm gonna be making today i'm excited
this is day three
of the medical medium morning cleanse
challenge
the morning cleanse is in this book so
that's where it is so you got all the
different cleanses the morning cleanses
in here
so so that's one thing i'm gonna make
for you guys
and i'm gonna make something else i'm
gonna make the wild
blueberry porridge from this book but
i'm doing it with
millet today now i know you guys love
your oats
not a lot of people do millet but this
is a better
grain a way better grain healthier in so
many ways
it does more for you than oats can do
even though i'm
fine if you guys love your oats your
gluten-free oats but the millet is
definitely an
option so what i'm gonna do is get it
simmering and cooking now
why i'm here good to see you guys i'm
excited that you're here so i'm making
the wild blueberry porridge but with
millet
um ardent says so good to have you
walking everyone through this
i've been doing the morning cleanse for
about the last eight
months every morning and what a
difference it makes incredible thank you
for being here
so great i'm excited um you guys
this is exciting exciting time um
because you know we're coming up on the
holidays
and what a perfect time to do this
morning cleanse i mean arden you're
doing it which is incredible and you're
doing it for eight months now
and the just have all that like
behind you like that getting you strong
so when the holidays come
you put all those months of that time
and energy into it during the morning
cleanse i'm really proud of you
and um it says exciting time but we can
jump on it now too we can start it now
that's what's incredible we can start
doing it now so
um grains are
scratchy though to me michelle l says
yeah well grains
are not a big part of medical medium
foods and information
a lot of people have different feelings
towards them they have different
sensations they have different reactions
the only two grains that i really like
if someone's gonna do grains are millet
which is a really
gentle gentle grain that one right there
and that's what i'm to do
or oats those two but i like millet
better because
people who are sensitive can do better
with it if
you want a grain so um
so what i'm going to do is take a cup
right here of millet
so i'm excited about this just dropped a
little bit up and that's
putting it in the pot here
so there we go it's about a cup
of millet and then i'm going to show you
over here i don't know if you guys could
see it hopefully
so that's it in a pot right there
okay and i'm going to add the water two
cups of water
in here now with millet
you just got to simmer it for about 25
minutes sometimes depending it could
take a half an hour
i'm going to bring it to a boil simmer
it
and what's going to happen it's going to
be this glorious thing i'm going to make
millet porridge so basically can be the
wild blueberry porridge but with millet
instead of oatmeal
i'm also going to make the smoothie so i
can't wait the apple cinnamon smoothie
so
let's talk about the morning cleanse a
little bit glad everybody's here this is
exciting
so let's start with the lemon water got
it right here
and so
you can do lemon water you can do lime
water
i did lime water yesterday i'm cutting a
lemon now
over here so it's my lemon as you guys
can see i don't know how
if you can all right putting half a
lemon in here like this
upon waking 16 to 32 ounces
of lemon water really important to flush
out the liver
here's a really important point you can
let people know
when you see it in the you know when
people are commenting about it
and talking about it this is a critical
point right here
you know what it is it's do not use hot
water
if you use hot water you can't flush the
liver
you cannot flush the liver of the toxins
in the morning
to get them out i'll tell you what goes
wrong when you use
hot water this this is a mistake that
came
after medical medium information so
medical medium information was
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water
okay squeezed into lukewarm water room
temperature water
or cold water first thing in the morning
to flush
the liver and flush the body of toxins
it's original medical medium information
with lemon water
and what happened was as the years went
on all the teaching
all the lecturing i did all the teaching
different practitioners
doctors throughout the years it the
lemon water thing caught on to flush
to actually flush toxins out of the body
stemmed from originally from the medical
medium information but what
something here's what went wrong with
the information somebody said
do it in hot water well they just ruined
it for a lot of people
so it's it's really becomes a wasted
effort
if it's done in hot water now herbal tea
is another story because with herbal tea
when you put lemon in herbal
tea you're doing an herbal extraction
and what you're really trying to get out
of that herbal tea anyway is an herbal
extraction so that's different but this
is a different situation right here
so um and
what people also do another piece of
information that doesn't work is it not
only put lemon in
hot water which is not good but
put lemon in a cup of hot water so have
your lemon water like eight ounces or a
cup
that won't work either so it's basically
distorting medical medium information so
that people
don't get a healing benefit and don't
move forward
these details are critical the details
matter they matter with getting
past the finish line they matter with
actually
really healing and getting yourself
better
they really count these details and
that's the difference of medical medium
information versus other
so once again 16 to 32 ounces
of lemon water for seeing the morning
upon waking to flush out the liver
and the body of toxins okay so that's
what you do
and then it was distorted as the years
went by
because medical medium information has
gone around the world and then some
health hacks
in in the health industry or some health
gurus decided
oh no yeah you do your lemon water but
put it in hot water
and here's what goes wrong the hot water
stays in your stomach
your body will not release hot water
from your stomach until it cools down
if it holds onto the lemon too long in
your stomach
the lemon will lose its potency the
ability to actually be able to help you
the second thing is you're destroying
the lemons
critical enzymes so a fresh raw
lemon has enzymes that help the process
in flushing the liver
that disappears the minute you put it in
hot water that's the disaster right
there so i just want to give you guys
that rundown so
you do your lemon water then you do your
celery juice
i'm going to grab mine right here
so i got my celery juice that's it
um not juicy today because i got a lot
of stuff to cook right now
this has come to a boil pretty much it's
simmering so these
are this is going to be the wild
blueberry porridge
from millet so i'm using millet this
time
millet is a better grain than oats
by far there's a lot there's a lot more
phytochemical compounds there's a lot
more nutrition in it there's
there's um with millet it's gentle on
the intestinal lining
so it's one of the only grains that's
actually gentle to the intestinal tract
and still if someone's sensitive with
grains they don't have to do grains of
course not but i know that a lot of
people do greens
they do them around the holidays they
they eat bread of course around the
holidays cookies everything else in the
sun
and i know a lot of people do oatmeal
and oatmeal is okay
but millet is that next step better when
it comes down to grain so
i said you know why don't i make the
wild blueberry porridge with millet
so you guys have an option i'm turning
down the burner a little bit you'll see
it
you'll see it cranking in here
so
there we go so that's what i love i love
showing you guys different options
so you have other ways to help heal
so i'm going to let this simmer and do
its thing
it's just cranking a little hot so i'm
going to take the lid off a little bit
there we go
but anyway after the 16 to 32 ounces of
lemon water
you wait 15 to 30 minutes okay
and you move into celery juice then you
do 16 to 32 ounces of celery juice
we'll talk about the power that has as
well so the celery juice
has a lot going for it a lot more than
what people know they don't
know what's in celery juice they don't
know what celery juice does for them
and one of the best parts about celery
juice is it revives your stomach glands
so you got these two little stomach
glands in your stomach okay
those stomach glands create your hcl
your gastric acid so those stomach
glands
get burnt out in everybody that's why
things go wrong
when those stomach lands get burned out
you can't produce enough
hcl and that hcl kills off bugs
pathogens it stops us from bloating that
hcl
breaks down protein and it
stops proteins from rotting and
putrefying so everybody walks around
with low hcl
hydrochloric acid and then their
proteins putrefy
in their gut and start to rot and when
they start to rot
it feeds more bacteria that's not good
bacteria
celery juice brings back your stomach
glands
allowing them to produce the gastric
acid needed
the hydrochloric acid medical beam
information is the seven
blend hcl because hcl isn't just one
acid it's a blend of seven and when you
lose your gastric glands
the gastric gland strength those acids
they weaken and you lose like three of
the seven four of the seven so your hcl
isn't strong
and uh celery juice brings that
back stabilizes the the stomach glands
it's a critical part of how we heal with
the celery juice
and you'll hear people out there i mean
there's millions of people drinking it
they'll be like
celery's used to help me celery juice is
getting me better celery juice has
helped me you know what my digestion but
they don't know why it's because those
little stomach lamps they're really tiny
they're like
they're like the size of they're smaller
than
a garlic clove smaller than a garlic
clove i got some garlic with me right
here
so i'm gonna i'm gonna leave this here
simmering like it is
you guys if you just got on here talking
about day three
of the medical medium morning cleanse
challenge
this is the book cleanse the heel and
just just for just for the record you
guys
on amazon.com us it's not only
51 off but there's a coupon on there for
2.55 cents
and you can get this book for like 14.50
right now
on amazon.com us i mean it's incredible
really
so check it out if you can you could
also just go to the library try to get
one there too if you want get one get a
free copy of the library
but that's cleanse the heel making
recipes today doing the wild blueberry
porridge but with
millet and i'm going to be doing um
apple cinnamon smoothie so i'm going to
start working on that next
i'm going to move this over a little bit
[Music]
glad you guys are coming on you're in my
kitchen which is the best thing ever
having guys with me is is
definitely the fun part of everything so
this is this is what i look forward to
so great um so i'm just gonna
organize things here i'm gonna get a
blender over here too so just bear with
me for a second
bringing this over
so the next thing i'm making is the
apple
cinnamon smoothie so that's what we're
that's what we're trying to make right
now
that's it right there so
susan said i got rid of a rash my son
has had
on his chest for years he didn't believe
it
it would work making believer out of him
slowly incredible
that's incredible it really is all right
let's make this now listen on the
medical meeting morning cleanse
okay you got your 16 out there 32 ounces
of lemon water i showed you
right you guys 15 to 30 minutes later
you got your 16 to 32 ounces of celery
juice right
okay you can do fresh fruit after that
you can have a
breakfast of like fresh fruit you could
have melons cut up
you could have mangoes papayas you can
go with something a little denser
papayas and bananas you can do that
or you can go further than that not just
have a smoothie or a fruit bowl
you can have steamed potatoes sweet
potatoes if you really want
something more denser you can mill it
you can have oatmeal if you really want
that's an option too you can have winter
squash that's one there yams is another
option so you can have that
right but you can also have the heavy
metal detox smoothie
that's one of my favorites because
you're getting metals out you can have a
liver rescue smoothie you can have that
option
so okay so let's work on this right now
so we need two medium-sized
red apples so that's the first thing
right there
so two medium sized red apples i got a
red apple right here
and i got another one right here so mary
says i missed the recipe for the lemon
juice
drink i do make my own celery juice
already
incredible very amazing so the recipe
for this
is you get your 16 to 32 ounces of water
you cut
a lemon in half that's one half i just
squeezed
okay and you squeeze it in there now the
key is don't put it in hot water
don't do the hot water make sure it's 16
to 32 ounces and do it upon waking in
the morning
that's the key wait 15 to 30 minutes
before you do the celery juice
so all right going to cut some apple
right now
[Music]
this over put my apple pieces in here
just reading some comments at the same
time
i gotta do the sporting cleanse
challenge more often because this is
really fun
[Music]
so i just cut that apple if you guys can
see that's the cord
so cut another one i could use this
knife too
[Music]
you could do it a lot of different i
mean i like using the small knives too
so that's that's the way i've done it
so cutting up the apple so this is two
medium-sized apples
[Music]
you don't want to put the core in
because you're just going to blend the
seeds up
the seeds are bitter so apple seeds are
bitter and if you blend that
up you're just going to make you're
going to make this smoothie bitter so
that's something right there
now these are frozen bananas i'm going
to show you next
so one and a half frozen bananas
so look at these great frozen bananas i
have right here
so i'm gonna put these in
[Music]
break these pieces up
and i'm gonna do a half a frozen banana
right here
okay we got that going on and um all
right so
that's in here so i'm going to do one
cup of water
so that's my water right here got that
in there nice
now this recipe just so you know if you
just got on here
this recipe's out of cleanse the heel
that's the book okay it's the apple
cinnamon smoothie there it is
that's the recipe that's what we're
making
it tastes so good
so i'm really excited so i'm going to
put a teaspoon of maple syrup in here
too
just so you know
now you can put a date in there i like i
like the maple syrup so i have this
maple syrup right here
now a teaspoon you could measure i'm
just going to dump it right in if you
guys don't mind
i put probably a little bit more than a
teaspoon in there
of course and then i'm going to drop
some cinnamon in there now
you got the cinnamon okay and this is
the recipe out of cleanse to heal just
so you know so i'm going to drop some
cinnamon in there too
so it's three quarters
three quarter of a teaspoon of cinnamon
this is how to cleanse the heel
it's a question right there aren't apple
skins
aren't apple skins um
full of pesticides so well these are
organic apples
that's number one so i have organic
apples here so keep that in mind
um yeah if you get in conventional apple
and it was sprayed recently before
harvest
so conventional apple if it's sprayed
close to harvest okay
if that's the case then you're going to
have some pesticides on that apple
okay and then they wax them so they put
the msg
wax on top of a conventional apple and
they coat those pesticides and almost
kind of
encapsulate them on the skin
conventional apples i
i peel so that's what i would do is just
peel them
these are organic ones so i'm gonna put
three quarters of a teaspoon
i'm putting the cinnamon in here that's
about right there
about three quarters of a teaspoon
probably a little bit more
okay and then i'm going to blend it up i
got the water in here so
now it's time to blend it up
so glad to have you guys here this is
[Music]
awesome
so i really like this smoothie
what i love about these recipes is that
they're
healing recipes and
there's something to be said about them
okay it's all set
[Music]
so um i have the smoothie right here and
i have a cup too but i'm gonna use this
real quick
you can put a little cinnamon right on
top
i like to put a little bit of cinnamon
right on top
that's what i like to do i don't know if
you guys can see this i don't want to
spill it over but there it is
i think you guys can see this
now i'm going to do a little grated
ginger
now what i like to do is do the fresh
so i got a piece of ginger right here
now the recipe calls to blend in the
ginger
i like to put it on top of mine but look
you know that
it's it's great blending it into
the millet is actually simmering over
there
but what i like to do is i like to just
grate a little bit of
ginger fresh ginger right on top
like this
there you go
now i put extra for me
since you know i mean look you could do
you can do
a lot less but i put fresh ginger right
on top it's grated
right on top just like that and what i
like to do is take a spoon
and i kind of like just to mix it up and
i like to use a spoon to eat it that's
that's the way i like to do it then you
can drink out of the glass too
so put this right here where you guys
can see it
so that's the apple
cinnamon smoothie right there that i
just made
it's out of cleanse the heel the book
cleanse the heel
which is this book right here
and um
we're doing the medical meeting morning
cleanse and this is an incredible
incredible meal right there so i want to
cover a couple little things with you
guys
just moving stuff out of the way here
[Music]
you can do lime instead of lemon water
just another option you can do lime
because that people ask about that all
the time and i got limes right here but
you can do limes that's perfectly fine
so that's an option in your lemon water
but lemon is
is usually best a lot of time
limes are really dry so that happens
i'm going to move this out of the way
okay now what i have going on here this
is the millet
i have cooking right here
what if you can't eat banana what's a
good substitute
papaya is a great one that's an option
right there mango's a great option too
so those are those are those are awesome
so you can do that
if you need to
um nina says i love millet too awesome
if you're somebody that if you're
somebody that has any kind of acid
reflux
struggling with your digestive problem
on any level um
in cleanse the heal there's the mono
eating cleanses so that's that's a great
option right there for you like the mono
eating cleanses are great you can do
the potato mono eating cleanse you can
do
the papaya one that's an option all on
its own
all it says it's an incredible smoothie
have you had it before
amazing so here's what you want to do
with your
medical medium morning cleanse you want
to keep the fats
out of your morning the key is
protecting your liver
the key is getting your liver better the
key is about getting the toxins out of
your liver and you might be like
well do i have a liver issue well do i
really have one
if you have any unwanted weight like if
you're gaining weight ever in your life
that means your liver is maxed out
and that means the liver is all it's all
filled up with fat to begin with
so that's the start of the problem right
there so if you have any kind of weight
issues on any level
if you're gaining weight on any level
the liver is maxed out
it's got too much fat inside the liver
so that's number one that's one problem
all on its own that that people have
if you have skin issues like vitiligo
eczema psoriasis rosacea
dermatitis dandruff
that's all a liver issue so that's a
liver problem right there
if you have heart palpitations if you're
dealing with migraines
if you're dealing with any kind of
autoimmune the liver is involved
too so crohn's colitis
acid reflux celiac ibs
the liver is involved that's a big part
of why there's a problem so
all this is important to know so what
you're doing with the medical media
morning cleanse is you're restoring your
liver you're bringing
your liver back you're bringing your
liver to where it needs to be
you're giving it a chance to heal and
here's the thing
your liver wants a routine that's what
it wants
it wants to do a routine every single
day and we break that routine by
bringing in fats in the morning we end
up bringing in eggs
we end up bringing in um we end up
bringing an avocado toast
and i never said avocados bad to eat if
you want to eat some avocado but have it
afternoon
have it afternoon that's the time to
have it if you're going to have it
if you're going to have nuts and seeds
if you're going to have walnuts if
you're going to have hemp seeds if
you're going to have almonds
nut butters peanut butter have it
afternoon you want to do the medical
medium morning cleanse and be
fat free in the morning as far as
radical fats
no milk cheese butter no bacon no eggs
no meat no chicken
no nut butters no oat milk no oat milk
because it's concentrated it's higher
fat and there's no soy milk
no almond milk you want to keep all of
that out of your breakfast
out of your morning and you want to do
your lemon water
you want to do your celery juice you
want to do your heavy metal detox
smoothie your liver rescue smoothie you
want to do some fruit bowls
when you do fruit and the fruit
smoothies or the heavy metal detox
smoothie
you're maximizing the most healing you
can do
in the morning and then that's and then
afternoon you can bring in those nuts if
you want or your
avocados or something like that
so i got the millet cooking right here
and it's done
turning it down
so this millet is is nicely cooked here
it is
now it's b it's this beautiful yellow
you see this
creamy yellow that's right here and
that's it so instead of oatmeal we're
doing millet so i'm gonna add
in the wild blueberries these are the
frozen wild blueberries
right here i'm gonna add some in
now i'm gonna mix them up in here so
this is the medical medium
wild blueberry porridge we're doing it
with millet
i mean millet is an incredible tasting
grain if you're into grains
all right so i'm gonna put it in a bowl
right now
and you can put some blueberries right
on top
so i'm going to put a few blueberries
sprinkle them right on top like that
and then i'm going to add some maple
syrup
right here
so that is the the wild blueberry
millet porridge versus oats and i'm
going to put a little bit of maple syrup
right on top here
and that's it and it's
really an incredible dish it's a hearty
dish if you're somebody that wants that
density
you can have it in the morning on a
medical meeting morning cleanse
but fruit is always just straight fruit
smoothies or the heavy metal detox
smoothie or the liver rescue smoothie
with the celery juice also the in the
morning and the lemon water is always
best for
maximizing your cleanse but at least
there's no fats added in here so there's
no nut butters there's no peanut butters
there's no coconut oil
there's no oils this helps you
cleanse in the morning don't put nut
milks in here whatever you do don't put
almond milk in here don't
put soy milk in there don't put oat milk
in there
so don't add anything like that you want
and don't put
you know don't put bovine milk in there
so
keep all of that out and this is an
incredible
dish right here so it's really exciting
see you guys
we just did the lemon water because hey
16 to 32 ounces upon waking flush the
liver flush the toxins out of the body
wait 15 to 30 minutes 16 to 32 ounces of
celery juice
okay the celery juice the benefits are
miraculous really
help it's a complete electrolyte for the
brain focusing concentration helps to
loosen toxic heavy metals it diffuses
toxins it helps to flush out
petrochemicals pharmaceuticals inside
your liver
old antibiotics antidepressants thyroid
medications anti-inflammatories cold
medicines
that stay in your liver and get toxic
and toxic and toxic and toxic
the celery just helps to loosen that up
helps to flush that out
and then later on have some fruit you
can have a fruit smoothie
heavy medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie
by the way right here in cleanse the
heel
the heavy metal detox cleanses in here
put the smoothies in here the recipes in
here you can have that in the morning
have additional fruit if you want and
then you can do 16 ounces
of water and 16 ounces of coconut water
all the way till noon
then afternoon is when you can do other
things or bring in that avocado if you
wanted to if that's what you love
or bring in something else or if you're
into animal protein you have it
afternoon or in the evening but that's
the medical media morning cleanse this
is a big
part of it here's some options um
incredible you guys
so glad you're here but check out
cleanse the heel if you can
because right now it's the price is
just can't be beat i've never seen
anything like it so it's not only
51 off but the coupon at amazon.com us
brings it down to like 14 it's a medical
textbook
it's got the protocols in there so you
can really move the needle it's got the
cleanses in there
so so glad you guys came here there's
the medical medium while blueberry
porridge right there with millet
just showed you guys really exciting and
here is the apple cinnamon smoothie i
got a little ginger on top i got a
little cinnamon on top it's just so
great
so really glad we could do this as day
three i'm proud of you guys if you're
doing this
yeah faith there's there's fat no milk
it's crazy but there is it's
concentrated more
more concentrated dr fun yeah
millet
amazing um
anyway drink at least 16 ounces of water
or 16 ounces of coconut water
two throughout the morning like i
mentioned a couple of minutes ago
you guys have that too in your morning
cleanse you got that
just reading some more comments
okay yeah susan coconut milk no keep the
coconut milk out
that's that's a problem you don't want
the coconut milk in the morning if
you're into coconut milk and that's
something you like and you love coconut
milk
you can do that after noon so
but don't do the coconut milk before
noon that stops the cleanse that stops
the morning plants no fats
no eggs no milk cheese or butter
none of that if you're somebody with bad
acid reflux
you keep the fats out keep the eggs out
keep the dairy products out
take a break from even meats if you can
just don't do anything in the morning
like that
and maybe even in the afternoon look out
for how many fats you're doing
and if you're dealing with somebody
you've got digestive problems acid
reflux if you've got ibs if you've got
bloating if you got celiac
crohn's colitis anything like that
there's even an
acid reflux protocol and cleanse the
heal
but keep in mind there's protocols in
here on how to heal how to move forward
over 200 symptoms and conditions and
cleanse the heal
and it's a book that is one of those
books
that'll blow your mind so much
information so many protocols
to get better and take advantage of the
sale on amazon us
it's incredible or just go to your local
bookstore thanks so much you guys i'm
heading over to ig now i'll see you at
instagram
wait and you guys just so you know on
tick tock
i'm going to be making a potato skillet
at 5 pm
eastern time 2 o'clock pacific time i'm
going to be making the potato skillet
only on tick tock
let you guys know so i'm cooking
something different i'm hoping it's
going to go
good so meet me on tik tok later on too
five o'clock eastern two o'clock pacific
i love you guys