here we are Anthony William the medical
medium with two great friends right here
this is incredible doctor Masha Cogan
dr. Gina Romano right here
dentists I think we got scoot down just
a little maybe maybe that's what happens
when we're live so we're talking about
dental problems and everything else I'm
the number-one New York Times
bestselling author of the medical medium
series help people out throughout the
years decades with mystery problems help
doctors out troubleshooting the cases a
little bit about me you guys know
already start at the celery juice
movement global the originator of the
celery juice movement right you guys
know that and we're drinking celery
juices right now so it's really fun so I
had them on and really lucky like this
is really a lucky day it's more than a
lucky day an incredible day because
these are the best dentists I've ever
known out there in the world and and I
know this for a fact because if they
know the knowledge they know the
information they're they're experts
extracting mercury fillings and there
are experts in general about teeth all
the different things that dentists don't
know about they know and that's what
happens just because your dentist
doesn't mean you know a lot about teeth
I mean is that true I mean like that's a
really important factor out there if you
look them up and and you'll you'll find
out where the practice is they're worth
a plane flight we're gonna talk about
they're worth a plane flight to get your
teeth looked at to get you know care for
your teeth they are worth it believe me
anybody wants to do that they should
we're gonna talk about mercury fillings
extracting them we're gonna talk about
heavy metal detox movie we're going to
talk about root canals we're going to
talk about TMJ that's the mandible joint
but we're going to talk about trigeminal
neuralgia which is a really important
one and how it's viral so don't miss
this episode you stay on here you don't
want to miss this this is important that
we're gonna talk about mystery teeth
pain burning gums fat you know you know
you know the fast shot all that the the
jaw jaw pain we're gonna talk about that
too we're even going to talk about the
plant-based movement you know how or why
everybody who's vegans believe the
minute they get a tooth problem
it's blamed on their diet and how that's
a misconception so if your plant-based
or big supporters of you
you know we're supporters of everybody
whether they need animal protein or not
or whatever we're supporters of
everybody but we're big supporters of if
you're a plant-based person and you're
scared and running because you've got a
cavity and you think maybe it's your
diet we're going to talk about how that
works why that happens so hey thank you
for coming you guys
thank you for having I'm even clapping
today because this is really cool thank
you
this is really cool so so basically
let's talk about let's talk about that
whole thing with the plant-based
movement right off the run um because
that's a big deal because I always say
that when somebody on a plant-based diet
gets the first symptom say it's not even
dental but they get the first symptom
they get scared they think I don't have
protein somebody tells me you got to go
back to animal products and they start
freaking out and they drop everything
and they just go running out of fear and
everything so and I always say that that
you know it's sad because so what does
that mean no one with a paleo diet ever
had a symptom nobody with an a really
high quality keto diet nobody with you
know however had symptom so where do
they run and they don't run in hide I
noticed they don't meaning because their
diets never blamed their diets never
blames if you're on the keto diet a
healthy keto diet or a new name-brand
keto diet high-fat diet you're you know
when you get your first cavity or you
get your first symptom it's never going
to be blamed on that keto diet it's
never gonna be blamed on that high
protein diet the minute your plant-based
though the minute you're there and
damned if you just your your whole your
whole days ruined your life is just your
your your shifting your gears and all
that it's really sad because you know
what I've seen all these years and I'm
talking about three and a half decades
of this you know is that it has nothing
to do with the fact that your
plant-based that you got a cavity
occurring and we're gonna cover like all
that and in in that whole area and stuff
of what happens there and then the root
canals we're going to
about that a little later too and so you
guys see this you hear about this though
when people are plant-based right yes I
mean when I was in dental school you
know people who were vegan who ate a lot
of sugar a lot of fruit it was always
that you know it's because of their diet
this and that but I've been out of
dental school for a while and I see it
in practice it has nothing to do with
sugar it has to do with your digestive
how you're digesting food things that
are coming back up things that you know
we speak about so it's definitely not
definitely not the vegan or the
plant-based diet
yeah which leads me to this thing which
you know I think I talked about this you
guys know this but our teeth are time
capsules and I mean you're like the only
dentist out there that truly know that
that time capsules means it's not what
you're doing even in the moment of why
you have a problem with your gums your
teeth your jaw you know it's what
happened in the past what were you
eating 20 years ago what were you doing
15 years ago what kind of stress were
you under did you have acid reflux for
ten years roading the gums and acid
reflux is one of the biggest thing you
guys we see all the time people with
digestive issues have acid coming up
when they're sleeping and just washing
away the enamel destroying the teeth
digestive issues for us equals teeth
problems and it's actually the hardest
to treat because anything you put on the
teeth if you're not fixing your GI it's
just yeah and then when you're laying -
you're laying down at night you're
sleeping everything creeps up so it
creeps up the canal you know there's
something that I always say is ammonia
permeability and and it's rotting
protein it's rotting fats in the linings
of the testicle track they're sitting on
the linings of the testing on track and
it's sitting there and it's putrifying
and you got a you know got all these
microorganisms feeding off that it's
putrifying and what you get you get
these ammonia gasses that creep up and
they're just getting into the mouth you
know the whole halitosis thing which I
didn't even talk to you guys know right
the whole halitosis things down breath
right and and people think it's because
of the mouth they think it's all because
of the mouth
it's the gut it's the good lives in the
gut it's all that ammonia coming up and
so and then you got the acid reflux
you've got the assets coming up to of
roading the gums starting to take out
the gums and you know in the thing is
it's one of the reasons why I say you
got to do your celery juice you have to
do your celery juice so you start your
celery juice now it's going to help you
later on because you're restoring your
hydrochloric acid when you restore your
hydrochloric acid you lose that acid
reflux because you know acid reflux
they're bad acids produced by
microorganisms and bad bacteria that are
in the liver better'n anywhere in the
gut and that's what's coming up the
celery juice three months three months
in how the doses will be gone you guys
will see the difference right away
you'll be it'll be incredible okay and
you'll see it and talk to your friends
they'll tell you you have no bad smell
coming out because we see it all the
time if you're not if you have that
ammonia coming up it's bringing the pH
down yeah when you bring a pH down you
allow bacteria to kind of grow and
that's you know you have to kind of get
the GI to a better position and deliver
to a better position in order to to kind
of lemon water yes so that's important
to you the lemon water
you know lemon water originally was all
about you know you put lemon in water to
make lemonade you make a tasty drink you
have lemon squeeze in water and and it
was hydrating that's the kind of
consensus that was years ago and then
what happened was spirit of compassion
new medical medium information they told
me at the lemon water when I was younger
flushed out the liver so it flushed out
the liver and it flushed out the toxins
and someone said to me recently said you
didn't start lemon water like oh no
people been putting lemon in the water
for centuries yeah I didn't start any
lemon water thing but what spirit didn't
do spirit of compassion didn't do was
teach people the lemon water for the
first time taught people had flushed out
the liver and flushed the liver out of
all those toxins that waited there to be
first thing in the morning because your
livers working all night long it's got
people you got people with all these
toxins building up all night long we got
a stagnant sluggish liver they're
getting the acid reflux they're getting
ammonia coming up from rotting peat
refined proteins and fats in their gut
and it's it's Glee Qing in their mouth
it's coming up they're burning out their
gums because of it
you see it every day every day and then
what happens is all those toxins build
up if you do that lemon water every
morning and you flush out the liver and
you flush out those toxins from the
liver you sweep that out and it's gonna
help you get there you know closer then
you bring in your celery juice which is
a big one too and I want to ask you guys
about mineral deficiencies like what do
you think about that like what do you
think about the whole mineral
deficiencies you know our teeth are made
of minerals we you know the whole bit
like like what you were saying basically
people could be on a specific diet 5 7
10 years and everything is great and
then they switch to diet that they now
believe was better and all of a sudden
they're like oh my teeth are falling
apart they have all these cavities I
have gum disease I have all this
happening to me
I gotta drop this new diet right away
because when I was doing the other diet
nothing was happening no it takes time
for the mineral silly child
it takes time for things to break down
teeth are such a complex tissue it
actually is said that it's the longest
to be made in utero when our moms are
pregnant with us did she take the
longest to form it takes a long time to
break them down so it's as empty I'm
saying it's a time capsule it will catch
up with you but later so don't see it
like in the moment what you're doing is
what's causing the problem it's what
you've done in the past yeah see people
people come into this world to begin
with mineral deficient okay because how
was mom eating how was dad eating right
and then they have emails yeah you know
I've always found that the metals and
I'm not just the the mercury fillings
those metals not just that the metals
that we come into this world with and
then we collect through certain ways you
guys can use your imagination
and you can get Nettles I talked about
it there's there's you know metals and
pharmaceuticals there's metals and other
places there's all kinds of stuff like
that but we can get metals and its
antibiotics have metals in them you know
I talk about that all the time so you
know when we have when we when we
receive all these we build all these
metals in her life I always find that
that breaks down the mouths immune
system and not even the metals being in
the mouth just through the body
lymphatic system our immune system
starts to break down from having high
amounts of metals in our liver and other
places in the body but when we have
these elevated metals it weakens teeth
and weakens teeths ability to stay
strong you know to keep the mineral
strong because metals basically cancel
out minerals in us minerals get affected
because water minerals there trace
metals but good ones minerals are trace
metals but good ones so you got all this
mercury you got all this aluminum you
got all these other toxic metals in us
and they react to our own trace minerals
we trace metals metals and and then
those trace those trace minerals are
actually part of our teeth and then and
then we get the mercury fillings when we
have you know and all that but we can go
in a little bit but the bottom line is
it's a time capsule to how a mineral
deficient you were when you were younger
exactly and your parents to when you
guys are pregnant you're making another
skeletal system a lot of minerals are
getting pulled to make that system so it
can kind of steal from your system so
something will suffer yeah your baby's
teeth or bones whatever more your bones
and teeth so eat some fruit when you're
pregnant yeah you know I don't see I
don't see dentist saying this out there
and it's really sad to me because
they're they're out of touch because
this is really powerful information you
know because it's it's not just about in
the moment because then just think right
in the moment what you're doing that's
what they always go after so if you go
to a dentist and you're plant-based and
you you're going there and they spot a
cavity oh you got to stop that plant
babe
right away you got to stop it right away
that's what they'll say and they'll be
like you you're obviously protein
deficient you're getting too much sugar
and but sugar isn't the cost that's the
whole thing and I want to I want to dive
into that a little bit so you're told at
the dentist office that sugar in general
like candy sugar like all that kind of
sugar is the problem with teeth problems
and then the other thing you're told is
citrus so I want to cover that a second
students of citrus so these are the two
things you'll get it that the D you'll
get at the dentist's office is yeah
you'll get the candy bad sugars fruit
sugar the lump it all together we don't
want to be on bad sugars you don't want
to be uncanny you guys we know that I
mean if you're dealing with a chronic
illness or anything you don't want to be
eating candy but fruit sugars an
entirely different thing you know that's
a whole nother a whole nother game it
creates glucose in the body it feeds
every cell but the bottom line is that
was a theory going all the way back then
sugar caused teeth problems because you
guys seen people eat sugar their whole
like bad sugar no problem no property I
mean we always tell our patients eat the
fruit sugar yeah the fruit is great for
you it's good for your teeth it's good
for your body you will not enroll your
teeth with sucking and lemons or oranges
is that there is no amount of water
ingest you can suck on to destroy your
teeth this just doesn't happen you know
there's fake truth out there and then
there's real truth out there that's how
the world works you know you mean
there's theories that create a fake
truth and then everybody runs around
with it and then you got real truth
right here and I paid dearly for
bringing real truth out you guys know
that I can't last you know kicked a lot
you you know the whole deal out there
but when you're bringing a real truth to
people so they actually stop feeding the
medical system so they start healing
that's powerful you know it's funny
real truth is real truth right here is
exactly that that we've seen I've seen
years and years of years and years you
have helped out over 250,000 individuals
like one on one over the last 35 years
look what many years ago and I've seen
people the
and E junk cakes sugar sugar cubes and
their teeth be fine
clearly you did sugar cubes oh I'll have
four more sugar cubes here and sucking
on sugar kids I've known people who
sucked on sugars that's a big yeah they
would pop the cubes and they did that
all day long teeth were perfectly fun
perfectly solid including like in every
way shape a but how come you won't
hear that from the dentist
how can you won't hear that like is it
because they just want to go with the
flow of what
you know whatever it's what they teach
us in dental school and then we see
ourselves what works and what is true so
it's like medical school you go to
America you come out you don't know why
somebody has fibromyalgia you don't know
why they have eczema psoriasis you don't
have any answers there's no answers
taught in medical school and all the
autoimmune conditions there's no answers
talked about lupus there's no answers on
anything you just kind of go to school
you learn the nuts and bolts you come
out they stamped out and then you have
to be you have to rise above with with
with something inside of you that's why
they are the best dentists there are
hands down that's why I'm like you know
you know out of line it just does
because it's so powerful the information
is powerful that you guys got well I
think as dentists and as physicians
after you get out of med school in
dental school you kind of have to decide
what's right for you um dental school
taught taught me the basics but once
you're in it and you start seeing that
you know sugar doesn't cause the
cavities and you kind of have to make up
your own mind that way
I think the dental community is starting
to come around I was just added
you're saying that just does not
cause which is that's something it was
if you had erosion on like the outside
parts of your teeth it happy were
sucking on lemons it was the orange it
was that but it not anymore so I mean
we're coming around and I know with your
help and just kind of getting the word
out there but it takes time you know
it's you have to change an old way of
thinking you know citrus is so high in
calcium so high in calcium it's
ridiculous because wherever citrus has
grown like if you got Florida citrus
that all that sand that it's grown out
of is calcium based okay so everybody's
worried about calcium calcium right
anywhere where citrus grows the the dirt
is high in calcium so citrus is your
teeth restore her this restore or work
your teeth restore okay it actually is
your that's how we can restore tea the
citrus it's sucking on oranges it's
sucking on lemons it's that kind of you
know and that's what I mean it's like
and that information I mean is powerful
because that will protect you so your
teeth aren't falling out down the road
you think have these problems now you
think do you think he got the root
canals now you think you got teeth
problems now gum issues and you're
afraid to you know have lemon water
you're afraid to suck on an orange it's
just gonna get you in trouble leader
because the other part of gum health and
deep health is vitamin C good vitamin
C's huge industry and huge what happens
what happens when okay what happens when
somebody comes in with an abscess and
they're like oh my god and they come in
through the abscess and it's like and in
the hole big vitamin C right it's like
you first of all you gotta be on a lot
of vitamin C yeah vitamin C is huge I
mean you can get it obviously in fruit
you can get it with supplements good
supplements with quality supplements but
vitamin C's one of these essentials
parts of dental health yeah remember
when I was 14 years old and I was
working on clients in the grocery store
I stocked shelves in right
you guys know the story I talked about
in the celery juice medical medium
celery juice book and I was juicing
celery in the back for clients walking
around the store with the carriages and
stuff and a number one one person one
individual had a you know whole thing
and they said it was puffed out to here
they had a bad abscess I said you gotta
have the vitamin C I said you got to
squeeze all these oranges all these
oranges and you got it you got to get an
orange juice orange juice squeezer
machine right I have something that time
and you can hand do it and everything
and it recommended lots of oranges every
day and the person said to me wait a
minute that's citrus it's gonna do
something to my gums and teeth and they
did the oranges they did this celery
juice and an abscess was going down when
no antibiotic touched it they were about
to literally go into surgery and avoid
they avoided their their surgery I mean
yeah and I'm not anti antibiotics when
we need them for certain things I'm
about making sure we are but we never
have to get there or we never have to
rely on them all the time we never have
to try to don't work but so those
accesses vitamin C is so important
that's why I like the very G vitamin C
it's a good quality product so it's it's
you know what the bottom line is is when
it comes down to the vitamin seeds
that's one thing you need you need the
minerals like in citrus you need the
calcium you got that you can I sort of
like you guys are like experts in
mercury removal mercury filling removal
like you guys pop those out we do have
them which is how I even got to know you
know because you're getting exposed
because I was getting exposed to so
mercury level was like off the charts
probably still is off the charts cuz we
remove them broken amalgam City move
every single day takes time to remove
mercury out of your body when you're
getting it in every day every day we
take them out every day and people who
come in with broken teeth corroded
amalgams defective restorations that are
just falling out yeah so I did the whole
medical medium detox for long
we're very long time incredible yeah I
had you know and that's that's
incredible for anybody who's dealing
with mercury issues she did that medical
meeting heavy-metal detox smoothie you
get it out you guys get it fresh in your
blood a lot a lot in and so by having it
every day you're capturing it there most
everybody who's not doing this they're
not getting it fresh in their blood all
the time they got it in their liver they
got it in their brain so you guys you
wanted you have medical medium heavy
metal detoxes you want to pull it out of
the brain you want to pull it out the
liver you want to get it out from those
deep places they're catching the mercury
as it's in the bloodstream right away
fresh and they're getting it from the
heavy Melanie detox movies gonna pull
that out and catch it fresh it's
powerful I want to ask you guys about
root canals you know there's all this
fear out there about root canals okay
there's a lot of fear every day we're
asked question with root canals people
now want to pull their teeth that have
been in canal in the past perfectly good
root canals that were done well with no
issues people are scared there's a lot
of misinformation out there that it
causes cancer that it causes all kinds
of chronic illness get those teeth
removed we don't believe in that I don't
think it's necessary I mean I don't know
how you feel about that you know what
what happens is this is that your I
always I always see it this way if you
don't get a root canal what's your other
option an implant or bridge which
sometimes you end up with implant do you
get the bolts for the bridge yeah you
know I forget they're calling the stems
or so yeah yeah like for the bridge and
then you need you need also the brackets
not the brackets but you know what if
the bridge yeah I mean you need the
framework I mean I agree and we talk
about this all the time people always
ask us they come in should we get my
root canals out what should I do
I mean sometimes you need to take them
out and get affected yeah they're some
reasons but I mean most of the time you
say you know you want to keep your tooth
because your other option is an implant
sometime
the plan won't work you know and not
having a tooth can be detrimental to
your oral health to your health all
around it help it affects occlusion and
mastication muscle tone so we both agree
you know we're bound to keep them if you
can if you guys come and see the dentist
and find a dentist who you trust and
we're not your enemy
but good people really here to help come
in find the dentist who you connect with
who you trust and that you won't get to
the root canal you won't need it because
you cavity won't grow you'll be taken
care of yeah you'll get it before the
cavity gets down - exactly yeah down to
the pulp of the root there and you know
the thing is with the root canals is
what I find all these years all the
people have helped is mystery jaw pain
can lead to a couple of things it can
lead to a root canal that shouldn't have
been done correct right it can also lead
to blaming a root canal that was done
yeah exactly
they remove the tooth you still have the
jaw pain you know you dig it out clean
it still happens you know you redo it
you still have the jaw pain so this is
something that I've run into all these
years because I've gotten to my source
I've been fortunate to have the source
that I listen to and if many of you
people don't know what that is you can
research me and so forth and whatnot
maybe I'll do a YouTube all about that
someday but the bottom line is is that
when you're there so many people have
suffered with something that later on
gets diagnosed as trigeminal neuralgia
yes any might not even be diagnosed as
that you know they'll have the pain
that's I've seen people with perfectly
good teeth you guys perfectly good teeth
right just have pain and they go to the
dentist and they're drilling good teeth
and doing root canals I'm good in and so
you need a good dentist to kind of catch
wait a minute is there a real problem
with this tooth or do we have something
going on and I just you want to go to
different dentists if you can't get to
them I understand wherever you might be
and but you want you want to go to
different dentists and get different
opinions because you might catch a
dentist that's like look I don't want to
I don't want to break into these teeth
because this jaw pain could be
mysterious stuff going on that's still
going to be there after the fact yeah
absolutely there's so much virus yeah
it's yeah the whole thing with
trigeminal neuralgia it's the shingles
virus I've talked about that it's
medical medium information I put that
out there a long long time ago still
putting it out there that there's over
30 varieties of shingles so you can't
get confused by shingles meaning in the
sense where if you get a rash or not
because there's non-rational
viruses you can get a rash you can get
the shingles and then it still become
trigeminal neuralgia eventually but
either way there's non ration for
machine goals so you got a unit you got
to know that this is behind it even if
you didn't have the rash that's the
trigeminal neuralgia can go and shave
iris can affect all the facial nerves
they can give you Bell's palsy it cannot
beat him up I think he could just give
you neuralgia it could give you burning
burning gums did you ever hear about the
burning dog man I heard
years and years and years of helping
people yeah and they go to 20 doctors
they go to a whole bunch of it then he
finally found me and and then I would be
like that that's the shingles virus and
you need an antiviral protocol and I
talked about that in the medical medium
books I mean I talked about that in the
first book right here I talk all about
the shingles in the first book the metal
being a first book yeah and so course I
got to pull a medical medium book out
there you know everything is there
sometimes you have to be you're not okay
have to just put it's a knife in there
it's in there I mean the liver recipe
book I will say I started with that one
there's a lot of information in there it
will completely change your outlook and
everything that was my first kind of
eye-opener but this book is great too
well I think spirit passion because
that's that's the medical information
it's it's untampered with it's untouched
by by the industry that pays for things
they get done so misinformation gets out
there both alternative and conventional
it's free from that it's it's for the
people to heal it's the truth that gets
something heal you know it's it's the
thing is with the trigeminal neuralgia
the hard part about that is is that the
agony people feel with that whole
syndrome and so you want a good dentist
so things don't get worse and going to
the into the wrong direction yeah you
know what's your general neurology it's
tricky to diagnose you have those you
have to know what you're looking for is
that you know people jump to conclusions
it's teeth and gums know it could be
something else let's wait a minute let's
not start working on the teeth just yet
we're not sure why it's happening let's
think about it yeah there's antiviral
protocols you can do for trigeminal
neuralgia I talked about that you know I
actually have I have a new book coming
out I'm trying to finish up I'm working
on it's gonna have you know things like
that for different conditions so you
know what to do what to take so that is
on its way I mean I'm I'm doing
everything I can to get everybody to
help I can in any way possible but it's
like so the whole thing with with I want
to cover a little bit more with root
canals I think so the bottom line with a
root canal is every not almost every
dentist will will blame bacteria
somewhere hidden down in a root canal do
you hear that sometimes we do we do hear
a lot yes a lot of information about you
know saying that fast root canal that
have been already done harbor bacteria
inside that's causing all these chronic
illnesses
all right now I want to cut into this
yeah this is really a good point okay
first of all I want to tell everybody
your chronic illnesses are not caused by
a little bit of bacteria buried deep
down in a root canal it's not possible
first of all that's bacteria that
actually sits down there if anything and
that can't create neurotoxins for
fibromyalgia chronic fatigue syndrome it
can't create all these different issues
they can't create multiple sclerosis
Rufus eczema psoriasis rheumatoid
arthritis it can't create you know any
chronic fatigue syndrome and can't
create tangles numbness aches and pains
all these different things throughout
the body all you know tics spasms
anxiety depression if you want when the
root canal is blamed on depression
it's what I've seen this is called this
is throwing darts at a barn door I think
that's that or it's just a crapshoot or
a guessing game musical chairs whatever
you want to call it that's what it ends
up being and people get really in
trouble from that whole philosophy or
theory that got around somehow in
dentistry that's really pissed me off
because I've seen so many people hurt
because of it when there are real
answers to why you have while you're
diagnosed with an autoimmune condition
there's really interesting why you have
problems and it's not because of a
little bit of bacteria that supposedly
could be at the bottom of your root
canal so we got to rip all your root
canals out people to get rid of your
enemy chronic fatigue syndrome and your
lupus and your Hashimoto's thyroiditis
and that's your thyroid problem and your
thyroid problem is because of your root
canals grave mistake your Lyme disease
now is because your root canals grave
mistake I'm telling you right now if
you're running into that out there I'm
so sorry you are this is a massive
mistake in dentistry I know so these
these to know this I mean right is that
this is just you not me and if I'm off
you know this is huge I'm still happy
just said that because we people call
and come in with exactly that let me
move my teeth that have been root canals
in the past because it's causing my ABC
and D no it's not yeah and so so this is
important information
I mean you share this YouTube share it
out there send it to people you know
that
problem said that you know they go to
their dentist and they have all these
questions just that I would pass this
one around because it's that powerful
and it's rare they flew out here okay
this is really rare they flew out here
okay from the East Coast
and they're out here on the west coast
right now okay and they flew out here to
do this they took time on their schedule
their schedules so busy they're working
on a zillion people and then and they
shut it down there's no practice to get
out here to help you guys and remember
being on the phone with you guys and you
guys are like look we just want to help
people we do that's really we just want
to help people like you know and it's
compassion that that matters to me and
they have it and so just know what you
got right here yeah I'm just saying no
that this is a really really important
day an important time and and we're all
lucky I'm lucky that they're here right
now you guys are lucky because there's
so much information so let's go into I'm
are you going to some other stuff teeth
sensitivities okay so I want to go into
that whole thing teeth sensitivities
doesn't mean the tooth has a problem you
know that's what I've learned you know
from my information from my source and
it's more of gum it's more of nerve
sensitivities that's what it is and it's
not the food that causes a teeth
sensitivity you know that's another
thing too it's not lemon water that
causes teeth sensitivity it's not yeah
it's it's not foods that cause teeth
sensitive it's like sugar or something
else it's just it's it's sensitive
nerves you know we see that a lot as
well okay and it's it's important to
antiviral protocol we think everybody
should be on it okay that's just even if
you feel great and it takes time I mean
you have to give I mean if you're in
pain and sometimes we can't really
there's nothing wrong with your teeth
it's you know something viral it takes
time to for it to build up I mean it
took time to get the pain so you have to
be patient we do use the viral load do
the medical medium interim protocol
there's so much you can do so so
basically a lot of problems we get in
dentistry
a lot of problems would get with people
going to dentists because they're sick
is because they got low-grade viruses
more high-grade viruses they got the ups
to one of the epstein-barr virus as I
talked about one of the over 60
varieties that's out there mutations and
strains they got that they got one of
the over 30 varieties of shingles virus
out there and if you guys think you
don't have bugs in yet I hate to break
it to you everybody's got bugs in them I
don't care if you're 20 years old if
you're 18 years old if you're 25 years
old if you're 35 years old if you got
bugs in you and you'll get symptoms down
the road I've always tried to be the
person to get that information out there
and since because I want people to know
now so you can stop it later and get
better and protect yourself so you don't
get something too so but the whole thing
is is what Masha is saying
magine are saying is antiviral protocols
you want to be on antiviral protocols to
protect yourself so that you don't get
sick because what's behind everything
the teeth sensitivities the nerve pain
all of this other conditions we're
talking about what's behind it is viral
loads viruses than the hhv-6 deciding
Begler virus in the HH v 7h h v 10 11 12
13 working undiscovered all these
viruses undiscovered many of them many
other mutations because i always talk
about in virology it's under funded
because virology holds the answers to
get people healthy so that no one seam
spends money in the medical system
anymore so that's why viruses are just
you know it's all it's instead it's
talked about out microbiome now or oh
it's Candida or oh it's something else
and around where you go every decade to
the young people that come up into
health right let's treat each them about
food combining again so we go nowhere
let's teach them about microbiome again
and even though they did it over and
over again for decades and everybody
still stays sick and they don't know it
let's teach the young people about
Candida again let's teach them about
this and what happens is this whole
circle is on purpose and then all the
practitioners they just become
innocently used for this whole thing and
then everybody each generation has the
same old crap information and it's
regurgitating it's recycled and no one
gets better and we
right that that's the whole point you
know we need to break that and so it's
about having a viral load it's about
knowing that it's knowing why you're
tired now it's knowing why you got
floaters in the eyes and you're getting
tingles or some numbness you're getting
an unfit its the low-grade viral stuff
it's so important for you guys to
understand if you're first you know
locking on to this so let's cover some
more dental stuff too why not
we give those questions everything else
yeah yeah yeah ran over not to remove it
I'd love to talk about that you guys are
open to we yeah absolutely we caught a
lot of how patients come in to us and
they've had these mercury fillings
placed 15 20 25 30 35 years ago that
length of time in the mouth which is
acidic environment heavy bacterial
environment they will corrode they will
break down over about ten year period so
we see a lot of these fillings corroding
pulling away from the tooth leaking
saliva underneath and decaying the teeth
underneath so if you have a defective
filling honestly you have to have it
removed if you have a fillings that's
fully intact we won't touch it we'll
leave it especially the person who has
symptoms and is chronically ill of
something again we don't want to push
him over I'll never forget 1991 1991
I'll never forget this okay I think was
my first I think was my first person
that came to see me that had a whole
mouth of mercury at one time right
nothing was wrong with them they meaning
they were they were there they weren't
corroding okay
they were pretty fresh right you know
whole mouth of it and they got told this
is right at the beginning you know you
know about the early 90s was right when
you get get him drilled out Mercury's
fillings are behind all of your sickness
right and this is poor woman ice why I
just I feel bad till today today so she
went to you knows before she came to me
to see me she before she came to my
office she had them all taken out they
were all drilled out everywhere
of them at the same time something I say
you've never been the same yeah I
remember you never you never made all
your hurt my feelings drilled out at the
same time you guys have been saying this
for years I said it long before anybody
knew it and so um she had a ball drilled
out right and then she had I guess I
guess at that time in 91 she had the
replacement that wasn't mercury and in
the early 90s it was a different kind of
strike composite the composite right so
the composites done but she was sicker
than ever she was sick to begin with she
had a ball drilled out because she had
the chronic fatigue syndrome which is
epstein-barr virus but nobody knew that
then they still don't know that now
unless I keep on bringing that
information out and all that mercury
vapor went into her system so all the
vapors for the mercury went into her
system from the drill Alex everything
like that it fed the virus or chronic
fatigue syndrome got worse because it
was so much mercury at once they didn't
even need to be drilled out at the time
there weren't any breaking down there
were none corroding but get this
so she's sicker now she's got the
composites in then another dentist at
the time said we need to drill out all
your composites you're sick because you
need mercury fillings put back through
they drilled all our composites out poor
woman god bless her I swear to god she
went through hell and back they drilled
every one out they refilled them with
all Mercury's like 1991 refill refilled
them all with mercury again I mean it
was an unbelievable process I had to
help her clean up the viruses because it
was her only chance at that point to
make sure we don't really get messed up
yeah and I was just like just antiviral
anti-federal celery juice yeah I was
recommending salaries you said early
absolutely I mean it came from it came
from spirit that's just celery juice
celery juice have you metal detox all of
it we pulled out as much mercury as we
can that was floating around and then we
went for the antiviral stuff we attacked
the virus all the different herbs I
talked about like lemon balm you guys
know about so that the chronic fatigue
syndrome that virus right there behind
it the epstein-barr was knocked down so
it wasn't gonna feed off of anymore
mercury but she went through
so you guys are not into like drilling
everything at once all of it breaking up
and if the patient is healthy has no
symptoms is completely nothing is going
on we can do maybe to two or three at a
time because your stuff it's something
you kind of play it by ear you see how
you're feeling and even afterwards you
know sometimes you have to push up
putting taking out more for a month or
so cilantro in the wild blueberries and
have all of that
yeah that's why that's why a good
dentist matters because it's like you
got a it you're gonna be up against
situations as a dentist that are you
know the the cavities were in a certain
spot you got teeth close together you
got all these things you guys got a call
that's when you call the shots where you
use like your intuitive abilities you
use your experience you use everything
you got and that's when a good dentist
really counts like you guys where you
guys are like you really know how to
work around that because you're trying
to you're trying to not create a
landmine you're trying to fix landmines
you guys are dying out fires and so it's
Pat it's powerful work you're doing I
mean you know I'm blown away to have you
here you know the whole thing so so is
with the mercury fillings and everything
so I've always said look you get one out
at a time
the most two out of time depending
whatever the situation shore but I've
always said that that's the best to do
if they're fine and nothing's wrong with
them work on getting mercury out of you
everywhere else in the body
you're the heavy metal detox throughout
the body you leave that alone for now
you know and depending on what symptoms
a person's dealing with are they dealing
with any viral symptoms you guys want to
know what viral symptoms are tingles
numbness aches and pains spasms twitches
floaters of the eyes numbness I said
tang and the tingles ringing in the ears
popping in the ears black spots in the
eyes that are because of the retina
you're detaching fibromyalgia that's
viable right there 100% chronic fatigue
syndrome fatigue that's
mysterious that's my role these are just
some of them neuropathy viral plantar
fasciitis viral Morton's neuroma viral
PCOS viral endometriosis PCOS so these
are see if you guys want to know what
viral are anxiety
got a viral load and some metals that
right there you know depression okay so
you're that's you know and then if you
guys want labels for things like our AMS
lupus Lyme disease viral I talked about
if you guys are new to knowing the truth
about Lyme disease because you might not
Lyme disease was snuck recently because
of medical meeting information powerful
of millions of the books millions of
medical media books going globally it
freaked out the industry so the lime
industry changed their game because of
medical media so just so you know
literally and their game new business
what they did because I brought it to
the world with more the millions of
books getting out there and everything
because people were healing and I didn't
get the books all these books didn't get
out there because I had help it was
because people were healing and they
spread the word it's know the difference
you know I didn't have money behind
these books like all the money that's
behind all the other you know authors
and stuff this is about people healing
is why these books got around and what
happened is it the woods of truth I
wrote about the truth about Lyme disease
and the industry decided to take Lyme
disease now and take it out of the whole
bacteria theory and stick it in the
autoimmune theory group so it's now
listed as an autoimmune disease which
means it's mysterious so they don't know
what causes Lyme anymore they actually
thought it was bacteria now they don't
know how to do it because of me and so
which is it which is which I'm actually
proud of I'm really right absolutely
because it's gonna heal that many more
people but the bottom line is is Lyme
disease right there that's a viral load
right there eczema psoriasis that's a
viral load so why is the viral load so
important it has everything to do with
teeth everything to do with teeth
problems too because when you got high
viruses you lose your immune system you
lose your minerals you lose all these
things you get your liver gets stagnant
sluggish you get low bile your acid
reflux happens low hydrochloric acid and
you're burning out your tea
you get problems and you think it's
because you're plant-based and then
whatever and I always say look you know
I'm Pro plant-based provegan ISM I mean
if that's term they even use anymore
veganism vegan and pro all that I'm Pro
also animal protein people that eat
animal protein good animal protein I'm
Pro all of it but I've always said you
know I've always said no matter what you
know that in dentistry the dental chairs
are not filled of vegans across the
globe because there's only this many
vegans there's only this many because I
know there's vegan youtubers out there
that that are out there and they're you
know they're into the propaganda of
veganism they don't like the animal
protein people and I know there's
youtubers out there that are vegan I get
it you guys got it seems like big
followings but just so you know there's
this many vegans it's this tiny it's a
grain of rice compared to a silo of rice
that's how many vegans are the rest are
animal protein people and guess what the
dental chairs are filled with they're
filled with animal protein people but
for some reason it's never blamed on
their diet you g1t from it's never
blamed on a diet but it's blamed on the
vegans diet so if you're vegan stay
strong and stay vegan your animal
protein hey Sam protein I'm just saying
that's what happens and I want it I want
people and I want people to know who are
vegan and play a base that I got their
back 100% because I know what they
really go through I know what they
really go through because they get they
get tricked peer pressure in the ways
like never before even when it seems
like they're strong as an ox tur it
meaning I'm emotionally strong about
being vegan for three straight years the
minute they get that first symptom and
they their blood Sugar's off a little
bit and they go to a doctor or some of
them they're gone they're out of the
vegan thing they're gone and I feel bad
for people like that because I want you
back into what where you were because it
wasn't your problem
it wasn't your your problem was viruses
your problem was that kind of stuff
strep bacteria that people get acne from
your problems were these other problems
your liver being congested and tired of
the fact that you weren't as a
plant-based person or a vegan person you
weren't drinking celery juice or lots of
it and don't fall for those people on
YouTube that say I drank celery juice
for five
it didn't help me you guys know you
changes but it takes time you have to
give it time and I try and tell people
at all the time you don't see results
right away but I mean even small changes
I've seen changes and my husband myself
my girlfriends who doing so I'm just
stay strong and trying to keep course
and you'll you'll see changes 100
percent yeah you know the thing is the
thing is with the dental work is when
someone's sick with chronic illness and
you guys know there's so many of you
sick with Roenick illness right you're
visiting already your internist or visit
visiting already your doctor you're near
your GP you're visiting your specialist
you're visiting your neurologist you're
visiting your endocrinologist right and
then on top of that you gotta go see
your day you're getting dental work
you're doing that - well when you learn
about how to give your health in all
these other ways you can see the dentist
last see the doctors less and that's
what it's about I mean that's what we
want people to do and want you guys not
to have your whole life based around
doctor's appointments in right
unless it's checkups at your dentist
lots of checkups or cleanings right or
clean as good I just always want there's
a question that always pops up that I
hear all the time like or too many
cleanings good how many like cleanings
do you get a year you know like that's a
question I always them always asks again
find the dentist who you can trust and
we will we assess our patients and we
propose the timeline for cleanings some
people come twice a year
some people come three times a year and
other people need to come four times a
year if you have heavy load of bacteria
and viruses and your gut health is not
great we see your teeth and gums
deteriorating so we need to monitor it
when we see that everything has improved
you don't have to come in as often yeah
you can come in twice a year I mean yeah
the main thing is just to come in is
amazing it feels changing in
we do want to help I mean that's why we
became dentists so you have to in our
office or I'm sure it's kind of you know
you want that trust with our patients
we'll find somebody that you trust and
go see them because it's not that scary
you know like I have people throwing
this at me all the time they're like hey
aw I don't have any I don't have any
toxic heavy metals in me
there's no toxic heavy metals I mean
that you know what I say is say did you
have a fluoride treatment did you ever
yeah I had a fluoride treatment at tons
of them or no I don't get fluoride
treatments but did you have ten of them
when you were a kid and you're like
right and you're like yeah yeah we
shouldn't use to give everybody drops
yeah exactly right
fluoride byproduct of our aluminum right
the severe neurotoxin but it's aluminum
just because it's a byproduct doesn't
mean it's not aluminum aluminum takes
different forms that's how chemistry
works so you know fluoride is actually
aluminum it's just in a different form
and so when you're getting aluminum
treatments you have a lot of them a lot
of heavy metal in you so I've had people
say anything I don't have Meyers isn't
me yeah you do you you do because this
is business this happened to you do you
know Anthony I don't have you know I
don't have heavy metals in me yeah you
do
how many fluoride treatments have you
had you know and that's just one aspect
of getting metal in you so what do you
guys do do you guys like do the
traditional fluoride for everybody there
or do no no no so you're basically
groundbreakers you're just you just yet
everybody everybody is trying to move
away from them everybody's heading there
I think so yeah everybody was
prescribing high fluoride toothpaste
they were doing floor treatments every
six months for months and the results
are there it's not really changing
anything so I think a lot of people are
stepping away from that which is huge in
the deaf community because before I was
the end you know when I fought fluoride
back in the early days see no one
realizes when they just get into health
now if you get into health now you're an
influencer in health because you're like
you're eating better and you want to
show your videos and you're in
Lewin sir and you got your first acne
and you want to like get it better by
getting off of gluten you don't know
with what would some of our open some of
us old dogs you guys are young but some
of us old dogs have gone through in the
old days
like for instance I went up against the
fluoride thing back when and I was
almost crucified for it I fought for
where we are today in fact what I've
done helped us get to where you are and
I don't think a lot of people realize
this or appreciate it and I understand
why I totally get it but the whole thing
man I remember being screamed at
screamed at but people come in to see me
their dentists calling me saying how
dare you question fluoride I mean you
don't know what we went through is
unbelievable I mean it was like every
day was you help and save lives but you
get your ass kicked along the way every
day all day long because you're up
against old grandfathered laws that are
evil and dark and that's the whole thing
they're evil and dark because science
and research thought they were on top of
their game now but they weren't science
research thinks they're on top of their
game now but they're not because even
though fluoride isn't so used so much
science research believes your body's
attacking itself your autoimmune is
caused by your body which isn't true
they believe your genes is all your
problem but that's not true your
problems or viruses and heavy metals and
that's just two things there's other
problems too but but basically the floor
I think what oh my god the stuff I heard
when when I would get when I would try
to protect people or I would tell a mom
just yeah if your child's got the worst
case of Epstein Barr this is really bad
things are bad or your child has a
really bad case of strep you can't do
fluoride right now you do a floor they
do a fluoride treatment and then
everything goes down you know downhill
doctors are leavin everything's
happening you just the thing is that the
fluoride the fluoride business it was
such an industry of just bankroll and
there's so many still left you can't
think we're safe because we're figuring
things out now like that there's so many
other landmines and potholes and traps
that are grandfathered in that we're up
against today floor I don't in fluoride
still you know they're still using
you're still using it they're still
using mercury goings they're still using
so using mercury cooling so yeah so the
war is still on but it's nothing like it
was but and then and then there's you
know that was the whole floor I thing I
find that when you use neurotoxins like
fluoride and your viral you just go
downhill quick so just don't ever do
them fluoride treatments and don't get
tricked into the natural fluoride
concept because that's still not even
the answer that's based off the old
fluoride concept so what about that
natural natural fluoride it's not that
it's not the aluminum based ones it's
like the more natural concept of
fluoride the you know of the lake on
that level and they they talk about they
put it in natural toothpastes I think
now they do other stuff so it's not the
real toxic you know high neuro
antagonistic level of aluminum so I mean
I'm hearing some dentist was telling me
about natural fluoride and he was saying
how natural fluoride is it's safer it's
it's got you know I wouldn't just buy
into it no good it's because people are
so there so that's what they teach you
when you get out fluoride for it you
know the president before our treatments
that's what they tell you and you know
it's kind of drilled in so it's hard to
let go those old concepts but yeah it's
really not doing anything for you so so
what about gum disease
ok so some of the people out that out
there and they're gonna watch this they
deal with gum disease in different ways
and you know they get told if they're
developing gum disease like what's your
recommendations when you're dealing with
gum disease - like how to keep your gums
clean how to stop them from progressing
is avoiding certain foods helpful I
think gum disease is definitely related
to God health we do see it all the time
I mean gum recession just deteriorating
gums deteriorating bone that's correlate
to your gut health if you're eating a
lot of processed food
a lot of other foods that are not great
for you we do see it and then you how
doses comes back and all of that is
intertwined if you lower the pH lower
the acid from eating a lot of processed
people drink six cups of coffee in the
Shu drinking coffee
I noticed a younger crowd still drinking
coffee they walk around with different
coffee coffee drinks all the time and
they try to try to use it as their
intermittent fasting weapon so what they
do is they drink coffee all day so they
don't eat all day so then they eat once
and once once you know once a day so to
try to pull the intermittent fasting
game using coffee all the time and
they're running around but are they
causing problems for the future future
because you're so acidic everything is
breaking down in your mouth and it'll
you know maybe not today they won't see
it but in a couple of years they'll see
it when they eating great food and they
like my great food that's causing my
countries it was the coffee which
drinking for two years in the wrong yeah
I believe in hundred percent what about
this is a tricky one what about
chocolate though you know I always tell
people that's a tough one it I know it's
yummy I know it's good I know people
like chocolate I mean I'm not anti
chocolate entirely I just know though
for adrenals for you know spiking the
adrenals it's really intense you got the
caffeine right and so that's really hard
but what happens is that I always find
is adrenaline can also cost teeth damage
and that's one thing I don't even know
if I talked about it recently on a show
or anything but adrenaline causes teeth
damage the reason why I say that is
because maybe then you see that people
who are stressed out whether they have a
loss in their life or just stressed
around work or whatever it's happening
stress people manifest prompts with
teeth and gums for sure and we always
say listen you under stress yes somebody
just passed away I'm so upset I'm
grieving and we see it we see it every
day stress will break down temporarily a
lot of times it's it comes it's in waves
and then they'll come down eventually
thank you thing is because it's rental
in is gross
it's the probably one of the most
corrosive substances and so you know I
talk about medical medium book 1 this is
so cool that I got the books right here
I just love this I love this YouTube
live thing I mean I love it it's really
cool and I don't know and so in this
book I talk about the 56 different
blends of adrenaline and what does that
mean science research has no idea about
this but adrenaline just isn't it isn't
your cortisol and epinephrine it's not
it's not that it's worse it's when you
have a loss or you been through hell and
back or you something's going on or
financial problems something is really
pushing you or you've been betrayed
backstabbed maybe a best friend betrayed
you because betrayal is is is really
brutal it's so brutal and hard I'm sorry
if you guys anybody ever experienced
that I just want to tell you that I'm
sorry and I understand because betrayal
is really rough I mean everybody
experiences at one point sometimes some
people experience it worse than others
is brutal trust when we get her trust
broken when that happens and something
that someone just breaks us back and
breaks our back of trust you know and
we're just like we're just we're spirit
gets down and we get hit you know you
you have a losses and everything else
and what happens is when you're going
through that there's a different blend
of adrenaline to these things and and so
adrenaline sports you got to be careful
you're going for you know more highs
with adrenaline sports I mean I love
sports is the greatest thing ever but if
it becomes this thing where you're
obsessed and it becomes an adrenalin
based you know direction you had to it
aren't you you shorten your duration
about you'll get other problems because
adrenaline is so aggressive it's so
abrasive that it works the bones it
works on our bones it'll get you the
osteopenia I mean especially if you have
toxic heavy metals and high adrenaline
you get the osteopenia you get different
problems get the osteoporosis adrenaline
is one of those acid dissolved basically
it's a dissolvent
and a solvent in a way to because it can
run through bones and so and and teeth
teeth are credibly that are susceptible
to this so when there's a so so we can't
we can't protect yourselves from every
loss and from every betrayal and from
every trust breakage and from all the
how we go through whether you're young
or older and we can't you know we can't
protect yourselves from every bit of
those things and really
in ships and everything I mean I've seen
I've had stories of you know a newly
weds getting married they're
20-something years old and the 31 years
old or something in that realm and they
get married and then the girl comes down
with Hashimoto's thyroiditis and the
boys like I didn't buy into this I don't
know what this is and it scares that you
this used to happen and over the decades
I've watched this for years and I'll
suddenly break up and then it's like
it's like it's it's a it's what happens
is it hurts so much you can't avoid all
these different things and I get this
happens but I gotta tell you that when
you take care of yourself you can defend
yourself from that adrenaline you can
defend yourself from that stress so that
your adrenaline doesn't start taking
down your teeth over time I've seen
people go through a really trying time
and a hard time and then the teeth
become time capsules to what happened
four years ago the adrenaline really was
high then whipping them whipping you
really hurting them and then four years
later they're thinking it's everything
else they're doing right but their teeth
are falling when it was four years ago
from a breakup they had a relationship
or some kind of problem they had four or
five six seven years ago
and that's how it works and I don't you
know and so this information is so
powerful to help you guys and they're
they're aware of it so basically there
are things you can do like the celery
juice to help protect you against your
ear and hear the adrenaline from
hardship and the wild blueberries and a
lot of the medical medium information
the different foods I talked about and
and here's the last thing I want to talk
about the no foods what foods to stay
away from you guys are food experts you
guys are doctors you guys know how the
world works you guys all you know what
what foods like are you thinking about
on your end I mean well we personally
implemented no eggs that was a personal
choice everybody comes to it on their
own time but we we've seen differences
subtle differences bigger differences of
deployments that have in my family with
my kids my husband definitely celery
juice and the detox heavy-metal smoothie
is amazing it's really great I think if
you stick with it for at least 30 days
which
so easy you will see the difference I
know that's incredible because um I mean
because you guys have witnessed it
yourself that's the whole point we have
and we you know we walk the walk we do
it every morning I'd better start
walking I'd better and this is the
better uh please when I first started
doing your protocols I was all about low
carb no fruit egg whites every morning
cuz that was what my trainer was having
me go I mean that's what you need and it
took time I've been doing celery juice
now with my husband every morning for
two years
did I see results right away no but it's
it's just changed our life my husband
used to suffer from eczema he doesn't
have that anymore I used to have just
like bloating issues everything is gone
it helps with like whenever you're
anxious about something it just kind of
calms you down
it's little subtle changes and but start
small start with the celery juice and
get rid of eggs to eat the eggs will
feed the viruses that's why you know the
dairy products that feed the buyers is
okay the gluten will feed the viruses
nobody knew gluten fed anything until
medical medium information came to town
they just thought gluten created in
fluent inflammation somehow but that's
not how it works the gluten has to feed
above the bug has to produce a poison
then you get inflammation and that's
information that only came from medical
medium originally and I hear doctors
talking about it now because that's how
many books got out there but the point
is is that the no foods is critical for
dental issues for dental problems for
keeping yourself healthy for making sure
you don't fall apart down the road no
foods is critical so whatever if you
believe in some animal proteins you know
eat them if you believe in being
plant-based you to go that route or
anything in between but just remember
keep away your eggs your dairy products
keep away of course your gluten duh but
you know I say Doug because you know
somebody we like oh well he you know
somebody else knew that pride before him
let me tell you I was telling people to
get off gluten when I was four or five
years old four five six years old and
I'm an old dude and that was a long time
ago I'm just letting you know and so a
lot of concepts
there now that have been out there
because you know I spread them out I
mean I've delivered that information a
long time ago and now they're out there
and people are trying to teach it back
to me
we're just hilarious and I love that
it's good news it's so glad I'm so glad
it got out there but the bottom line is
that no foods is important so keep that
in mind so you can stay healthy not feed
your pathogens not feed your viral viral
load not not cause any problems but uh
this was incredible you guys I'm blown
away I'm honored and anyway you can find
these guys you know their name okay it
says dr. Monica Cogan
yes dr. Gina Romano okay they have a
practice in Connecticut we're in
California right now they flew out here
but they're worth the flight without a
doubt if you guys need work in my
opinion but I get it if it's you know
hard to get to your office it's already
get to your office but fine so I find
somebody out there yeah their dentistry
is amazing don't be scared just find
your person you'll be great
make your dentist watch this though
watch this because we got to the best
dentists there are out there here so I
love you guys
all right so I guess we'll uh we'll call
it well I appreciate everything
appreciate you guys here and thanks for
being here it's just really an awesome
time and I say a legendary day and in
health so awesome alright then thank
good gonna come over to the Machine and
we're going here