hello Scott Bakula here I'm with my wife
Chelsea field
we're here with and we're back with
Anthony William number one New York
Times bestselling author creator of the
worldwide phenomenon sell reduced
movement he's been working with doctors
for decades to troubleshoot chronic
illnesses and troubleshoot difficult
cases we're grateful to have another
opportunity to kind of double back after
we were here against two weeks ago yeah
two weeks ago and there are lots of
questions that you all wrote in and
asked about and and we're back we're
like a bad penny we just turned up again
can we please come back on YouTube and
talk to everybody so here we are and
it's good to see everybody and thanks
for all the great responses that we got
last time and we got a lot we're going
to try and answer some questions but you
all wrote in and talked about and
without me talking any more let's get to
Anthony this is incredible I can't
believe what happened back right now you
guys I'm sitting we've been laughing for
the last few minutes have you started
we're latest but it's my fault
I had to get my hair right I think it's
live that's why I Drive and it's just
it's just raw and this is the way it is
Scott Bakula Chelsea field you guys know
who they are the whole world does
obviously and so yeah so we're here
together we're gonna talk about powerful
healing information just information all
around I mean this is gonna be a really
good thing too they wanted to come back
they wanted to support us they want to
support you guys and what you're doing
yes because you're going through the
stuff with the struggles and the health
issues and the complications and the
doctor visits all the time and you're
doing all that and you know it takes
them it really takes the toll on people
when you're running around in your whole
life is about visiting doctors or
visiting nutritionists doctors
dieticians and then you think this and
this and then you're on the internet and
you're looking for something else and so
you guys are here because hey we're
trying to make sure you have the answers
that you know that this is powerful
information that works and that's what
it's about I mean it's about the mission
of getting medical medium information
out there and I can't believe I got you
here again yeah you know there is
something that
that we were talking about before which
is if I'm not mentioning something if
I'm not talking about a product like
Moringa powder collagen or something
else if I'm not behind something I'm not
behind beets you know what I mean don't
you louder exactly if I'm not behind
something like that meringue that's not
go G berries if I'm not behind something
that means you don't need to have it in
your regimen because it's not gonna make
or break your movement forward with like
a real problem with like real sickness
real health issues the whole bit I mean
you hear about it all the time right
people always like what about this right
absolutely so let's let's take beets for
example yeah so a lot of people ask me
about beets and I had just on my own
notice through all of the books that
that I had read in the healing foods
book he never says anything about bees
and one time I it might have been on
your podcast or an Instagram live or
something one time I heard him say beets
and you don't need to you know use beets
you don't need to like go out of your
way to have some beets and I remember
that lodging in my brain I'm thinking
okay well I don't know why but I'm just
not going to bother and I like beets but
there are so many other foods to be
eating that are healing foods that are
gonna help you process or pull out your
heavy-metal detox you know all your
heavy metals and so why not focus on
those so what is it with beets what's
your count of the beets man well beets
is like God what about their growing you
know what's your problem I know I know
you can eat them you could totally them
to find I mean you can do that they're
fine they're not gonna hurt you you know
there's no okay beets out there
obviously there's heirloom beets out
there but one of the things is that the
GMO beets have really cross pollinated
okay so like people were worried about
GMO well you get these crops were there
GMO beets now justice fields and fields
and fields of GMO B and so what happens
is pollination time boom cross pollinate
then the other beets and other fields
get affected so beets essentially are
not really GMO free it's but it's
impossible got to have a GMO for it it's
just impossible that's number one number
two is it's a filler it's a great way to
make money in supplement world for years
the whole beet thing mm-hmm it's a great
way to make money
it's a great way to be like yeah this is
gonna be good free than you put it in
supplements you'll see it in all these
different supplement blends where it's
like you know you got this in here this
in here this here you got a little bit
of this this this this like 50
ingredients and one of those powders you
know you got the powders and you'll see
beet powder in their spinach powder this
powder carrot powder and it goes all the
way down which really is just a little
speck of this in a speck of that and it
just rips people off and then you pay
like 100 bucks for a big protein powder
thing or fifty bucks for a protein
powder thing or whatever a juice powder
or whatever that might be and so beet
greens would be the same thing because
it's all the whole thing is GMO without
corn it's the same thing the beet green
is actually healthier for you okay then
the beet but it still got the GMO
tendency your possibility that's why I
always tell people you know you don't
really have to have beets and it was a
filler in the juice world back in the
old days you juice you juice your carrot
to juice your beets you make it nice and
sweet you put a little spinach in there
was always a filler it was always look
does it have healing benefits sure it's
a healthy root vegetable it is a healthy
root vegetable it's true what is it is
it a game-changer no does it clean the
liver like wild blueberries no that's
the whole point how do you get better if
you're getting information everywhere
else so then all of a sudden someone's
not doing their frozen wild blueberries
anymore and now the brain worried about
beets and beet powder and beat this and
eat that it's always a confusion now
they're bringing in their collagen now
they what about the Moringa powder doing
they're doing all the stuff and then
they lose track and then they get
another doctor telling them oh you got
your microbiome off another doctor
telling oh you've got Candida oh you got
this you got that and then what happens
is you're lost and five years go by and
then you still got your Hashimoto's
coming on and nobody realizes that you
still got your autoimmune diagnosis
coming you still got all these other
things because the Medical mean
information is about the truth about
what you really need and you have to
adhere to it and you have to keep to it
so you can really stay on track
absolutely and you find that people end
up saying what the the medical medium
stuff didn't work for me but if you're
combining it with five other people's
ideas or philosophies yeah that's not
fair really to any of the philosophies
you have to
you have to jump in well normally that
mixing yeah they're always mixing right
and that's a human nature because you
know a and P if people are in trouble
and they're sick they want yes they want
to get well right away and it's hard to
be patient and I understand people's
frustration if it's their skin or
whatever's going on and they want may
want results but that's where you have
to trust you have to look at some of the
posts on your Instagram and stuff of
people the changes and listen to their
stories and understand that there's
nobody writing that I did this in a day
later I was cured they commit to
something it takes time and patience and
you have to be have to be kind to
yourself and your process because it
just it's not like taking you know
medication it doesn't change overnight
it takes time and everybody's different
I see a lot of comments I looked at the
comments from our last live and also
whenever I'm watching Instagram or the
Facebook stuff and there's a lot of
comments in the community and that's one
of the things that I wanted to say was
there's so much information in a the
books be the podcasts to see the
Instagram live posts all everything at
all of the medical medium information
that is gettable there's so much
information there and in the community
because the qalaat of the community has
been through a lot and they know and
they'll put things on comments and
answer questions so that keep keep aware
of that and keep watching that but also
all of the all of the questions that I
saw from last time and in all of the
years I've been you know following what
Anthony and medical medium says they're
all in the books they truly are so I get
it some people aren't readers I would
suggest maybe getting the audiobook
because they aren't their audience so
you could get them on audio and listen
in the car if you're driving or you know
on the subway or whatever cuz really the
answers are in the book it's not as
direct as like Anthony what's the answer
to this like getting the opportunity to
speak to him directly but I didn't even
do that I'm his friend and I don't call
him with all the questions that I have
or one of my friends had it it's tough
cause yeah I don't want to bother him I
respect and honor his well you guys
stopped calling yeah you guys stopped
calling you're like let's leave him
alone he's no he's got too much going on
he's got he's got so much going on but
seriously the answers are all in the in
front of all the medical medium
information it is there you you have to
read and you have to listen and you have
to go through it and you have to put it
all together and it you'll find your
answers there's a lot of sand traps out
there set for the people there's a lot
of potholes there's a lot of sand traps
and they're set purposely they want to
keep your brain washed about protein
whether you're vegan or your or your
animal protein diet or keto diet
high-fat diet they want to keep you all
we still set on protein being law
somewhere in one of your diets it
doesn't matter because meanwhile
everybody has enough protein has been
getting enough protein has always got
enough protein but it doesn't stop
chronic illness and the keto diet I know
they talk about how it's just a high fat
diet high fat diet but anybody I've
talked to doing the keto diet they're
still worried about how much protein
they're eating they're still worried
about where they're getting their
protein because no matter what it's
always about protein so you got
everything you know protein warning
shakes protein this protein not what
happens is that's a sand trap setting
the stage so you never have answers to
what causes chronic illness and so say
you're in good you say you're in good
health right now and you're just focused
on protein sure but when you start
getting sick later then then you're
third you're still going to be focused
on protein meanwhile you've been getting
enough protein everybody yeah you can't
not get enough protein no matter what at
all times it's not it's not you know
it's always been like that and I'm going
to talk about fats a little bit too
because when you're doing high fats
where that gets you in trouble so here
there's so many traps you got the high
fat trap that just bogs down your liver
and pancreas sex your sets the stage for
sickness later on - even if it's healthy
high fat diets then you get the pie
protein where it's all about protein no
matter what you see so these traps
receptors yeah and the hydrating I mean
the animal protein has so much fat in it
now the problem with these include
exactly I mean it's fine if you I guess
we want to have animal protein but
you're automatically having fat when you
have the animal for exactly and if you
want to go claim pee so you guys are
plant-based but you don't innovate
yourselves with fats 24/7 and that's
what they're doing so you got two
plant-based people so many of you guys
are and you're bringing in the facts all
the time and so it's all about always
setting potholes there's reasons for
this that you don't
so you don't move forward there's a
reason for why that's happening the
industry's all of them including the
other alternative industries are set up
so you fail somewhere down the line one
way or another and that's the difference
between the macro medium information and
making sure people have a chance because
I want people to have a fighting chance
because sure when you don't have much
going on and you have a little bit of
acne and you got a few symptoms and your
digestive tracts a little off and you're
yelling you're young it's just who cares
right you just try this you're doing
this you're trying to do this but man
when you start it you're now in your 30s
now in your 40s you get diagnosed with
autoimmune or something else and then
you'll feel fine just sinking ship fast
between the high protein or the high fat
or the collagen you'll find that that
ship sinks it starts to sink and people
start learning whoa until they know what
it's like to go on the path of doctor to
doctor to doctor looking for answers
trying to find you all of it is when you
know it breaks my heart it breaks my
heart I've been watching this for so
long I have a specific question about
this so one of the questions was
heavy-metal detox smoothie which we do
every day or I do the liver rescue
smoothie and I have generally I always
do water but a lot of times I'll do cook
will do coconut water in the heavy metal
toxicity is that okay because I know
you're late I know coconut meat has fat
yeah but I keep googling coconut fresh
coconut coconut water coconut water is
is the sugar I mean that's the glucose
that's the yeah that's the you know the
minerals with the glucose coconut orders
and it's an amazing electrolyte there's
not but is it good but it's great you
can even find a trace of fat no there
would be a trace of back okay that's
that's nothing it's like it's like but
what people are doing you got to have
your two avocados you got to have your
nut butters you have to have your peanut
butter smoothie Bowl in the morning you
have to it's nothing but lots of fat yes
movement now and you know what it's
great when you're working out in a gym
for two hours a day it's great when
you're 24 years old but you take someone
who's 35 and they're not in the gym you
know two hours a day and they're you're
locking on to the high fat movement
whatever it is and they're but they're
getting sicker and they've got the
thyroid problems and they're too getting
diagnosed with
this and getting the eczema and
psoriasis are getting the rashes
everywhere and in all of a sudden it's a
sand trap right it's like constantly
there right so no matter what
alternative medicine you think it's
advanced it's actually not advanced
they're teaching people to do green
juices they're teaching people to do why
would you place the amazing taste of an
avocado in a smoothie I mean like save
that avocado like to put on your salad
or or you know in your baked potato you
know if you want to do that but don't
stick it in a smoothie especially I mean
if you're doing a heavy metal and it
look here's the thing you know you guys
like it it's okay to have a little bit
of fats whether you're animal protein
whether you're not whether you're vegan
plant-based it's okay to have a little
bit in there but right now we're being
taught by complete mistakes just like
we're always making guessing games and
mistakes all the time we're being taught
high fat high fat high fat you know it's
taking advantage ration and guess what
it just means heart palpitations it
means hot flashes later on it means
sluggish stagnant liver it needs all
these things and it means eczema eczema
can't go away on the high fat diet you
might improve it once you've gone off of
processed foods high fat so here you are
processed foods high fat you got to
winter of donuts cakes cookies whatever
I'm doing right and you move on to the
you move on to the better diet where
you're now you know at the clean keto or
a clean high-fat diet right yes you're
gonna get some improvements your skin
might show some improvements in the more
in the moment all of that but sure later
you're destined it's just getting here
it's just the whole point yeah the
system is set up no matter what because
by mistakes just total mistakes there's
reasons for that I mean there's a whole
bunch because then you get the art you
get the articles backing up those
mistakes you get the propaganda you get
the studies that are really not even
real and you get all of that and then
everybody hops on the internet they're
like oh this article here this study
here on this person said this and then
they try to validate what they want to
do and they're still doing it all wrong
right and look I'm only saying this
that's not like I'm it's not like I'm
sitting here selling something now I'm
gonna do an infomercial on hey so buying
this product right no no I'm not so
that's the whole point this is about you
guys
this isn't getting any kitchen so you
guys can heal and you don't all heated
up and passionate about this because
someone just told me the other day they
said how come you know how come I'm not
getting better and I'm doing I'm doing
your diet and I said what you are I said
what's the diet and they basically
explained the keto diet and I said
that's why you're not getting better how
long you been doing they're like well
I've been doing that for like three
months now and I'm like no wonder why
and they're like I thought it was your
information I'm like why would it be my
information so that's what's happened he
said there's so many different landmines
out there about what to do and I'm not
ripping apart the keto diet still better
than any standard American diet I'm not
ripping apart you know I Pro Paleo diet
I'm not ripping apart the best vegan
diet I'm not ripping apart that it's
just about you guys are spits and pieces
miss and that's what you guys see
writing this up absolutely I had a
family member just last week asked me
why is Anthony bah bah bah bah bah I
said well where did you get that he goes
oh I heard it from some people at the
office and I'm thinking okay well hey
that's not true and B you have to you
have to understand what he's about by
what listening to other people no you
have to read the book so you have to
watch his Instagram you have to you know
do the work unfortunately there is some
work on your part you know and and you
need to take responsibility for your
healing in that just talking to people
and just listening to what they say is
is not good enough read the books the
information there I probably want to
encourage you that if you do that that
the results are there their results good
results to be had but and and also at
the same time saying we recognize it
it's not easy and you know we've been at
it you know if even when you start to a
simple you know achievable it's like the
pikelet Kloster that's another thing but
you what what can a three point three
foot talks yeah what can I do today for
myself can I get up every day and say
can I do my 16 ounces of lemon juice
lemon water yeah with with two lemons in
it squeezed in it are can I commit to
making sixteen ounces at least of celery
juice every day and forget everything
else and that's all you can do that's
fantastic
yes so is it is there a specific amount
of lemons I mean I used to do two in 16
ounces now I do one I mean is there a
specific amount and also when how soon
should you hydrate when you get up in
the morning I mean I do it pretty much
right away yeah is is there because your
the body needs to hydrate as soon as you
get up and start cleansing right wait we
wake up dehydrated yes just we just
automatically every morning we wake up
dehydrated if you have anything
neurological going on it's really a cool
point right there this is so critical if
you have aches and pains that are kind
of unexplainable if you've got tangles
and numbness ringing in the ears
dizziness balance issues any vertigo in
the past if you have focus and
concentration issues if you have any
kind of insomnia if you have any kind of
sleeping issues all of it anything
neurological migraines headaches all of
this including things I haven't even
mentioned that that are neurological
tics spasms and so forth maybe I did
mention that but the bottom line is
anything like that maybe you've been
diagnosed with neurological Lyme maybe
you have a diagnosis that involves the
nervous system and you don't know it and
it's all based around central nervous so
the whole point is we wake up in the
morning dehydrated and our nervous
system is is desperate for like a lemon
water desperate for something like that
lecture lights and everything else and
it's so important we all night long your
liver is packing up the garbage is what
it's doing and if you had a really high
fat dinner at night then it's really
packaged working hard it's over labored
it's trying to cleanse but there's the
fats are in the bloodstream that's
really hard for the liver when we have
really high fat dinners so here we are
you know the whole high fat movement is
supposed to be so good for you but man
when you have a high fat dinner and okay
maybe someone's like well what does that
mean how fat dinner you know what I'm
saying if you're putting oil on
something and on your dinner if you're
if you're doing too many nut butters at
night if you're doing if you're doing
two avocados at night if you're doing
you know oil on on your food whether
it's vegan or some other different meal
or whatever eat whatever it is and maybe
you're doing CMM you're doing animal
proteins at 92 plus oil on your salad
you're just doing it's just too much fat
right there your bloodstream but yeah
but err exactly whatever it could be you
got and then and then all night long
your blood fat is really high you have
less oxygen to your brain less oxygen to
your organs any kind of illness can
actually move forward and getting worse
over time versus getting better because
the fats are too high it's not like you
had a half an avocado it's not like you
had you might have had nut butters that
day if your plant-based but that should
be about it if you had nut butters that
day maybe dinner time shouldn't be so
high in that and so it's it's in that
kind of you know on that kind of level
so all night long your liver struggling
it's indicated with fat it goes up the
paddock portal highway into the liver it
soaks into there so your livers battling
to take out the garbage to detoxify by
morning time you're extra hot
dehydrating because fats the hydrate us
so we're extra dehydrated and so by
morning time if you don't get that lemon
water you know that flush in the morning
not hydration and flush you can be it
compiles it then the new livers backed
up another day another week in your life
then another month in your life because
your liver can even though it's still
working it can back up weeks and weeks
and in years and then become diseased
like stagnant sluggish fatty liver
diabetes type 2 diabetes anything like
they get the hot flashes you get the
weight gain and the weight gain comes on
and all that because your liver is just
too stagnant and sluggish over time and
they work we can be dehydrated for
decades where's my lemon water well and
I'm sorry Kiwi I remember you saying and
the dehydration gets us off yeah yeah
okay so go ahead no I just saw her so
then the lemon water will take that
liver and give that liver flushes in our
yeah it helps it flush in the morning
that's the thing it flushes out
delivering nobody knew that nobody knew
that that's medical medium information I
mean people put squeezing lemon in water
for centuries okay centuries that's what
they've been doing they've been
squeezing lemon in water that's that's
been around long before me but as far as
it's flushing out the liver as far as it
flushing out toxins out of the body
that's a medical medium information now
it's become law out there meaning it's
out there and after people know
that information region eights from my
source that's the whole point and so you
know look the whole the whole point is
and I've actually talked about that on
the years about the lemon water doing
this through lectures in the past right
many years ago this isn't just three
years ago five years ago is doing
lectures thirty years ago in places I
mean I was on the bottom of churches I
was in church basements I doing last
year's four to three hundred people at a
clip then going to the next church to
three hundred people at a clip the next
church at war health food store or
whatever back in the old days teaching
people about these various things about
all of it including avocados are good
for you teaching people that avocados
are good for you yeah okay
meaning you don't want to over eat them
but they're good for you yeah that
people thought avocados were poison back
thirty years ago doctors wouldn't let
you eat them people people they know in
the health movement you can find one in
the health food store okay and and
literally I went from state to state
over the decades teaching people you can
eat this at Mikado it's actually good
for you now everybody's over here and so
now I'm actually doing the opposite slow
down I mean out of the two hundred and
fifty thousand individuals I helped out
in the last thirty five years one on one
not even the lectures and other things I
taught them about the lemon water so
when someone says he didn't delete it
knows what lemon water he didn't he
wasn't the guy that's know about
flushing out the liver flushing out the
toxins and hydrating you first thing in
the morning not originated from a mean
and it does help and it's critical so if
you're doing that in the morning it
makes a huge impact on how does it
matter
yeah two lemons oh it doesn't matter one
lemon two lemon there's eight ounces
sixteen ounces I mean more that's a
really good point you know some people
they don't like the lemon it's sharp
they don't like the hit by and you know
they feel kind of like it's too intense
they can do a half a lemon in sixteen
ounces if they really want that's fine I
like a whole lemon in sixteen ounces
what I do yeah in some limits are much
more juicier yeah so you just got this
game going on and then you wait how long
before the celery juice yeah yeah half
an hour's past 20 minutes you could do
probably and the question I get all the
time is why
sixteen ounces of celery juice in the
celery book I know it's in the celery
right now in the book but I just was in
the book yes but we're not gonna tell ya
no no yeah we're gonna let him tell ya
it's people asked all the time yeah I
want the short cut what yeah yes okay so
yeah 16 ounces because you need the
travel time it has so many obstacles
that celery juice has so many problems
meaning it's gonna run into because
everybody's a mess they're a mess inside
everybody is a disaster inside meaning
you know and that's what happens so you
said whatever you know basically what
that means
you got you got streptococcus e.coli
people got all kinds of different levels
of bacteria they could viruses in their
system in their livers they got bacteria
in their intestinal tract lymphatic
system they have that to begin with you
know that's just to start with they have
putrified and you guys everybody has
this putrified fats that are lined up on
the intestinal walls just sitting there
and what's behind it is is bacteria okay
and that is why this has nothing to do
with microbiome crap that you hear out
there like the new like that's just a
new talk because Candida is dying out
that whole fad and shrank basically I
knocked out the Candida trend back yeah
the first publication of medical media
but I hurt that trend so bad good
because because it was completely
misguided right because Candida without
Candida we died right so the whole thing
about Candida being died for you and and
and how do you have to get rid of all of
it we stopped that the medical medium
information so then they had to move
into something else they had to move
into the SIBO they had to move into
their microbiome and now I got to
actually work on that now where that's
not it either because what it is is we
have purified protein and fat lining on
the intestinal lining is just on the
walls of the gut right and that's the
problem with with Lobel reserves in the
liver weak livers low hydrochloric acid
in their stomach and that's where the
real main problem is so then bacteria
harbors behind this fat lining that's in
the intestinal in intestinal walls and
and behind that protein fat that's
actually been it's rancid and it's cake
on all the way down which is why when
people have this this feeling of like
they have to go to the bathroom right
away when they and they drink it and a
lot of people have that I had it for two
years
yeah so learn to use I dream my celery
juicers went to the bathroom and then it
stopped because that 16 ounces is
working on dissolving that lining it's
dissolving the sodium cluster salt said
science research has no idea about is
actually dissolving the fats the rancid
fats and rancid proteins on the walls of
the intestinal tract and starting to
break it away and your body wants to rid
that poison so it's just like yeah I got
to rid this poison I got rid of it and
get it out so it's trying to push it out
fast some people are so toxic you guys
know you probably know somebody some
people are so toxic where they haven't
hit something it's like whoa yeah and
and so yeah and if you're and if you're
not you know if you could do more
sellers you should do more and you if
you can handle it you do more you do 32
ounces or whatever but that's how it
works but just stick with it if that's
the effect on you and you're like I
can't do this because I have to run to
the bathroom right away get up a little
bit earlier you have your celery juice
being home so you can run to the
bathroom when you need to because
literally I had that for two years and
after about two years year and a half it
started changing and now I don't have it
anymore and all I can assume is that
most of that sludge that was packed on
the sides of the intestine have has gone
away and now everything is normal in
terms of I get up you know well then
then the sodium plus the salts of the
celery juice can kill off the
streptococcus and people say well I
don't have strep well did you have strep
throat when you were a kid because it's
day menu it's still there yeah and it
causes acne later
it causes UTIs bladder infections
interstitial cystitis right it causes
you know overactive bladder kidney
infections it causes yeast infections so
when people get the yeast infection
diagnosis that's streptococcus behind
that interes that's what that is
so yeah people don't know that there's
so much work so when you says the celery
juice has so many obstacles there's you
need 16 ounces because there's a lot to
do there's a lot to do right there's a
lot to break down and each person
there's a lot of poison to move out of
the liver there's a lot of poison to
move out that you test the line you ever
dissolve that
that and that old protein that's been
caked on and then then you got
everybody's pharmaceuticals inside their
liver they've got things inside their
liver then you got to push all that down
old pharmaceuticals you guys ever taken
antibiotic well you need 16 ounces or
more soda juice because you got to flush
out those old antibiotics and push them
out yeah you know and so it's got so
much work to do and then then what if
somebody had a big dinner the night
before that's in the way the celery just
has to find its way into your liver it's
got to go down your intestinal tract
it's got to go up the hepatic portal
veins right up into the liver and then
it's got to go out of the liver and back
into the system it's unbelievable what
it has to do right and it's kind of
simple it's simple if you just accept
that and try it yes and then be amazed
and then you got people that got focused
concentration issues they got they got
brain issues and and yeah they got the
high anxiety they get focus
concentration they got it different
brain issues and then the sodium cluster
salts have the electrolytes have to find
their way to your brain so you need the
16 ounces to go all through that and
then find the way to the brain so you
can get sharp so you can get your your
neurotransmitters back so you can start
thinking see your electrical impulses
can do what they need to do so they
could run down the neurons and actually
fire so you can be sharp and quick it's
all of that I have a question so yeah
we're talking about the internal body
and there were a couple of questions
that came up on the last life about one
person said oh I had back pain but when
I started doing celery juice it went
away and another person said that they
had tennis elbow and when they started
consistently doing that so talk a little
bit about like the external physical
skeletal muscular part of celery juice
helping that yeah tennis elbow if you
have an injury it's one thing if you
have something mysterious happening like
tennis elbow mm-hmm where it's not
really an injury it's just not it's just
inflammation that's there you're dealing
with low-grade viral activity so when
you're drinking your celery juice you're
lowering your viral activity or you're
knocking down your Epstein Barr virus
you're knocking down your
hhv-6 or shingles viruses like the back
pain yeah back pain Epstein Barr doesn't
necessarily
go to the back to off minutes it's
actually rare that it heads to the back
too much but shingles always goes to the
back and you don't need a rash to have
that right you're drinking your celery
juice you're knocking down your shingles
inflammation right because that's what
happens people get this the sciatic
nerve
yeah and they get the static problem
since that's the whole point and you're
going every much jingles you should be
on celery juice mom yeah yeah that's for
my mom I played tennis my whole life
very seriously very competitively and
the amount of tennis elbow that I came
across in my life that was always
unexplicable nobody knew really what to
do they tied a little band around your
forearm here to somehow relay and some
people would do it it still didn't work
and there was no there was it was
completely undiagnosed and and random
and I literally played thousands and
thousands of hours of competitive tennis
Wow and there was no reason for why one
person would have everybody's hitting
the same ball the same way to graa
there's no reason but one person would
have it why wouldn't everybody get it
everybody's playing the same amount of
tennis and that makes a lot of sense
when you describe it
yeah when you're viral what happens is
that when you use a part of your body
when you use a part of your body a lot
and you've got a low-grade virus that's
in the body it takes advantage of
anything you're using too much interest
that's what happens I don't even know if
I talked about that in a radio sure if I
talked about this it's probably talked
about that in the focus I definitely
know I probably talked about that in the
books for sure but I haven't talked
about it only about that too much
if you're using too much of something
like you're using your back too much
you're using your leg to your knee if
you're using someone like that you got
the little great viral thing that we
cleaned up with you yeah that's what
happens saying the tennis elbow same
with tendonitis the whole tendinitis
thing that whole thing that's all
yeah yeah all of that is low-grade viral
activity when you're using something too
much whatever it is then what happens
there yeah you start taking care of
yourself you get celery juice in you get
the right information you're not doing
all that collagen junk powder which will
just make you sick I'd be doing yeah
yeah exactly gotta be careful whatever
dye you subscribe to does it matter
you got to be care and then you can
clean these viruses up
you know the protocols you learn the
supplements I get a new book coming out
that I'm not announcing it's a surprise
I've been announced a new book for him
know in the old days this is a
retraction but it's a live retraction
right I mistakenly last time we were
here I said they haven't he was working
on a brain book and people responded
very positively about that instantly
about it it was a complete fabrication
on my part I misunderstood something
that I thought I knew I thought I'd
heard and he is not working on a brain
book so I I just want to say that
publicly so pleased I apologize for
getting people's hopes up there will be
a great book down down the road he gets
to say that yeah I don't there will be
there will be my bad I got a surprise
daddy myself from YouTube video I just
rated myself on the island yeah no I got
a surprise book coming I'm gonna talk
about the gut involved in there it's
gonna be like some of me a lot of that
it's gonna be really it's gonna be
mind-blowing I think when people get
this but I also so you want me to let
you announce that you don't want me to
announce yeah that's right but I will
say I'm you know give people a hint know
I have over 200 different like illnesses
conditions and symptoms in this book
also with how to address it with the
right dosages great of supplementation
how to really move people forward like
never before even though all the books
do that yeah sure this is going to be
quite a surprise this comes directly
from me on the questions but again I
know a lot of people that suffer from
allergies and people always say oh my
gosh my allergies are horrible the
pollens out there I've never had
allergies and so but I do i do empathize
because I have friends and family
members that suffer from it
so why do we blame nature for allergies
like isn't it something because I mean
if we're doing all this shouldn't we
eventually shouldn't that ologies
eventually be cleared up why do we do
when you take care of yourself they do
it
one just gets off of gluten their
allergies start to actually improve
mm-hmm it's it's incredible because
gluten and this is medical medium
information feeds bugs nobody knew it
fed bugs like they took the whole gluten
thing the wheat thing being bad all that
information but not one single
professional whether they come out with
books are not new gluten feeds bugs
until the medical media information came
to town to teach people that's the
reason why you get sick when you have
gluten versus somebody else who doesn't
get sick when they have gluten he says
they don't have the bugs feeding off it
as someone else does so that's how the
warming okay so if you're if you're if
you're somebody is high you know prone
to allergies you have pathogens like
bacteria and viruses in your liver and
in your lymphatic system and in your
sinuses and in places in your body so
think you're gonna be now sensitive to
other other things so we're gonna Paul
and it's going those triggers those
triggers but it's because you've got
those things in your the blood in your
bio Buster because the bugs are already
producing toxins like Mars has produced
neurotoxins to actually make you
chemical sensitive so the epstein-barr
actually makes people chemical sensitive
you know and then and then streptococcus
gives people sensitivities in their
lungs and in their sinuses and even in
their bladder
it gives them sensitivities they'll get
the status feeling stuff go get the
bladder irritation still get the sinus
problems to sinus headaches they'll get
the lung stuff they'll have you know all
of that going on because they got this
long-term chronic streptococcus
infection and there's over 50 groups of
streptococcus undiscovered by research
and science with all with so many
strains it's not even countable you can
pick them up in a public bathroom you
can pick them up in a restaurant doing
we're eating restaurant food you can
pick them up for relationships you can
get a new strap that's highly enigmatic
resistant from somebody who's got a
strep you know in a relationship and
they've actually been you know
bombarding it for antibiotics for 20
years then you pick up the strep and now
you got this strip and then strep is
just everywhere and so what happens is
that you become sensitive you sensitive
allergies pollen you can be sent you can
be a young child that senses pollen
because it's trap because children have
strap they just
they do they do and so you end up with
these long-term allergies but when you
knock down that strap that streptococcus
bacteria your allergies go away you get
rid of gluten your allergies can improve
great you get rid of dairy products your
allergies actually start to improve you
get rid of eggs they really start to
improve and then okay and then you get
somebody else they don't really have
much going on inside of them make it eat
whatever I mean I know people they're
like nine years old they can eat what
they want sure I mean but they don't
have maybe as many bugs so very very
little and they just they're just some
of those old dinosaurs out there that
that that don't exist anymore coming up
the world has changed
yes mr. Silva this next question is
exactly about that there was a question
that why do we have more pathogens today
than we did in the yesteryear and there
was a flight attendant who said she's
been you know flying for over 20 years
and she noticed that seems to be so much
more chronic illness from she was seeing
customers coming on the plane you know
every day in her in her career just
saying so many more chronic illnesses
now than there was when she started from
yeah yeah because because what's
happening well that's why the industry
wants to blame it on your genes they
want to say that literally yeah the
global population our genes went bad in
the last 30 years that's what they want
to say yeah they want it they want us to
believe and they want women to believe
especially women yeah they want women to
believe their genes are bad that's what
they want because it's a way to control
women it's disempowerment yeah that's
how the industry's work if women get too
much power the world gets better that's
how it works I mean I mean what happens
so you have the key to land without keep
them in the dark
keep them sick teach women that their
bodies attacking itself which is which
is evil yeah that's the autoimmune
theory that your body's attacking itself
so they want to teach women that your
body's attacking itself and it's sad
because they'll use women doctors to do
it the only thing women doctors they'll
use women doctors to actually do it to
carry that on then you know your bodies
are destroying itself it's actually your
body's immune system is just
- thyroid causing Hashimoto's your
body's immune system is destroying your
skin causing eczema psoriasis it's a
technique of the industry to use
something that has no science behind it
that's valid whatsoever because they've
never seen the auto antibody they
supposedly see they've never seen it
create an issue in an organ ever it's
not possible so they have no proof
whatsoever it was a theory that came out
in the 1950s no really in the 1950s when
when technology was what in 1949 and
1950 52 think about it so it was a
theory that your body's attacking itself
so they want to control women disempower
them kick them down keep them down by
keeping everybody sick with chronic
illness especially women by telling them
their body's attacking itself or it's
your genes or bowles
yeah and so there's a reason for this
because then you think your genes are
bad so you better get your breasts
removed yeah that's how it's done your
genes are bad so you better something
else
Eugene and the reason why they do this
is because the industry has to protect
itself because it doesn't have the
answers right right so it doesn't have
the answers it just does and one
examples Lyme disease medical medium
information has moved to the Lyme
disease diagnosis the industry changed
it because of medical media right they
took it out of bacterial and they put it
in autoimmune because of the books
because the books have went around to so
many doctors so many people around the
play had to put it into something else
they had a shifted because the Lyme
disease is viable right it's not
bacterial this is a prime example so you
stuck it in autoimmune now they're
trying to shift the game they put it not
on me to mean the meaning they don't
know what causes Lyme disease now and
the Lyme labs are hurting because of
this will leave me there hurt and
they've note the big industry off of
that and they're hurting so they moved
it off often to autoimmune into the
history it's it's shifting and to miss
realness but then they can say it's your
genes that's causing a lot of disease
now or autoimmune and your body keeps
swimming down because you're
disempowered you don't please
you don't have the answers to really
help yourself heal yeah and so you think
your body's the problem isn't that body
shaming you have been saying this for a
feel ever it's it this is the new body
shaming that's happening with the
industries and no one even sees it they
just accept it like we're just supposed
to be brainwashed and accept it and you
know what ability when said when a
doctor tells that to you and I had one
talk how many years ago before I had
thyroid issues it come I can remember
the feeling the minute the doctor said
it to me I remember the feeling it's
like I can sit remember it to in one
second I was sitting in a chair he said
it and there was a feeling that went
through my entire body that just it felt
horrible that my body would be attacking
itself and it's I've never ever
forgotten it and I was probably about
thirty years old so that was 32 years
ago yeah well you know when you're
telling a 16 year old a daughter when
they're telling you know 16 year old a
15 year old and they're looking online
and they see they have Hashimoto's and
then they see that their bodies are
attacking itself at age 15 this is on
purpose because they've never ever seen
in a study or a test that the body is
attacking itself so why would they do
that to our kids why would they do that
when they have no proof there's never
been a study to prove it yeah how is it
possible that they're actually putting
that I'm in right now that information
out there because they want to yeah
that's what they want for desperate for
answers and they they want that you go
into it we've been trained to go into it
believing everything their doctor says
yeah because and instead of my dad have
a saying said if you don't know say you
don't know yeah but but no that's if
that's honest that's yeah we don't know
so maybe there's some other medical
people saying what do you mean you don't
know you're my doctor you if you don't
know then what's gonna happen to me
there are doctors who say to me
the world is changing there there are a
couple of doctors that have said to me a
couple of Surgeons actually and another
doctor that just said we just we don't
know we don't have the answers and that
was the most honest thing and I
respected those doctors because it takes
a lot of courage to say
doctors are incredible yes science and
research that's not coming out and
saying we don't have the answers right
because they're protecting its
protecting its of course and and so it's
not being honest and saying we don't
have the answers of why you have
excellent psoriasis we don't have the
answers where you have Hashimoto's we
don't have the answers where you have
multiple sclerosis we don't have the
answers with whatever this is and so
instead they don't care doctors care
yeah doctors care they care what they
care they're in it to care yeah but
science and research doesn't care about
the doctors doesn't care about the
doctors that get sick doesn't care about
anybody because if it did it wouldn't
torture 15 year old 16 year old 17 year
olds I know mom's talk to me all the
time or all through the years that
literally their child is sitting there
like thinking this is it it's over yeah
because they found that wait a minute
there's this it's autoimmune
and so that system set up to hurt people
and you know what and then when you put
out something to help reverse it all
help you know get people better they
attack someone is using say there's no
science of research behind celery juice
meanwhile there's no science and
research about the body attack so that's
actually valid right but no they'll
still turn around and say there's no
soldiers use meanwhile people are
actually healing that's the good news
do the celery juice for six months and
you see how you feel and you look at
your numbers my girlfriend I just went
through breast cancer and she reversed
her 100 180 degree with her diet
she no celery juice every day and you
know very very little fat no added salt
or sugar she's really like amazing and
all of her numbers have drastically
changed in less than a year and all of
her doctors have said how are you doing
and she's like through diet through all
of this food and it's been amazing and
that is science that's her own science
and research she's done okay I'm gonna
move on to something light-hearted will
you tell the story you tell the story I
think Anthony told the story maybe in
one of your podcasters oh no you're
scaring me no no I'm scared it's really
a great story because I want to try one
of the things that Ivan
wanting to do is to try to find somebody
who can teach like wild food gathering
and that what does it call like I'm
foraging I kind of want to do that and
it reminded me of the story of the
fiddle firm
oh yeah the fiddlehead ferns because you
can eat fiddlehead ferns so it's
inedible to wild edible plant you know
I've spent a lot of my early childhood
like gathering wild food because my
source tells me what's good what's bad
whatever and I would eat all kinds of
weird mushrooms out in the field you
come across a mushroom and yeah all
right I'm gonna risk it don't do that
though don't pick wild mushrooms don't
play with that don't risk
don't risk that it's not worth it no I
mean I have known professionals that
know their mushrooms huh data burn their
tongue out of their mouth literally
because of putting the wrong wild
mushroom on their tongue why they were
out in the field you know and I've
always said just I don't just don't play
with it yeah yeah don't play with
mushrooms and you know and I would you
know but fiddlehead ferns they taste so
good and you know so I just Saturday
take I just sat in this little area that
I found a big crop and I just ate one
after another until the spirits say
don't eat too much don't eat too many
because they're so they're so not only
medicinal but they have like an alkaloid
on them that you're just really tough on
the intestinal tract if you've eaten way
too many of them there so they have this
bitter alkaloid that it just could make
you just feel so sick if you overeat
these you know maybe four or five of
them are fine you know and I don't know
I must have eaten 30 or 40 or 50 of them
I was just laying in a patch just I was
in fetal position I was laying in a
patch I was so sad and then you know
what after I got over it
I picked a whole you know I picked a
whole like bale of a more and just
brought him back to the house and ate
him again and then that was it I was
just it was the stupidest thing it was
the stupidest thing
yeah you ain't even tell the story good
and you know there was - two times it
happened there is a time work there's a
store that had into while yeah
I've been mean and then I bought a
marinade over ate them because you know
what it is it's like it's like it's like
when something tastes so good and it's
so good for you you just say you know
what a little bit more why not
you know I've sat in a while too many
Oreo
picking wild blueberries until I
couldn't eat another like I just like
just till I just laid in a wild
blueberry feels like blue from my toe
and just stuff that wild blueberries
because it's just that one moment where
you know you get a chance to do that in
your life it's a special moment okay so
some people wanted to know what we ate
the rest of the day because on the last
live I guess it sounded like all we ate
was donors you the celery juice and the
lemon water and Alan and and and our
heavy-metal detox smoothie which is not
all we eat but we obviously we do a lot
of recipes that are in Anthony's books
we love the spaghetti bolognaise that's
amazing and we do that for gas a lot
that come over we I make the quiche a
lot probably once every couple of weeks
and I was going to say if you're able to
make your own food and do some of the
recipes do them in bulk because you can
like I made the the quiche last week and
Scott was in you know New Orleans and I
had a girlfriend over and we both had
and then I had it like for lunch the
next day and then the next day for
dinner I just threw it with a bunch of
greens and a little bit of lemon on the
greens and a quarter of an avocado and
that was my dinner and we also do the
lentil I do the lentil tacos that's
really fabulous and easy it's mostly
chopping it doesn't really take a lot of
time the potato pancakes we've done for
a lot of our
dinner parties those are delicious and
then ours kind of standard dinners like
when we're running around we don't have
time to you know cook or plant a menu is
just stick and potato and you know in
the oven or steamed potatoes with some
kind of steamed veggies and a salad we
do that a lot or we have a rice dish
that's really easy to make we'll prepare
the rice ahead of time and there's this
great rice here in California called
Kota Kota farms and it's there it's
amazing brown rice Wow no I gotta bring
you a package I'm sorry there was
something else I was gonna bring into oh
yeah we'll look out so that we just will
do rice and then we'll roast a sunflower
seeds and some sesame seeds in a pan
with no oil and then we'll take the rice
and mix the seeds up and put a little
Bragg's the coconut Bragg's
in it and it's really delicious and it's
a great side for you know all the
vegetables or salads or steamed any
veggie that you want people mango frozen
mangos bananas milk tumeric on top of
that and we do a homemade granola we'll
mix in with some coconut you know fresh
coconut that is not fat-free so we'll I
usually I used to have that in the
morning but ever since the liver rescue
came out I do that either in the
afternoon or sometimes even if I'm
really tired and I don't feel like
making dinner I'll do it at night for
dinner and that'll be it gluten free
pasta with tomato spinach those kinds of
things we also just learned that we
don't we make zoodles we make noodles
from zucchini yeah and we get to I just
got like a little doodle you know in a
little what do they call it where you
make the spiralizer just to put the
zucchini in there and you turn it and it
makes little noodles and I'll make like
a really fresh red sauce and anything
that you want to saute if you want it to
be fat-free like he says and all of his
lectures and stuff that you can just
saute your onions and garlic or whatever
in either water or I use vegetable broth
that I make from scratch so I freeze a
lot of vegetable broth and little you
know jars and then I just defrosted and
I sauteed in that and then I'll throw
them in like fresh tomato
and then you throw the zoodles in and
you just turn the zoodles over like for
even a minute and it just barely cooks
it if you overcook it then it releases
that sort of zucchini taste which if you
like that that's great or if you want it
to be al dente I'm not kidding it tastes
like capellini pasta yes so great and
it's agression yummy so we do that once
in a while and yeah so those are a lot
of the other things a lot of leafy
greens that we you know the rest of the
day it's not just celery juice all day
that's amazing that's incredible I'm
like actually getting hungry now
no that's incredible and people could do
a little bit of fat you know they can
put a little bit of their fats they're
high quality fats in their food it's
just so much but it's such an over
an intimidation as that yeah that's
going on people are overdoing it it's
like look if you got a chronic illness
if you got symptoms you don't want there
if you got you know if you're dealing
with even acne you mean you're doing
that or something else you want to make
sure you lower them or even eliminate
them for a while art or to maybe like
exactly one of the you know the 20 day
cleanse in the first day can keep the
paxil or whatever it is but yeah yeah no
that's a credible diet though like
that's an amazing diet yeah that's kind
of our our standard and then a lot of
people are asking are we 100% no we're
not 100% I mean we make mistakes or we
yes everybody's everything stuff
sometimes it yeah sometimes we're like
we don't have the time to do it or
whatever but and it's also a process
like I've been doing this for six years
so it didn't we didn't get to this place
where we're at right now two years ago
you know or four years ago we've been
slowly shifting and changing and cutting
more and more things out and we like
Scott was saying on the way here we eat
it out at restaurants way way less
because if you've heard the restaurant
podcast on restaurants oh that's scary
but we eat a lot less than when we drew
and everybody's oh my god but when we
went to a restaurant about a year ago
and we had heard about it I'd seen it
being promoted by a bunch of different
people on Instagram and different
places and it was close to her so I was
like oh yay a new place so we went there
and I for some reason I got a hit to ask
a general ill ask do you use control
oiled and I'll ask questions and you
know if I see corn on the minyak make
sure you know please don't put any corn
on and whatever I'm ordering for some
reason I asked about nutritional yeast
and I said well what about then they
said oh we have a nutritional yeast in
that like okay what about this literally
everything on the menu happy release so
beware of the vegan restaurants I mean I
know that they're vegan but there can be
lots of toxic ingredients in vegan well
you know no one else are pretty even
even here's the funny everybody thinks
he's great yeah everything's right all
the vegans use it they live off of it
it's disastrous yeah I know people they
put on a pop yeah it's toxic so oh no
and be church leaders yeah yeah it's
it's not it basically it's why it's a
form of glutamic acid that's what it is
you can't have nutritional yeast without
glutamic acid being present so it's like
a form of MSG you know say you know a
nutritional yeast company be like no
there's no MSG in our product there's no
way we don't have msg in here it's not
true there's just glutamic acid derives
from the gusto literally nutritional
yeast in the way it's created it's just
it's naturally occurring but it's bad
and it's toxic so if you know if you're
putting in a nutritional yeast and
everything yeah and people will be safe
why why isn't he talking about
nutritional miso because if I'm not
talking about it don't do it
yeah don't do it that's the whole thing
and or if I'm talking about it bad like
I have before I have mentioned don't you
don't do the nutritional yeast
it'll slow down your healing if somebody
be like I did his medical medium
information I did it for a year it
didn't move me forward they did
nutritionally East all the time I got a
whole thing
I mean seriously think I don't know this
like I'm blinking there's a spice in
that you recommend in a lot of the
recipes and in the spaghetti bolognaise
and it's the poultry seasoning and
remember seeing that - like poultry
seasoning what because I'm thinking
there's poultry nut but then of course
you read the ingredients and it's just a
bunch of herbs and it's it's there it's
recommended for some of the recipes so I
would think whatever you're putting
nutritional yeast on get rid of the
nutritional yeast and maybe try the
poultry seasoning on stuff you'll have a
better shot with it you know the thing
is
with msg it's it sneaks into everything
it sneaks into all these different
things and what happens is migraines
nutritional yeast
it can give you migraines it can give
you headaches it can up your anxiety
game you can do all these different
things even if you're just using a
little bit same with natural flavors
it's another thing someone will say yeah
look I did medical medium information
for a month and it helped me a little
bit but didn't take me all the way they
were doing natural flavors and 10 items
I mean I've talked to people that do
everything labors and also like natural
vanilla flavor natural almond labor
right yeah you know what extract is not
a natural flavoring that's not an MSG
based you know flavoring so vanilla
extract is different but vanilla
flavoring you know a flavoring organic
flavoring is msg if you see organic
flavors that's msg if you see all of
that if you see the word flavor flavors
or flavoring all three of those if you
see berry flavor strawberry flavor
that's msg if you see raspberry flavor
msg doesn't matter if you see a product
it says no GMO all whatever all
plant-based all whatever it is the whole
thing and there's flavor yeah in there
somewhere
that's msg that's how it's done so you
know and people don't know that so
they're getting the natural flavors
they're pounding the nutritional yeast
are doing the high fats you know they do
the celery juice for two weeks and go on
YouTube and say why I quit celery juice
after two weeks meanwhile celery juice
to save countless lives yeah around the
globe literally from death defying
diseases so there's so much
misinformation and how it works and how
it's all set up out there it's
incredible so I mean but yeah that's a
really good thing boys are we are we
close to being over I think yeah we're
close do you want to say we're close
we're almost at an hour do you want to
say anything about disinformation
or misinformation that's out there yeah
absolutely because it's hard sometimes I
think it's hard for people to discern
whether it's misinformation and there is
so much information out there it's crazy
for me I just follow what Anthony says
that's how like that's how I I am
dissect the misinformation and people
ask me all the time what about this one
that I'm like I don't know if it's in
the book if he's talking about it that's
what I do if he's not I just let it go
misinformation has been out there for
decades people been sick for decades
because of it it's not new it's just
that the younger people haven't learned
yet yeah but the people who are 50 or 40
they medically the hell or 60 they've
been through the hell they've been
through years of misinformation finally
found the right source which is the
American medium information finally knew
how to heal meanwhile when you're young
you're just gonna get swamped in all
that misinformation because every 10
years everybody forgets that the whole
Candida theory didn't work they know
they keep on forgetting and they
repackage and remain things and then
they threw like the lectin thing at you
which is actually all rubbish then they
throw something else at you and then
they throw something else at you then
they think it's endless and you just get
tangled up in the misinformation and
it's all backed by paid-for studies when
you can I could get a paid for stuff
sort of me you can get a pay for I think
it a paid for study and make it look
like oh okay this is now cited rice is a
paid for study all you need is money and
then you do the money okay and then you
get the study done yeah and then you
haven't support your cause which you
will make money that's the game so all
the things that are out there are all
contaminated with the bad bad game yeah
Ford for for reason
that's the whole reason that's a whole
new kombucha tea all of that that's all
backed everything's backed and then you
just go into the trends and then you
just get sucked into the trends and the
painfulness information and all the sort
of stuff
this information is pure untampered with
and look be open to it so you can work
on healing because I love to always bark
that out and you don't have the same
agenda as a lot of these so that's a
huge difference okay anyway if you like
go yeah if you like these youtube lives
subscribe subscribe that's it everybody
says right subscribe but you will also
like it also click the
likes and if you liked the video and
subscribe click the bell do the thumbs
up in YouTube sent to a friend spread it
around because look I'm doing it this
way
hardcore live like this and raw I'm not
doing big productions and going out and
doing his big productions out there yeah
getting people no no getting people even
pay for it big production to get people
yeah I'm trying giving out free stuff
that's what I did last week sorry dude
right through I can take my popularity
and learn how to bankroll it and make
sure people have to pay for everything
on my website pay for everything there
is and whatnot in you name it
I've never done that it's always been
about me it does have a huge amount of
the celery farmers go to the library
books any libraries if any of you guys
don't have them in your libraries and
nobody mentioned anything so we're
serious we'll buy books and send them to
your libraries just let us know what
library and work with city and we'll get
them off to the library so if you don't
have the money by him and you want to
want them in there look your library and
they're not there let us know okay
that's to some some person that will no
I don't know good one you guys not a
direct message or something like that
you guys and what's your font what
you'll find on these YouTube lives a
YouTube live series there's none of
these advertisements at the beginning in
your way before we go on before we you
know that you see this YouTube okay and
I'm not exactly doing that you don't
mean you know that you go to you gonna
watch it YouTube yeah there's all these
advertisements just non-stop
advertisements there's none on this
there's a reason I could have
advertisements I just don't want in
there I want you guys getting the
information I want it free bottom line
yeah right no all right I'm gonna click
it up because this is where we do