[Music]
in this book I reveal truths about
chronic illnesses you won't learn
anywhere else you won't hear it from
your doctor read it in any other books
or find it on the internet these are
secrets that have not yet surfaced about
how to finally heal and I'm bringing
them to light to you for the very first
time when I was 4 years old I Heard a
Voice I am the spirit of the most high
there is none above me but God
himself that night at the dinner table
Spirit came to me but you know I liked
[Music]
it I'm
sorry his mouth never moved but I could
hear his voice speak to me I here for
you I'm not a doctor I have no medical
training but I can tell you things about
your health that no one else can I can
give you Clarity on diseases that
doctors often misdiagnose or treat
incorrectly or they just give up on and
label mystery
[Music]
illness stop making
excuses I used
to everybody always makes brownies they
always have so much of that
stuff say lung cancer lung cancer where
it die I didn't even know what those
words meant say it again say l lung now
say cancer cancer now say grandma has
lung
cancer grandma has been
cancer are you okay huh my grandmother
visited her doctor and the chest x-ray
revealed she had lung cancer for over 20
years I've helped tens of thousands of
people recover and heal from illnesses
such as rheumatoid arthritis
fibromyalgia chronic te syndrome lime
disease and so much more it's time for
you to learn these secrets and gain
control over your life it's the way it's
meant to be it's the way Spirit wanted
it to be
[Music]