Anthony William you the beginning get in
the ship anyway the nun at the medium
right here well yeah they're right here
Scott Bakula Chelsea field dear friends
of mine we're here today I'm gonna talk
about medical medium information you
guys know me number one New York Times
bestselling author medical medium book
series helping out people around the
world helping doctors troubleshoot
patients for years and years that's my
history and you guys know there are
history of history is an amazing amazing
history out there and people around the
world know who these two amazing people
are I'm honored to have them here in
fact it's it's mind-blowing and really
incredible to talk about medical medium
information because Scott and Chelsea
they use that information they've also
given out books over the years I've
heard it so many times from them over
the years you guys buy all these books
and then your lives and you're handing
them out and friends and people and
family people on the street just hey
look you've got to get this information
so you can work on healing the whole bit
so it's great to have you guys here
it's an honor to be here yeah it's great
we got this right here so cheers yes
this is good - Cheers yes so you guys
drink the celery juice right I mean you
do every day how many years have you
yeah every day we've been trying to
figure that out I think it's about four
maybe four years yeah maybe a little bit
more I don't miss a plant-based for five
and a half years so your plant-based
yeah oh cool and I'm four and a half I'm
a year behind thank you got sick and she
started and then we all we all followed
her yeah
Anthony basically saved my life a number
of times but specifically one time when
I had a foodborne illness and then it
went into appendicitis and I had an
appendectomy and it was rough recovery
but I got through it
thanks Anthony and all of his advice and
reading his book which I think only the
first one was out then it's a long time
ago yeah yeah I mean it's five years ago
I think yeah it'll be six years in March
when everything changed for me so yeah
it's been great and we do celery juice I
do I'm up to about 20 ounces every
morning me too
okay that's amazing after the lemon
water yeah first we can come in water 16
to 20 ounces in lemon water and then we
wait about half an hour yeah and then we
do the celery juice and we got a new
juicer we have a we have a green star
here in LA and he has the Omega in New
Orleans Meghan yeah and once we went
from the centrifuge to the masticating
it made a big difference because it just
you do a whole thing of a whole bunch of
celery and you get more than 16 ounces
so we just kept doing it yeah the mega
juicer the Omega juicer is my favorite
it's just it's so easy to use it's easy
to think we're always asking me like
what do we do for juicers what do we do
for juicers and and I always tell people
look use the one I use it's a mega
juicer so when om EGA go to go to their
website thank you because people will
buy the wrong juicer and get frustrated
if it's too hard to clean it's too hard
to clean they give up in that it this is
like a medical device a juicer is a
medical device it's not it's it isn't
just some kind of like thing or holistic
thing to do or I mean natural thing oh
hey have this have this your salad
spinner you got that you got your mixer
you got your thing know that that's all
great but the juicer is an actual
medical device when you run like
something like this which is an herbal
tonic
herbal medicine so you're doing herbal
medicine you that's what it is it's
extracting or medicine yeah yes I like
the Omega but but but it's incredible so
you guys are juicing you've been teasing
for a while yeah I was thinking that we
know you going back to working with her
mom and that's no no no I want to say
six or seven years so I think it's
longer I think longer eight years yeah I
agree
I think it's somewhere about a year's
and well you know the thing is with you
guys is what I've always noticed is when
you and when you find something that
works you find something that's good you
guys stay with it and you become like I
mean it's basically your do you dedicate
yourself to it I've never heard you guys
ever say well you know what I'm trying
this now or I'm trying you guys just
tried everything and it didn't work and
it didn't stick so this is yeah and I
think also were super discipline we're
both you know I was a dancer he's an
athlete so that discipline is already
built in and that does help but also
when when you have tried a lot of other
things and problem still arose and
disease is still were happening then and
this when you when we started doing this
there we didn't have that issue there
was no reoccurrence of illnesses I mean
I I don't know the last time I got sick
it's been a while no it hasn't and I
think that's relevant is that we've seen
we've seen results not just for
ourselves but for so many people in our
lives that we've either that have come
on to Anthony on their own or we you
know talked him up and they've joined or
somebody's called and said I've got this
problem going on she's like she's read
every book every but she's she's like I
haven't read as nearly as much as her
but so many people have used the
protocol and different or you know
relatives of ours
her mom cousins nephews our own children
ourselves and they've had amazing
results so it's not it's not like I
think you change when things aren't
working yeah it's like well okay and
it's also not something that you can as
we always say we ate a certain way me
for sixty years of my life and then you
cannot expect I mean this is the hardest
thing for people understand you can't
expect to do celery juice for a week and
then everything is everything is there
life is great now when I switched over
to not eating
anymore I would say it was at least a
two-year process of kind of getting
through just not quite feeling right and
not and I haven't the idea of going back
to me isn't doesn't easily I mean that
exists for me at this point in time but
it took time and the celery juice and
and then the the smoothies and all the
other protocols that we follow
throughout the day they all they take
they take time to settle in and but yes
it's worth it yeah I mean I think that
some people get results right away I I
see on Anthony's Instagram which is so
inspiring for me all of you out there
you guys inspire me because people from
Instagram here today either share
incredible pictures you share your
stories I read them all and they truly
are inspiring to me and keep me going
because sometimes when I talk to people
I'll be affronted with doubt and a lot
of questions and well you know how do
you know this and a lot of times I'll
say here's the book read the book and
they want me to do their research and
and and try to defend what they're
saying and it's like you all the
information is there you can read it if
you want to so then when I go on
Instagram and I see the positivity and
so many stories of healing and
especially the pictures which you can't
argue that I mean I tell people that are
doubting I like go to Instagram and see
the results you cannot argue with those
pictures ya know it happens that's what
that's what you know journalists and
media they don't go to that and they
don't look at that and then they all of
a sudden say oh celery juice doesn't
work yeah I can't tell you how many are
they do it for a week just doesn't work
really yeah I can't say how many
articles I talk about the people with
chronic illness they're suffering their
skin problems everything they cut all
that out yeah and they don't look into
that sometimes you know when it's at
because when you look at that's what's
powerful about Instagram because
Instagram tells the real story the real
story and you guys are fighting for it
out there you're cleaning up everything
you're healing you're working on it
you're staying strong on it you know
with Scott and Chelsea exactly they're
they know you can't drink celery juice
for just one week and so many people
they hear about it out there and they
don't look into the stories and they
don't look into the powerful healing
information that's happened and they
don't read the books and they'll just do
summary for five days and they'll say
hey this is my story of doing celery
juice for five to seven days really
doesn't work really doesn't air you
think you guys know you guys know just
like so many people in the medical
medium community once you do that celery
juice and you really stay within each
month at a time how it's a lifesaver and
organized I've seen it out of the
picture walking from over there okay
seen so many people healed so many
things from it when they stay with the
long term and you guys you guys know
that you guys read the books you were
you doing even if Scott says well I
haven't read as much but look that what
happens is you guys really do read more
than I've seen a lot of people do out
there because people don't get the book
and they'll rush to the recipes or
they'll go right to the chat
specifically their data that books tell
a story all through it where they have
to read the books all the way through
and it's about understanding the big
picture because I I've had friends call
and say I have a this specific issue
whatever whatever it was and there's
nothing in the book about it and I'm
thinking to myself yeah there is but you
have to read the whole book because it's
it's the overview and the understanding
of the whole picture of what happens for
you to understand oh this little thing
that I'm dealing with pretty much I can
understand this is what I need to do
because it's going to help the whole
body function better so I encourage
everybody to read it and some of it is
like for me I reread all the time I have
two or three books by my bedside out if
I wake up in the middle of the night and
I can't go back to sleep I start reading
and then I'm the next day and I'm like
oh no it's six o'clock in the morning I
gotta go
Anthony we go to the grocery store
there's no celery in the grocery store
like dang those don'ts anywhere dolls
you know it's funny the sour notes play
now they're going to eat what I care
people say well you know I'm gonna stop
drinking celery juice or I'm not gonna
show you my good actually that's good
that's good in fact you know when you
see when you see something out in the
world of like science and research
hasn't discovered celery juice you know
being anything good for people even
though millions are healing globally
right so am I good keep on doing that
because I can't find it anymore
and I needed to calm down I got people
to stop drinking it a little bit if you
look you know I'm gonna get selfish for
a second and say well everybody stop
drinking it I'll always be there for me
i buy lots and lots of cases and make
sure my friends have lots of cases but
you know that I'm owning I want you guys
to have last year we were in Colorado
and in the mountains and we were trying
to get
celery organic celery juice celery and
in the middle of winter time and the
person at the store said it's weird you
know so people are coming in and they're
buying celery and and some people are
coming in they're just buying cases of
celery and like hey but now we're
screwed we can't get it will do cucumber
juice yeah which is power double up on
our lemon water and there's always
there's always substitutes and that's
usually not for very long when the store
is out we have a couple secret stores we
go to the camera so it helps to have the
lemon waters a backup because it's its
flushes out the liver washes out the
kidneys if that's what it does you know
and so that's really important concept
that's in the in the liver rescue book
you have that whole idea of the liver
waking up in the middle of the night and
trying to let it just work quietly by
itself until noon or whatever without
having introducing anything that's going
to you know fats or any any breakfast
stuff that's going to make it take it
out of its kind of like cleansing it is
is fascinating to me it's something I
never knew but it kind of makes so much
sense and when you
acknowledge how important the liver is
and how much liver related illnesses
there are out there is everything it
feels like it does it jam feels like
it's everything although I know I have
to under I'm diverting what am i doing
yes I'm diverting for a moment but of
late I've been keep bumping into people
that are having brain stuff yeah going
on and I'm like okay when's Anthony's
I'm sorry no no I know I'm just worried
about you but you shouldn't be here you
should be working on last night writing
trying to finish up this book I'm
working on now exactly and and now
you're so quiet in your life well you
know the thing is with the brain the
brain gets clogged up when the livers
clogged up so that's what goes wrong
when the livers all like all congested
stagnant sluggish it's got all the
poisons petrochemicals in there
no one pump their own gas years ago you
guys know that right
no one pump their own gas there's 60
year old daughters six year old sons are
now pumping gas they're breathing it in
like it was nothing it didn't exist in
the past we have all that Patrick
chemical going on in people's brains
like never before the livers getting
filled of toxic heavy metals mercury
cadmium lead arsenic all of it
mercury especially luminol right and all
of this and then it gets overloaded and
then pathogens people got the
epstein-barr out there they got all the
cytomegalovirus they got all that kind
of stuff and with all of that adding up
inside the liver it just it goes to the
brain after the liver just kind of
coughs it out like Oh overflow and boom
it all comes out anymore yeah anxiety
stars yep depression all of it that's
why the liver so incredibly important
that's why I had to do that big old
liver rescue but but the brain had
orange juice so that brain book is gonna
come on its way to working on the liver
and cleaning it well well he's writing
the book about the brain and we just
need to keep working on the plan of
cleansing the liver
it's a big job yeah no it is it's always
got to be there it's like you have to
have that Plus exactly but I mean the
thing is though is is with you guys is
what I've always noticed is that you
know you you learn the information and
then when you're telling other people or
you're telling me you tell me the
information no you know what I mean and
I like that no I get on the phone with
you it's just a nosy you're just like
you're just you're just like you know
what the thing is with this and this and
this is what you needed your your
digestive system your hydrochloric acid
and I'm doing the celery juice because
of this and and like you guys like
really learn it and I know I know
there's a lot of medical medium
followers and they read the books and
stuff and they know what to and they're
sewing on it yeah right but you know
it's it's also a lot of people where you
you know it's like no that's your
hydrochloric acid don't sorry just
builds it up it written it and it takes
time to get them to kind of learn about
but what happens is they get diverted
out there because the Internet's filled
with all this other information that
doesn't work yeah that is filled with
all these other theories and concepts
and then it gets all mixed up in
Kabbalah then joggled out there so now
awesome something somebody's putting
lemon in their celery yeah the stores
are lined now with like with lemon in
celery juice while it's HPP high
pressure pasteurization that means it
was pasteurized so you think it's fresh
it's got lemon in there it's not gonna
help you then someone says I drank what
I trans celery juice for 30 days and it
didn't help
and so it's so it really pays off to
actually know the information to get
help others so you can actually change
the planet change the world and the
healing cuz you know do you guys see it
are people getting sick out there or is
that online a bubble now I'm just so
weird kind of bubble and I don't know
what the hell's going on you can just
look around and go what we're doing
something wrong so we've done something
wrong for many many many years you can
look at our society even look at the
amount of disease that's out there you
know when you want to know something
about a culture and a society you look
at what's at the intersections when I
was in the South shooting some films
like 20 years ago every intersection had
churches literally there before churches
on an inner
in the Bible Belt and you look at our
intersections now they're either
restaurants or drug stores or banks
that's it that we have created a Sikh
culture a sikh society and you know not
specifically anyone's fault a lot of
good people out there trying to help
like like you say all the time but
misguided for sure and you know for me
and for our family or most of our family
this is you know been incredibly healing
and I know I'll never I'll never eat
animal products again I know I'll never
know that work for you guys I got a lot
of people that are living that are doing
the animal products but they're keeping
away from the right ones I always tell
them to stay away from the bacon keep
the big we're in the eggs the cheese the
milk stay away from those and yeah if
you want some other animal products that
works for you make sure you're doing all
the other medical medium information
well for you guys what works for you is
the plant-based and I always say the
plant place is great absolutely the yeah
definitely I mean for a medium if we try
to get in by the time we wake up and you
have lemon water and then we have our
celery and then usually either it
depends if I'm going to like if I have
work or something or a class I'll do an
apple on the way or I'll take my
heavy-metal detox smoothie in a in a
thermos or my one of the liver liver
rescue smoothie so I'll do one of those
so I do one of those smoothies every
single day and then by the time that and
then I'll usually have a second Apple I
mean it's like after lunch you know it's
almost dinner time and then a couple of
snacks and there isn't time really to
have a turkey sandwich or something
there's I'm trying to fill my day and my
diet with so much and a lot of we're
leaning more and more into raw so we're
trying to get as many fruits and
vegetables in and by the time you
actually do that for me there isn't time
or room in my stomach to put something
else in whoa so an apple is medicine
that's a thing in people people don't
know that out there they're afraid of
fruit it got the fruit fear because of
all the misinformation out there
floating around that's something that's
really hurting people bad so Apple
that's Madison right an egg is
medicine there's nothing medicinal in an
egg instead the egg will feed every
pathogen people haven't they have acne
that means they have streptococcus in
their system if they have eczema that
means they have that scene bar in their
liver with copper so it's like and if
you get if you eat the eggs you're gonna
feed those pathogens and you're gonna
get sicker but you know what's sad is
there's a lot of people out there
whether it's you know dietitians and I
love dieticians and I love nutritionists
and I love doctors you guys know that I
mean that's all right all I'm about I've
worked with doctors my whole life but
there's a lot of different people in the
field though don't know any of the good
stuff and they tell all women just eggs
eggs do eggs and protein and eggs and
eggs and they tell them eggs just get
sicker down the road and you know what
it's all fun and games until you're
suffering until you got like really bad
fibroids and you're really suffering
until you got PCOS and so you got
endometriosis and it's out of control
and your whole life becomes doctor
visits yeah because you're getting
information out there about how oh it's
protein you should be eating egg oh you
should be eating this or that and and
you know what gets people in trouble so
and what happens is when you say you're
gonna be doing the apples and you're
doing the different snacks you do all
that that's medicine you're talking
about that's what that is and we need
that because the world has changed it's
really polluted like never before
yeah and and we were the ones actually
just absorb any now plants absorb you
know how plants are if they keep the air
healthier right yeah thing right that
that whole thing well we keep also the
planet healthier because we're sucking
up all that garbage that's floating in
the air we're taking in all that plastic
and petrochemicals we're taking in all
everything else we're like the sponges
now our livers like the sponges and
we're keeping the planet cleaner in a
way by becoming the ones that are filled
with all the garbage and just like the
plants are and people don't realize this
so hey we're you know guys and we're the
most vulnerable we're not walking around
with armor and fur and that other
animals have where where our skin it
absorbs things and we're breathing in
stuff every day so exactly I think the
hardest thing for most people that I
talk to about all this is just finding
the time and also accepting a certain
amount of respond
ability for your health because we live
in this tough in this era and I was
thinking about this last night it's hard
I know people say we don't have time we
don't have time to get up in juice we
don't have time we've got two little
kids we don't we don't have time to do
that we can't afford a juicer all those
kinds of things and it's easier to have
somebody to go to the doctor one time
and get the pill and say this is what's
wrong with your stomach
take this pill it seems easier but in
the long run all the pills go to your
liver and they're not you're not solving
a problem you're you're putting a lid on
it you're covering it up and it's it's
in Fester's and that's what I think
we're seeing in in the pandemic of
health issues that are going on around
us now chronic illnesses and and mystery
illnesses which was kind of one of the
big things that I hooked into in the
beginning when Anton I first met Anthony
was talking to he's like yeah what are
people doing for that I always go back
to oh there is no cure for the common
cold but there we spend billions of
dollars on this planet with on products
that are on a shelf every month or two
months in the wintertime for all of our
kids and all ourselves in the cough
medicine all these things and in the end
they're just kind of getting you through
something masking and making it last
longer but there is no cure but we have
all this products that don't fix it they
don't they don't prevent it they just
kind of hear it makes you feel better
because you think you're taking
something to help you and instead of
saying what is there something I can
take before I get sick that I can do and
make it habit and carve out that get up
an extra half an hour earlier a day or
in my case I get up an hour and ten
minutes before I have to leave to go to
work to make all the food and drinks
that I need to take to go with me in the
corner but it's become part of my like
therapy it's almost like a meditation
and it's and I say it's something that
I'm doing for myself and then a trend
you know then I pass that on to my
family and to other friends so I'm
getting I'm sharing something and the
beauty of Anthony is that he's sharing
this with everybody and you know he
always says you can go to a library and
pick up his books if you need to
and if you can't get him in your local
library send us a letter we'll send the
book here we'll buy the books I'm send
them to your library I don't care where
you are we'll get you all the books and
put them in your library and then you're
you're taking there's something healing
and just saying I'm doing this for
myself
and taking this time for my own health
and well-being every day and it
translates through your whole body not
just whatever you whatever your ailment
specific ailment is and it becomes a
life kind of a life a habit and it's and
it's life fulfilling and and anyway it's
I rambled a little bit but well I never
stop talking about how people are sick
of us talking about family and they're
just like oh here we go again
sorry um what I was gonna say is one of
the simple things that I like to say
never fear if you think about our all of
our bodies as a machine okay or like a
car right you would never take a car if
you had a gas part electric car you
would never take a card of gas station
and you choose choose the gas you can
choose gas or you could choose part gas
parts and or all stand you wouldn't pick
the sand pump to put in your car or the
part gas parts and pump because your car
wouldn't function I don't know how far
you would get on sand and gas but
probably not very far you're gonna pick
the gaps right to put in your car
because that's how your car is gonna
function not its optimum well our bodies
are the same you can we can be eating
you know a lot of the common stuff
that's out there eating and your your
machine is going to break down at some
point and it may not be now but it will
be later and you know little things
start to creep up as you get a little
bit older and or you can put stuff in
your body that can actually use 100
percent of which is the celery juice and
that's why it was soupy I always tell
everybody that no one's immune to
getting a symptom there's a lot of
people who think they're indestructible
now they're young they're working out
there doing their thing but they will
end up with symptoms because everybody
is
that's the problem right now yeah and
you know when you said Scott you said
mystery illness that's how can you like
locked on to send the medical medium
information begin with the first book I
talked about you know that's when she a
spirit of compassion coined the whole
mystery chronic illness thing yeah and I
say that because nobody knew did all
these illnesses like eczema psoriasis is
a mystery they didn't know they thought
because it had a name the research you
know what it was about
yeah multiple sclerosis yeah I wrote my
ology they're all mysteries right so
it's not just this random case of
mystery illness where someone gets sick
somewhere in some part of the country
and doctors are good you know perplexed
every single condition that has a
symptom that has a symptom or a
condition that's mean that you know
anything that has a label as a mystery
to research in science the medical
science of research now all of it
autoimmune complete mystery to research
in science they don't know that's why
they're telling everybody they're
blaming it on them now they're saying
it's your body being faulty your bad
genes okay we all got bad genes just in
the last 20 years that's centuries and
centuries centuries our big genes just
went complete just dinner down the tubes
in just the last 100 years and you know
so every so the young people that you
know older people and people in their
40s and 50s whatever and they all know
they're learning now that there isn't
answers out there hello and you're
younger you're brought to think oh wait
a minute no the doctors got all the
answers well when you start getting that
AXA money you're going to doctor doctor
and then you start getting neurological
symptoms and now you're got the anxiety
and other stuff you going to a
neurologist and then in your 32 now
you're 34 you're 38 what I'm saying is
you want to learn the truth about
chronic illness you guys did you want to
learn the information so you can protect
yourself and you can print because
everybody's getting symptoms you know
what people look at me sometimes when I
say that I mean some they go glassy-eyed
all right they don't see I really I
don't know about that because I'm eating
healthy I'm eating a healthy keto diet
or I'm eating a healthy whatever and I'm
working out I'm doing my my weight
training whatever it is and they're
young and they kind of get glassy-eyed
over that they're like he does he's out
of touch but I'm not out of touch
because you'll remember this you'll
remember that no everybody's getting
something on whether it's UTIs that
become
whether it's ringing the ears whether
it's tingles numbness whether it's
anxiety depression aches and pains
spasms twitches back pain leg pain
plantar fasciitis on the feet whatever
it is you know you can just keep on
going and a diagnosis and everything
else about it everybody is coming down
with something yeah and that's why this
information so critical but you got you
guys see it out there you see people
getting sick you see it all over the
place it's heartbreaking it really is
it's heartbreaking and I feel like we
have this little gem of information
medical medium and I want to share it
with everybody and I want everybody to
at least try it and I know it's hard and
one thing I want to say about Scott is
you know he works really long hours I
mean like nobody like me seriously yeah
and you know I'm sure people are
thinking oh but he's an actor and he's
probably got all these people doing this
stuff for him he does have an assistant
that will sometimes go to the grocery
store for him but I think you prefer to
pick out your own stuff usually he does
everything but he does give up even
after a 16-hour day he'll he will go to
the gym and then he comes back and in
the morning he gets up an hour to an
hour and a half early to prepare all of
this because he because he then can do a
16-hour day and go to the gym literally
that the reason he's able to really do
that is yes he's got discipline but
mostly because of the celery and the
heavy-metal detox smoothie and the food
that he eats during the day and not very
much fat and all the stuff that he's
doing to keep his machine running yeah
and look it's not I by I'm not perfect
and I sometimes eat things that I wish I
hadn't eaten and I sometimes don't have
time to prepare the things that I wished
I had time to prepare for but I can tell
you this that I can my energy through my
days has changed also a year ago was it
a year two years ago no that I stopped
drinking coffee and I think I know ring
is closer and so because I think it's
two years in March and so my my energy
level and you know I'll arrive I'll work
on over 16 hours on three and a half
hours sleep
night before because I flew in I didn't
have time and I gotta get up at 4:00 in
the morning but I'll go 16 hours and I
will go to the gym afterwards can do and
I am using but I'm by using and eating
this way I have solid consistent energy
throughout the day and I'm not a young
person anymore but I think most of the
young people's ass on earth all day long
because I'm I'm just eating better than
they are and I'm putting better fuel in
my body and and I and I also had carry
that positive attitude through the day
with me and that comes from just feeling
what I what I'm using and what I what my
energy level is coming from it's all
good and positive so I feel you know I
just I'm incredibly grateful that we've
had this big change really huge change
in our life and it's and it's like it
literally is life saving life extending
and more importantly quality of life
when you're looking at you know it's
easy when you're 18 it's like don't
worry about it so our 18 year old
friends and members of our family that
are young they whether they choose to
use this protocol now they've been
exposed to it they understand it when
they use it they see in me they do see
immediate results because when you're
young your body is is cleaner and for
the most part you hope and can process
things quicker and get to the truth of
stuff faster but one of one of my
relatives who was diagnosed with
borderline celiac he and he's in college
so what do you want to do in college you
want to drink beer and eat pizza beer
out of aluminum cans all of those things
and he was in trouble and his stomach
was giving him a lot of trouble and he
switched he made a switch to sell reduce
he committed to doing that in college
which is horrible Anthony always calls
him his hero which makes him feel really
good and and he had he's amazing stuff
he's slowly changed but he would
have amazing immediate results and then
periodically as a young person he'd go
out and have the feet set with the guys
and and he couldn't always get
gluten-free pizza and you know and he
couldn't always find a wheat free beer
and those kinds of things and so he
would slip and then immediately if his
stomach would go again so he knows he
has the information that's my point
he has the information and he knows if
he wants to take care of himself or he
wants to make it change he has all the
information it's in the book he calls
her all the time we talked about it and
so that's the good news
the information is there it's it's it's
out there and millions of people are
picking it up and and we feel we feel
tremendously grateful for that and we
want more people to do it because
there's no reason that we can't take
charge of our own health that's that's
the other thing that's the that's the
blessing within books is it really that
all the information is in the books you
know so you you I know everybody would
love to be able to sit here with Anthony
and tell them your everybody talked to
Anthony all the time we're like it's in
the book doesn't it ease please just
talk to us though because we're do know
you can't he doesn't talk to us anymore
he's too busy and we're okay with that
and we want the book you know we I was I
think every year I gotta figure out a
way to get you to work 23 and a half and
very important information all the foods
I mean I can keep you here talking all
day oh we could talk about it because
we'll talk about the rest a day now but
he does - he's not kidding around
right he means he's know he cares no one
can get anything else out of me I'm like
yeah but you gotta understand the people
that are struggling what they're going
through with you guys are how hard
you're working no one can get anything
else out of me but that that's pretty
much it there he goes again
you know I mean yeah because you know
what I mean
when you get kicked down or cut out from
underneath you you're driving back from
the doctor's your Hashimoto's diagnosis
and not me and you're you're reading
something and on the internet saying
your body's attacking itself your doctor
says your body is attacking somewhere or
you got a mommy and the baby's got
eczema and then there's there's no
answers and it's just you lose sleepless
night you get sleepless nights you get
all people are struggling and you know
what's it's it's even the stories in
that and you know oh yeah we got a care
you know we have to care and I always
say when I was younger six seven years
old spirit of compassion said to me
you're gonna have to care cuz you're
gonna have to deliver this powerful
message out there to change the world
because it's gonna be a lot of
misinformation out there in all kinds of
books and TV shows and everything else
about how to heal and it's all it's all
propaganda and then all backed by money
and all set up to people do whether it's
alternative or conventional not
everything but most of it and spirit of
compassion said you're gonna have to
have that compassion and care about
people because they're gonna be
suffering and they need the right
information so I stayed alive personally
you guys know I haven't had an easy
journey know at all and I stayed alive
to make sure you give you guys this
information they're actually those doing
a better job at getting information
anyway link your celery juice yeah
well people drink their celery juice
it's a process do the best you can and
then keep on keeping on well and be good
to yourself kind of to yourself yeah see
you guys listen to Scott listen to
Chelsea
all right signing off I love you guys
dearly okay click on I button here