right here gonna make the liver rescue
smoothie and that's what it does it
rescues the liver
medical medium tools do they do rescue
the liver because that's a big part of
why everybody's sick
um if you've got gout that's the liver
eczema psoriasis the liver
any skin condition in the liver vitiligo
the liver
and it just goes on and on and on i mean
there's so many different conditions
heart palpitations
the liver i mean you just should go on
and on and on and on liver liver liver
and that's a big part of why everybody's
sick
we walk around we don't know about it we
don't understand
we our liver needs a routine and it has
a routine but we
break its routine and then we break its
routine
and then we break its routine and that's
what we do and that's what happens to
our liver is we
break its routine all the time and then
we also
we also do a lot of stuff to our liver
that we don't know about we're eating
those hot dogs we're eating those
cheeseburgers
we're eating the bacon you know and even
if we're eating too many nut butters if
you're eating too many nut butters if
you're eating all that coconut oil
if you're doing like two tablespoons of
coconut oil because somebody told you it
was a good idea
and then what happens is that that
you're doing all that coconut oil and
then boom your liver is paying the price
for it nobody realizes it even though
coconut oil is
seemingly healthy right but we we end up
we end up um really burdening our liver
more and more
even though it's already burdened it's
already under pressure it's already
stagnant it's already sluggish
and the medical media morning cleanse is
to save it's really to help save our
liver at the same time but who cares
about the liver who cares i mean
you don't see it we don't feel it no one
cares about it so why should we really
care about our liver well
the weight gain happens that's the liver
right there
the minute the weight gain starts
happening you start putting on
unwanted pounds you know you start
putting on those unwanted
ounces and they add up and they add up
and they add
up and then you know we get in trouble
where all of a sudden we got we got an
issue there
i'm glad you guys are here i'm gonna
make lemon water then i'm gonna make um
celery juice then i'm gonna make the
liver rescue
smoothie i'm gonna make that
and then i might make some oatmeal too
so i might make some oatmeal as well so
uh
um so yeah so yeah so we're on
day two the medical medium morning
morning cleanse
challenge it's day two so that's where
we're at
um so uh lunell says liver rescue book
it's incredible it really changed
everything for me it's an incredible
book i have it behind me somewhere right
here
and that's the liver rescue book that
lunell's talking about it's an
incredible book it's a medical textbook
it's actually covers so many different
conditions so that's a book right there
but we're in cleanse to heal morning
challenges that's what we're in right
now
so this is also another incredible book
that's saving lives out there all around
the world
it's really exciting what it's doing and
the morning cleanse is
in this book of course and uh some
recipes too so i got the liver rescue
smoothie right there if you guys can see
that so
there's 75 recipes in this book cleanse
the heel
it's on sale at amazon right now 51 off
and there's even like a coupon you can
get so you can get this book for like 14
on amazon right now it's just it's
unbelievable
really and you can look go into your
local bookstore
and i'm sure there's also great book
stores that have it all around the world
and wherever you guys are go into your
local bookstore you can get a
medical medium cleanse the heal and um
but anyway we're doing
the medical medium uh morning cleanse
i'm gonna start out with some lemon
water right here talk about that
um so yeah
got some water right here
and i'm gonna look you know what you
guys i got limes right here so check
this out
i got limes so you can do
lime water you can do lemon water
you can do one or the other um
i switch it off myself personally you
know i'll do lime
then i'll do lemon then i'll do lime not
too lemon
so i'm gonna do lime today though
hopefully there's juice in the slime
sometimes limes aren't juicy at all
and there's no juice in them so
i'm gonna squeeze and sometimes they're
really juicy
this is a really juicy one so i'm really
lucky i'm gonna read comments too if i
can
um so the liver the liver rescue
smoothie is gonna be coming up i'm gonna
try to make
some oatmeal too if i have
sometimes a recipe and
cleanse the heel so i'm squeezing some
lime in the water right here
upon waking you want 16 to 32 ounces of
lemon or lime water okay that's
a half a lime right there i'm gonna put
a little bit more
so it's great great you guys are coming
on here incredible lime juice this
morning that's what you had megan
great great michelle
um lorraine's here a lot of people are
here you guys are it's incredible
lorraine says she's not keen on the
taste of lime i understand
understandable sometimes it's good in
guacamole though right
it's good and guacamole so um i just
made the lime water right here you can
do lemon if you want to
um of course but look i like to switch
it off like i was saying before
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water in the
morning when you wake up
because your liver has this routine and
we
break that liver's routine i'll talk
about how
so that's the water right here so what
happens is that
our liver has to work all night long to
keep our blood
clean so we walk around with dirty blood
all the time and i talk about that in
the past and you know what happens is
when we walk around with dirty blood we
end up getting dehydrated the toxins
build up in our system
they go back into our liver they get
sucked back into our liver
over and over again and our liver has
this routine throughout the night
which is really early morning where it
likes to package up all those toxins the
petrochemicals the plastics
um colognes perfumes that we might
breathe in they get trapped in the liver
air fresheners
uh scented candles they get trapped in
the liver all that gets in there
and our our liver wants to get it out
and then
gasoline at the pump at the gas station
we're breathing in the fumes that goes
inside our liver
antibiotics we might have taken years
ago maybe even recently
go inside our liver antidepressants
anti-inflammatories cold medicines all
go inside her liver thyroid medications
outside of liver
and you know so what happens is it all
adds up
and it adds up and then the toxic heavy
metals pesticides herbicides fungicides
rodenticides and insecticides all of it
um add up and they're built and they all
store up and store up inside the liver
the liver has this routine of wanting to
get rid of this stuff if you hear
somebody say
you don't need a cleanse you don't need
to worry about any cleansing there's no
reason to cleanse
who can you know your body does it
naturally just eat good
just eat a balanced diet just eat
healthy enough
you know just do that and your body will
cleanse fine
just so you know you're getting taken
down the wrong road
um that information is really just
it it's not gonna help anyone really
it's gonna set people back if anything
our bodies do need a cleanse because
we're up against so much and then
we're up against all the high fat diets
so a lot of people eat a lot of chicken
they
eat a lot of beef they eat a lot of
bacon they eat a lot of eggs
cheese milk butter nut butters
even avocado people i've i got a friend
who eats like 10 avocados a day
and it's just basically like eating
sticks of butter every day right and
okay sure avocados are a healthier fat
but the liver
still needs to cleanse and when we fill
our bloodstream up with fat all the time
our liver can't cleanse
so the goal is to
the goal is to actually give it a break
like allow it to do
its routine and not break that routine
so
when morning comes early morning comes
your liver's getting ready to pack up
all those poisons and toxins and get
them out
so you do 16 to 32 ounces of lemon water
to
flush that out out help it flush it out
of the bloodstream help it flush it out
push it out of the liver
and get it out of the body and that's
what you want to do in the morning
that's the goal
that's the key you're assisting your
liver
to actually cleanse and detox and that's
what you're doing
so with that said we usually
break that by we put we end up eating
some butter
we end up eating some nut butters in the
morning we put peanut butter in our
smoothies we put coconut oil in our
smoothies
and hey maybe we just do eggs in the
morning maybe we do bacon in the morning
whatever it is
whatever it is before noon when you have
those fats before noon those radical
fats i call them
when you have those radical fats before
noon
your liver shuts down boom it's just
shuts down
and it can't do what it's got to do
that's it meaning it can't get the stuff
out
and then the toxins float around in your
bloodstream float around in your
bloodstream and float around in your
bloodstream
and as they float around in your
bloodstream they actually get
caught up and they get stagnant in there
and they end up
they end up back into the liver is what
they end up
they end up back in and then we get in
trouble
so the point is is we want to make sure
the lemon water is there for you
first thing in the morning so that's the
first thing we're going to make some
celery juice that's the next part
you got to wait 15 to 30 minutes minimum
15 minutes to 30 minutes
before you have your celery juice we're
going into that right now i'm gonna
juice that
up here this is the next part of the
morning plants remember we're on day two
of the
day morning cleanse challenge um if you
guys don't have plans to heal you might
want to get a copy of cleanse to heal
[Music]
a little celery juicing
how are you guys the sound is gone
okay
let me know if it comes back
sound is gone huh
you only hear the juicer how do you hear
me now you guys hear me all right now
better better okay so maybe the juicer
is just right up against the mic
and i think that's what's happening
still vibrating though
sound problems still
so maybe the juicer was okay so it's
better okay great
so the juicer was covering the sound
[Music]
[Applause]
had the mic up against juicer so i'm
making some celery juice you guys
it's good now okay good now all right
everybody's happy
so are you guys doing the medical
meeting warning plans
it's a great way to really protect
yourself during the holiday
a lot of people have strokes heart
attacks during the holiday
and talking to a doctor and he said if
only
people were doing the medical medium
morning cleanse during the holidays
it would have prevented a lot of heart
attacks
a lot of people are on lots of salt and
fat in their diet
their blood gets really thick they get
dehydrated during the holiday
they're under stress and pressure right
and then it's just that perfect time for
boom a heart attack
and the hospitals talking to
an emergency room doctor friend of mine
and he said right now a lot of people
are coming in with fake heart attacks
they're coming in with real heart
attacks they're coming in with anxiety
attacks
panic attacks into the emergency room
some are real heart attacks some are
just
basically big big old panic attacks
which they call
fake heart attacks and it's it happens
at this time of year
and i like to think about this as being
a preventative
for a lot of people because when you're
doing your celery to
16 to 32 ounces of celery juice and
you're doing that
and you're doing your 16 to 30 ounces of
lemon water and you're doing the liver
rescue smoothie or the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie right
you're you're preventing all kinds of
calamity total
adversity and all kinds of problems so
it's really a helpful situation
so right now i'm juicing always know
that with this juicer you're always
going to use less celery
all celery changes as far as how much
juice i'm using two kinds of celery
right now
from two different batches couple of
sticks are juicier some sticks have no
juice in them
and it's not about how many sticks you
put in the machine
it's about how dry the pulp comes out if
that pulp comes out
bone dry like in this machine here then
guess what you get all the juice
and that's the key right there that's
the key and that means
out of any other juicer this juicer will
actually cut your celery costs in half
because you're getting every drop out
[Applause]
i think you guys know the model i've
talked about it so many times
um but i know that that might not matter
so michelle crane's asking how much
celery are you using
to get how much juice i mean
some bunches of celery have are very
juicy so with this machine you'll only
need like five or six sticks
seven sticks some are really not juicy
this is not a bat this is not a juicy
batch this is a really
skinny celery stick so i'm using about
for these 32 ounces of juice
i'm using one bunch of celery
actually probably a little less maybe a
little less
but um so
celery juice is
it's like a little a little miracle is
what it is
it's changing people's lives i love it
in the medical media morning cleanse
what it does it's just extraordinary so
i just used some celery right here and
what you'll see
is this pulp is bone dry it's a little
piece of pulp right here
that that is i've used so many juicers
this is just incredible
by the way for all this juice it's
really incredible
um
i'm gonna pour the celery juice down
there we go and there's still more
uh in the container
so i got the 16 to 32 ounces well this
is this is 32 ounces roughly
of the celery juice that's the second
part of the second step in the medical
meeting morning cleanse
really important to do if you don't have
celery you can't do celery
look do aloe water do the medical medium
aloe water do the medical medium ginger
water if you want these are different
options right there
that you can do so um but
right here i'm about to do the next step
and we're going into the liver rescue
smoothie is where we're heading into now
you guys
so i'm excited um so like i said 16 to
32 ounces of
lime water i got today you could do
lemon water
which is great 16 to 30 ounces of celery
juice i have right there too remember 15
to 30 minutes is what you want to wait
before you do your cellar juice after
your lemon water
and then you want to wait a little while
after your celery juice too so that's
what we want to do
so i'm going to move things around i'm
going to move the juicer out of the way
so that's where i'm going next okay
bear with me you guys
just gonna get this out of the way here
so i got the blender in front of me i'm
going to make the liver rescue smoothie
is what i'm doing next
know i love preventative but real
preventative stuff
not stuff like not stupid talk
preventative like
where someone says this supplements uh
scientifically
you know there's a scientific study that
vitamin a
could help prevent an eye problem or
something like that great
that's really not real preventative to
begin with
that's not like real serious move the
needle preventative like preventing
disease preventing heart attacks
preventing
chronic fatigue syndrome like really
understanding what causes illness and
really preventing because that's what
medical medium information is about
when you're doing medical medium
information like in cleanse to heal
you're doing what you're really doing is
you're really protecting yourself
and from from problems you don't even
know could even have been coming and it
happens to people all the time
they live their life then now they have
thyroid disease then they live their
life and now they have something else
and
and when you're doing some of these
things you're preventing that for the
future and if you have problems you're
reversing that and that's the key
so i'm in um medical medium plans to
heal
so i got the blender right here i got
the book in front of me you'll see the
recipe
right there okay and so just so you guys
know what's in the recipe it's pretty
simple
you can do merida papaya or you can
switch off and do bananas i'm going to
show you
here's the blender fried garden
so i got some pattaya right here half a
cup of pattayas what i have
so that's what that is dragon fruit um
it's frozen so you can get you can get
dragon fruit frozen
okay pattaya all right and you can even
do
two tablespoons of pataya powder if you
don't have the frozen dragon fruit i
don't want it to spill so i'm kind of
showing you guys just enough right there
there you go
so i'm going to put it in here
that's the dragon fruit i don't know if
you guys
you know some people love dragon fruit
some people don't know about it yet and
they haven't learned about it but
that's the dragon fruit right there
which is amazing too so
and then um you can do two cups of
frozen
wild blueberries you could do two cups
so i got this right here
so that's a big part of it too so the
liver rescue smoothie you got the frozen
wild blueberries
so you guys i don't know if you've had
these before many of you have they're
just they're really incredible
so i'm gonna put the two cups of frozen
wild blueberries in here you can put the
powder in two you can put two
tablespoons of the powder
but what i like to do is i like to do
the powder
and the wild blueberries just so you
know that's what i like to do
um i like to do them both because the
powder
this not not any powder but this the
vimergy wild blueberry powder
is so incredible it's like well if i can
get more of those phytochemical
compounds
more of those antiviral compounds more
of those
um those antioxidants if i could get
more of that then that's what i want
i want as much as i possibly can and
this is
really concentrated it's an incredible
product so i don't know if you guys know
vimergy but that's what this
is these in victor i am as in mary ergy
it's the wild blueberry powder so i'm
going to put some of that in there too
if you don't have the wild blueberry if
you don't know what frozen wild
blueberries you can go with this powder
i mean i've done it a lot of times i
don't have the wild blueberries
and i go with the powder and it's fine
that's what i'll do
so there's that right there i got that
in there
so um right now i'm gonna do the bananas
because i have these awesome bananas on
hand right here so i'm gonna do bananas
in my liver rescue smoothie
you can do merida papaya that's an
option right there
um i got bananas so what page am i on
i'm on page 298
of liver rescue i'm on page 298 it's the
liver rescue smoothie
right there this isn't liver rescue it's
cleanse the heel it's a liver rescue
smoothie right there so
and um you guys books
not only on sale on amazon but it even
has the coupon on there that i saw
you can literally get the book for like
14 amazon us
it's unbelievable so i'm gonna put two
bananas
in here which i'm doing now
um you know it's unbelievable when
people make fun of bananas sometimes in
natural health like oh bananas
whatever it's sugar when they don't even
know what causes illness
it's incredible that everybody can be
such an expert when they don't know why
anybody's sick
isn't that amazing medical medium
information changed the roles in chronic
illness because we had
we got answers for the first time in
history about why people are sick with
chronic illness isn't that unbelievable
how it works
and it had to come from above it's like
science of research for some reason just
can't find out why anybody's sick and
everybody's rolling around sick out
there
so i had to get the answers from bub
since i was a child i put it in the
books and people's lives are being saved
and
i love when people out there they'll rip
apart a banana or they'll rip apart
something and they don't even know why
everybody has lupus
they don't know why people have multiple
sclerosis they don't know why anybody
has eczema
and if they do spout out something it
comes from medical medium published
information they'll say oh it's the
liver now a god x mug that's funny
because
the only place that ever came from was
medical medium published information so
it's you know that will happen out there
because because all millions of books
got out there in the world but
when nobody knows why anybody got sick
or gets sick
and they're suffering and struggling
it's funny how they could be experts and
maybe tear down a banana or rip apart
something else it's
really kind of if you really think about
it it's just
yeah you're right michelle they'll just
say it's genetic that's not an answer oh
so our genes all went bad in the last 20
years
chronic illness is literally exploding
and our genes seem to all go bad in the
last 20 years
after thousands of years it just all
went bad interesting right
so yeah so anyway i just put the bananas
in here
so i got that you can add some water
into this it's optional in your
liver rescue smoothie got a half cup of
water
i put a half cup of water in there
that's fine right there
so that is it right there here it is i'm
going to blend it up that's the liver
rescue smoothie let's get this going
i love this smoothie
just made the liver rescue smoothie
right there
awesome i'm really psyched
so
you see that color in there right
see all the antioxidants anthocyanins
all that color in there
there's undiscovered antioxidants in
wild blueberries
undiscovered antioxidants in potatoes
they haven't even scratched the surface
food science knows nothing about foods
yet
and what's in here just as a decades
roll by
and if someone does do a study and they
really look
into these foods they'll find little
miracles in them
and it's really incredible so that is
the liver
rescue smoothie okay another thing after
another option if you don't deliver
rescue smoothie you can do fresh fruit
you can have bananas you could have
berries
you can do a whole melon if you want you
can do some papaya you can chop up some
mango and do some mango so you got all
these different options
so you guys if you just came on here i'm
in cleanse the heel we're talking about
the medical medium morning cleanse
that's it right there
and um right now i'm doing the liver
rescue smoothie
just an incredible incredible
healing tool medical medium tools are
vast
it's not just celery juice there's so
many different tools there's the
spinach soup which is a lifesaver
there's the mono eating cleanses there's
all these different tools a liver rescue
smoothie heavy metal detox movie all the
different supplementations and dosages
but there's so many different protocols
that you can make
work for you so it's not like hey i
tried medical medium it didn't work well
actually you didn't try medical medium
you tried maybe one thing or maybe not
even that and then you said you tried it
so
but really trying it means you you get
you and you really
uh it's comprehensive and you go into it
and you can find your way
and and see the other side and get
better and that's what mm info does
really incredible so that's the live
rescue smoothie you guys
all right and um you can do look you
cannot if you want something denser
something more meatier something that's
more packed
something that feels more satiated say
you're somebody that's used to eggs and
bacon in the morning right
even though it's it's good stuff the
good bacon people say
or with no nitrates or whatever it is
that you're into right
even if you're into something like that
and now you're like well how am i going
to get by with a smoothie in the morning
well then we can go with something a
little dense or steamed potatoes
steamed sweet potatoes we can do that
you can do some oatmeal some millet
some yams some winter squash but what
you want to do is you want to keep out
the radical fats you want to keep out
the
oils you want to keep out the nut
butters and nuts no peanut butter no
almond butter
you want to keep out the chicken the
meat the eggs the milk cheese butter
in the morning until at least noon
at least noon i'd go a little further is
what i would do be right there
just moving stuff over so i'm glad you
guys so here
we are so um i was thinking about making
a little oatmeal so i'm going to do that
now with you guys
so i got this little burner right here
it's easy to use
okay i'm going to move well i'm going to
hold these over here instead
so if you just got on here there's the
lemon water there's the celery juice
liver rescue smoothie i'll give you a
recap on that a little while
um so
i got the pot on right here okay
and um
so i'm going to start out with with the
oats look um
you got a couple options you got a
couple of options depending on how many
people you're feeding if it's just for
yourself if you're feeding your family
you could always double the recipe
triple the recipe you can go you can go
there i'm gonna do a cup of oats
so here's a bowl of oats right here i
don't know if you can see it with the
lighting or how it works there but
there's
there's a bowl of oats right there
and um
so you put a couple of oats in here okay
it's about a cup a little bit more than
a cup that time
i'm gonna put two cups of water in here
and i got the burner on
so there you go i got the pot
a cup of oats two cup of water so and
then i'm gonna add cinnamon
right here so
depending on how much cinnamon you like
some people don't like a lot of it some
people like a little bit of it
you know i mean half a teaspoon is what
i do usually
you know i've measured it a lot so half
teaspoon is really it's just
about four taps for me so i just put the
cinnamon in there i don't know if you
can see that without it there you go see
the cinnamon on top
right so i put the cinnamon in there
gonna mix it up
got a little wooden utensil i don't like
using metal utensils if you're gonna do
any cooking
because your metal utensil is just going
to scratch scratch scratch scratch
scratch
i'm mixing it up and then i'm going to
cover it and get it to a simmer
get nice and hot these are rolled oats
they're gluten-free oats
i know you guys want the gluten-free
oats right
now you can have the maple syrup you
could add the honey to taste to think
about that
that's the option there honey or maple
syrup
so i'm going to make sure i have mine on
hand
so you guys i got these got these
cooking right now
so i got the heat on them so i don't
know if you can see it i'm gonna move it
into the
try to get it into the frame
so this is a recipe that's in cleanse
the heel i'm gonna show you what the
recipe is
this is the wild blueberry porridge is
what this is
so i don't know if you guys can see that
this is in cleanse the heel you guys
don't have a book i mean
now's the time to do it if you're going
to jump into it because
cleanse the heel is beyond dirt cheap on
amazon.com us
right now it's just it's actually
ridiculous it was 16.99 and then there's
a coupon
from what i saw when i looked at it on
there this morning i was like whoa
so this is the wild blueberry porridge
already this is this is cooking up
hopefully you guys can see over
there i'm going to stir it a little bit
what you do with the medical medium
morning cleanse as you bring in 16
ounces of
coconut water sometime in the morning a
little later
16 ounces of water is an option you can
bring in a little bit later
so you can do that too
i'm just stirring because
it's what you do it's coming out so nice
right now i love the smell of cinnamon
i don't know about you guys but i really
love it
and
cooking that up so let's do a recap
while the oats are cooking while the
wild blueberry porridge is cooking so
i'm making that the wild blueberry
porridge if you just got on here
all right this is cleanse the heel you
guys and this isn't just a recipe book
there's 75 recipes in here
yeah but there's cleanses in here
there's uh
so many medical medium tools if this
book is studied
and used properly someone can get
anyone can get to the finish line with
their conditions
the opportunity is here people are doing
it around the world
um the book's designed like that it's
designed to get
someone to the finish line you know
thyroid problems
eczema psoriasis the list goes on i mean
it's designed to get
people to the finish line that's how
it's done
spirit of compassion writes the books on
the messenger i put the
the words to the paper but
these books are just incredible and this
one right here is just
is a whole another level so i'm going to
lower the heat
this is done
depend uh depending on your consistency
that you like
with your oatmeal okay um i don't like
it creamy watery i like it thick
i don't know about you guys
so i got a bowl right here i'm going to
scoop it out
now you can do a couple things what i do
is i put it in my bowl then i put
blueberry wild blueberries on top
you can mix it in right in here too so
you can do that you can i'll do you know
maybe in on ig i'll do a different
option
but you can add them in the oatmeal
right here so i got some
frozen wild blueberries and i'm putting
them in
right here
and you could mix it in here a little
bit
like that
sometimes i like just also putting them
right on top
so i'll do either or but this is just
looking so good this is the wild
blueberry
oatmeal right here the porridge
so they're mixed in there
moving this over
okay and then i'm gonna actually put a
few more wild blueberries right on top
is what i'm gonna do
so there it is there's the oatmeal
then of course i have the maple syrup
right here now i'm going to put a little
maple syrup on top
now you can do it to taste so i'm
putting a little bit on there
maybe i'm putting a little bit more
can't help it
so that's the wild blueberry
porridge and um
it's steaming hot the oatmeal trisha
marie says it's beautiful
yay amazing and
but it's really incredible i mean
honestly it's just incredible you got a
little bit of the cinnamon in there
you got the frozen wild blueberries that
were mixed in there
and then you got some wild blueberries
put on top that's how i like to do it
right
and then you put a little maple syrup on
top you can do this with millet too
that's the other option you don't have
to use oatmeal
for you know but for the most healing in
the medical medium morning cleanse
try to even just do fruit up until noon
you know you do the
lemon water right here 16 to 32 ounces
first thing in the morning upon waking
flush that liver is what you want to do
okay and then 15 to 30 minutes later you
do the celery juice
right after that okay 15 to 30 minutes
later minimum
you do the celery juice 16 to 32 ounces
of celery juice
can you imagine how much healing is
already happening inside your body
with that alone 15 to 30 minutes later
you got the liver rescue smoothie i just
showed you in the book if you just got
on here
then you get the liver rescue smoothie
that's in cleanse the heel
and that has the pattaya that has the
wild blueberries you could watch this
again too
the video is saved okay and
then you know you do some fruit that's
the most powerful way of doing you could
do a fruit bowl you can chop
some bananas and mangoes together you
can do frozen mangoes but
you can also do yes the oatmeal for sure
this is the oatmeal this is the blue
wild blueberry porridge a little maple
syrup in there and cinnamon cinnamon
you guys i'm heading over to ig that's
where i'm going next
i love you guys we're in the day two of
the medical medium morning challenge
after ig i'm going to tic toc letting
you guys know i hope you come with me
all for the ride
um two o'clock pacific five o'clock
eastern i'll be on tick tock
i'm heading over the ig uh ig now so i'm
heading over there soon i'll see you
then
love you guys and keep up all the good
work