e
let's go come up through
here all
right let's go
we
ready we got
sound we got sound check one
two thank you thank you nice
all right
welcome
incredible we got some fun in store for
you guys we got amazing speakers I'm
going to come back up multiple times all
right so it's going to be great but I
just want to thank everybody because I
know how hard it is to just get here
especially so many of you that have gone
through so much in your life I know that
there are a lot of people here that
healed and because they healed they were
able to travel and get
here it's going to get I'm going to
start
crying I Gotta Laugh got to get a laugh
going here uh get choked up so and I
know how hard so many of you guys worked
believe me it doesn't come easy it
doesn't it's hour by hour for many of
you minute by minute right for many of
you I know okay
so many of you guys were in a situation
where you felt hopeless you didn't know
if you were going to heal you didn't
know you know the the next bit of
information or Trend out there or
whatever it was that you can find or
biohack you guys have been through hell
and back you've risen out of the ashes I
know so many of you guys have risen out
of the ashes am I
right yeah and if anything you're
keeping your yourselves healthy taking
care of yourselves it's a big deal I
know how hard you worked and I just want
to thank you I know people have come all
over the world to be here I mean it's
unbelievable Taiwan Germany Australia
Austria it it's incredible the
UK and I want everybody to know that
truly truly I am grateful and I don't
use that word lightly I do not okay I
really am grateful for all of you and
I'm so excited I want to sign some books
and um I'm going to come back up here
again don't worry we're going to have
some fun we might even do some other
stuff too that we weren't really
planning on so it's going to be really
really good really
good really
good and uh you guys seriously to get
here this is a very very incredible
moment in time I I I am absolutely Blown
Away
just blown away all right so let me sign
some books we'll get going anyway I love
you guys
you
[Music]
the
e
e e
the
[Music]
is
on for
okay thank you thank you I want to but I
can't thank you
so hi Anthony just a backup cuz we only
have one can you sign here the T-shirt
[Music]
please I thought you miss your arm I'm
so sorry with that marker oh my God
my on his shirt shirt anywhere you want
just put a little a right here in his
shirt okay
okay thank you so
much your
arm love
you want want to give you stickers
stickers
stickers brother here please be careful
table
pict sorry Sor love you guys love you
guys
ours this your book I think it is oh
it's yours
sorry okay thank you for being here
okay you know means the world to you to
hear that okay thank you so much I can't
I can't get enough of that believe me we
appreciate you thank you you know God
bless you bless love you love you can't
wait to keep watching you thank you
folks trust me I I'm honored truly no
pictures thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank
you oh
your thank you
so thank you so
[Music]
okay be good thank
you a bless your heart thank you for
coming okay hang out today and oh my God
a p oh my God it's so adorable little p
they mean the world to me puppies thank
you they're always puppies aren't they
yeah always he means the world for me
thank you so much Anthony you're welcome
you're welcome
thank you so
much I really appreciate
being
truly a thank
you oh man I love you too bro I do okay
one my heart to know
[Music]
that for
coming the
best oh
thank you so much oh you came from far
away yes from Germany oh my God I know I
know I can see I saw the
book oh thank you okay thank
you oh hey you got a permit marker on
that one that's
great thank
you thanks for coming ser
far from Germany oh my God I just can't
believe it seriously thank you for
coming means the world to me okay thank
you
Anthony oh my gosh that's awesome
perfect yeah that's a good one
there left no way that's yours oh my God
I'm honored I can't believe
it well I hope you stay for the rest of
the
day by thank you
[Music]
thank you so much you know thank you
okay that's really what it
is you save my son's life thank you for
believing in me okay that means the
world to
me yours oh wait that one's
here oh my God that's yours no way
[Music]
good to see
you oh my God the only other I know how
are you doing I'm good how are you
amazing thank you I know
you thanks
[Music]
Rock
buddy thank you
m is here mm is here third person Set Me
Free of a prison you Anthony God that's
all that counts that's all that counts
it's all that matters is that you get
better
I love that book that's the
original I can't believe you
[Music]
have thank you okay we love
you and we appreciate you thank you
Anthony God bless are so cool is that
mine God thank you thank you please read
it
trust me I will read every single thing
I promise okay thank you for the love
I'm looking forward to it thank you for
being here okay
seriously thank you for such an
Inc oh my God I'm H you're going to make
me cry I'm doing everything I can hold
back tears today all my mind I know I'm
going to
fail thank you for
being oh my God bless your heart
thank you so
much here
amazing that that's your thank you so
much yes oh my
God thank you for everything thank you
for traveling right the world thank you
so much I found you in my desperate
attempt to get pregnant oh my God still
working on it just don't give up give
upk always more to do always more to do
thank you you he my daughter here today
so thank you so
much thank you for
coming
experience what is that a picture for
you oh my god start drinking salary you
want me to have this or do you want me
to sign in
for me I will keep
it
thank thank you so
much we brought you a gift so you'll get
that I can't wait two gifts I can't wait
looking forward to it
seriously thank you so much
we all love
you what's this you got some books for
me what's going on here come all the way
from Australia oh my God we wanted to
say thank you for respect respect all
the way from Australia that's a
flight thank you for coming truly and
I'm coming here long thank you so
much follow your book please follow your
book to the counter please you got some
notes in
[Music]
here no pictures
you can away from New Zealand New
Zealand yeah love you oh my God
that's
than thank
[Music]
you please
Inc Absolut
Inc no way no way than you I appreciate
you oh this one's oh these two are mine
I'm sorry okay
[Music]
book have my book Thank I'm so nervous
thank
you you got a shirt oh thank you down
[Music]
you oh my God are you
kidding book
book you
beautiful very nice nice to meet
youant Sharpie
or step aside what you done
pleas pictures no
pictures no
pictures got keep moving ma'am keep
moving Anthony it's sunshine and
cilantro I thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you so much love
you I feel the same
way thank you
[Music]
step up please step
up step up with your R please it happens
really
fast oh my God
[Music]
favorite thing all your items to the
left please thank you
[Music]
oh my
God having you
here oh my God this is yours yes it's
for my friend Dana thank you you're
welcome
[Music]
you want the front or this who's this
that's for me you want the front
[Music]
or mine yeah hi Anthony thank you you
saved my family my whole life going to
make going to get me choked up life
changing Foods is for my friend
Catherine she's too sick to come could
you write her name tell her send my love
my love
please thank you Anthony thank
you I'm Kelsey thank you very
[Music]
much than you
Kel says thank you for my
sanity get it back Anthony thank you
can't
believe your book
[Music]
awesome I'll take any c you got I'll
send some thank you I pleasure to meet
[Music]
you have very
follow your item okay follow your item
please you got everything yes I'm
missing one another chance thank
you want me to thank you so much that
saved my life I'm honored truly that's
all that matters thank you so much for
everything all that matters if you get
better okay keep on working on it
okay hi it's my music I'm oh my God
incredible
[Music]
for I will
no way no way the new edition I love
that book thanks
aw thank you being here thank you my
brother thank you for taking trip okay
absolutely thank you so
much folks we need you to keep moving
please hi Anthony how are you hi SE
thank
you good to see thank
[Music]
you somebody want to say
hello say hello hello
hello you're taking care of
yourself huh you know I love you
right thanks Anthony day at a time love
you brother
[Music]
hello thank you for what you do the same
way you okay you're working on
stuff so I'm proud of you thank you the
words
from are in these books thank
you
amazing hi
Anthony oh my God you someone said it on
a live and I'm like I'm doing it oh my
God such an honor to be here I just did
a live interview really
yes thank you thanks for having us you
have no idea we so we're all so happy I
am are
[Music]
you I know I know you
are I just wonder if you can sign
in A's going to come off I'm going to
try to save it thank you so much thank
[Music]
you my birthday
today
you thank you
[Music]
so thank
you all right come
on what you got something to give to him
oh my God is this your book these are
yours I am honored I can't believe
you're here oh my God that's your book
I'm blessed truly
[Music]
truly Qui question how going be service
you thank
you in any
way if you can find somebody you know
one of the staff let them know okay
your thank you my
trity yeah she's my best friend oh my
God worry I love her okay I will she
knows that
thank
you here we go thank you for coming okay
yeah is this yours yeah that's mine
awesome
[Music]
the world toight that's why I exist why
I
[Music]
live we love you so much thank you thank
you you guys seriously I'm
honored thank you we have a car for you
way I just want to tell you thank you
because I'm one of those Mas who
struggled a lot oh no you made a big
difference oh no you got their whole no
one understands no one out there unless
they've gone through it thank you so
much you made a huge difference in the
world thank you thank you thank
[Music]
you thank you thank you thank you came
down you're doing
it hey my man you deserve the Noel prize
thank you thank tell how we can be
upheld okay you got it Andor you're here
okay that right oh my God oh my God the
is amazing that's incredible L thank you
take care that is amazing bye bye bye
this your
than is your hand falling
off not yet I'm lucky I'm lucky thank
you thank you guys thank you hi a love
you it's my original I had to bring it
my
baby amazing thank
you love you can't say it enough oh I
got a double sign hi
Anthony thank you you guys am love love
thank you thank you thank
you e
God bless you take that
trip that's me that's all that matters
want to come and you got your life back
it's all that matters thank you is this
yours
thank you thank you thank you so much
love you're
welcome
yeah oh I I got the cover that time
she's
doctorr really you're a doctor oh my God
what kind of medicine do you
practice oh my God find the staff find
the staff
and give them your number please thank
you than you thank you
Anthony nice love
it nice to meet you how are you nice to
meet you too thank you foring this is
incredible see I can find a little spot
on
here how are you how are you good to see
you no pictures no pictures move the
wall okay no pictures
amazing thank you for coming okay thank
you sorry to mess up your cover it's
okay a grippy table
table thank you yes thank you yeah thank
you
oh well yeah it helped me thank you I
see an emotional
dog you know to give you emotional
Comfort oh my God I love dogs so much
life so you have no idea listen and tell
you what that means okay you mean
everything to me get choked
[Music]
up I'm trying to not cry
myself you guys are amazing you made the
trip you made the trip okay mindblowing
that you made the trip by the way we
both came from Denmark
mm love you got
Germany oh bless you thank you for
coming that's a long
trip
incredible hello morning thank you for
everything thank you so much you guys
you guys are definitely my heart thank
you love you guys j j j j I think we GNA
take a break in minute let these people
know know a break at at the end of
that J at the at the end of these last
people J yes
sir after these last people we're going
to shut it down for a little
bit it's okay when I do a photo no photo
oh you you you could have did it while
you were talking but too late
now I do it really quick thank you so
much thank you guys thank
you thank you thank you Sor cover
is this
yours good to see you
[Music]
thank you thank you for
coming love
you got one in there too no I don't know
what just happened that's not the do we
have a book problem
Molly she might have a wrong book I'm
not sure someone in front of her then
that's up there right in front of you
yeah go
check I think she ended up with a
different book yeah she caught him
though she got I just want to say thank
you thank you seriously thank you for
being here okay and and truly truly
honored thank you so much yeah thank you
for your work so very much oh this is a
good spot here oh
that's my four-year-old self right
there can't believe I was 4 years
old I found it Anthony oh no this is it
that's it you don't mind I hit the cover
right there you go
you that's it that's it oh my God oh my
God bless your heart thank you thank you
for coming
Rebecca amazing
you want all together you want all
together
that's
[Music]
where e
good morning ladies and gents this is
you speaking we're going to bring the
music off a little later because we Pi
me for you so please please I make I
want to make sure you having a great
time here at this special event and I
also want to make a little announcement
for everybody guys I see that you
brought a lot of blankets here but
please be aware that other people want
to sit down as well so if you can put up
your blankets and just leave more room
for other people to enjoy the floor that
would be great you can still SE on the
floor but please put off your blankets
because they take a lot of space and
other people want to see and share this
wonderful experience with everybody once
again I wish you uh to have a great time
at this special event we're going to
bring you music up a little later and we
also going to have our speakers pretty
soon I should say 5 minutes or more or
less so please be ready for that ladies
and gents
[Applause]
hello everyone welcome to this wonderful
day excuse me we're going to get started
with our speakers we have a lot of
amazing people who are going to be out
here speaking today creating this space
we're so happy that you're here thank
you so so much our first speaker is
Kelly
Newman she is the writer director and
producer of the 2017 awardwinning
featurelength document
heel all right so we're g to just bring
her on up Kelly if you want to get on
the stage I'll hand you this
mic areful
that e
ACC be definitely the
besteller um so Anthony came to I love
the story of meeting Anthony because I
was making
the back
201 you haven't seen it yeton
a moment of disappointment but she she
offered me um Anthony she said you need
if you're going to New York you need to
meet Anthony William Kelly broen and
Kelly Turner and so she said no but it
led me to Anthony and two other
brilliant people that made the film as
powerful as it is so I just I love that
story as a reminder that you know
sometimes you get a know in life but you
know rejection whatever you want to call
it is God's redirection and protection
so what a
[Music]
gift um and that brings me I I kind of
just wanted to review speaking of Kelly
Turner she did if you don't if you're
not familiar she was um the researcher
who wrote the book radical remission and
she was
so blown away by the possibility of
spontaneous healing and she was not she
was wondering why nobody was
studying how those people healed they
were kind of just dismissed in medicine
as as anomalies and she's like but
there's there's so many of them she kept
thousands and thousands so she studied
she made it her research project project
and she studied like 1500 people that
healed from cancers they were told they
were not able to heal from so these were
Radical
remissions and she discovered that they
did they all did 10 things consistently
to heal that helped them heal and so she
shared those things as the back when I
made heal was only nine but then she
added movement because they all did some
sort of movement or exercise so it's now
10 things and I want to just read them
to you to remind you because I don't
think that this just applies to cancer I
think it applies to all chronic illness
in mystery illness um and the
fascinating thing is out of those 10
only three of them are physical so 30%
is and the rest are mental emotional and
spiritual and so let me read them
because don't want to forget all right
so the first one is radically changing
your diet
which obviously the medical medium
information is going to help you do
thank god um thank you Spirit of
compassion and the second one is using
herbs and supplements the third is
movement exercise and just moving your
body so those are the three physical and
then it goes on to taking control of
your health we've got to take our power
back when it comes to Healing um the
fourth one
is following your intuition which I'm
going to talk a little bit more
about um then releasing suppressed
emotions increasing positive
emotions embracing social support we've
got an amazing Community around
us it's it's proven to help when you
join cancer I think cancer survivors
that joined um support groups are like
50% more likely to heal so Community is
is massive um deepening your spiritual
connection and having strong reasons for
living so those are the essentials that
people that spontaneously healed or
healed when they were told they couldn't
all did I think those are important but
I wanted to talk a little bit about
intuition because you know so many
people back when I met Anthony he was
still reading for
people and you know I I seek out
intuitives I seek out healers and you
want that validation you want that
support you want that feedback from
people that have exceptional gifts but I
think the time has come now to really
hone your own instrument because our
bodies are so brilliantly designed we're
tuning Forks to the Divine we're all
little fractals of the Divine and
healing you know the root word for heal
is actually wholeness
and you know we are whole spiritually we
are whole and perfect Divine beings and
we come into this Human Experience and
there's some distortions that come
through um and so healing is is is
remembering your Divinity
and I feel like now in is a time in the
world where we're inundated with so much
information obviously there's a
frequency change frequency is rising
there's a lot of pressure on the planet
and it's pressure to release our own
gifts
and so I know yeah so what I'm trying to
say is that our bodies are brilliantly
designed to be our biggest Aly in this
you know we're Spiritual Beings in this
human body and we all have even though
Anthony has a spectacular amazing gift
that is helping Millions access the
healing
within we all have our intuition is the
strongest Truth for ourselves so now is
the time to hone that instrument and
it's okay to get feedback from other
people to
strengthen that um confidence in your
own
wisdom but with like the rise of AI and
this artificial intelligence that is
amazing in so many ways it becomes scary
when we lose our discernment of what is
reality and what's true truth and so now
is the time to hone our own gifts and
tune in to our own intuition because
that is what's going to guide you on
your journey and to your truth and and
our bodies are designed to give you that
feedback but we need to cleanse our
instrument in order to um hear those
messages clearly and so that's why we
have to do the heavy metal detox and
release depressed emot
and do all these healing things and I
think um I just want to remind people of
their own gifts and to access them we
have to keep our instrument as clean and
pure as possible so that we can receive
those
messages to guide us on our way um and
you all have that ability in you that's
how brilliantly and beautifully we're
designed
[Applause]
[Music]
so um
yeah and let's see I think we're GNA
bring up Coya now to guide us through
one of those healing Essentials
breathing and moving our bodies which is
another way to get that instrument clear
and high vibration change the frequency
so that we can connect and get those
Divine downloads to guide us on this
amazing journey called life
[Music]
thank you thank you okay now we are let
me uh let me just tell you about Miss
Coya web our next amazing
speaker I think that's better it's
better than having that ringing in your
ear okay here we go Coya Webb is a
renowned holistic health coach a yoga
instructor entrepreneur and author she
is the founder of get loved up and
lifestyle design to LIF style Brands and
communities promoting holistic health
and wellness Coya is known for her
expertise in Wellness yoga Fitness and
plant-based nutrition and has inspired
many through her workshops Retreats
certifications and online courses she
authored the book let your fears make
you Fierce which provides insights into
overcoming challenges and living a
balanced and healthy life coya's work
emphasizes the importance of self-love
well being mindfulness and sustainable
living so let me see if I've got Miss
Coya right
here everyone Coya
web thank
you thank you all thank you all so much
wow y'all look good all right yes give
yourself a round of applause let's hear
it I need to know that y'all are
divinely aligned so when I say cleanse I
want you to say to heal
cleanse louder
cleanse all right all right we'll awake
hey so it's just such an honor to be
here to connect with you in community
we've all been through this journey
right of understanding who we truly are
and our personal power so I'm going to
go through a couple of exercises that
have helped me when I felt down when I
felt
oh yeah she lives a healthy life and
she's traveling the world with her
fiance and she doesn't have a care in
the
world but what they don't know is that I
experience High functional
depression what they don't know and this
is my first time sharing publicly was
years ago when I got my blood work done
I found out I was I had Lyme disease and
I was fine I look just like I look today
I had no symptoms but it came up in my
blood work we are all in a very toxic
World we're breathing in that every day
so it's important while a lot of us see
the symptoms some of us are experiencing
things we have no idea about until it
hits us like a ton of bricks so I stand
with you not above or below but with and
I truly think in community
is the way we heal the best and so this
practice I'm going to do with you is
something that I do before every single
meeting and it start with the breath
because breath is spirit and it's our
free tool that we have to regulate our
system and even if you're on your
hospital bed you can breathe to connect
and to start the healing process are
y'all down to that with
me all right so everyone who can I
invite you to stand to your
feet yeah we're going to get some
movement in because we're it's going to
raise our vibration it's going to raise
our energy we're going to inhale through
the nose and we're going to let an
audible sigh out of the mouth just a
little bit of breathing just breathing
take a deep
inhale exhale sigh it
out Breathe In
Love exhale
fear breathe in
peace exhale
chaos in
inhale and exhale you might start
feeling energy moving move your body a
little bit you're like yeah that feels
good yeah we are alive we are living
beings we're meant to move and smile and
laugh even though we go through those
moments when we can't get off the couch
and can't be happy so if you want to
laugh you want to yell at any time I
invite you yes yes yes fully expressed
fully expressed fully expressed
absolutely because that's the way we
release fear that's the way we release
trauma that's the way we release lower
vibrations that don't serve us right all
right so the next thing we're going to
do is like an energy release it's a
somatic practice we're going to inhale
bring the arms up if you can and exhale
bring them back behind you
inhale exhale inhale love exhale fear
inhale exhale any negative energy you
experience on the way here at the
grocery store maybe on the drive we're
going to release that right now because
when you release low vibrations what do
you do you align yourself with the
highest and most powerful version of
yourself from that place you can heal
she's doing it with the dog that's what
I'm talking about one more time inhale
and exhale Let It Go all right now move
around dance around dance around dance
around all right now we can relax a
little bit right did that feel
good all right awesome so what I love to
do is really start with these six areas
of well-being the first area is
spiritual well-being right and for
Spiritual well-being that's how we
connect as Kelly said to our divine self
when we are well and we are connected in
Divine Alignment with our source we get
the Divine downloads to heal and all of
us are unique some of us more powerful
than others because we've tapped in a
lot like Anthony I mean give a run of a
for Anthony y'all he does a lot of
incredible work despite being ridiculed
despite being touch I'm going to need
you to be a little bit louder because
it's not easy it's not easy to lead this
charge it's not easy to do this work and
it's not easy to keep going when
everywhere around you no matter how much
good work you do you're being turned
down so I just need to give him his
flowers while he's here and rushing out
and now I want to give you your flowers
give yourself a round of applause for
showing up for standing in line to
buying those smoothies to doing
everything you needed to do to get here
this is called celebration there's a lot
of crazy things going on in the world
but one thing to spiritually align is
gratitude gratitude for your life
gratitude for your family gratitude for
your community and gratitude for our
leaders so give yourself another round
of applause because you've been through
a lot to get here you're here
shining when you are well the world is a
better place to be when you are well
your family is well and so long we're
like oh put yourself last when did we
start that why did we start that because
we all know when you are well everyone
around you is well so raise your hand if
you're going to commit to prioritizing
your
well-being I don't have everybody yet
raise your hand if you want to commit to
prioritizing loving on yourself first
and most because you know when you love
on yourself everybody else benefits all
right put your hand down all right so
that's spiritual well-being just really
activating through the breath through
movement so you can Divine a line
despite what happens to you so whenever
you're frustrated on this journey on
your journey home remember your tools of
breath to regulate your nervous system
bring you back into that parasympathetic
alignment so you can rest digest and
come back to love every single time I
was on Kelly's podcast yesterday and we
were talking about heated stuff and we
were both energetically charged and
she's like oh I didn't want to end the
podcast this way I was like cool we'll
change it right now and we went into
breath and we left on a very high note
so you can do it just like that right
but sometimes it's not easy sometimes
you need to move sometimes you need to
shake sometimes you need to take herbs
and supplements that help you come down
and come back to your truth but remember
your tools every single time cuz no
matter how far you get in your healing
Journey because we live in a toxic world
you need your tools to stay healthy all
right the second is emotional regulation
and emotional well-being how many people
know how to regulate your
emotions okay that's less than 1% all
right so we're going to work on that so
the first thing I want you to do is
think about how you feel place your
right hand on your
heart and I invite you to close your
eyes or gaze down at the ground if you
you feel safe if not do whatever feels
good to you now take a deep
inhale and exhale sigh it
up another
inhale and exhale side it
out if one
word could describe how you feel right
now what would that word
be joyful okay love
peace life
light
hope
thankful yes yes
grateful yes take a deep
inhale and
exhale now I'm not an all rainbows and
unicorns type of person so let's think
about the last week if you felt anything
outside of love let's be honest about
that emotion too I'll start
frustration I got another one
overwhelmed what about you
fear
uhhuh anybody else anger
yeah anxiety
yeah depression yeah it's okay to
acknowledge when you're not feeling your
best it's okay to acknowledge when
you're not well because it's in that
acknowledgement that the healing starts
right if I never knew and never was just
doing this random activation with a
company I would have never known that I
needed to do some more things in my life
to improve my well-being even though I
felt good and then I just started my
fertility journey I found out oh you're
still low in DHEA you're still I'm like
what I feel great but the numbers are
telling me the truth right so I took
that frustration and took control of my
life and said all right I'll add some
more herbs and supplements because I
know how what that does for my
so remember don't feel alone if you feel
like man I'm taking like 15,000
supplements how many people are taking
like 15,000 supplements okay yeah give
it up for yourself because whatever it
takes to be well right and I can say
when I started to do these things the
spiritual wellbeing the emotional
well-being I feel better than I've ever
felt in my life shout out if you feel
better today than you've ever felt in
your life
and I know Anthony's a big part of that
for me and for you if Anthony's a big
part of that let's make some
[Applause]
noise yeah yeah because it takes leaders
like Anthony to help wake us up
inspiration is becoming in
spirit and not only is Anthony
inspirational but each one of you is
inspirational not by telling everybody
but that's good to but by
being the light being love choosing not
to curse that person out even though
they pissed you
off choosing love when it's hard
choosing love when it's sick choosing to
do whatever you need to do to be well so
next we're going to go into nutritional
well-being which what is your favorite I
want all of you to say it at the same
time I know it's going to be different
for everybody what is your favorite
medical medium book
y'all I'm hearing my favorite too
cleanse the heel okay let's say it
together what's your favorite medical
medium book The all right anyone have a
different
favorite lifechanging foods all of them
the first original medical medium I
heard all three of those that's great
but I think I there's a consensus out
here we love cleanse to heal and we all
love all the books because they're all
equally powerful in helping us go to the
next level so y'all AA so that
information in that book has helped so
many of my clients and my communities I
feel like I'm
forever no matter what going to support
and guess what we're all humans so guess
what humans aren't perfect right humans
aren't
what humans aren't what so I don't have
to be humans aren't what so I don't have
to be perfect yes so many times we feel
like we have to be perfect to be well no
we have to be perfect to be loved we
have to get everything right and if we
don't we go into this spiral of guilt
and shame and remorse no you don't have
to be perfect to be great you don't have
to be perfect to be well this is an
ongoing journey and I don't know anybody
and I've worked with and had some of the
incredible most incredible light workers
in the world on my podcast we've worked
together and I have not met one perfect
person now some people are close like
Anthony oh yeah you're welcome to sit
down if you want to sit down y feet y
feet feeling good y'all
okay not one perfect person right I had
y'all standing up forever see I'm not
perfect sorry but it feels good to just
own the fact that we all have some flaws
here and there and in our health Journey
we don't have to have it perfect
physically physical well-being is also
important where to be walking or dancing
or yoga
I want you guys to shout out what do you
do for a movement one two
three oh you know what I heard the most
dancing right yes how many people love
dancing yes dancing is one of the best
ways to move your body get that movement
in your joints and ligaments and also it
releases endorsement so you feel better
and you release the dopamine and you
feel good in your body so moving every
day even if you can't go to the gym even
if you can't leave lift heavy weights
just dancing around moving your body or
just shaking it's so good or if you're
just in your bed just you know moving
around a little bit is waking you up to
your true
self and then the next area of
well-being that I
teach is social well-being you all are
doing it now for being out here in
community we are not in this Jony alone
but sometimes when you're sick you feel
alone sometimes when you experiencing
something you never heard of before you
feel alone sometimes when you get a
diagnosis and they tell you you can't
heal you feel
alone but the truth is you're never
alone look around you look at all these
people still people in line just look
around make ey contact with
someone and tell them you are not
alone you are not alone my fiance just
looked at me and said you're not alone
that's why I love him yo give give my
fiance a round of applause
I'm
42 and there was a time in my life where
I gave up on love I felt like you know
what I've been dating the most toxic
humans and some of you might be able to
relate and I'm like you know what maybe
it's just not for me in this
lifetime but I had some healing to do
she's like don't put me out sis but it's
okay I feel you I'm with you
right but then I did some deeper healing
work
and I reached out to my mentors and my
leaders and I felt like I had a I had
some fatherhood trauma that I needed to
heal I had some experiences that
happened to me including assault that I
need to heal from and I did that work
and guess what we're getting married in
November thank you but it's because I
didn't give
up and I'm here to tell you not talk at
you but talk with you we can't give up
even though it's hard even though we
spilled a lot of trauma even though we
get a lot of hard diagnosis we can never
give up on love never give up on health
never give up on trying because you
never know when you're going to have
your
breakthrough you never know when your
health is going to go to the next level
and the last area of well-being I'm
going to talk to you about is financial
well-being how many people know finances
is
important yeah yeah but we don't talk
about it enough we don't talk about you
know what I'm not doing okay right now
I'm someone that came from humble
beginnings I was raised in a trailer it
was six of us we drank powdered milk we
didn't have much I never thought I would
be living the life that I'm living now
traveling the world working with some of
the most incredible people leading the
world I never thought that would be my
reality I feel like that's something a
life for someone else but I had this
desire in my heart and in my dreams I
saw myself speaking to crowds like this
and I was wondering like why do I keep
having these Visions why do I keep
getting these downloads of I'm supposed
to speak and help people
heal because it was my
path right and when I Surrender so if
you're getting those downloads listen to
them all of us have the opportunity to
receive the Divine downloads from above
and we all are unique and if all of us
are fully EXP rest and well guess what
we are all a part of the healing of
humanity if you believe that give me a
round of
applause yes you are a part of the
healing of humanity and you being well
is
important you being healthy you being
energized and the work that anony is
doing in these books is important
because we all have to be well so that
we can fight the
darkness yeah give yourself a round of
applause your well-being will take
Humanity to the next level a lot of
people ask what can I do I feel helpless
help
yourself help your family help that
person right next to you that is what
you can do and big things if you could
do those those are great too but don't
take for granted the small things that
you can do that make a big impact you
guys thank you so much it's been such an
honor to be be with you to speak with
you everyone stand to your feet one last
time take your time but if we are able
to stand up let's stand up for those who
can't stand let's stand up for those who
are in pain let's stand up for those who
are being abused and oppressed right now
right and I got one more call and
respond when I say Anthony you say
William
Anthony
Anthony Anthony will and on three we
love you one two three
thank you so much I'm Kya Webb have a
good evening
[Music]
stop Yes
St I
[Music]
hey
everybody we have a very very special uh
our the man we're all here for is going
to come back on stage before he signs
some more
books um
so um I'm just so excited to welcome our
amazing Anthony Williams back to the
stage yeah what's going
on all right no I'm busy right now yep
yep there's a lot going on uhuh what am
I doing I'm about to do a light blast
yeah you believe it I know I know all
right I got to go I got to go
[Applause]
[Music]
wasn't sure if I would be able to do it
but we're going to do a light blast
[Music]
[Applause]
okay all right I don't know if many of
you have actually experienced it the
last one I did publicly or live in in a
physical form was probably nine years
ago okay we've done them virtually many
of you might have experienced it right
have you
yep it's pretty intense but it's going
to be great it's going to be great okay
so since I was 4 years old Spirit of
compassion taught me about this light
that can come down if spirit and I are
communicating and this light can come
down so when I was a child I used the
light to heal
animals so if there was a baby bird with
a broken wing I would ask Spirit send
down the
light if there was an injured dog or an
injured
cat or an injured animal or a turtle I
would ask Spirit of compassion to send
down the light and then if I was driving
in the car with my family and I was in
the back
seat and driving by people and then
getting readings that people needed help
or their health was was in some kind of
condition where they were struggling I
would be in the backseat of the car 8
years old 7 years old and I would say
send the light down that's what I would
do and the spirit of compassion taught
me how to use this light and I've
learned how to work with spirit with
this and so what's going to happen here
is the light's going to come down and
it's going to hit the top of everybody's
head that's where it's going to
hit it's not going to hit their shoulder
or their arm or their hand but it's it's
going to hit the crown of everybody's
head here
and even going as far back from what
spirit's telling me even far back there
all the way there and in the line over
there
too okay think about what you want
better in your life think about what you
want healed in your life think about
where you want the light
directed where is it that you want it
directed is it your heart is it your
kidney right is it your
back is it a loved one too that's
somewhere else and maybe try to direct
it to
them but either way it's coming down and
it's going to hit the top of our heads
okay so what's going to happen is I'm
going to ask you to take a quick breath
you're going to hold it and then I'm
going to tell you to release and right
when we take that breath and hold it for
that second the light's going to come
down right on top of everybody's head
okay now this light
some may see it some may not a lot of
people do they close their eyes and they
see it a lot of people feel it
immediately you might feel tingles you
might feel a funny feeling in your body
you might feel even a little bit of Joy
pop up you might giggle but something's
going to
happen now this light's going to stay in
you for today and tomorrow and the
effects of it can even go as long as
weeks after after this and a lot of
people things change for them they their
their healing is
ignited because that's what it has done
for so
many there the reason why I don't do a
lot of them it's pretty intense takes a
lot out of me but that's okay because
this is the time to do it if there's any
time to ever do it it's now it's now
we're going to do it a couple of times
now A lot of people have blockages in
them they have emotional
blocks maybe they picked up some
negative energy not because they're a
bad person because they happen to be
around negative energy somewhere right A
lot of people have been misunderstood
you guys have been judged along the way
the medical medium crowd is the toughest
crowd though the toughest crowd there
is and it's the only heal Community
where people have come back from
wheelchairs they've come back from the
worst conditions they've risen out of
the ashes okay so I know you guys are
tough you guys are
strong think about where you want that
light directed inside your body and even
if for some reason you have it directed
to some place in your body like your
brain or your heart or your soul or your
soul anything can happen
when that light goes into us anything
can happen anything even if you say I
wanted to make my heart better that
light's going to run through all of us
now many of us have blockages like I was
saying before and it may take a little
bit of time to get the light all the way
through to everybody but there's a lot
of people here it's going to go right
through them right from the top of their
head down to the ground but a lot of
people it's going to get stuck somewhere
some people it's going to get stuck here
some people it's going to stop here so
we're going to do it until Spirit of
compassion says enough people it went
through and down to the
ground
okay we'll see how we'll see how blocked
we
are we'll see how many emotional
blockages
okay definitely I talked to S so before
this event and I wanted that to happen
direct the light to somebody else okay
if you have to you'll still get it but
it's also going to go to somebody else a
little
bit okay so let's get ready we sit down
you can stand up you can sit down it's
whatever anybody wants to do whatever
you guys feel comfortable in
doing all right
so did you ever look up at the stars at
night okay and you get a good look at
the stars
right behind the Stars Behind the stars
is where this light is coming from
that's where it's coming from so
Envision that if you can for a moment
you know you can see stars you can see
the night sky right you've seen it
enough in your life to know that you can
go right back to that right
now so you envisioning that
right and it doesn't have to be perfect
you just see one star two stars you see
the sky that's where the light is coming
from but it's going to come down fast
and it's going to hit the top of your
head very quickly everybody take a deep
breath now
release okay we're going to take one
more deep
breath
release if there is a place inside your
body that you feel gets
stuck something gets
stuck whatever that word means to
you H have the light going there
whatever that is if you're struggling
emotionally depression anxiety if you're
struggling with
depersonalization if you're struggling
mentally emotionally if you think you're
struggling
spiritually if you have a lack of faith
or you're struggling with your faith
whatever it is or
hope have the light go there have it go
there okay we're going to do the first
light
blast what we're going to do is when you
take that deep breath I'm going to tell
you to hold it I'm going to yell light
while I'm listening to Spirit of
compassion and then we're going to
release get ready on the count of three
one two three deep breath in hold it
light light light
release lot of blocks a lot of blockages
it went through a few people but it's
going to it's going to take a little
time because you guys have been through
a lot in your life and it hasn't been
easy has not been easy get ready we're
going to take a deep breath
one two 3 well everybody take a deep
breath okay release release okay this is
going to be a
stronger stronger light blast we got to
start out with the smaller ones count of
three take a deep breath one 2 three
deep breath in hold it Light Spirit
light light now
release okay all right A lot of people
were cleared a lot of people would went
right through to the ground we still got
some more to do there's some tough ones
over here on the left and right in the
back there's a few tough ones but that's
good that means we're all going to get a
lot more
light be we're being it's good to be
grateful for the ones that are blocked
the
most we did this years ago one place and
everybody was just freed on the second
light blast and that's all we're going
to get a lot more and the count of three
deep breath and hold hold it 1 2 3 deep
breath in hold it light light light
light now release that's the third
one okay
now go back to where do you want the
light to go again get focused where do
you want it to go if you don't know
where it's going that's okay that's all
right if you don't know where it's going
but if you do know where it's going
think about it again is it going to your
child is it going to your reproductive
system is it going to your intestinal
tract because I know there's a lot of
people that suffered with colon issues
and intestinal tract issues here so many
of you have had gut problems is it going
there okay get ready count of three one
2 3 deep breath in hold it light light
light now
release okay great great half the crowd
is clear to the bottom we still got a
little bit more Spirit of compassion is
up ticking upgrading the light meaning
it's more powerful now we can we can
deal with it cuz we can acclimate we've
acclimated we're ready we're going to do
a quick one right now one two 3 deep
breath in hold it light light Spirit
light now
release all right how many of you guys
are feeling it what's going on okay all
right you're feeling it okay good good
how many of you guys are seeing it you
seeing it great great all right spirit
says now we got to do another one really
quick count of three one 2 3 deep breath
in hold it light now light light light
Spirit now
release okay now it's going to get
really intense I just want to tell you
guys all right look look at the sky
again in your mind with your vision not
now but look at the sky your in your
mind you see that night sky you see
those Stars this one's
coming from far away it's stronger it's
going to hit the top of your crown
faster we're going to do it get ready
count of three this is a big one one 2 3
deep breath in hold it light light light
Spirit now
release how many of you are feeling that
right
there
okay we have about a 100 people here
left where're has stopped in different
places here you feel it it stopped for
you right right around here that's where
it is okay you're one of them okay good
good I'm glad you're
here because we're going to get more
light because of
that all right let's go on the count of
three deep breath you're going to feel
this
one one 2 three deep breath in light
light light now release
okay a whole bunch more people are
cleared where is it now on you you feel
it it's down to your knees now yep you
feel it right okay you guys this should
probably do it right here this should do
it and we're going to try to get this
light as far back as we can down the
line you guys feeling it down the line
all the way
down okay there's a there's a stubborn
one way down there there's a stubborn
one down there spirit says okay but good
good good that's good get ready count a
three 1 2 3 deep breath in hold it light
now light come on down
release okay I felt that
one we got one more one more and
everybody's clear you're clear that went
down right your ankle right your ankle
[Music]
you've been holding on to some stuff
you've been holding on to a lot of stuff
you must be a very special guy a very
special guy truly truly okay okay get
ready get ready
okay and this is where the snow
blindness comes in but I'm going to have
to deal with it it's all good all right
fuzzy fuzzy fuzzy in my eyes get ready
this is the last one I
think thank you
okay
[Laughter]
[Applause]
spirit all
[Music]
[Laughter]
right okay get
ready okay spirit says we're ready all
right there's one over here here there's
one over here you still got your ankle
over here can't see you anymore but you
still got your ankle and there's one
somewhere back here get ready count of
three one 2 3 take a deep breath in
light light light now we're cleared
release definitely cleared definitely
cleared you're down to the
bottom amazing guys
amazing all right
all right I love you
guys I'll see you later I'll be back up
here you're coming back up you comeing
up thank you
a all
right thank you thank you so we're going
to take a little bit of a break just a
moment for um Anthony to recoup and then
we're going to start signing again so
get ready okay thank you enjoy en the
day hang out we've got a lot more to
come we have more
speakers it's going to be a great
day thank
you we're we're live streaming
this so hopefully people enjoyed it
love
[Music]
you make my
G you
[Music]
you my
Dre you make my dreams
[Music]
you make my dreams
upake
up I don't
want wake me up you
I'm me
[Music]
up yeah
yeah out of
hey everybody I'm sorry to stop the
music for a second um I just want to let
everyone know that you know the way we
set this program up anon's going to come
back on stage a couple times and that is
because we want everyone to have a
chance to be here okay so if you've if
you got the light blast and you signed
your book and you've got your merch we
really want to make space for everyone
to be able to come into the park and
have this moment with Anthony too
because right now there are so many
amazing people here that it's we're
getting some push back from around so
we're going to have to take the
umbrellas down we're going to be moving
people into the park so I just want to
let you guys know that's what's
happening so we're going to start the
book signing now um and then there's no
climbing trees or anything like that um
but um we're so grateful that everyone
is here but we do want to ensure that
everyone who has come out is going to
have an opportunity to be here with
Anthony so thank you all thank you all
I
[Music]
know
were
the
[Music]
back
my
f
back
[Music]
h
you
ladies and gents a little announcement
from DJ Maxx uh we found uh we found a
small back that was left on the chair
somewhere in the middle of the park so
if you guys lost your small back it's
like a purse Green
Collar uh mint colar I should say please
come to the DJ and pick it up
[Music]
Ang
oh
guys going going please thank
[Music]
you go ahead go
ahead thank you
right one more time we found the small
purse somebody lost small purse me
please uh go to the DJ we waiting for
you to pick it up and the second
announcement if somebody found a special
prescribed glasses please bring them to
the DJ sunglasses special
if you find them please let me
know that's the one that was causing all
that
step up please thank
you are
somewhere I think I think John already
de where's your car
please step up please
nice
also ladies and gents a little
announcement for everybody we are
filming testimonials right behind the
northern disable so please if you have
something to say something to share with
everybody and you'd like to record this
special
information please go to the behind the
Gazebo once again it's nor one the one
that is right next to the main entrance
of the park and please recorded the crew
is waiting we are recording testimonials
ladies and gents as well as interviews
that's why the music is down we want to
make sure we hear every single word of
every speaker thank you so much
spe
we got married inal
[Music]
I love priming thank you
book off
the all of
these guys guys
are you no
[Music]
come
got
move your foot thank you
bring the item up open to where you sign
please where'd you put
it okay thank
you oh my
God have to get there I have to I
have thank you thank you
[Music]
have your books open to you want sign
please have them open
do me a favor guys
Ming love you
[Music]
Anthony hi everybody this is a note um
for everyone in line we are only signing
one book at this juncture okay guys the
book you want to sign and that is the
one book that we're going to sign okay
that way anthy maintains his energy for
everybody for the rest of the day so one
book okay one book
Thank no more t-shirts no more hats one
book
only oh my God that's
amazing keep moving guys please guys
keep walking please one
only keep walking guys please thank you
one book only no hats no T-shirt guys
let keep walking
[Music]
please one B let's keep walking guys
please walking
please ladies and Gentlemen please keep
[Music]
walking getting away from us
here thank you for coming thank you
thank you
one book
only one book only one book
only do me a favor guys keep walk
got a
[Music]
book got to keep moving please thousand
of people behind
[Music]
you thank you very much
thank
you thank
you
down
street for you
[Applause]
[Music]
me
thank you
[Music]
understand
only one book
only ladies excuse me just let her go
and we'll get your bag
[Music]
Ladi can we help
you Mom
okay H up
please going please keep moving thank
you
[Music]
guys keep walking please keep
walking thank you
[Music]
all right everyone have to turn the
music one more time we recording
another paent with me I'll
you thank you
can I help you
Ma have a
great ladies and gentlemen keep walking
please keep
walking St
after ladies and gentlemen keep walking
please
[Music]
are you kiding without AES only love
love you man love you brother
good
good you want
break Joey go get some
water yeah solid yeah what are they
doing after
go do your thing you take 15 at
least do it do
iter Sher hold on where is
it um Dr Sher is a podiatric uh
physician um she has worked in the field
for many many years she has transferred
all of that study to get certified in
everything from uh you
know uh work all of the amazing healing
things certifications um and that is the
way she approaches everything she
doesn't treat just the symptoms she's
looking at the patient holistically she
is an amazing woman and without further
Ado Dr Sher green
so great to see you all here today um
this is quite the magical moment
especially after having like six light
blasts come through the timing couldn't
be perfect so I'm so so excited to be
here and I I really feel like this is
Cutting Edge medicine that we're
standing in right now with all the
information on all these books and I
know I'm preaching to the choir that you
guys all know that and and really feel
it um I really believe it's like in my
curiosity and passion for truth that led
me to be here on the stage today and I
know you're all truth Seekers yourself
um I'm just going to say uh my first
light blast with Anthony was back in
2015 uh in Connecticut and that was such
a powerful event and I'm sure some of
you might have been there um it was
quite the experience of feeling that
light and I had been studying with other
teachers at that time and other uh
experiences of energy and it was just
something so different and so incredible
um but um I just wanted to give a little
story about when I um when I came to uh
the airport to come here today uh I ran
into a family who actually called out my
name and said hey Dr shery Green and I
turned around and it's the Rini family
who I didn't know in person I only knew
them by uh Instagram name and they were
just it was so nice to when you feel
like you're in the middle of you're not
seen or you're not heard or or you're
isolated all of those feelings that you
know when you're doing something so
different than the rest of the world and
how important it is to meet the these
kindred spirits that show up on your
path and we compared food bags and like
how much food we were pcking on the
plane and to get here so that was really
fun and when I got here today and just
circled Awan and saw these smiling faces
and just this event today is just so
magical and I feel like I've definitely
waited a lifetime to be right here in
this position right now so
anyway um I do
I did write a speech out because I
really don't want to forget some
important points that I want to uh call
out today so bear with me
here there are a few moments throughout
our lifetime that truly take our Breath
Away allowing us deep reflection and
gratitude this is one of those moments
for me I am absolutely Overjoyed to be
here amongst this incredible community
of healing Warriors doctors and
practitioners who have journeyed from
near and far to show up today it took
some of you immense Faith courage and
perseverance to be here now celebrating
this momentous occasion Anthony Williams
very first book signing after an
incredible eight published
books and how fitting That We Gather
here at Awan also to launch the highly
anticipated heavy metal detox smoothie
on their menual
hopefully ushering in a new era for more
health food stores worldwide to follow
in their
steps as Anthony says it's truly
remarkable that we could all be here
today in this Sacred Space at this
moment in time there are no
coincidences for me being here
represents the Fulfillment of a long
cherished dream to transform our broken
medical system and reimagine the
landscape of healing
yeah absolutely no longer would those
suffering from chronic illness feel lost
their conditions unresolved and labeled
with no real answers in sight we have
real answers now the Pearls of Wisdom in
these books podcast lives and emails are
Priceless and not to be taken for
granted my life was forever changed when
I discovered medical medium information
in 2015 through a dear friend of mine
who was also also suffering during my
own healing journey to L to a heal a
list of disabling chronic symptoms I
just knew that this was something
extraordinarily special and different
from anything I had ever researched or
studied before and I had studied a
lot my first call with Anthony in 20 the
November of 2015 turned my world and
practice upside down in the most
beautiful and enlightening way with the
invaluable knowledge he has gifted us we
can now now perceive root causes like
never before I've witnessed incredible
healings unfolding before my eyes I
understand the profound workings of the
human body and spirit in ways I could
have only dreamed this is true deep
multi-dimensional healing of the Mind
Body and
Soul I personally have needed to stand
strong amongst the doubters naysayers
professional colleagues and bullies in
my own field as I know you all have
faced as well
the commonality for us is when the truth
is felt within we don't just back down
or walk away we can't it's an unspoken
drive from the heart spirit and soul we
need this Divine guidance to navate
navigate the incredibly complex chronic
illnesses we are facing today afflicting
our patients our families our friends
and
neighbors I pray more people open their
hearts and Minds to embrace this
information no matter how difficult the
lifestyle changes may seem and I pray
that practitioners across all Medical
Specialties find the courage to come out
of the closet and share these teachings
far and wide I pray the rest of these
sacred teachings to be to continue to be
revealed unobstructed we all deserve
true healing it is our
Birthright I pray this information stays
sacred and
safe and then passed on and on through
the generations to come that will need
this information more than ever to
ensure Humanity continues to thrive and
this planet is
saved Anthony from the very depths of my
being I thank you you have touched my
heart spirit and soul in ways that words
cannot fully
Express you are a profound gift to this
world and I am truly honored to know you
in this lifetime thank thank you for
your unwavering care your friendship
your mentorship your compassion and
tenacity and for boldly ushering in this
long awaited truth my life's mission is
to help carry forward your mission of
healing Humanity in this planet you have
my eternal gratitude and love thank you
aw and thank you to all that I've had
the honor of working with who have
touched my life personally it is all
extremely meaningful for me
blessings and love to all here and to
those of th us that are not here today
and in spirit we see you we hear you and
we feel you and we know you're here with
us today let's enjoy this light filled
event so that it carries us through as
we move forward together let's enjoy the
[Applause]
party thank you thank you so much
[Music]
radi
iary world
have
[Music]
to
is
good
[Music]
Ro
Thanksgiving dinner e
all right everybody let's welcome
Anthony back to the
[Music]
[Applause]
stage on
I want everybody to know that all the
proceeds from every medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie the proceeds that
go to me go to an incredible
Foundation Underdog
Warriors and I want to introduce you to
Liz
shabaria and have her come on
[Music]
up um Liz is an amazing human being
she's been supporting the medical medium
Community she's uh stood by medical
medium information through thick and
thin no matter you know the evildoers or
the naysayers or the critics or anybody
else she has
survived the time all the way through it
and just like all of you have seen the
value of this powerful information from
above and live
always wanted to do things for the
community and that's been your passion
and I always saw that in you and I
always knew you wanted to do that she
created a 501c called Underdog Warriors
have any of you heard of
that incredible and so the goal is to
get money into under Underdog Warriors
and that's what's happening with this
that's what's incredible so I thank all
of you for being here uh purchasing a
smoothie um it's just an absolutely
incredible and every penny that goes to
me instead gets directed directly to
Underdog Warriors so Liz I'll let you
talk and thank you for being up here
thank you for coming thank you so much a
do it's
incredible thank
you well I am deeply honored I never
imagined that I would be up here
speaking
and I just want to say a few things but
first I want to begin with my heart is
truly with everyone that wasn't able to
come
here for whatever
reason
and I just know that we all love and
care about you and know that you are in
our thoughts so that's what I want to
start off
with um thank you so Underdog Warriors
is a 501c3 not for-profit
Corporation and I am one of the
co-founders
so this
organization
began due to my own
experience
and I remember being in
and then in this small office and just
kind of walking back and forth and then
this idea came to me and it was one of
those things that felt like an Angelic
moment and that was it I felt that an
organization needed to be started to
help support people that didn't have the
financial means to support their healing
that was me for a very very long
time I didn't have the support I
needed I would watch people online make
their micro shock
therapies
and I didn't have the means to purchase
the micro to make my micro shock therapy
so I would watch people online and I
just knew that there would be a time
where I would have the opportunities
that I needed come my way and and to
feel better whether it was
physically emotionally spiritually just
to feel better in all in every sense of
the
way and so that's really how it came
about and Underdog Warriors was formed
the
name I'm not quite sure how I coined it
together but I just knew that we are The
Underdogs we are the people that aren't
seen out there that are held back that
our voice isn't
heard and that really doesn't come until
we come out of it but I've also learned
that during the process you do find your
voice and and that's what makes us The
Underdogs and we all know that the
chronically sick are always held back
and as a always puts it we're always
swept under the rug isn't that
true so many people go through this life
suffering not just
physically
emotionally
spiritually and Underdog Warriors is
there to help support those
people now
throughout the
years and especially this
year I have come through some big trials
and a lot of that is is shaping what
Underdog Warriors is and what it is now
and I wish I could say more about it
it's just it's a lot just know
that that my heart is there and I want
people to just feel
supported I
myself I stopped counting I made a list
I had over a 100 symptoms I still have
some symptoms but that's okay I'm in a
much much better place now and all those
years of suffering all those years of
being alone all of those years without
being
support in the end it all just makes us
who we do become and who we are and how
our voice develops
and so what I want to say
is and just to
emphasize Underdog Warriors is going to
be that
organization that helps support the
whole Community whether it helps to
support other organizations within the
community and the individuals so far
what we have done is we've
supported uh so we go through an
application process
and we have we announc that through
social media through email uh and VI and
our website and so what we do is we go
through this application process we
choose the
individuals uh that need that that may
need supplements and quite
honestly I would say that every single
individual that
applies needs
support up until now though we have not
been able to provide the
supplements vimergy supplements Wyman's
wild blueberry
juice uh other healing tools such as
medical medium a recommended uh what any
other supplement or even juicers Omega
juicers to people so we have bought all
of these items for people
and and here's the best part about it
there's so much admin work we have to do
and
behind the scenes so many things that
need to be done but the best part about
it is when our recipients get those
gifts and because they know the value of
them and they know how much how much
it's there to support them and their
healing
and and we for the most part people have
told us that they don't
feel that they are worthy
of receiving what I perceive to be just
a small
act and and that's the whole touching
part about it because there's a lot that
needs to be done behind the
scenes but I'm most grateful for those
moments and I wanted to share that with
you because that's what your donations
do we promise from our Inception that
every single dollar that would be
donated would go right back to the
community none of the directors up until
this point or anyone else have received
any
compensation and I'm very very proud of
[Applause]
that it's how it was meant to be and
it's how it will always be meant to be
and and that's one of that that's one of
the things that I just find the most the
most joy in I I don't care
about being compensated or anything like
that I just want this organization to
thrive and for some
reason well it hasn't come so easily
that's what I was just about to say
there's a lot of hard work go going
behind it it's for some reason reason
God has just supported us and and the
means have just have just come and
everyone has reached out as I mentioned
before we provide our recipients with
vimergy supplements Wyman's wild
blueberry juice we're working towards uh
providing our recipients with the proper
medical care that they may also need and
we're just expanding and trying to help
people and however we
can and and with that we've just found
so much support something that I never
had before or or even felt
supported uh my parents are here with me
I can't say that I've
always had the support that I've needed
from them I know they love me but
they've never understood what I've gone
through and that's why I want Underdog
Wars
to help be a bit of that support for
[Applause]
others so again it's just deeply it's a
deep deep honor to even just be standing
here because again it wasn't something I
expected it's just something that's
happened just like everything else that
has happened within the
organization and I of course am just
representing everyone behind it everyone
there have been so many people that have
just supported us to get us where we're
at
and and to have the heavy metal detox
smoothie and all the proceeds go to
Underdog Warriors is just such a
blessing again it's the support that
wasn't expected
and I just want to say that we are here
please reach out to
us if there is anyone you know anyone
that may need support because they can't
afford the tools they need please reach
out to us please let them know I know a
lot of people apply and they didn't know
about Underdog
Warriors and so please look out sign up
to our newsletter underdog war.org slash
newsletter to be notified of anything
new again I really really appreciate the
support
it's it's quite
incredible I just know that those out
there suffering and those people that we
haven't been able to help will now be
able to have the support they
need now I just want to end with a few
things I never imagined that I would
speak about this up here on a stage we
ran a fundraiser at the end of the year
so back in December and that fundraiser
went
beyond expected it
was it was so incredible we had one
donor come to us for a
$115,000 matching donation well what
happened
what ended up happening was we exceeded
our goal we had another donor that
approached us with to to be able to
match the 15K so he also put up some
money you all know who you
are um and then we received an anonymous
donation in the mail for
$15,000 Plus
we made a little over $10,000 from our
social media fundraiser our end of year
campaign so if you add all of that up
it's quite a large amount of
money and we're working on Distributing
that in the best way possible so that
the people that do need it in our
community do receive
it and now we'll have the proceeds from
the heavy metal detox smoothie
collaboration mm with airwan how
incredible is
that I just want to thank everyone
behind it I know everyone has put so
much work into it uh I want to thank uh
Anthony and the whole
team and every everyone else involved
this is just such a
blessing and I know I know we're going
to be supported every step of the way
now so I just like to thank you thank
you for
listening thank you for being here I
know it's a bit
hectic I myself didn't
know I was going to be up here and I
actually didn't have time to prepare and
um I was just going back and forth so
I'm glad that you're all listening here
to what I have to say and what I have to
share thank you all very much I really
really do appreciate
[Applause]
it thank you
Liz all right this now let me welcome Dr
Prudence Hall she's been helping all
genders from around the globe to reclaim
their health lead a long active and
joyful life she is a Pioneer in
perimenopause and menopause for the last
four decades while also treating other
hormone conditions such as low
testosterone in men thyroid disease
adrenal deficiency and metabolic
disorders instead of just treating only
the symptoms of a patient's condition
her approach goes to the root cause and
balancing of the deficiencies that can
lead to degenerative diseases later in
life yay Dr thank you hello beloved
followers of Anthony let's give it up
for
Anthony yay beloved Anthony so w how
fitting is this that we're all here in
the City of Angels when we have that
angel amongst us so
welcome medicine needs to
change and we are that change you are
that change
because the era has changed in medicine
over the last 30 years the way we
practice medicine must change we need to
get to the core or the root causes of
Aging now what are those number one
toxicity who what is Anthony doing he's
going to detox the entire world and I
certainly follow his detox number two
imbalanced hormones hormones are our
body body software and when men reach
about 50 or 45 their testosterone tanks
and oh my God they become irritable they
get belly fat they develop heart disease
and all kinds of things so women start
to go into per menopause in their late
30s and that's really a problem because
when our hormones decrease up go the
core root causes of diseases so the core
root causes are balance your hormones
you know imbalanced hormones toxicity
inflam
and stress when you have those four
components present in your
body diseases arise we feel terrible I
take care of so many patients who can't
get out of bed yeah they'll get out of
bed get their kids off to school but
then they go right back to bed so if we
address those core root causes what do
we have
Vitality energy good sleep we age
beautifully with beautiful skin and
bones and hair and we don't develop the
diseases like cancer heart disease the
number one cause of death in women and
men we don't develop all the autoimmune
diseases that Anthony has also talked
about nor do we develop the diseases of
inflammation you know all the arthriti
and the body pain that we have
so medicine needs to address who we are
and first of all we're Spiritual Beings
we come from source we're also emotional
beings especially the women that I work
with we're emotional and our thoughts
create our emotions create our reality
and our health so when we can change our
thoughts the emotions change and our
reality
changes
also what I've learned over the last 40
years of practice is that medicine as we
practice it in the western world is
about 80 years old when was Penicillin
invented
1928 when was the first patient treated
1945 so how can we as doctors and as
practitioners in Western medicine come
on with this arrogance I know what to do
you you be quiet I know the answer so
this is not the
way we need humility and we need
partnership with our
patients I can't approach a patient
without knowing what his goals are or
her goals are and I want to know know
what's important to you how do you want
to address your health
concerns so arrogance has got to stop we
need to really age in a way where we are
increasing our biological wellness we
can't create a different chronological
age I'll always be this age but in terms
of biologically addressing all those
core root causes we can create Miracles
so our biological age is sometimes 30
years older or 30 years younger so what
goes into creating better biology
balancing your hormones getting rid of
inflammation decreasing stress the core
causes one of the pearls I've learned in
medicine is that and I've done this for
for almost 40 years is that when you
balance your hormones back to youthful
levels or preserve your hormones
diseases just fall away now what are
some of the symptoms of women who are
going through menopause oh we sweat we
can't sleep we're Moody we're crying
angry I think some of you know it many
of you are my patients and we don't need
to live that way because once you go
into menopause you stay that way your
whole life so what do we want to do we
want to prevent the decline of our
ovaries and of our thyroid and of our
adrenal glands and detoxification is
essential we're so toxic they we've done
uh W I would say rather Innovative
people in medicine have done biopsies of
muscle to see how toxic we are and every
single one of us is filled with toxicity
does Western Medicine address that even
with one
suggestion in our arrogance we don't but
Anthony is doing that and he's done it
successfully for many many years and as
I deal with patients and put them on the
detox diet his diet and work with them I
see real Miracles occur so balance your
hormones back to youthful levels and
prevent the decline by
detoxifying now people think very
frequently that we develop diseases due
to our
genes not true guys 90% of diseases come
from lifestyle
so what do we need to do we need to
sleep eight hours eat that great diet
that Anthony talks about and that I talk
about we need to uh get some exercise
think good thoughts meditate decrease
our stress so when we do these things
Miracles can occur we don't need to go
downhill we don't need to have a decline
in our hormones so our thyroid gland I
actually wrote the forward to anon's uh
medical medium book
and yeah it was it was a real eye opener
for me uh so when we uh balance our
thyroid hormones by detoxification I
would say the number one cause is as
Anthony says it's it's viruses and also
toxicity that cause our glands and our
hormones to decline so what happens when
we lose our thyroid well we get tired we
gain 20 30 pounds the brain is foggy we
get sad we cry and what does Western
medicine do well first of all they
ignore and Miss 40% of low thyroid
conditions I come on 40% of us are
walking around with low thyroid and
we're given
anti-depressants we're given uh you know
adol to make the brain work better so
these are incorrect
Solutions we can't keep on practicing
medicine this way so the thyroid gland
is important the adrenal glands are very
important and I work a lot with my
patients on that they little glands that
sit right back on the kidneys and when
we have stress you know stress kills
stress causes diseases then what happens
is those hormones soar they go really
high and then slowly they tank and when
they
tank all the symptoms of fatigue and
anger and irritability and lots of
weight gain start to
arise so if you have one hormone
abnormality okay okay well we can maybe
deal with the two hormone abnormalities
not so good three hormone abnormalities
were tank plus you throw in a virus like
Cy omegal virus or Epstein bar and we're
just we're
dying so we want to maintain our
hormonal balance now I want to tell you
how I met Anthony because I think it is
such a touching story a patient came in
and she said Prudence I have a gift for
you and it's like you do I'm a little
shy receiving giest but oh thank you and
she slapped that medical medium book
right in my hand I looked at I thought
medical medium ah there's a long
tradition in Western and Eastern uh
medicine of having people who see the
truth and who know for example the
medicine men directly in contact with
God and they helped the tribes it it
goes back thousands of years so medical
medium oh my goodness this is
interesting so I got home and I was
really so first of all I was interested
because I know that there's lots of
different ways to obtain information and
it's probably not from the double blind
studies I mean that's important but it's
also from other media so I got home
looked through the book and I thought
this is very interesting and I turned
the book over and there was a uh a
little um I would say it was sort of a a
tribute to Anthony from one of my dear
friends Alejandra anger he's Dr
clean re resets the gut and he's a dear
friend and I called him up I said
Alejandro who's this medical medium and
he said oh Prudence he is the
best he knows how to really help your
patients and about three hours later I
got a call hello this is Anthony and I'm
going like Anthony Anthony Anthony it's
like
Anthony are are are you Anthony
William and what has birthed is the
sweetest relationship enormous knowledge
that has been passed on to me and I'm
very very grateful because I love this
field I'm never going to retire I love
helping people and I will find every
single Source that's helpful in order to
pass that on to you and to collaborate
with you for your highest health so I
want to leave you with
this where are you now with your health
goals how's your energy your vital your
sexuality your your mind and all of
those things that make you who you are
where are you now and where do you want
to
be what is the difference between that
and how do we get from here to there and
it is a beautiful path we're all on this
path we're all on this path I'm on this
path every day I'm I'm here to learn and
then as soon as I learn I want to share
it so we're one
Community that's important because in
order to make change in this medical
field that has gone down the wrong path
we all need to be voices voices for
ourselves and our loved ones and our
children voices that are heard in
Congress so that laws are changed and I
am honored to be with you on this path
oh this is my partner Max Danish man and
uh he's been a enormous source of
comfort to me uh on this journey and you
can all have my book for free it's
called radiant again and forever you go
to the hall center.com put in your email
and you got the book it'll download
right away to your uh to your email so I
am here to educate and thank you for
your attention uh I look forward to
meeting you individually and go team go
team Anthony
[Music]
Bel
every
m
ladies and gentlemen
walk have your guys Books open pictures
front please let's keep the line
going e
all
guys
on hello everybody we have an
announcement Nas and Sam are looking for
shafag yeah can you please come up here
to the stage Nas and Sam are looking for
you
shafag if anybody helps or
maybe can point them in the right
direction
okay thank you
than
I'm so sorry
love
up
be
thank you thank you for being
here honor I'm H watch
back do everything
[Music]
sorry
it's
really thank you very
much there is
go thank you
thank Youk
you long time ago all you had was a
Polaroid back there
oh are you kidding oh my god oh
[Music]
the music is about to be back sorry for
the silence we try to fill as many as
possible in
but I think we're going to take a break
for that and I know that we need some
music in this park to brighten up a
little bit right because the event is
still going on we're still waiting for
Piers to go back on stage of course
Anthony will be back soon so please
ready for that
please enjo Wonder
day wonderful Parts by wonderful people
and by the way guys please if you have
something to say
[Music]
we or you just want to share with
everybody how great Anthony is please
please do that the crew the testimonials
crew is right behind the
northern right here the main entrance of
the par is please proce there please
make sure you record your
short we would really appreciate that
ready for the music I hope somebody
ready to dance do I have some people are
ready to dance here okay even Under the
Sun you still ready that's great that's
respectful thank you guys do
next oh thank you brother appreciate it
thank I'll I'll get some more
I didn't get your
name I
already make sure no one like you're
doing great by the
way bang yeah cuz they're all this is at
least I couple million right here it's
exp I don't know about
that I do photography and
everything AI yeah
bro try try 10,000 right there that's
10,000 just for the body yeah easy easy
then you have lenses and everything
camera body alone yeah I wouldn't doubt
if that thing like probably like 500,000
all right
here thank
you hey why rob a b r this
right follow the we're not here for that
[Music]
the
St
St St
[Music]
see
you
[Music]
very
stay
[Music]
down
I'll
[Music]
Lo
I'm TR to tell you
[Music]
my
[Applause]
[Music]
every
watch
[Music]
the
you
[Music]
one
that's the way to do
it thank you love you
[Music]
than
thank you young
man
you all right people we still have a lot
of interviews to record so here's how
we're going to do it we're going to do a
short music session so then we turn down
the music we're going to record a Q
videos we're going to bring it back so
please stand by for more super
cool keep moving thank you guys if you
don't mind watch out behind you thank
you thank you thank you very
much thank you very much
[Music]
all the way up all the way
up guys step up
please be
quick thank you thank
you thank
you oh my God I wish I was a
rockar yeah yeah we got a mom baby over
rockar got it
easy watch out right behind you Ma thank
you come on come on come you want your
book you thank you sir all
right
ladies ad very thank you
good goodar I
love Warriors Got Warriors
Denmar thank
you this yours
thank you walk keep
walking no I'm just waiting on my
friend
[Music]
than much for
coming it's an honor to sign your books
you guys
walk thank
you got thank you sorry we just have so
many
people
El you got a dou
one it's hard to take it in two seconds
thank
you thank you very much have a good day
you right all the way up
love Engish love you thank you so
muching
you every person coming up you
guys believed in me believed in me saw
the
information thank you
that thank
you hi
[Music]
watch your St thank
you thank
you nothing wrong with that that's
amazing and that's a long
trip thank you watch your St guys
pleas thank you watch your
okay give me a fav just give me a high
sign let's go guys keep moving please
ladies and
gentlemen
Bo
wayg can't that
no it
ain't got keep we all got to
keep love
you good look though hey I'd rather it
be wrong
[Music]
watch your step watch your step
lon
l everything that you're healing that
everything awesome awesome okay I will I
will drink it never seen me drink all
that maple
syrup amazing amazing you're amazing
this
yours thank
you what are you doing
you waiting in this
line stuck in this line you got patience
for
[Music]
patience thank you
old school high school rap I like
that hello everybody I am making another
announcement we are looking for or a
woman named Shaak she's in a blue hat
with um sort of
rhinestones on the hat nass and Sam are
up here waiting for you if you hear this
Chef please come to the stage thank you
guys so much I hope everybody's having a
good time staying hydrated enjoying the
healing enjoying this gorgeous day thank
you for being out here and again shafak
if you you hear this message please come
to the stage to NS and Sam thanks
guys thanks you
[Music]
original book right here's got this one
that's the
first I know you guys are holding light
for me too and I know that
thank you watch your
St thank you thank
[Music]
you what is going
on thank you for having patience okay
okay I got
you get choked up up God bless you too
okay I don't know I'm going tost
out thank you watching okay thank
you that's incredible all the way all
the way
love a
[Laughter]
day right here yeah
I'm waiting for the one person that
knocked I'm trying to deviate people
doing that everyone be blind to
it kind of in a bad
[Music]
spot I'm where's the gift basket that
way I'll
take okay I'm getting a picture from
here got to be really quick okay cuz I'm
not allowing anybody to do that oh it
will be
the basket on the other
side walk around
[Music]
yeah lovexo
very
patient in the all day
[Music]
somebody
from one yeah here
today I know you a way
say
work your support make work
[Music]
easy you
go hey that's for
[Music]
you thank you
you
[Music]
the tree the get back okay thank you
let's go around that
way got
[Music]
it number one right there
you
guys I know I'm saying
[Music]
you
than
[Music]
you want here
baby
[Music]
there
watch behind you
[Music]
thank you
how Longo you
[Music]
than
wo yeah I know
[Music]
favor
going thank you
thank you she'll take
carek you
[Music]
thank
[Applause]
you
everyone minute from now please be well
be ready to welcome our main host
Anthony but meanwhile I want to make
another an announcement ladies and gents
we found two side books in the middle of
the bar somebody left them there that
would be such a tragedy if a person who
stood in such a long line lost this book
so please if
you if you know that you are missing two
boots signed Anthony please go to the DJ
[Music]
let's go guys keep
moving you guys have a
[Applause]
bra watch Step
please thank you watch your step
okay thank you thank you
watch thank you
watch
camera all right let's go
this thank
you love you guys I'll be back don't
worry oh yeah
people are asking are you guys
Gentlemen Just line just not letting
anyone else get in line
[Music]
friend told us of
sign that's all I
got all I have for now
I'm coming to look for
you hey yo yo yo yo
I just had a couple
here e
how many tickets did you have
than
and I didn't get her name
wow that's amazing that is amazing
we love mm
community for
you're e
to
[Music]
are you filming
hi yeah
get together
you know
[Music]
[Applause]
humus every months some kind of parents
are wiy
[Music]
it's
right everybody get ready because
Anthony is going to come back to the
stage um so let's
maybe yeah this is amazing this is great
um without any a
[Laughter]
do all right let's do
[Applause]
it nobody knows what it's like unless
they've been there before you know if
you're really sick you got fatigue you
don't feel good you got anxiety you got
depression aches and pains your legs
feel like sandbags got pain in your neck
you got migraines got Tremors and shakes
ticks and spasms seizures all kinds of
things
right but nobody knows what that's like
unless they had it themselves so it's
really hard out there I know many of you
have run into that and then it's the you
look
great but you don't feel great right you
know you look good on the outside
meanwhile you feel like you're dying
inside right and so many people
experience that but these are just a
couple of things and then there's a
resistance right I want to eat healthier
I want to take care of myself I want to
do this I want to drink the celery juice
and then there's people around you or
people that you bump into that are like
don't do that don't do
that that's a whole another struggle all
on its
own and then there's the inner inner
inner struggle the inner struggle of
is anybody listening to me is anybody
hearing me do they understand me how
come they're misunderstanding me how
come they're judging me right how many
people go through
that when we're indestructible and
everything's fine and we feel good and
we're walking
[Music]
along you're on the beach for two hours
on 100 degree day no big deal you're
working out that morning 5 in the
morning for an hour or two you're in the
gym everything's great
the world is your
oyster and then you get sick boom and
then the real fight the real struggle
happens I know people they work hard
every day to achieve
things and they do things every day but
when you're sick and you're chronically
strug struggling and suffering it's
another story it's a battle no one
understands out there unless they've
been there before you can't compare it
you can't I to a friend and they're like
yeah I'm working out in the gym I'm in
there for 2 hours a day you wouldn't
believe how hard it is aw I'm like
that's
nothing nothing compared to can't get
out of bed can't feed my kids can't take
care of my kids can't drive them to
school can't go do this can't do
that that struggle and then the struggle
of no one understanding because they're
not there with you because they don't
know what it's like sure we have
relatives around us and friends and
family that that they they connect we we
have that many people have that many
people
don't many times it's just I'm alone in
this and then you see people they seem
fine you you see them driving down the
road everybody seems healthy everybody
seems perfect how about that everybody's
enjoying their lives and living their
lives and they look healthy and they
look great you see them driving down the
road all day long like this that
person's living it up that person's
living it up and you're
struggling it's all it's all difficult
and it's what I call rising out of the
ashes cuz when you come back from that
that's gold medal
[Applause]
stuff
I I talk to a lot of Olympic athletes
the ones that get sick for the first
time in their life they're working out
every day they're doing their thing they
got their trainers they got their agents
they got their publicists they got
everybody they're doing it all day long
then they get into the Olympics they're
doing it doing they get a silver medal
gold medal bronze medal and then they
get sick
and then they say Anthony
aw I didn't
know I had it made I got up in the
morning made my protein shake did my
workout trained all day had my trainer
with me went to bed cuz I was tired
started the next day over but that was a
joke compared to being sick and
something being
wrong and I talk to Olympic athletes
that aren't sick yet
and I say I get it I know what you
achieved it's amazing I'm proud of you
but it's nothing compared to being sick
and
bedridden stuck in a wheelchair not
knowing what's wrong legs don't work
arms don't work something's off battery
of tests how many people went to so many
doctors which we have to have doctors we
need them but how many people went to so
many doctors had a battery of tests have
been through it all right
this
is an achievement you got to patch
yourself on the back you truly do and
maybe your symptoms are mild maybe
they're severe but either way and then
it's how we feel about it some people
I've seen people they're struggling so
heavily they're so sick they've been
through so
much but there's just so nice they're so
nice it's incredible the nice people the
people that are sickest they're not
complaining they're just pushing through
and then you see people out there that
aren't sick yet and they're nasty
they're
mean right
pushy
ungrateful they take everything for
granted not
everybody but you've seen it out there
right but you see the people who
struggle they got chronic illness and
they're suffering I'm me the nicest
people they'll take their shirt off
their back they'll rip their shirt off
their back and be like here here's a
shirt oh I can't walk good I got fatigue
I don't feel good but take my shirt God
bless
you the medical meum community is
different much different than any
Community out there I see it out there I
don't know if you guys see it out there
do you see it out
[Applause]
there I'm telling you there's some
Community Health communities out there
but you see the difference this one has
Soul I'm not just saying that I know
it the sickest people came to the
medical medium books and found the
information the sickest people came to
mm and they knew what they were seeing
they were seasoned how many people are
seasoned out there you're seasoned in
the health
movement you guys are the health experts
that's the whole
thing social media
came right it's gotten vicious
right trolls and everything else and
everything that people deal with okay
and they don't understand they don't get
it the medical medium Community there's
none other in the world there's none
other you guys are the are the seasoned
experts came from hell and back many of
you I've heard that many times you don't
understand I've been through hell been
through hell aw been through hell have
you heard that you've heard that before
I just I'm Going Through Hell you heard
that yeah exactly and that's in the
medical medium community and the thing
is people come here they come here to
start with not because of me that's not
it because why would I believe in the
medical medium why would I think the
medical medium has anything there's all
these people out there health coaches
health professionals everybody's on Tik
Tok everybody's out there talking about
do this do that try these five things
for this try this I'm an expert now
right right you see it all out there why
go to awmm Medical medium
information you're not going to wake up
one morning and say I'm going to go and
do that Medium
stuff no you guys been through it
already you been through it you know
what's going on you seen it out there
you came here because you're like I can
tell what's real I can tell what the
real stuff is I read these books from up
above I know what I'm seeing in here
and the information comes from above
because I can't come up with that
information and put that in words I just
can't there's no
way but I'm a messenger to take that
information so we all can have it and
it's here for you and you recognize it
you know what's real you know the you
know what it
is and then it's how you found the book
many of you you found the book somebody
gave it to you somebody said hey look at
this and you're like maybe you weren't
even open to it at first uh no no no no
no no that's crazy that's crazy medical
medium stuff I can go here I can go
there check out this guy in Social check
on this person here I don't need to do
the medical medium stuff but something
tells you deep inside it hits and it
kicks in and then that's it you're like
this is right this is real this is
information it's speaking to my soul
some people get the book find the book
they're in the grocery store and
somebody hands them one sometimes in the
doctor's office somebody hand them one
somebody hands them one here they're
there they bump into it one way or
another it's as if angels from above
said listen to this book here read these
Pages or a supernatural Force look at
this here this can
help and I tell people I don't care what
you believe in all walks of life do
medical medium information all walks of
life all walks of life all religions
people do medical medium I don't care if
you believe in God you don't believe in
God you believe in the light the Creator
you believe in the universe maybe you
think we're just on a rock it's floating
in space and there's no faith no
spiritual no nothing no Ghosts no
anything nothing exists in the spiritual
realm we're just on a rock and everybody
is just living on here if you believe in
that I don't care I'm just glad you have
the book so can turn your life around
it's open for anybody with any belief
[Applause]
system doesn't matter if you're vegan
plant-based does it matter if you're a
pescatarian does it matter if you're
macrobiotic doesn't matter if your
animal protein medical medium
information is for
everybody if you
notice you notice the books were never
like this is vegan book that's it you
know only do vegan you can only be a
vegan that's it was never like that it's
information put into the books and
people who eat animal protein can use it
and people who are plant-based can use
it I'm not against anybody you can heal
eating animal protein and doing this
information you can heal doing
plantbased and do this information in
heal it's for everybody and then the
words in the
books when SSC gives me the words and
I'm writing them down I'm just blown
away every
sentence every sentence because there's
words in these books like Soul's gold
right how many of you guys know about
Soul's gold
right purpose plus it's when you have a
purpose Beyond a purpose way bigger than
anybody even knows
okay and then that information and brain
saver or Spirit of compassion told me
about a soul traveling through time and
space did you ever read that
it's
unbelievable most importantly no matter
what the tools are in there for you
guys and it takes guts guts to do it and
you guys got guts like I've never seen
before in my
[Applause]
life is it possible we all knew each
other in a lifetime
before right were we here
but years and hundreds of years ago did
we do
this some of you guys are really old
souls and I said it before way older
than me just because Spirit of
compassion spoke to me at age four
doesn't mean I had the oldest Soul trust
me I try my best but some of you people
got the oldest souls and many of you
people were born into this world with no
ego at all at all it's
incredible I mean true salt of the earth
the real expression of salt of the earth
is in the medical medium community and
that blows my mind every single day
every single
day and when I think about it I'm just
get overwhelmed with joy sadness too
sadness too I know you guys have
suffered and struggled you come a long
long way and it's not like you get an
award many you guys you just every day
do it again do it again metal smoothie
every day celery juice every day do the
tools every day look into the books
every day fight forward and no one's
coming over to you and saying here's a
medal here's a trophy no one's giving
you a trophy but you guys keep on doing
it and you keep on moving
forward takes guts man it takes
guts and then there's the compassion
right I've worked hard to try to get
some compassion going just because I
talk to Spirit of compassion doesn't
mean I'm the most compassionate person
when I was younger I told of compassion
I don't want to do this I was 10 years
old saying I don't care about people
being sick I want to ride my
bicycle but spirit said no no no you
have to care and never forget you need
to be here for people you have to care
it's critical and I said okay I will
make it a point that I always care from
here on
[Applause]
out I I hear that word compassion out
there and the first thing I think about
is the medical medium Community being
the most compassionate people out there
that's the first thing I think I hear
somebody say the word compassion out
there and I instantly go right to the
medical medium community in my mind and
said no no no no no no the most
compassionate people there are on this
planet is the medical medium Community I
don't want anybody to forget
that don't ever doubt yourself and think
you're not don't ever doubt yourself to
think you're a bad person you're not a
bad person always remember that so one
thing that Spirit of compassion always
told me at the beginning is you tell
someone who's going through this and
moving forward that you didn't do
anything wrong and it's not your fault
it's not your fault do not forget that
you make sure you have it in the heart
is if you think it's your fault and
you're the problem and you caused it and
you're a bad person we are not in a good
place you have to understand that has to
be fixed
immediately every morning you wake up
you say no I'm a good person I didn't
get sick because I'm a bad person I
didn't create this and I didn't cause it
and guess what my body is not destroying
itself my body is not attacking itself I
got diagnosed with autoimmune and they
told me my body is destroying itself no
it's
not always
remember your body's fighting for you
every day every single day it's working
for you if you got a symptom and it
won't go away your body's still working
really hard every minute every day it's
working hard for you you have to know
that you have to know it in your heart
and in your mind your head your soul
Consciousness subconsciousness
everywhere you have to know your body's
fighting for you everything you do for
it your body's saying yeah yeah give it
give it to me more more more more more
accelerate juice more more more give me
those nutrients phytochemical compounds
give me those antioxidants give me
everything that's what your body's
saying most important thing to know is
here I'm going to tell you you did not
create your illness you did not create
it and it wasn't because in a lifetime
before this you were a bad person and
had your head chopped off in England or
in someplace
else or 500 years ago so you were I
don't know burned at the stake because
you were a terrible
person you did not create your
illness okay and it's not your fault
there's happen
there are certain circumstances that we
run into trouble with here on this
planet cuz this planet as we know is not
a fair place you tell you tell me if
this planet's a fair
place it's a beautiful place sure it's
not always the fairest place so it's not
our fault when we get sick or something
happens or we get exposure or we get
something in us that we it just we
didn't do it to ourselves it happened
for a lot of reasons even if we think we
did it to to ourself it's not true
something happened emotionally something
happened me mentally some kind of wounds
from the past that aren't your fault can
also get in the way but that's not you
creating it those are
injuries
right but keep in mind that no matter
what okay have compassion for yourselves
every day don't kick yourself in the ass
whatever you do don't do that
and if you fall off course or fall off
the wagon and you eat something that's
not helping you and you drink something
that's not helping you that's okay
that's okay it happens to the best of us
because this is a hard place to live in
this world and I understand if we trip
and fall a little bit and we eat
something and drink something and we do
something like Dr NES he drinks alcohol
every single day
yeah and Dr Joby who sells $53,000
bottles of wine in his own Winery and
wine
estate keep in
mind keep in
mind if we get tripped up and we're
doing something that's not helping us
it's okay we can get back on the horse
when we can we can customize stuff for
ourselves
out of the information we can be good to
ourselves don't beat yourself up don't
be hard on yourself whatever you do do
you guys want a light
blast
[Applause]
okay I forgot to do this do you
want all right all right this one's GNA
be a little bit more intense than the
last
[Music]
one so's telling me there's still a lot
of blockages out here there's new people
in here that didn't get the white loss
from
before but did anybody get the light
Bloss from
[Applause]
before
no this is going to be intense then cuz
you're getting another round all right
everybody take a deep breath and then
release
release okay and then release now
listen where do you want the light
directed do you want to direct it to
your heart do you want to direct it to
your
throat your thyroid do you want to you
do right you want thyroid right brain
liver you want that light directed
somewhere down in there intestinal track
colon right lower back a lot of people
got really sore feet their feet are
swollen and hurt right that's there's
there's people with edema you want the
light directed there do you want to
direct it to your
[Music]
soul all right let's do the first thing
now there's blockages so it's going to
take time to get the light through some
people let's see what happens most of
you guys that are probably here right
now had a light blast earlier you're
free you're clear this is going to go
right through you to the ground get
ready so we're going to take a deep
breath and I'm going to have you hold
that deep breath I'm going to say light
light light and then release Spirit of
compassion is going to drop light down
on the crown of everybody's
head just
waiting did I go to early
spirit all right take a deep
breath
release spirit's not ready yet now now
we
are count of three take a deep breath
and hold it one 2 3 deep breath hold it
light light light now
release that went through a lot of
people a lot more than I than I would
think in that fast anybody feel
that okay get ready for this light blast
right here on count of three one two
three deep breath bring it in hold it
light light L now Light
release all right now the ray of light
is going to be
increased about
20% let's do it again get ready
everybody hang on hang on to your
britches count of three one two three
deep breath in hold it light light light
now
release incredible there's somebody
really stubborn over here it's only here
and then somebody back here it's really
stubborn uh there's a few more it just
means everybody else is going to get
more
light all
[Applause]
right this might do it right here we'll
see remember the light's going to come
down on the top of the head and really
quick think about the sky the the nicest
Sky you've ever seen at night with the
Stars the lights coming behind the stars
and coming down really fast so think
about the nicest Sky you see at night
constellations whatever you see up there
stars whatever you're looking at UFOs
aliens whatever you're trying to see up
in the sky just look up
there you got a visual of the night
sky all right we're going to get ready
for this one on count of three get ready
one two 3 deep breath in hold it light
light light light now now
release okay okay I felt that one
I felt that
[Applause]
one I felt that one it it hit the ground
hard it ran through most everybody here
there's one still over here there's one
over here and there's couple by the tree
over there ready one more time should do
it and we're free get ready you guys
count of three one two three everybody
deep breath light light light Spirit
light now release that's it you guys
success went through everybody even
through somebody over here that was
really
difficult
incredible
amazing all right you guys you know I
love you I'm going to pop off the
stage thanks guys
[Music]
okay everybody we have more speakers
today so I want to tell you about our
next speaker Dr Win fan is an internal
medicine doctor he's practicing in
spring in addition to learning and
working with season Specialists his
experience in acute Hospital settings
allowed him to understand the
limitations of current medicine for
chronically ill patients all right so
he's going to tell you a little bit more
about his journey welcome Dr ly
[Applause]
fan hello was was I the only one who got
the memo to to match Decor I mean maybe
I
was uh before we start I want to tell
you a little story about when I got the
call from Anthony to come down speak his
team needed someone who could Inspire
the audience and leave them with an
uplifting
message and he said Dr fan we need you
to come down and give your
best um because the person that we
really wanted couldn't make
it I was I was like no I'm ready to do
it I'm ready to do this right after more
than 20 years of being an internal
medicine doctor after starting my
medical beating journey in 2015 when the
new book I the first book came out after
speaking to thousands and thousands of
patients about the medical meet and
protocols I was like I'm going to fly
from Spring Texas to California and give
him the best shot I can give so you know
of course I I don't want to like be too
groupy so I was like when they asked me
I was like yeah sure I can do it right
so um imagine Anthony William right the
this healer Global healer to millions of
people many bestsellers you're Idol um
again I look up to Anthony because when
you're my height you have to look up to
everybody and it was an honor it's like
it's like the peak moment right like
after let's say after getting to medical
school after marrying my high school s
sweetheart after having two sexually
transmitted dependent
uh this was this is one of the best
things I could imagine so I thank all
you guys for coming out here and
supporting me and Anthony you basically
right um but immediately after accepting
it I was like mini panic attack mode I
was like what the heck am I going to
speak about um you know I got material
on YouTube and MD you know Instagram I'm
MB was Spirit MD WIS
PT um sham plug there
uh I thought well you know I got to
relax what would people around me want
to hear what what could make them what
would my make my wife laugh right then I
thought no no no no no no I can't get
naked in front of the audience that
would be Pro totally inappropriate and
maybe final by law so I thought about it
again and I thought you know I just I'll
just talk
about why why your medical medium
healing story is more important than any
medical journal article or scientific
study right and how do you talk about
medical medium to other people and
keeping a light heart at the same time
so
um first today though we're celebrating
the
hmds right for those who are new who
don't know what it what it stands for
let's let's say it together it's the um
St with me heavy metal de detox sexiness
oh no um smoothie yes yes or helps me
detox smoothly but it's a heavy metal
detox smoothie and it's healing many
many people across the world and it
tastes good
too um so you know what you know who's
not having a good day today though the
people who are not having a good day are
the the I hate Anthony William club
they're not having a good day right oh
yeah they're they're still drawing
mustaches on his picture they's drawing
darts at his picture on his the D board
they're still going in Barnes no
probably tearing page out page one page
144 or 369 out of cleans of heel and
shoving it in their mouth and eating it
and then putting that book back into the
Shelf but we have to help Anthony be
brighter and lighter to outshine them so
keep on going guys um additionally it's
Dad and grad season so happy Father's
Day to all of you guys who celebrate and
congratulations to all the graduates out
there but but in reality we are all
graduates of healing we are the the
healing class of
right um many have worked so solidly to
get here uh many have Juiced cleansed
and smoothie their way to healing and
you may not be totally there that but
we're we're on the we're on the path
your journey has been so long your
journey has been so hard it's been so
long it's been so hard there's a bad
Viagra joke in there but uh it's a
family channel so I'm not going to go
that right um
so we've all watched your stories
whether that's Amber or Britney or Mary
Michelle or Josh or Matt your stories
Inspire us your stories make our eyes
perspire you're the cream of the crop
you rise to the top you never eat the
pig cuz the pig makes detox
stop I always wanted to say that in
front of an
audience regardless I commend you on
your hard work even if your journey has
just begun you just met you know medical
medium today we are we're all at our own
PL Pace right for your efforts you
deserve to be recognized you are seen by
Anthony you are seen by S so and the
angels they are witnessing your plight
your fight and your right your right to
heal right live a healthy life
so by the power invested in me by uh
well I I really don't have any Authority
anywhere but by the power of uh the
power of grade school I want to give you
an honorary degree this honorary degree
is called the
BF because you guys are all badass
mofos give yourself an Applause give
yourself
[Applause]
Applause one of the most common
questions I get as a medical doctor is
how can you recile Medical Science with
a guy who hears a voice in his head and
he's not even a doctor so I say to you
well like many of you I've explored
these alternative treatments I've I've
spent a lot of money I spent a lot of
time and you know what Anthony said
about oh somebody's telling you that you
died in past life and somebody chopped
your head off that was us and I was like
how did you know that I never told him
that how did you know that they told me
that because of the law of attraction
that I attracted to a family member of
mine I'm like how did I attract this
crap to my family I don't understand
that so whatever Anthony says I mean I
learned from Anthony like The Compassion
that he feels for people he feels what
they have and I had a little glimpse of
that through through his writings and
his lives so I very much thank you for
that um you know many of these doctors
are and practitioners they're not bad
people they have a belief system you
can't I can't fault them for trying to
earn a living I can't uh fault them for
not knowing the right
information um and I was immediately
drawn to Anthony after the first Hay
House Radio podcast you guys remember
that stuff he get on the phone and you
talk to people like oh my God this guy
know what he's talking about how does he
know this stuff he's not even a doctor
it's amazing so I was really intrigued
by that and and um you know I I
Implement some of this stuff you know a
little celery juice here get off gluten
dairy eggs and people feel great I I
look like a genius you know I tell my
patients like you need to adrenally
snack so you can calorically stack so
that the sugar doesn't go whack and
viruses attack
and and hopefully they they learned that
um but like for instance there was one
one 36-year-old woman she was I think it
was like four rounds of IVF over eight
years or something like this I can't
remember the details now because I'm on
stage and I met her for the first time I
didn't even change her th do of
medication I told her start some celery
juice get off the Troublemaker foods and
guess what a few months later prar right
she was pregnant thank Dr fan thank you
for getting me pregnant I'm like don't
say that you're you're going to get my
medical license revoked but we have
countless stores like this right I mean
not everybody does medical mean people
come my to my office and they're like
eating barbecue and they're not going to
do this stuff but at least I try and I
sleep better knowing that I've tried for
them and for my own conscious
so
um you don't need to spend thousands of
dollars on these these tests right you
know there's something called um in
clinical practice called weighing the
risks versus the benefits of something
so for instance penicillin penicillin
can help you clear an infection right
like you've got infection you might
stepsis you might die it can save you
but also you can get
anaphylaxis so you always weigh the risk
benefits of a treatment modality celery
juice what are the risk benefit ratios
of celery juice I got to go wash the
celery I got to cut the celery I got to
poop in my
pants but it also clears the skin it
helps the liver it helps the blood
pressure go down I know had a miracle
with blood pressure in my family so
that's it's important to weigh the risk
benefit ratio of a certain modality when
you're talking about foods and
supplements I mean not a lot of side
effects uh that you can tell about right
um but some everybody's sensitive so
there there's that to consider right
let's talk about exercise compared you
know risk management Dr fan when I
exercise I get wet on my skin and my
heart goes nuts and I get adrenaline R
so I can't exercise at all I'm like no
exercise is good for you long term if
you can if if you can do it if you don't
renally stress yourself so you always
have to think about the the risk that's
how you say look look the doctor's going
to put you on medication or you can eat
better and you can add some celery juice
which one do you want to
do um but then a loved one says well
where is the scientific evidence for
this medical medium right after all mom
you the one who is recommending this
crystal energy infused enema or this
homeopathic feces and and that didn't
help your microbiome right you've seen
that you're seen your mom or dad like
they doing these crazy stuff right they
find medical meeting all of a sudden
this is the thing well you don't need uh
a randomized clinical trial to tell you
that you shouldn't go play with wild
bears okay it's kind of like no no no
our study shows that only less than 1%
of these participants did not get their
arm ripped off but you don't need to
know not to go play in traffic that you
know a study to tell you that so um
our you
know I'll tell you that as a fourth year
medical student when I was doing helping
uh doing research for a paper this poor
faculty Professor he was just trying to
publish so he could stay keep his job
and a lot of that that data was horrible
data that he he tried to publish and so
it happens a lot there are actual
Journal articles talking about the
benefit of celer juice and hypertension
uh while blueberry on dementia um but of
course the truth is you can find any
Journal article to support anything you
want you can cheer i cherry pick these
things when I post things on you know
social media so these are the same
influencers who use this information to
say you got to buy my collagen powder
you got to buy my you know electrolyte
formula or something like this get this
martial Angel that's a good name to have
a Marsha Angel who worked at the New
England Journal of Medicine for two
decades and became the chief editor said
this it is simply no longer possible to
believe much of the clinical research
that is published or to rely on the
Judgment of trusted Physicians
authoritative medical guidelines I take
no pleasure in this conclusion which I
reached slowly and reluctantly over my
two decades as an editor of the New
England general of medicine right or how
about this 2016 John Hopkin study
suggests that medical errors were the
third leading cause of death in the US
that is scary not to mention the people
who were like lose a left arm when they
were supposed to be the right arm that
they had supposed to cut you know did
you know that a recent study published
in the bush Journal of Psychology and
Behavioral Medicine showed that 96% of
participants in the study believe that
something was a scientific fact when an
actor spoke congruently and confidently
about a particular topic if one armor of
the in one armor of the study
respondents were told that birds are
gradually and secretly being replaced by
drones that work for the CIA to spy on
people and people believe them now I
totally pulled that study on my butt
it's not real I made it up but it
sounded nice
I'm just I'm I'm jumping in because I
need to make an announcement to everyone
the park has been shut down because we
are at capacity so in order for everyone
who is still in line to get their book
signed I'm going to have to ask all of
our wonderful people here
to say goodbye and kind of head out to
make space and we're so grateful for you
guys to be here but we want to make sure
that everybody who's been waiting all
day can get in so thank you so much Dr
fanan I'm so sorry to interrupt your
your talk um but I had to do this
immediately because the Fire Marshall
has asked us to do
this okay so I'm going to let Dr fan
finish up real quick and um you guys
please make your way out of the park so
that we can get everybody in thank you
so so much I'm so sorry I thank you so
much I'm I thought I said some bad words
or something I was getting kit off the
stage but we will we will meet up and
listen and I'm going to just continue so
we can while you guys leaving you can I
can finish up for you guys but um so
again
um it it just goes to show that if I say
something with confidence that you
believe in the carnivore diet or the
keto diet or the eat right for your hair
type diet or something like this so five
years later you can just change your
mind and uh get on YouTube and then you
can just say I was wrong and get clicks
and still sell your supplements and make
a lot of money but you thank you thank
you guys thanks for for coming out and
we'll uh we'll keep on going thanks
guys my name is Win fan p h an is the
last name
yeah yes I'm I'm GNA finish up real
quick though I'm not still talking sorry
guys um but if you guys would just kind
of vacate so this um where's I at there
sorry well
uh so how how does it
these these stories keep on coming right
um remember that your story is important
and your friends telling you advice you
sometimes take that more importantly
than what I tell them as an MD and their
their doctor they'll believe people they
know so your story matters and you have
to get out there and talk um so apply
some of these talking points that I
brought up right do not approach someone
and say on you know on a Sunday
afternoon and and with a medical meeting
book in your hand go brother have I talk
to you about accepting medical medium
into your life you're going to kind of
scare them so just not do that right I
um I wish you success and pray that
Angels help you at every turn and I pray
you succeed the first part of succeed is
to suck how many of you people have
things that suck in your life right
you're halfway there we're going to go
forward right and then the next hand the
next thing is the seed seed is to give
up something seed this this this idea
that the body wants to attack it itself
that you cannot heal that you have
faulty genes or something like this give
up that idea and then SE is in SED see
the thought that you can heal see the
thought of Tomorrow a better day the
vision of of of helping yourself and
others um read other people's stories of
how they healed when doctors and others
around them thought they were Nut Cases
because you'll get that confidence right
this is this is why these stories are so
inspiring uh because encourag other
people to believe your one story could
be one person in Germany or Finland who
heals because of this and we've seen
that happen
right class of 2024 he in class I'm
going to end on a cliche but instead of
telling you to spread your wings I'm
going to tell you to spread your adrenal
snacks throughout the day instead of
telling you to reach for the stars I'm
going to tell you to reach for the
stargazing meditation and forget the
boring advice that don't do it for money
no you better do these things for to
earn money so you can afford these
15,000 supplements that Coya talked
about
right I leave you with this advice from
the great poet Neil diamand he wrote
turn on Your Heart Light Let It Shine
wherever you go let it make a happy glow
for all the world to see thank you I'm
Dr Win fan and go heal be we're live and
we're doing all the stuff live all right
guys MD with
spirit thank you guys and everybody
please please make your way out of the
park if you have been here to make space
for others coming in you can head out
this way we just got to make space for
everyone else thank you guys so so
much all right guys thank you
I guys behind arow one there's a whole
pedestrian area so this is a really
walkable T part of La so you don't have
to leave the whole area but you can't be
in the park thank you guys so much
oh no over there over there people that
were waiting only thing that blocked
them from going up to him to a freaking
metalion and they sh him and
they
was I'm going go put this in my car no
worries I'm here
oh
ATT
folks please have
[Music]
than
I don't want to stay right
thank you have a bless day thank you
guys thank you thank you
thank you so much
[Music]
I know
you saw you on Thursday
thank you guys than
[Music]
are you kidding oh
my oh my God God it just happened it
just
happened
your oh my God that's
amaz
you what did she say what did you tell
God bless you Anthony
[Music]
No cameras
what is
[Music]
this what's it from I can't figure it
out
[Music]
cam guys camera
thank you than
ladies
good afternoon ladies and gents
those who just
arrived Welcome to our
specials event with a thanks for being
here we really appreciate every single
one of you so please I hope everybody's
having I wish everybody to have the
smoothest signing
process and uh please stay safe stay
hydrated we're going to continue later
with a few more speakers and of course
anony will be on stage pretty soon so
please be ready for that and of course
we also have a testimonial Zone where
you can record something that you would
like to say or maybe some healing
experience that youve had so please
don't be shy go there it's behind the
Gaz in the middle of the park we will be
happy to have
your experience recorded on camera
please enjoy this wonderful special
EV mus little later
toj thank you so much
everyone
[Music]
allate thank you
amaz
what's going on is that
yours oh my God that
book BL away
really
fory words are very wonderful
right youur have
am thank you
[Music]
piur oh my God so
excited finally
[Music]
you away for so long
imagine 6: a.m.
[Music]
see
right promise
you try to push everybody thank you
thank you I appreciate it thanks for
being patient guys no problem
[Music]
you guys thank you very much
okay
[Music]
okay everybody so our next speaker Amber
viaro is an alternative medicine
practitioner with over 10 years of
experience in helping people all over
the world recover from chronic and
autoimmune
diseases she's helping to do this
naturally Amber has been applying
medical medium information into her life
been practice for over 7 years she's
been featured on the medical medium
podcast as she's been actively working
on exposing a group of individuals that
have created one of the biggest scandals
that have ever happened in the health
industry let's welcome Amber to the
stage hi
everybody I recognize so many of your
faces this is crazy
okay I want to know at this point in the
day how many of you are from out of
state raise your hand wow okay okay how
many of you are from out of the
country
wow
wow I mean this crowd is
unbelievable there's nothing like this
that's ever happened before per usual
for medical medium information and I
just have to also say that for the
number of people that are here I've
never seen a more peaceful crowd or a
more respectful crowd you guys are
incredible and I've seen so many of you
I mean for those of you who don't know
me or my story I've been around in the
community for over seven years and I've
watched so many of you grow up and
graduate from high school graduate from
college get married have kids it's just
it's unbelievable how much this
community is like a family and it's such
a blessing to be here with all of you
guys and my journey for those of you who
don't know my story I mean I started
when I was a kid I was I had some minor
symptoms and chronic and autoimmune
illness runs in my family and I have
family members who struggled very
greatly growing up and I watched people
in my family get bullied and
disrespected for their symptoms and the
world was an entirely different place
even just 10 years ago 15 years ago I
don't know who remembers there was no
information out there about what was
causing people's symptoms and it was
even really difficult to get diagnosed
with anything and so much of that has
changed now because of medical medium
information and the influence that it
has had upon the world the medical
industry the entire health profession
now people
who are just out there in the health
industry are talking about toxic heavy
metals they're talking about toxic heavy
metal DET they're talking about heavy
metal detox they're talking about celery
juice and even if they don't have full
information it just it's unbelievable
how much all of that has disseminated
out into the world and the health
industry and we've got doctors now where
it's it's common practice to test for
Epstein bar
virus right
who remembers how many of you H have had
an experience where you read it in his
books something about Epstein bar you
took it to your doctor and the doctor
looked at you like what Epstein bar
virus what do you mean and you couldn't
get tested you couldn't get diagnosed
and that's so that's so not that's so
different from the reality now where you
can go into pretty much any doctor's
office and it's they will even tell you
you if you present with having fatigue
if you present with having brain fog
brain fog wasn't even a label for a
symptom before medical medium
information nobody knew what brain fog
was and there are so many people who
felt like there was something wrong with
them because when you don't have
information and there's something going
wrong in your body and you're
recognizing that you're having a
difficult time putting sentences
together you're having a difficult
time having having enough energy and
Clarity to get through the day and when
you're told oh you know your test
results show that everything looks
normal and and I can't find anything
wrong with you then of course it goes to
there's something wrong with me there's
something you know it's it's maybe it's
in my head that has changed that has
changed so significantly because of the
books and I feel very blessed to have
been fortunate enough to find the books
and to find the information pretty
shortly after the first one was released
and I mean after having those childhood
experiences of watching my family
members just suffer so much and not have
answers and be disrespected and and
confused you know and blaming themselves
as a result it just gave me this like
this fierceness to want to protect
people who who suffer and then I had my
own symptoms I had more minor symptoms
throughout my childhood I was always
sick I was always the one with a cold
sore when nobody else at my school had
cold sores or knew what cold sores were
you know and I almost didn't graduate
from high school because I missed so
many days of school due to being sick
and I had fatigue I had blood sugar
problems I had anxiety I had
depression and then when I got older
there was a time when I had a series of
really stressful events that thankfully
I learned from medical medium
information served as a trigger not a
cause because at the time I thought it
was a cause I thought I was creating my
own symptoms due to my stress and due to
the situations that I found myself in
that weren't within my control and
that's also something that it's really a
lot less commonplace now for people to
think that way and feel that way because
of how much medical medium information
has gotten out there and because of how
much we have access to real answers now
and so when I first got really sick I
was in college I was planning on
becoming a naturopathic doctor and I was
a science girl I was so everything had
to be evidence-based I had been
plant-based I had been eating clean I
had been off of processed foods for
years and I thought I was taking really
good care of myself and then I you know
a series of stressful events can can
knock anybody down if you don't have
accurate information and so I got so
sick so quickly that I wasn't able to
work wasn't able to go to school I was
bedridden I was in this cycle of being
hospitalized every two weeks for months
and months and months and I was 21 years
old it was it was terrible and nobody
around me understood what was going on
and every time that I would go to the
hospital I would be told that my blood
work was fine as so many of you have had
similar experiences and I was told that
I was going to have to live with my
symptoms and conditions for the rest of
my life that the best thing that I was
going to be able to do would be to use
antibiotics and pain medications to
manage my symptoms forever and I had
Interstitial cystitis I had my fatigue
got really bad at that point I had a lot
of neurological symptoms I would get
heart palpitations and mystery fainting
spells and I had acne I had gained
weight even while I was I thought taking
such good care of myself and I was
somebody I learned through the
information that just needed to go a lot
further and I also learned from medical
medium information why it was that I got
to the point of being so sick even when
I was taking better care of myself than
anybody I knew it was because I
inherited pathogens talks cevy Metals I
inherited other exposures and then I was
also exposed to a lot throughout my life
and then the stress was a trigger and so
just having that information of it's not
my fault it's not it wasn't that I did
something wrong it was all these factors
that were out of my control and then
once you get empowered with the
information then you can do something
about it and so I'm very fortunate that
I you know my mom had gotten me the book
The First Medical medium book for
Christmas one year and because I was
such a science girl a Premed I at first
I scoffed at it and I was like medical
medium what is this guy going to tell me
about my health and you know what are
his credentials and I was that girl and
boy was I
humbled I shortly after is when I got
really sick and you know what when I was
bedridden and was seeing naturopaths I
was seeing every different type of
practitioner that was out there and
going on elimination diets doing
everything that I was told to do and
still not getting better and still not
being able to function I was like all
right what is this medical medium guy
GNA say and I cracked open the book gave
it a chance and within the first page I
was balling my eyes
[Applause]
out how many of you guys cried when you
first read the book yeah yeah you don't
get that right like where else where
else do you get that kind of experience
what other kind of book you know in the
health industry would you read and and
so many people have just described
having a spiritual experience and just
getting emotional within even just the
first few pages you can just feel
there's so much and the living words and
the books and it just resonates as being
such truth that just doesn't Exist
Elsewhere and so I had that experience I
was humbled and I was blown away blown
away because I could not believe how
much that first
book it made so much logical sense
everything that's in there more than
anything I had studied in my premedical
program more than anything I had seen
out there in alternative medicine I
could see what I was missing and how I
had to take it further and then I
applied the
information and it took me some time you
know to get it right and then I within
six months healed over 30 symptoms and
conditions and lost over 30 lbs without
even trying
[Applause]
thank you guys and it changed my life
it's the reason why I've been able to
all these years help so many other
people and support so many other people
with their health from all over the
world and I'm very blessed to have been
able to have the experience of being
able to be a part of so many other
people's healing Journeys and to witness
people healing from Parkinson people
healing from the most severe
neurological symptoms and conditions
I've worked with young people who are
literally not able to leave their house
okay bedridden you know in the dark
light sensitivity you name it and my
heart goes out to everybody who's not
able to be here today you know because
they're very sick and and it's amazing
that everybody who made it here today
was able to make it here and that
deserves a shout out okay
we do not take our health for granted
around
here and you know so it's I'm very very
fortunate for how many miracles I've
gotten to witness over the years and
when something is so pure so truthful so
powerful there are always going to be
forces that try to stand in the way of
that or that get jealous of that and so
I'm also you know really fortunate to be
a part of you know protecting medical
medium information that's something that
I will always do
and thank you guys for all of your
support we're like family here and this
is a day that's going to go down in
history this is an event that's going to
go down in history and thank you
everybody for all of your support and
for showing up here and you guys are all
healing Warriors and every single minute
that you spend investing into your
health and your healing is worth it even
in the time that it takes it can take a
long time for some people everybody's
different and even in the time that it
takes to see results there's so much
that's happening in your body before you
see it yet before it shows up so you got
to keep the faith and we're here to
support each other
thank you
guys will you stand with me while I do
this okay you guys so Amber and I are up
here and this is a medical medium family
plea that those of you who have been in
this park would please once now that you
have your book and you've been here that
you would move on because there are a
lot of people who've been waiting all
day and they're not being allowed into
the park so if you've had your book
signed and you've been here I need to
ask you to please make way and let
others come in because they're not going
to be able to get their stuff signed
they won't be allowed in the park so
please please please on behalf of all of
us have a wonderful day and head on out
of the park thank you guys thank you as
quickly as you can because we only have
one hour left thanks so much guys
heavy on
my and
[Music]
seems to know
I
[Music]
seems
I
[Music]
day
you
[Music]
of
Lon heart
[Music]
only when
hello
hello new mic same person Hi everybody
so we have our last speakers of the day
they are dear friends of anon's and they
are wonderful artists actors um active
in the community wonderful human beings
Chelsea fields and Scott
bacula hi who man that's hotbody
hi well how's everybody
doing
okay this is insanity right but really
good positive in a good way
incredible to be in a group like this
you think about all the groups that are
organizing on the planet today to do
different things for people to take the
time to come here for themselves for
their bodies for their health for their
lives for their fam's lives for their
friends lives it's remarkable and that
of course speaks to Anthony you know
plain and simple uh he's been in our
life 14 15 years yeah I think since 2010
long long time um we've been
doing lemon water celery juice both
smoothies and a variety of other things
for at least 12 years yeah right yeah at
least 12
years I stopped eating uh meat at least
probably 10 years ago and that went and
then Dairy and uh sugars and
caffeine um and then I did fish for
about two more years and then that was
the end of the fish and I miss my
oysters but they don't miss
me they're Happ be there stay in the
ocean do your thing uh but uh we were
drawn to Anthony for a variety of
reasons which my wife Chelsea will
explain but I just want to say it's an
honor to be here and to be in the middle
of all
of all of us likeminded people who are
interested in doing taking control of
our health situation and and doing
something positive and sharing it and
putting it out there so uh I I Applause
to everybody that's here and for showing
up it's hot it's a long line all those
things you are all to be commended and
I'm just honored to be uh a part of this
community myself take it away I'm going
to get some cards and go hand them out
at the end of the line so if I disappear
that's where I'll be um yeah I I second
what Scott said it's just an honor
to um have like-minded people to discuss
all things mm because I'm sure you can
relate to talking to friends who aren't
mmm minded and it can be frustrating
sometimes
right where do you get your
protein
many the best cartoon I ever saw was a
um
T-Rex and wait is it a t no the long
neck what's that called long the long
neck yeah that and then the Velociraptor
behind it and the Velociraptor was
saying but where do you get your protein
and the long neck was going geez this
guy how we all feel those of us who are
plant-based um what do you guys want us
to talk
about um well the way we met Anthony was
through my my mom um and it was kind of
you know I think orchestrated in the
stars because uh my mom had a cont
contractor that was working for her um
doing some work at her house and I
didn't know him very well and he was
telling this story of his adoption which
was sort of a touching story and I was
you know listening and compassionate and
about two weeks after that he called me
and said
um hi it's Joe and I said hi and he said
I and I had noticed when he was telling
us the story
that he was coughing like that every
once in a while and he was a big
strapping
like that he would do that every you
know 30 seconds and he was very strong
strapping young guy and I at the time I
sort of unconsciously thought well
that's interesting he must be a smoker
and so he calls me like three weeks
after working for my mom and says um I
have some problems in my health and I
got this guy's
number and he's like he used the word
psychic he's like psychic he tells you
what's wrong with you do you think I
should call him first of all I'm like
why are you calling me I hardly know you
you know and but I said well Joe like he
goes do you believe in those things and
I said yeah I do absolutely and maybe
that's why he was calling me but I said
yes I do and I said what's the worst
that can happen once you start talking
to him you're going to know your your
cells in your body are going to tell you
this this feels right or this doesn't
just like when I read Anthony's first
book how many of you just your whole
body was going yes yes yes yes
right you're reading this you're like
this but this makes so much sense this
is so good okay so back to the story
with Joe so he says okay I'm going to
call him well that was Anthony that was
way back in 2009 or 10 when he was still
um doing
appointments and then I didn't hear from
him for a while and then he called me a
few weeks later and told me the whole
story which was Anthony said you have
this very unusual bacteria in your lung
it comes from and I don't remember the
exact River but it was like it comes
from the Black Snake River in Arkansas
let's say that's what it was but it
wasn't that I don't know what it was but
this was a long time ago and so Joe he
goes I don't know how you would have
gotten this Anthony says this to Joe and
Joe says well my partners parents live
on the Black Snake River in Arkansas and
I was there for a
month so he says okay why do I see
drywall and Joe said well I'm a
contractor um and he said okay the
drywall is not causing the problem but
not helping you get better can you
eliminate some of that so he said yes so
anyways Anthony said to him your doctors
are good doctors they're great but
they're going to misdiagnose this
they're going to misdiagnose it as
cancer and sure enough about a month
later Joe gets a call on a Friday night
from his doctor saying get your partner
come in here and get your things in
order
meaning you're done and of course Joe
freaked out called Anthony Anthony's
like you're fine they've just m
misdiagnosed us keep doing your protocol
and Joe is completely healthy and still
working and killing it so
yeah so how that connects to my mom is
my mom had a sciatic nerve pain for like
two years and she kept going to the her
doctors she was 86 or 84 at the time and
one doctor said to her oh Barbara this
is just this is what it is to be 80 for
and I was
like that no you shouldn't be in this
kind of pain and I kept begging her to
let me call Anthony and try to make an
appointment I didn't know him I just
heard through him through Joe and so
finally after three months of me
bothering my mom she said okay and we
called and Anthony immediately diagnosed
it as shingles a certain variety of
shingles that is not the kind where you
get the rash and we got the um
supplements for her and he recommended a
few dietary dietary
changes and within two days I called her
and I said hey Mom it's chelse and she
goes oh hi darling how are you and I was
so surprised because it was her voice
was back her real voice not the voice
that I'd heard for the last two years
that she had been in pain so she got
better and lived to be
95 passed away a few years
ago so you know we've been doing this
protocol for a long time as Scott said
and um we love it and I don't know I
maybe a few months ago I was having some
little tingling stuff down my leg and I
was doing the juicing and our whole
morning is like we have dueling juicers
we have two juicers mm juicers and our
youngest over there Owen does the whole
protocol o also so we're like excuse me
excuse me excuse me trying to get to the
sink and do our cleaning of our celery
and all that and I was I was juicing and
I was kind of like H you know why am I
even doing this this isn't because I was
having some you know some symptoms and I
was feeling discouraged and then I
thought well what else am I going to do
I'm GNA like half a cup of coffee
no so I kept
juicing um it's the best as you know um
and we love Anthony he's incredibly
generous and compassionate as you know
sometimes I talk to him on the phone and
I'm like you are so patient how do you
do it um
and anything else anything else you guys
want to know
or yeah you're all
good
how I guess maybe he has grown with his
patience over the years because his
mission which is to help everybody and
to get the books out um just override he
really is incredibly patient because
I've heard him like do you guys remember
when he did the radio show and he was
doing the before the yeah the hey House
Radio Show before the podcast sometimes
when people would call in I would just
be
like and he's just saying oh well you
can try this and do that he was super
patient because people would ask about
things that had nothing to do with their
health and that's when I'm like oh my
goodness gracious no um I think that
he's just obviously very gifted you know
he's had this amazing gift given to him
from above and
um beautiful person and we feel
incredibly fortunate to call him our
friend
yeah just one I want to say one more
thing and then we're going to go do some
other stuff uh my wife says this all the
time to everybody because we get a lot
of phone calls all the time can you get
M information to Anthony can we ask
questions can we do that
and it really is in the books and if you
and if you if you haven't read them and
if you haven't explored them um the
reason he has stopped doing in person
and all of those things was so that he
could get the information in a book so
that it would be there for everybody to
take advantage of for years to come and
that's a that's the biggest gift uh I I
I I don't think people will understand
that because we T we take for granted
Anthony's here we can you know he's
going to keep doing his thing and we're
going to keep getting question we can go
and watch him online and da d da but
it the books are invaluable and um I
encourage everybody to spread them
around and read them if you get a chance
the Brain book is insane there's I just
kept saying I can't I don't no I don't
believe that I can't believe that that's
amazing where did that come from um that
and that's a a a big read but as equally
is the celery book and I'm not selling
books up here I'm just saying uh there's
so much value in that and I'm grateful
that he
really really put himself out there to
make these books as a gift to all of us
so thank you and thanks for being here
you're amazing everybody's amazing stay
on the
[Applause]
[Music]
path I want to break free from your
time I know
I
e e
spe
know e
way e
all right ladies and I hope everybody's
having a great time this wonderful event
we are happy to have all of you here I
wish we had bigger park for all of you
guys but it is what it is I just want to
make a little announcement so um earlier
today we found two books in the middle
of the park and uh the person who lost
it they lost them came to me but
unfortunately somebody else took these
books somebody who didn't own them so
please if this person is still here
let's be fair let's bring the books back
and uh give them to the right person
okay so please ladies and gents let's be
honest and fair to each
other anyways we are still waiting for
some speakers to be here on stage
probably Anthony will be here as well I
I think I think he's going to be on
stage pretty soon and meanwhile guys I
also want to make an announcement that I
found that we found an iPhone in the
middle of the park
somebody lost an iPhone with Mickey
Mouse cover so please if you lost your
phone come to the DJ and pick it up and
we also found some Rayband glasses
please don't be shy to pick them up as
well
e e
it
guys keep walking
[Music]
pleas got here we go guys keep walking
please ladies and gentlemen
you
[Music]
ladies and
gentlemen they waited in the
line I need
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah I think we're good
[Music]
I I wouldn't take a everyone's
no I was working last night last night
from I was working up until
only
can't all be that busy you got to get
some rest oh yeah yeah
all right
everybody I'm sure Anthony will be on
stage pretty soon meanwhile just want to
remind that we found Sunglasses if you
lost your sunglasses please go to the DJ
booth we're going to give you this
pressure thing back thank you
hands together Anthony is back on the
stage
[Applause]
there we go all right you guys it's been
an amazing day an amazing day um I hope
whoever didn't get a book signed got a
signature card I don't know if you guys
have been getting those but they're
being handed
out
um those are cards that have been
infused with light signed by me recently
you got one okay and
um I can't thank you guys enough for
coming out here seriously traveling out
here I know know that everybody's
Journey was different you know some
people came from different
places some PE that's incredible some
people and many of you have overcome so
many struggles and you did everything
you could to get here I I see it I see
it and and treasure it just so you guys
know and respect it um with everything
in me truly respect it so I want you to
know that and another thing too is I
have tremend respect for each and every
one of you okay I want everybody to know
that all right
um so has been talking a lot to me
throughout this process today okay and
um I mean seriously you guys are just
incredible incredible Souls incredible
human beings and it is just an amazing
honor for me to be with you guys today
so I just want to thank you okay you
need to thank everybody's been saying
thank you to
me everybody's been saying thank you to
me and I'm like no no no no no no I
really need to say thank you to you guys
that's that's important very important
um I know that at 3 o' the park is
shutting down um so I just want
everybody to know that we're going to do
something else um I didn't expect to I
didn't think we were going to do
something else I meaning another time
another day in the future I thought
probably not maybe 10 years from now
another 10 years another nine years but
but I am going to do something soon I
want everybody to know that okay and
we're going to try to make we're going
to try to make it the best experience
anybody can ever
have and so I'm get I'm going to get my
team working on it we're going to work
hard trying to figure something out I
want everybody to know that and I hope
you guys we all get together again
someday if you guys are up for it I'm up
for it it's up to you though
okay um and I just thought I think
there's a guest I was supposed to bring
on stage do you guys have Nesbit in the
[Applause]
[Music]
back you got Nesbit we got to be careful
with Dr Nesbit
[Laughter]
of
course all right we have Dr nesbet up
here
okay Dr
asbet I know you're not a kitten I know
that don't worry but I I know you're not
a puppy dog Dr nesbit's up here Dr nesb
wants to say something Dr Nesbit is been
has been drinking too much today and I'm
really
sorry I can't get Dr Nesbit to go dry
and and get back on the
wagon he says does anybody need surgery
he's he'll be happy to perform surgery
later
on we'll set up a tent Dr nesbet I told
you that you're not supposed to say
anything crazy up here okay if anybody
knows Dr nesbet they know that he says
some pretty gnarly things and he
promised me he would stay calm and cool
and only say good things but Dr nebet
says he you know he's a board certified
psychologist and and psychiatrist okay
his answer for everything is tell
everybody just to let it go and get over
it Dr nesbet that's not
good he says if you have a problem
emotionally Dr neb says just get over
it Dr nesbet that's not the way it works
we know that okay anything anything
productive to say Dr Nesbit says truly
loves each and every one of you okay
truly does all right I knew he had it in
him I knew he I knew this chicken doctor
had a
INE all right okay I'll let Dr nesbet
go Dr nesbet wants to leave
[Laughter]
okay I don't know if that was
seamless but anyway you guys seriously I
treasure all of you get home safe
have a good time in Culver City an
amazing amazing amazing City can you
believe Culver City let us do
[Applause]
this I mean
seriously I'm gonna have to do something
for Culver City I have to do something
I'm going to figure it out anyway you
guys God bless you bless your hearts
okay have compassion for yourself
all
right and we we'll see each other again
we'll make it work somehow okay you guys
all
right all right everybody thank you so
much have a wonderful wonderful day
let's all move out orderly happy hug
have a great great
[Music]
day okay ladies and genten
uh great news uh as you remember the
story somebody took a book by
mistake uh so we got it back so I'd like
to ask the person
who lost the book to go back
[Music]
please to
one more time we found the
[Music]
e for