Anthony William the medical medium here
with a friend this is an amazing moment
for me because we you know it's
incredible work were here
this is Andrew coos ah so he's gonna
actually talk about what's happening
with his eczema how he healed from his
eczema this is going to be a great story
of healing story inspirational some
people are suffering from skin problems
too dear friend of mine we're sitting
here and hey it's great to have you here
really nice though it's really and so
the whole thing that I've always seen
out there with all these years of
decades is is that when people are
suffering from skin conditions and
whether it's eczema the psoriasis or
another skin condition that they get a
diagnosis of or don't get a diagnosis
whether it's a dermatitis or even a
vitiligo or anything and like its
grossest whatever it may be skin
relieved it it's one of the hardest
struggles that we have for so many
reasons because we can I mean there's so
many people they can't even put clothes
on it hurts so bad and the rashes can be
so difficult they can crack and they
bleed and and what I've always seen all
these years going back since I was
younger is people who probably they
can't get answers and it hasn't changed
you know 40 years ago when I was a
little kid and people would actually ask
you know they would say well does he
have answers for eczema psoriasis and I
would say well yeah Semler juice is part
of it and there's other parts of it too
but what would happen is you would think
40 years leader signs of research would
have solved it and that's what everybody
believes they believe that science
research has an answer in ten years for
everything what are we going to be in
five years do you ever feel that like
you don't I mean with other things like
it's like where are we gonna be and and
for some reason for some reason it's
it's unbelievable how it works I'm gonna
actually do some point you have a
feeling yeah mother Laurie lens
hey we're live totally unscripted so um
but you know hey everybody's looking for
answers they still are and and we get
comfortable thinking hey you know if I
ever do get something happened to me if
I ever do get some type of interruption
in my life where I'm dealing with
something because that's what it always
feels like it's like okay well now I got
a skin problem and now I have to go see
a doctor now let's go see another doctor
now you know and and deal with in the
discomfort of it all we always think
that if I was if I was to ever have
something science and research surely
would have the answers by then the
doctor must have an answer at the
doctor's office but what happens to
people with excellent psoriasis they
don't they end up bumping into walls
with this you had like some serious
stuff going on with it it's pretty so
like for us this was spring 2015 I had a
little looked like a spider bite or a
mosquito bite yeah that's persisting on
my calf and weeks were going by which
turned into months and then it started
it wasn't going away and I was getting a
little worried and then it started
getting a little like fussy like red
spots around it and that freaked me out
so I went to my primary physician look
at a bunch of ten tests biopsies blood
work everything came back inconclusive I
wasn't allergic to anything the biopsies
came back negative so she sent me to a
dermatologist and went to the
dermatologist he without testing right
with this his eyeball test said it's
ringworm and that freaked me out gave me
a bunch of antibiotics with two went
home got two antibiotics within a
12-hour window my whole block body blew
up yeah in in spots and I freaked out
called him told me to get off it I went
back into his office that same day the
following day
initially of seeing him put me on more
antibiotics and then that kind of set in
motion this four and a half year journey
that I've included seeing three
dermatologists one in Encino and in
Westlake one in Beverly Hills
I saw one dermatologist in Tokyo I saw
two allergists I saw a pathologists I
saw two acupuncturists my primary
physician and they basically all told me
that there was no cure that my body was
attacking himself it was some type of
blanket autoimmune situation happening
well that's a thing so you've heard that
your body's attacking itself hmm I mean
definitely from pretty much from all of
all the doctors I hope they said yeah
and that the only treatment for it was
steroids
one one of the doctors went so far as to
say I might like to wear loose clothes
that it might be the materials in my
clothes that to stay away from extreme
hot and cold weather situations humidity
you know not humidity you know dry here
too you know that's something you
probably always throw you know I noticed
none of it made sense it was it was it
was a very I was kind of thrust into
this vicious cycle of just confusion it
created more questions and answers and
that kind of set me on this path of I
was sick of using the steroids but I was
still using it to levy eight the
discomfort and pain of it and that kind
of sent me on this path of trying to
figure out some alternative methods so
that was I tried doing a gluten-free
diet but I didn't really know why to go
gluten-free because I Paul my allergy
panels came out negative to it so I did
that for six months I went sober for two
separate six months things thinking
maybe alcohol was playing a role in the
operations on my immune system I did a
blood type diet ultimately none of those
things were working with
I wasn't it wasn't attacking with the
root cause with because no one knew what
it was so fast forward from spring 2015
to this past fall of 2018 I got some
more flare ups they were persisting I
was using the steroid cream wasn't going
away January of this year I went to
Paris for work and the flare-ups got a
little worse they started intensifying a
few weeks prior to leaving overseas my
friend Karina had put me on to your
information and I bought the liver
rescue book brought it to Paris with me
hoping I could kind of read it during my
travels but I was too busy with work but
on the on the trip home at 11 hours to
kill so I figured I'd break into the
book you can crack the book with 11
hours my whole thing was I'm gonna read
a couple of them I'm gonna read a couple
chapters and pass out and was I read the
entire book I was up for 11 hours was
moved to tears you're fast reader it's a
big book with like jaundice and pandas
so it was like the introduction wrapped
me in yeah the high cholesterol
situation is something I've been dealing
with up in dealing with strap which
isn't particularly mentioning in
chapters but there's the supplement
regimen you to help with strap and then
the eczema obviously so I was able to
kind of fast-forward through a lot of
pages in the middle of the book because
it didn't apply to me and so that's how
I was able to kind of work through it
but I had my phone next to me the book I
was taking notes I was in sensing pages
it triggered me it make sense it made
all the sense in the world it was I had
never gotten an explanation what was
happening internal
yeah it was only it's autoimmune your
body's not explained how he's attacking
it was the three of your pillars of what
they were your body is attacking the
skin that's what you get out there and
the problem is with that even with the
best functional medicine doctors the
best alternative doctors conventional
doctors they still go with even if they
believe in a different modality of
healing mm-hmm okay they still believe
in the old grandfathered law that was
wrong to begin with that your body's
attacking itself that it's autoimmune
that your body is actually attacking the
skin that was a massive mistake in 1950
and it wasn't even proven there was no
science research proving it it was to
protect science it was to protect
literally science not the person because
they put the blame on you so you go to
the doctor you got you got a condition
you need help for help from and it's not
the doctors fault he doesn't know but
what happens is that you leave what's
just the answer is your body's attacking
its own and then in top of being in pain
that doesn't help because you're
wondering why is my body doing that you
know I mean that's what happens
well the inflammation thing kind of
triggered me I was taking Dragon's Blood
which sounds nefarious but it's a tree
sap yeah Amazon yeah we always look for
something in the Amazon we always look
for the new thing we always look for
something that's out there that's what
usually happened and we get told hey
someone says this let's try this let's
try that thank you awesome no no no it's
this is incredible I was doing neem oil
yeah that's one that's always play
that's getting thrown around out there
these are the trendy things that are
backed by some money and agenda the
trends that get thrown into the system
John I've seen trying this world and
you're trying that away and exactly but
it was all topical so what really kind
of resonated with me when I cracked in
the liver rescue and also I'd listen to
Anthony's to podcast episodes there's
one in 2016 I think another 2018 on
eczema psoriasis acne
and those are extremely well informative
but that was the whole point
everything was this topical thing and
the podcast and in the liver recipe
chapter on eggs I'm going to attack the
internal root of what's happening and
that's kind of exactly what I was
searching for when all this confusion
was getting stoked by the doctors that I
was I was seeing so when I finally had
gotten these answers reading this on the
plane it completely changed everything
for me in my life it changed the
trajectory in my life I ended up a week
later getting home I went to Japan for
two weeks so I couldn't institute the
protocols right away but I ended up
bringing some dulse with me and some
spirulina barley grass powder - do you
have your do you have some of this stuff
cause it's so you brought a bag I
brought of it okay I'm also paranoid
about leaving like my laptop in my car
but yeah every morning I this is some
tumor you're better at this than I am
stack them up there that's that's
unbelievable so it's like you prepare
that in the morning I prepare this in
the morning so my morning routine
[Music]
essentially I've been starting to do
some breathing exercises in the morning
for the past couple like six weeks I do
a cold shower and then I drink 40 ounces
of lemon water after the shower nice
nice and prettier direction waiting 30
minutes after you drink the lemon water
that have anything else
it's the perfect 30 minute window to
make all these and once these are all
made after that 30 minute give or take
window I make 20 ounces of celery juice
yeah
clean up the juicer do the dishes got my
stuff up and head out but all of these
are basically being a vessel for me to
take in as much fruit and
vegetables without I don't want to say
the burning but I could never eat this
much yeah vegetables in leafy greens and
fruits this is a know you're busy too
for sure you know I mean you're really
on the run you're working you're doing a
lot so having this blended up in
tinnitus this design is incredible and
and really helpful for I mean and maybe
other people try it to this way if you
can't do it this way you just try to you
get the book you learn you learn the
food see you try to get the heavy-metal
detox movie in you I have oh yeah I mean
this is this is incredible right here
when I see this I get blown away and and
I can't even tell you because he's
actually doing everything to the letter
and I mean what were you with your
condition to how to how bad it was where
I mean how uncomfortable it was to where
you are now these days I mean we're in
the past when it was at its height and
state what was it like because it'll
help people with Pima they're also
dealing with that now does they feel
they feel like they're alone and they
feel like they're the only ones going
through it and that there's no hope and
I know so many people and so many of you
guys have so many different skin
conditions and it gets so bad where you
can't even put clothes on and you're
just an agony and everything else and
you know and so by knowing that you went
through this you had that skin condition
to that degree and I maybe it just tell
me what kind of where were you at when
it was really at its all-time work
there's an all-time worst was actually
when I was detoxing prior to that it was
bad I mean it was blowing up all over my
body my legs my back arms but to the to
the weight of how of the worst it ever
got when I actually started detoxing and
I'm getting it out of you attacking the
pathogen
metals and having the state of the
topical steroid withdrawal all those
things compounded to make the flare-ups
that much worse and crazy I mean it was
literally all over my torso my back
shoulders arms legs and I want to talk
about that for a second to why that
happens because I don't even think I got
a chance to tell you about that is is as
there's a pathogen called epstein-barr
okay there's over 60 varieties of
Epstein Barr everybody has Epstein Barr
that's why you want to learn how to take
care of yourself because you can have an
Epstein bar that creates an eczema
psoriasis condition you can have an
eczema you can have an Epstein bar that
creates a bit of LIGO situation you can
have one that creates chronic fatigue
syndrome one that creates Hashimoto's
it's the reason why because there's over
60 varieties of mutations of Epstein
Barr we all have them in us that's what
we have to take care of ourselves it's
no joke that's why you need to know what
the truth is so you don't end up 10
years from now or 20 years from now with
a diagnosis and a doctor telling you you
have autoimmune and then you think it's
genes or your body attacking itself and
then nobody has answers and you're
looking for neem oil and then all of a
sudden you're looking for something else
and next thing because that's what
everybody does and and so the bottom
line is is that what's what's happening
here is that the liver gets built up
with all this toxic matter that toxic
matter is created from epstein-barr
feeding off of copper when it's eczema
psoriasis so when it's eczema or
psoriasis those two conditions that you
could get diagnosed with that's the
pathogen epstein-barr the variety of
epstein-barr there's over 60 varieties
when someone says wow he thinks that
I've seen bars everything no there's
over 60 varieties of epstein-barr
unknown to research in science the
really important a really key thing to
know and and so one of those bugs that
we all have everybody's got these bugs
in them bottom line it's not like andrew
has this bug oh wait a minute no
everybody's got it so I need you to know
so you can protect yourself so you can
actually make sure that you don't get in
trouble or anything and you heal so what
that virus does it the feeds off of
copper and he has high copper so where
did the copper come from
and that's the thing that I was kind of
perplexed on yeah
tell everybody about that whole thing I
was like where's the copper coming from
if Anthony's family thinks he's got
copper and the book says well you got
eczema psoriasis where'd the copper come
I mean I just honestly had chopped it up
to it being part of my diet with
whatever the herbicides pesticides
fungicides if it was there's copper
let's eat foods that I was eating in the
water so shower there's a lot of copper
and fungicides pesticides herbicides
rodenticides all that stuff we get in us
all the time if the neighbor spraying
something that's that's copper getting
in it and someone spraying something if
you live in a condo if you live in
apartment building and they're spraying
things pesticides whatever it is or the
highway you're driving down the highway
and your windows open and they're
spraying the sides of the highway you
just get the copper in you so you're
chalking it up to maybe some of them
that's what I had assumed it was after I
had kind of gone through what my second
369 liver cleanse I was kind of just
thinking and it kind of dawned on me at
my old house that I lived in for about
eight years
I had a copper sink the copper saying
literally a copper sink and this is
before the eczema this was before the
exec Simone exactly so I had lived in
this house starting in 2000 summer of
2010 so summer 2010 fast forward to
spring 2015 is when I got this little
bump which ended up becoming what the
eczema brake was so that's about a five
year window of me living in this house
that had I don't know if it's that
specifically but it makes a lot of sense
of getting exposed to that much it does
a toxic copper sink yeah because a
copper sink is oxidizing is what's
happening so that copper sink is
constantly oxidizing even the fumes from
that copper sink mmm the fumes alone
inhaling it getting into the bloodstream
then going up into the liver that could
be a problem that you may not have a
copper sink don't get that confused
because coppers everywhere it's in every
we're high in copper all of us and if
you have a variety of epstein-barr that
feeds off of copper you're gonna end up
with eczema and a lot of people with
women and men are ended young that women
and men are ending up with their first
sex bun the first thing that happens at
the doctor's office because here's
science and research the first thing
that happens is it's ringworm that's
that all the time I've heard this really
hurt deck decades as well I did here at
the dermatologist they think it's
ringworm you're out the doctor and the
interest he thinks it's ringworm right
at the beginning when it's really really
on how many look like it I mean I have
the pictures it was literally a ring of
spots yeah because it exactly because
and and so because it's so confusing
eczema when it starts or what it becomes
it can easily come a process we'll wait
a minute maybe it's a brain worm maybe
this is something else maybe this is
scabies maybe this is some dermatitis
maybe this is you know and that's what
happens and the family you can have
answer so for dermatitis and other stuff
anyway but the causes of course but you
know or some of these other things but
it's usually that that start up where
you get the diagnosis of that you know
ringworm could be this or it could be
Lyme did you get bit by a tick did you
get bit by a spider these are the places
they go and I get it because they just
don't understand the x-men's rises so
much but the copper the copper sink yeah
that's that's a great way of getting
toxic copper in us but copper pans
copper pots I've seen it all around if
you go to a restaurant and you don't
know but they have an old copper pot in
the back and you know and then they made
something in this copper pot in this
restaurant that you just got infused
with a whole bunch of copper and they're
scraping the bottom of that pot and it
went in the restaurant and that's how it
works you just the water supply
literally the talents the city water
supplies load it with copper a lot of
times elevated way too much copper than
it should and then we end up drinking it
we end up getting it in the restaurants
we get it and we get it in all kinds of
different places so we need to know
we're not it's all of us are high in
copper we deal with it it's a toxic
heavy metal you know it's why I drink
the heavy metal detox movies so
you said to me like you don't need to do
these things you Anthony you got
everything out of you whatever no that's
not true if I gotta eat in a restaurant
if I got to do something I'm like okay
when's my next copper load gonna happen
and but the bottom line is is that you
have to have that that bug like the
epstein-barr and you have to have the
metal copper in order to create eczema
psoriasis and this is lightyears ahead
of science and research light-years
ahead because they want it they want it
to be your body is attacking itself
because it disempowers people especially
women it disempowers be blend men you
know it disempowers you I mean and in
and there's a reason for this because
science research is there not the blame
squeaky clean squeaky clean that's how
it works and and that's the problem they
should just come out and be honest and
just be like we don't know so let's be
open to things that are working let's be
open to things that are working because
lives are critical they're important and
when you suffer and you struggle I've
seen babies with head-to-toe of eczema I
mean can you imagine a child head-to-toe
about what you had absolutely not born
with it dealing with at a young age
because you actually not know for sure
but I think back to the kind of yeah
empowerment thing I mean I think that's
that is kind of the main thing that
Anthony's information and reading his
books was podcasts following his
suggestions and his protocols has really
anchored me in a sense of getting that
empowerment back and taking control of
my health of sorts it's translated even
into some dealings with strep I used to
get strep throat pretty consistently in
my 20s then it went away I was every
time I would just go to the doctor get
amoxicillin
whatever the other antibiotic was would
do the full regiment the five seven or
ten days I forget and it would be gone
then about a year and a half ago this
was around summer fall of 2018
I got strep again for the first time in
years that have been a really long time
seven eight some odd years since I've
gotten a case of strep throat same
routine went down to the urgent care got
amoxicillin and within a few days or
within that week it's gone then fast
forward to this past April I got it
again and this time around I had
listened to Anthony's podcast episode on
streptococcus so I decided I made a
conscious decision to try to institute
some of his suggestions in there and
treating the strep throat and if it
wasn't gonna work I had prefaced that by
calling my doctor and scheduling a
meeting you'll get antibiotics the the
following three days so it was about a
Wednesday night I was feeling sick and
didn't really know what's going on then
that following Thursday
I started getting spots on my throat and
I knew immediately what it was so I
called the doctor told him I was gonna
come in on Monday so I was gonna be out
of town to schedule an appointment to
get on the antibiotics so but between
that thursday in that monday i had
loaded up on garlic thyme aromatic herbs
oregano sage honey garlic ginger i was
doing all my juices here i was taking a
lot of the supplements that he suggested
that crossover between the supplements
that he suggests for strep or have a lot
of crossover with the supplements he
suggested for eczema the reason why
because the reason why is because
epstein-barr and strep go hand-in-hand
the reason why you had this
was because you had this epstein-barr
since childhood because everybody has
strep and epstein-barr they work.they
the strep piggybacks on the epstein-barr
that's what it does they work off of
each other and and they live together
and there's a reason for this because
the distrib tends to break down the
immune system so the epstein-barr can
cause more trouble that's they work off
of each other so what you are doing now
you were you're knocking down the
epstein-barr through information and
liver rescue book you're cleaning up
your copper and then the strep was like
you're not now it's my turn basically
you were it was like wait a minute rest
the party's over and it was it was
looking for a fight and that's what
happened now it was time to actually
start kicking kicking it a lot is what
you were gonna do you've had it in your
system all these years you've been
getting bouts of it and now you're like
okay let me go after it we also said in
the podcast episode the antibiotics
actually strengthen dis Rankine it so in
this Franklin every time you take an
antibiotic it strengthens both the virus
in the bacteria streptococcus is the
bacteria the viruses epstein-barr those
both get strengthened from it from
antibiotics it's why the eczema blew up
remember when it was starting you only
they need to be anyway and then it just
blew it exploded right because it first
of all that antibiotic feeds both those
things that feeds the strep in the
epstein-barr but especially the
epstein-barr antibiotics have copper in
them antibiotics have metals in them
that's another thing too I'm not against
totally against antibiotics for certain
things but when it's used for the wrong
thing it can make things worse right
that's why the phone issue is that I was
doing with yeah these particular so it
took me three days so Thursday Friday
Saturday of doing a heavy regiment
the aromatic herbs of the garlic of my
juices I was eating a lot of bananas
which you suggested a lot of words
outside of the juices I woke up Monday
morning to go to my ten o'clock doctor's
appointment and I looked in the mirror
getting ready and the spots were gone in
this without any without any antibiotics
all using aromatic herbs juices fruit
and zinc selenium metal mall in all the
various supplements listed on what did
it feel like to take control over you're
helpless
you got your drive in the machine you're
driving it now you're driving your car
you're you took control you know content
the full context of it so that was in
April of this year I'm jumping around
here but I had attacked the eczema three
months prior so in January when I read
the book was in overseas read the book
came back then I went to Japan we might
a last-ditch effort at used doing a
conventional path and saw a doctor in
Tokyo she said the same thing loaded me
up with steroids but for the sake of
having a livable trip I was using the
steroids so then when I got back I
actually bought a juicer in Tokyo as
well I was doing celery juice every
morning so when I've gotten back in
mid-february
I started my first three six nine I
lowered my radical fat intake I bought
some of the supplements I did the lemon
water and the celery juice and the first
three six nine I did I didn't notice a
huge change I thought I was gonna be
leaps and bounds like detoxing like
crazy but what ended up happening was
was it was getting worse I was the spots
were getting worse and I listened to his
podcast about signs of signs and
symptoms of detox and it just made all
the sense in the world that my body
actually healing itself by pushing this
stuff out yeah this is how it this is
how it happens and and actually cut
myself off earlier so so going into that
nothing you know a lot of moving parts
it's the only way to do it you gotta be
dealing you gotta be you gotta be you
just got to be real and make sure
everybody we get to help them eat the
bottle yeah the bottom line is when the
liver gets built up with with the
pathogen yeah that's where I was earlier
it was the pathogen epstein-barr and the
copper when the pathogen I've seen bars
feeding off of copper inside the liver
it's releasing a derma talkin inside the
liver before you get eczema before you
get your first signs of sickness or for
this condition and so your liver starts
getting built up with more and more
Dermott oxygen your livers trying to
protect you so it holds on to it it's
keeping it there it's putting it in
storage bins it's putting it in pockets
is what it's doing and as it keeps on
building up and keeps on building up the
liver finally says okay I can't handle
this anymore what happens is people are
these on hunt on these high-fat diets
they think they have the Holy Grail when
they're on the high fat keto high-fat
you know whether it's whether it's
plant-based or not playing a bass and
they're doing these really high fat
diets what they don't realize they're
beating down their livers so if they
have the epstein-barr inside the liver
and they're doing all these high fats
and they think that's the answer because
they took away processed foods and they
took away clue and then they took away
or whatever and which is all helpful but
there's still really high fat diet
they'll end up and they're doing the
bone broth and all these things and it's
all high fat they'll end up with a
problem where they're weakening the
liver waking the liver and the liver
can't hold on to that
Dermott oxidant protect you anymore and
it can't fight the epstein-barr anymore
because the liver has its own immune
system so we all beat our livers down so
so our liver gets congested stagnant
sluggish but filled with that Dermott
oxen it's the epstein-barr
feeding off of copper and then releasing
a Dermott on st. so what does that mean
the epstein-barr is going to bathroom it
goes the bathroom in our box
that's how it works when you have lupus
it's going to bathroom releasing
chemical toxins for neurotoxins for
lupus when you have excellent psoriasis
it goes about the releases copper toxins
Dermot oxen so when it's vitiligo it
releases aluminum toxins but I'll maybe
I'll talk about that a little later so
here's the deal when you're detoxing
when you're cleansing this so you start
doing something about it
your liver is filled with this stuff
it's filled with it and before anybody
cleanses or does anything about it
little bits of it you guys little bits
of it are leaking out of the liver
because it's overburdened because we're
doing the high-fat diets all the time
because we're not taking care of
ourselves and hey it's nobody's fault
it's just it's just life you know it's
how it works nobody knows nobody knows
how to take care of their health down
here and it's all guessing games no
matter who's a professional out there I
still don't know it's unbelievable so
the liver gets filled up with these
copper toxins the derma stalks and it
starts to leach out of the liver and you
start getting your first signs just say
you're a girl and you get your first
signs of eczema you're like why am I
getting these little bits of x-men you
go to your dermatologist and they take
go off gluten you go to your your doctor
and they're like go off of this maybe
you do a clean keto diet and you're
getting a little better but then it
comes back once in a while
that's your liver being overloaded and
then releasing little bits of this
copper toxin this Dermott oxen into your
bloodstream science research does know
anything about this is all medical
medium information from my source if you
guys that are that are new here just you
can look into my books and look into the
source you'll learn how it goes but so
and then when you want to clean this up
finally when you want to do something
about it and really heal and it's the
right way to heal you're gonna end up
releasing a lot of that Dermott oxen
because you have no choice and you're
gonna clean it out or cleanse it out and
so that Dermott oxen is gonna flush out
of the liver and it's gonna float around
and it's going to end up going to her
skin and we're gonna feel like we're
getting worse before we get better and
that's the that's it's a problem with
eczema psoriasis because it's no fun it
throws us off track sometimes and it's
also a problem because there's protocol
out there or there's modalities out
there or belief systems that actually
make it worse and it's not detoxing out
it just makes it worse and that's the
problem too and so I understand that
like the the the fight out there for
wanting to heal and find things that
work because you can try a new diet or a
new way to heal or an AIP diet for your
excellent psoriasis and you can try
something and it could make it worse and
you could think you're getting better
because you're detoxing no it's actually
a diet and making it worse sometimes you
know a diet like AIP will help it make
it get a little bit better but you'll
still be in the zone of it never getting
better because what happens is like an
AI P diet the makers or the or the the
system that's built around it doesn't
even know what causes your illness to
begin with they think you have
autoimmune and your body's attacking
itself anyway they believe in the same
thing everybody else does so until you
can get away from that and realize
there's four answers and real answers
like with excellent psoriasis it's
epstein-barr feeding off of copper
coppers in your liver the Epstein bars
in your liver it produces a derma stalks
in that dirty toxin builds up in your
liver it leeches out a little bit as we
break our liver down and stagnate and
get excited and stagnant sluggish and as
it leeches out we get our first bouts of
excellent psoriasis all on our body and
we're getting our first little patches
wherever it might be and then you know
that's how it works and then if we want
to really heal it and heal it the right
way it's it's a little it's it can be
confusing when you're healing it the
right way because all of a sudden you're
cleaning up that liver and that's what
happened you're cleaning it up and it's
flushing all those Dermott auxins out
and now you got kind of a bigger bout of
it as you're chewing yeah well it was
seemingly confusing on why I was getting
worse it actually was the sign that it
was actually working so so maybe when I
first did I did my first 369 I didn't
start off the supplement excuse me
regimen that he suggest in the book
right away I really incorporated that
after my first 369 then I tried having
my normal day
they diet according to the first three
days of deliver rescue three six nine
which are basically just removing your
radical fat intake lowering your animal
protein so once if you're gonna do it
for dinner preferably and to bring in
more fruits and vegetables throughout
the daytime so I pretty much molded my
day my daily routine around that then
the flare-ups were getting worse of
sorts so I decided to my second three
six nine the following month in March
this past March and that really
accelerated things because I was doing
the supplements that's the book right
there so if you go open the book so you
were doing I mean I was doing like a
child I see nettle mowing analyzing
licorice root spirulina barley grass
powder so so like on here you'll see in
the liver rescue book excellent
psoriasis right there I don't know if
you can see it there I'm sorry guys I'm
doing this to you but you'll see
excellence crisis right there I don't
know if it's backwards boards whatever
it is and you'll see a list of
supplements in dosages it's in liver
rescue so did you ever take a look at
that oh why did I take a look at it I
got all 15 of them I did the daily
dosage recommendation and I was
basically operating on this how do I
like fully optimize myself to get rid of
this as soon as possible I was just
completely fed up and over it so I was
gonna sacrifice and do whatever it took
well you know like in the book it'll say
you know it'll have a list of things and
you'll notice in the list of supplements
one is barley grass cheese powder
because that's part of the heavy metal
detox smoothie that takes out copper out
of the liver but it's in combination you
know there's another thing spirulina it
says one teaspoon twice a day in here
but you can put in your heavy metal
detox smoothie which is actually in this
book to the whole thing but you'll see
that some of the things in the
supplement list are part of the heavy
metal detox smoothie to make sure we
the metals metals on I I'm blown away
that you actually just got into this
book like read read this book and
understood this book yeah and then
because you know it's I try to I try to
make it as easy to read as possible but
I when I get in this book this book Evie
this books got a lot of material in it
calm parents do something get into drink
but but I gotta say I'm blown away that
you went to the supplements I mean I
didn't help them I didn't help you first
of all we know each other
second of all I mean I want everybody to
know clear here that yeah we didn't have
a consultation because I don't do the
consultations because I had to just
write the books and all this and also
I'm praying that people knew that they
would know that the information is in
here but I mean you're obviously guided
because by your internal source or
workout Hertel outside source to and I'm
blown away and I'm proud of you because
I wasn't there to help you you know well
I mean the thing is was you were and I
think that that's something the the
community that antthony's to be able to
foster with is it's essentially free
information I mean he's putting all the
information out that's mostly mostly all
the information in his books is provided
for free in his hour of our long
episodes on his podcast which span like
three years in the library you can get
it out in the library not to that's the
social media is insane with all of the
live videos the catalog ones that go on
specific things there was one on eczema
and psoriasis that I'd listen to maybe
half a dozen or something just to kind
of try to familiar we're producing a
free a free video right here right I
mean you and I are just doing this right
we can help people I mean this alone you
don't have to pay for two it's insane I
mean and that was one of the biggest
kind of eye-opening experiences that I
had when I read the liver rescue for the
first time when I started really diving
into his social media and looking on all
the information on his
website was that all of this stuff was
for free and it's out there whereas all
these doctors and specialists are
requiring you to have a subscription or
they have a serum or a powder or a
tincture that they're selling or some
other websites always have you gotta you
gotta get your credit cards now then you
know look I don't even want
advertisements in front of this video
you need good YouTube you gotta wait 30
seconds and then click you got to click
the button saying you know what does it
go to stop the iPad or something it's
like no we don't want to do that because
isn't this about you healing that's what
it's about you know is it and that was
the genuine nature and it was well
received on my hand so that's what was
the easy part so like when you said that
you weren't there to directly help me
you actually were because you provided
all this information and the onus was
really on me to kind of take control and
to really Institute the things one of
the big things that I had when I was
exposed to the information and really
dived into it was the source of it I was
a complete skeptic I mean man's talking
to a spirit and what is it what is it
what is he talking to is he talking to a
ghost is you know I get to experience he
talking to an angel is he talking to a
dead physician in a thousand years
confusing that's my initial reaction I
mean just on a human level it was a
little like wait we're used to these
analytical scientific empirical that's a
thing I mean you're yep you're highly
intelligent you know you know tech you
know this you know that I mean you're
broken man you're an artist yeah you're
an artist not an artist oh man your art
is your creative he you know he's your
humble is what you are okay your humble
your and but I know I know that you're
an amazing amazing individual and being
and but but it but it took it took you
to be like wait a minute how do i well
yeah I mean it took because you know is
this guy talking to right
and I grappled with it a little bit it
like was hard for sometimes when I was
suggesting and referencing Anthony's
material to friends and family it was
like he's not a doctor right okay I
can't tell my mom I can't tell he's a
doctor he's not and my mom I mean she
when I was going through the worst of
this so this was like in March of this
year I mean she lost her her noodle I
mean she was ready to take me to see our
cousin who works at one of the best
hospitals in like Philadelphia or
something and I just tried to convince
convince her that this was part of the
process of the healing process that
they're getting worse before it got
better
so yeah just back to receiving the
information and kind of instituting it
so when I had done when I had finally
gotten all the supplements and I decided
to do the second liver cleanse the
following month in March that's when the
real the weight of how much of the
flare-ups and the intensity of it was at
its all-time high I mean I was having
sleepless nights my I would wake up in
the morning and my sheets were bloody
from from scratching it was highly
uncomfortable one measure of comfort
that I was able to find was taking
oatmeal baths that's something that kind
of just calmed me down and it alleviated
some of the pain temporarily came back
during the detox process it was very
helpful but so my own thing was like
fully optimizing so taking all the other
supplements so I'd done my second 369
and then it got worse and then finally
it started subsiding in about early
April of this year and then I decided a
few weeks then two weeks after that I'm
sorry is when that strep story I told
you about happen and I instituted
Anthony's suggestions from the
streptococcus podcast episode and within
three and a half days the strep is gone
spots the swollen asana tonsils in my
throat when you can beat strep with that
in any biotic the positive thing about
that is it wasn't saying it it means
that the strep really did weaken because
the strep gets immune to antibiotics
that's how it works that's why acne gets
worse in people because acne is caused
by streptococcus that's why you know son
strep sinus infections UTIs bladder
infections all strep related all of that
can get worse with me with antibiotics
over time but yet we meet anyone it's
because people get so bad and is so out
of control they have to take one in
order to survive did you try to reflect
but if we could learn to actually break
down that strep naturally like you did
and that's the whole thing the
information is there and the medical
medium information is there what happens
is if you get a win one win with strep
without the antibiotic you're now ahead
of the game because it's the antibiotic
that gets us in trouble with strep so
now we're ahead of the game we did you
did that with your own immune system you
did that with your own with the with the
right healing tools and when you knock
that down that's amazing what did you
feel like what you didn't have to go and
get the anyone how did you feel like
again and it's kind of circles back I
mean it was a major trigger and it also
part of the skepticism that I had and
kind of the waffling back and forth rows
like it's not it's definitely true but
the source is just bothering me of sorts
just kind of like it's hard for me to
reason but when I all of these things
kind of happen together where the heavy
detoxing of the eczema eczema was
happening in that march in leading into
the April and then that's when I got
this other thing happened with strap and
once I was able to cure that and heal
that without any drugs just aromatic
herbs supplements fruits and vegetable
the right kind the right kinds of water
and so forth yeah it sees that really
really reinforced that what he was
knowledge that he was putting out there
for these specific instances that I was
dealing with was strep and eczema were
completely accurate and on point
so after that lap that bout of strap of
couple like a week or two later I did my
third three six nine to really try to
nail this because I was gonna be
traveling in May overseas I tell people
that repeats three six nine you do it
repeats on it exact right that's that's
yeah so you did your third one
I did three so I did one in February
when in March and one in April and by
the time I did my third it was pretty
much cleared up I mean I still have some
flare-ups here and there but the the
intensity and the pervasiveness of how
much is that's completely gone I mean I
have pictures I don't know to show them
kind of where I'm at now and past but
after that third 369 it was really a
matter of kind of maintenance and how do
I make sure that I'm continuing the
protocol so that this never comes back
something I never wanted to do with ever
yeah yeah and you know when you keep on
getting rid of the copper inside your
liver and inside your body and then you
break down the epstein-barr then you
know sure you probably could go back to
eating foods that you used to eat you go
back to things I always tell people
don't eat all the fruits and vegetables
get the right stuff do for three six
nine because you know something could
happen you can get more we can get
another epstein-barr you can literally
get one you can be in a public bathroom
and get one off of a toilet seat people
laugh at that but it's just the true you
can get an Epstein bar you can get an
Epstein bar in any relationship you know
I mean I have people that have over the
years have come to me all the time and
they and you know they got sick right
when they were they were on a loved hi
they were on a loved high of a brand-new
relationship and and everything was so
excited then boom mano hit right away
and then you've got a new Epstein bar
and said why why do you think the mono
is called the kissing disease you know
that's why we but that's why they named
it that but the point is is so we're
good work we're gonna get epstein-barr
along the way everybody's got it and you
know the point is is you still want to
take care of
you still want the answers you still
want to know what to do you know they in
the liver rescue book I'm holding up
right here I have the section here strep
throat and that's the strep throat
section here and it talks about
different supplements that those are
just right there so right in there
they'll say strep throat mystery sore
throat all this other stuff and because
so many people have strep and it doesn't
even come out to the to the to the to
the full capacity where you don't get
the white spots people get this strep
throat once I wanna yeah all this trip
I've ever had were just white [__] yeah
really really gnarly a lot of people get
it that way and then a lot of people get
the mystery strap where it's that but
it's also a sore throat but the white
spots didn't come out yet and these
people get like I know I got a little
bit of sore throat this week I'm a
little rundown that's strep mmm that's
sitting there so it's important to know
that and but but when we have strep
penis there's epstein-barr and it's the
whole bit we got it knocked both those
down but um I mean that's empowering you
knock out your strip without antibiotics
one part of that there is no yeah tell
me so first strep about that I've had
that I had had in over a year and a half
was in April this past October I noticed
to a tee because I was was Wednesday it
was Game five of the Dodgers gnats game
the night before step that Tuesday
before that Wednesday game I was feeling
a little sick thought it was the
changing seasons something allergies say
men wins whatever I woke up that
following Wednesday and was completely
knocked out I mean body aches swollen
throat looked in the mirror and of
course I had I started to get spots I
heard up going to the game that
following night and was that full day
leading up to the game I was again added
in the aromatic herbs the sage the
oregano all the time garlic shots the
tumeric ginger these juices eating
bananas to alleviate the pain I was like
drinking tea and the one new thing that
I did
in this last bout that I had last month
of strep was I bought elderberry syrup
and talked about that which was
incredible it super helped alleviate the
pain that code in my throat so Wednesday
is like day one of sorts Thursday day
two of it Friday day three of it that
following Saturday I went to a wedding
in Santa Barbara and sure enough I woke
up that Saturday morning and the spots
were completely gone the body aches were
gone and it was just another
reinforcement was of late another
formation and it would talk about
empowering and heart going back to the
things you were talking about with that
but it was really kind of taking this
into your own hands and it just proved
to me that my bodies are meant to heal
themselves yeah I've read somewhere that
our gut lining re-established itself
every three days so we're in constant
motion of healing ourselves so adding
aromatic herbs and supplements and
fruits and vegetables it's just another
thing to help accelerate the healing
process and right now as it stands you
know my eczema is subsided significantly
I had the last time I saw my general
physician when I got blood work done was
2018 I think spring of 2018 and my
cholesterol level bad cholesterol in my
family and my cholesterol reading was
304 and my LD 8 March eggless
triglyceride panel there was it was
unknown and I asked I inquired with my
doctor and why there was no number
attached to that he said my
triglycerides were so high that it
didn't register there was no a number to
register I haven't gotten blood work
done since that but I have to imagine my
mind my cholesterol I can't wait and
I'll definitely follow up with you but
there's just there's no way you know why
it was off the chart like this because
I'll tell you
I thought it was just a genetic thing
because my family it runs in my family I
didn't have the best diet for a long
time I'm just kind of eating whatever I
wanted partying doing the whole thing
sure isn't really mindful of course the
reason why is because that's your liver
cholesterol is all about the liver
that's the whole point and even talking
about that in the liver rescue book with
the but that's the cholesterol producer
that's the cholesterol container so
basically that cholesterol liver gets
weak sick stagnant sluggish bad
cholesterol it's the producer of good
cholesterol that's all the liver right
there trick this arise all the liver
right there it's all about that and
insulin resistance and blood fat and all
the things they talk about and so your
liver was just in and you got copper in
the liver
you got the epstein-barr on the liver
the liver is gonna be all clogged up
with all that Dermott oxen that was
given you all the rashes of course
you're going to be having liver problems
other kinds of liver problems
cholesterol you're gonna have that issue
you're gonna have the end of the
tracklist right you're gonna have other
you're gonna have other liver issues and
that's the thing with eczema psoriasis a
lot of people actually have other liver
issues it's in different ways and a lot
of different ways not just cholesterol
they might not have the cholesterol
problem but they'll have something else
but they'll have liver saw signs of
liver condition you know liver condition
in so many other ways so but that's
incredible where you get another win
like that where your your body is meant
to heal itself when we give it the right
things when we know what we're doing
when we're not playing do you feel like
you do you feel like you're playing a
guessing game anymore if you like it
honestly feel like I have the cheat code
to life right now so it's not a guessing
yet the password I have a password I
have the cheat code it's um and it's
been transformative I mean it's pretty
much been the anchor I mean I've
incorporated a lot of other things in my
lifestyle I do cold showers I do
breathing or yeah I want people to do
that you know somebody said to me hey is
it okay if I'm out there and I'm deep
breathing in the morning at five in the
morning
and praying to the Sun I'm like yeah did
you do it go do it is it okay if I do
yoga everyday for now yeah go do it but
that here's the thing this is the hard
core answers though right because you
could do all the yoga you want and you
can do all the other practices you want
you can do all the things that I believe
in in love you can do all these things
but if you don't have the answers right
so that the real the the guessing game
problem that happens when we're sick
with things because if people they're
doing all the different stuff they do
the meditations they do this they do the
rewiring of the brane meditations with
how they think and they're thinking
positive and they're doing this and then
I'm doing the yoga now all the things
that I love out there but you can be
really sick because I've had a waiting
list of millions of people back in 2014
that all did that kind of stuff they had
all these things they went to retreats
they did this they did they were in the
hot springs they were in the Cold
Springs they were doing all these
different things and and it didn't fix
him it was great and they were also
doing and even while they were doing
this and everything else that it didn't
like so because they needed the answers
the science of research doesn't have
other than that's a guessing game don't
feel like you got the cheat code I got
the money another huge aspect of this
one when I was going through the worst
of this this is the months of February
March in April of this year I was
completely knocked down helpless and
thankfully I was able to rely on
Anthony's repost with testimonials of
various people you guys had appealed and
I had nothing to lose so I slid in and
message them on their Instagram teams
and kind of told them my story and what
was happening to me and they had any
suggestions on how to kind of deal with
it as I was going through this process
literally every single one of them
replied back how do better maybe a dozen
15 people I love you guys for helping
him out like that that is my greatest
dream right there is is you guys are
working hard on it I know you guys got
the books I know I listen I know that
many of you out there
Andrew and you know the answers in there
in the medical medium information you
guys got the cheat codes to and in but I
gotta tell you I bow to you for doing
that because you really do care and you
have compassion so when he reached out
you when you reached out and you DM them
it took people very excited a fly fly
back really fast some took a couple
weeks which was fine but literally every
single person that I am essage Don on
Instagram DM that he posted that he
posted their stories about every single
one replied to me a major major level of
comfort and reinforcement when I was
going through the whole process I mean
one of the people that stands out is a
woman named what spirit says she had
crazy debilitating okay I'm eczema
head-to-toe
she was super kind and helpful I talked
to her a bunch thank you for giving a
husband and wife in Australia I think in
down the line but also one of the main
things that I've tried to when I've kind
of told my friends and family about
Anthony and his suggestions and his
protocols is that none of these things
are like mutually exclusive like you
can't I couldn't just do celery juice
and not lower my fat intake and do the
lemon water for this connection run need
it you need it the whole puzzle right
because they know that all the card
oh it's accelerator slot and all be
that's a thing on YouTube I've seen this
on YouTube where people like I did
celery juice for five days and now I'm
gonna give Anthony a bad report that
every part and they'll do that because
they don't realize wait a minute no
medical medium information is the whole
package but yeah you can you can fix a
lot of things with celery juice on its
own which so does use by itself I had
people say hit my blood pressure's fixed
head right my aches and pains are fixed
hey this is fixed this is fixed all day
long people drinking celery alone by
itself with a crappy standard American
diet they still can fix things but with
a lot of conditions like this were the
ones I'm talking
you know with this yeah and it's you you
want to make sure you do the whole
package because that's a thing the
medical medium information correct me if
I'm wrong you can totally do that
you can set me straight you set me
straight all right but the bottom line
is with the medical medium information
what I always thought from my source ok
spirit of compassion was that it can
take you as far as you want to go that
it can keep on taking you as far as you
want to go that's what it can do if you
need to go deeper the answers are in
these books they're in the medical
scripture from my source so it can take
you further and further along
everybody's different to what's
happening with their conditions and
there's an answer in the books for
everybody and for their conditions you
just got to know how to read them and
know how to actually get through them
and get through the material and find
your answers they're in there they were
designed from my source for this you
that's major facts and that's completely
my personal experiences that's exactly
what that is what anthony's knowledge
and what liver rescue and his podcast
episodes and what his instagram and
social media provided for me is a
complete anchor so everything else that
I'm doing with the breathing exercises
in the mornings with cold showers trying
to just to be active surfing so the song
sort of all of that is rooted and
fostered because of this regimen that
I've been able to incorporate in my life
as a result of Anthony's information and
one other thing that I think is worth it
was were part of my experience that I
think might be worth mentioning that
people can relate to is when I had a
ridge below I hadn't been exposed to
Anthony's information I stopped eating
gluten or tried to stop eating gluten
for I think about a six month window it
didn't help because obviously there was
all these other things that were
happening it was never attacking the
intro
thing but when Anthony offered the
information that lutein and dairy
actually are the food sources of
pathogens that knowledge and another
that knowledge is not out there I mean
if it is it came from this source right
because I we put it out there but it
wasn't out there and I'm saying that
because it mattered to you right there's
matter no I always hope it matters to
people that they know that because that
piece of truth can sit I mean it can
save people's lives it can keep them on
track yeah it's good not to think you it
provided a sense of purpose
okay I'm removing gluten and dairy for
because of this specific thing it's not
throwing darts at a board like it might
be an allergy it might be I have to
interject with this right here because
when people think out there is that
gluten causes inflammation and that's
why you remove it but that's nonsense
because that that you only get
inflammation if you have a pathogen
that's feeding off of the gluten
creating the inflammation because that's
why there I know nine year olds they can
eat all the pizza they want pizza the
the bread they want all of them donuts
everything wheat base and everything
everything
they not only I know people all over the
world that eat all the wheat they want
here in the US they eat it wherever they
go all of it and it doesn't even affect
them because they don't have a pathogen
they don't have the strep and they don't
have the epstein-barr the feed off of
the gluten that information it comes
from my source that's where it
originated because science research
doesn't know that pathogens eat things
in order to make people sick they would
rather think it's your genes they would
or tell you you it's your genes they
would rather tell you it's it's your
body attacking itself so all I mean I
see it on YouTube choose if my friends
tell me I have friends that watch all
the youtubes out there in health and
they try to tell me what's going on out
there like aw there's there's this
person on there an influencer and
they're saying you know they're glutens
causing their inflammation because
they're reading this book or whatever
and they don't even know that it's
because it's feeding the strep causing
their acne and that's why they're
getting their acnes because the strep is
feeding off of gluten so there's you
know no one they're all guessing right
there
the vegans and the Palio's or the vegans
of the animal protein people they're all
slinging science at each other and they
all they don't even know what causes it
conditions and illnesses and people tell
me that all the time they say aw they
don't even know what causes anything but
there's all these experts constantly
putting feeds out there saying this and
this and this and the whole point I'm
trying to say is it didn't feel good to
be free from that because most matters
in freedom and that's that one atoms
life yeah medical medium information was
always about freedom you know when
spirit told me when I was younger and
said you're gonna free a lot of people
and I'm like how when I was young when I
was a kid I was like how in what way
like what do you how do you want me to
free anywhere you're gonna you're gonna
be able to message the source of it that
the information that you don't have to
be a prisoner to all of the belief
systems that are built on misinformation
and I was big words for me when I was
younger I was like what I believe system
what just information I was like what
and you know and it took a while to
figure that out I mean that how they
think that works but I just wanna I feel
good knowing you're freed from that
stuff yeah and not just being like why
stop gluten why stop dairy lactose
intolerance first of all it's not
lactose intolerance that doesn't exist
it's bugs that feed off of lactose and
create inflammation and science
researchers and know this this is
advanced information it's probably 30 40
50 years ahead of science and research
now yeah well I'm dead and gone
hopefully is a long time from now what
do you say unless someone gets mad at me
yeah and picks me off my pajamas out
there dumping the garbage out there yeah
in the aliens ooh but anyway your
information is gonna live forever that's
one thing that's funny but the bottom
line is the bottom line is I gotta tell
you something that you know I'm proud of
you man
and I'm blown away because I can do all
the talking I want I can do all the
talking I want because I got a big mouth
right that's what I hear
and but you did the work you under you
read the book you not only did that you
looked for help you went to you guys you
know me Andrew went to you guys
for help and you guys got back to him it
blows me out of the water
I adore you for that you don't even know
and because you're warriors - because
you guys are like because you you see
the flak out there and you see the
negativity because of everything because
of my source and all that because you
know no one likes a smarty aleck that
has all the answers out there and so and
I got it
but you guys are staying strong and you
were helping him you helped him and then
and then you you're making all your
stuff you're doing the heavy metal detox
movie you understood the books you
understand the supplements you also
suffered through your condition which I
mean like honestly you know that part
gets me welled up inside because knowing
that I didn't even know you mmm but yet
knowing you were suffering like that in
that agony it was it was debilitating it
was the most trying those difficult
times in my life that's 100% true but
being able to dig myself out of that and
being empowered and weaponized with this
information I like that weaponize has
been something that's leaps and bounds
change the course of trajectory in my
life and it just took some sacrifice and
just as much as Anthony sacrificing so
much of his time and his effort and
doing all the providing all this
information writing books doing speaking
engagements doing podcasts doing these
interviews you know I'm trying to
measure up to that in a sense by
instituting some more discipline in my
life and sticking to these these this
regimen with things one quick thing that
just I just realized one thing that
really gravitated to me that I
gravitated to in the liver rescue book
was when to take supplements to take
them with a glucose source not to just
take them on it oh my god it's it's yeah
that's so critical no tell us about how
big that was kind of like a big light
bulb that went off in my head was I've
been taking supplements without a
glucose or I don't know if my body was
absorbing it is that this is how it
works so everybody out there and they're
afraid of sugar they're afraid of fruit
sugar so you got fruit in here I
I mean I though their fruit fear is fear
yeah I was I fell victim to that same
misinformation up there there was
there's too much sugar in apples and in
pineapples and all the various fruits
that I've now reincorporated into my
regimen yeah that's that's another
that's another misconception out there
holding people back and that's that's
that's how it works it's be fruit fear
afraid of fruit and all the different
modalities take on that fruit fear
because they all kind of attach
themselves to the same misdirected
belief system and it's just gets people
in trouble because here's how it works
if you're taking a supplement you guys
you say you don't like me you don't like
what I'm saying
regardless listen to this if you're
taking a supplement and it's not even
recommend it by me or anything and
you're taking one out there you're only
going to receive what's in that
supplement if you have enough glucose if
you're eating fruit in your diet if
you're eating something with sugar in
your diet meaning healthy sugar because
it takes sugar to bind on to that and
drive it into the self so if you're
taking a supplement it takes sugar to
bind on to that and pull it into a cell
and that's what Andrews talking about
right now and and it's that critical so
nutrients and vitamins and minerals were
taking or anything you believe in that's
not on the medical medium directory or
or whatever the only way you're gonna
get something good out of it is you're
gonna be able to draw it into yourself
through sugar the very thing all the
different belief systems are afraid of
it's incredible how and worse celery
juice is the other helper because it's
so sodium cluster salts that bind on and
also drive the bay bind on the sugar too
and go to your brain they go to your
cells it's how we build muscles and
don't judge my muscles I'm not in the
gym every day I'm not in the gym ever
I've never gone into a gym and for a day
like that ever never been in a gym but I
ride my bicycle once in a while my
spirits talking about okay but I'm not
in the gym I'm working on the books I'm
getting everybody what they need but the
bottom line is it's the celery juice
it's a celery juice there's something in
this celery and you know and so yeah so
it's really that was a really good point
that you were saying before I threw
something it's nice and helpful because
I cannot take
my daily regimen of supplements which
I've scaled back a little but I'm still
taking a vast majority I'm taking Molly
I'm taking Mullen House roof take
register Steve taking cats claws
let me run down that for a second if you
guys got a couple more minutes if you
get hang on and be here for this is
really critical so just throw it at me
cat's claw right right
what's the cat squad I'll tell you what
it's doing on the cat's claw right real
quick I'm taking off my daily because of
my daily kind of usage of this I can
take
you know three three stuff supplements
and then drink my juice and this is
glucose source to help to low so it's
it's easier on a regimented basis
incredible yeah anyway that's in comes
ba casbah is knocking down any viruses
any streptococcus viruses like
epstein-barr which is behind excellence
Rice's you're taking your cat's claw the
vinner G cat's claw is the only one I
care about because it's the only one
that that that's incredible out there so
if you guys you know look of energy v as
in Victor I M as in Mary e rgy calm and
then they they have the best stuff that
exists on the planet right now thank God
out there and so and I applaud anybody
who makes really good stuff so the cat's
claw I'm gonna be 12 yep you got a 5 mm
CHF yes ok go together both those are
good because they both support the liver
and with eczema psoriasis you need to be
12 once again the members use the one I
use here if I had it in front you you
know on the b12
okay that's critical the bees are
important you got that cover that goes I
take lemon balm lemon balm there you go
lemon balm powerful antiviral anti-hbs
what you need see and you're taking it
now that's the key so we're covering
into this a little bit
selenium I take yep selenium is good for
the immune systems good for a lot of
parts of the body allies Annette take so
yeah well I see breaks down epstein-barr
knocks it down
powerful licorice root nettle leaf
blowing yeah but they're in the books
and we talked about those so they're in
the books yeah and there's something
else I wanted to say is that you know
it's it's you're helping people and I
gotta tell you on my honor to here
helping
I mean it's thing you know when I was
when I was a kid when I was a kid I
never thought in a million years when I
was a kid I would be on YouTube live
okay and I would be with Andrew Kusatsu
in 2019 I'm you toot a lot when I was 12
years old listening to spirit getting
ready to do my work I'm you know doing
my reads when I was in it in a stock boy
ever start doing my ratings up until 14
years old there and and I never thought
it'd be on YouTube live in 2019 June I
was 19 and this is just how incredible
is talking about your x-men how you
healed my cholesterol life is a precious
thing it's a magical thing I want to
think like your food your dinners yes
yes so this is obviously my daily
regimen and then for dinners I've just
pretty much followed the 369 protocol as
much to a tea as possible and that's
been reducing my animal by-product
intake altogether pretty much we're
moving it out I don't really eat dairy I
don't really eat eggs anymore it's good
feed the virus that creates eczema
psoriasis I'm sure that's something I've
asked well you know I see that in
YouTube to lick someone's tell me hey
there's somebody eating eggs with their
xmas rice is something like well there
goes that option and getting better
because you can't well that's you know
one of the things like for eczema
specifically it's like you can't pluck
out like celery juice all a car and
think that that's gonna heal you I mean
you got to do kind of yeah he's gotta
bring in the fruit there's no there's a
note I want to tell you that's
interesting with with celery juice
whatever good you do in your life so
you're doing all these other good pieces
of medical medium information so reduce
even makes it even stronger right if
you're doing something that's not
medical medium information that has any
value to it and not a lot does out there
if it has any value to it some of the
juice will make that value rise up and
whatever else you're doing in their life
always remember that it enhances
everything so but it's not the fix all
for certain problems but it enhances
everything you're doing making it more
powerful that you're doing good yeah so
so but so your dinners go back to that
right so I
a lot of those things and I've brought
in I've been making a lot of like soups
i steamed sweet potatoes i steamed
aggressive potatoes i make like a salad
on the side
i've been doing a lot of like a
Mediterranean kind of inspiration with
like based with a tomato Persian
cucumber onion and then I'll add like
some olives or some artichoke hearts
some avocado to switch it up because it
get kind of boring or whatever but so
that I do steamed potatoes yams sweet
potatoes and then I'll make like soups I
did a zucchini soup last night super
easy it was garlic onion zucchini some
vegetable stock some coconut milk I've
been doing squash soup so I gave the
kombucha or kombucha kombucha squash to
squash the kombucha tea kombucha tea if
you want actually heal an ailment I have
nothing against kombucha tea but it's
it's it's not it doesn't help people
heal actual conditions and yeah real
conditions so I use your recipe for that
squash soup and then I did another one
like a week or two later and just did
butternut squash instead of the common
kombucha squash it's gonna be confused
yeah you got kombucha squash delicata
toppling all the squashes to the winter
squash and you know everybody up in
North in North America or wherever were
any luck I mean different parts of the
country
planet did the winter squash is out
right now right yeah I mean it's
everywhere it's and caps and all the
Trader Joe's Buttercup butternut what
else about doing like vegetable stir
fries you know I do eat meat once in a
while but I've really kind of made a
conscious effort to really just kind of
limit that I want it's awesome talk
about that for a second t you know and
medical medium information isn't just
one way it's not just all plant-based
it's not just all raw plant-based vegan
vegetarian it's not just all paleo or
animal protein or keto or all that so
it's not any of that it's about the
right information you could bring into
what you're doing when to deal with
eczema psoriasis you do want your animal
products lower bottom line you want them
low you don't want the dairy products
you don't want the eggs you don't want
the milk the butter cheese you don't
want any
bad for it you know and you want your
fats down lower it's not even about
animal products being bad you just want
a lower animal products you want to
lower your plant fats your animal fats
because that's what it is if you're
eating an animal protein it's animal fat
so that's what that is it's animal fat
if you're eating a plant protein usually
a lot of that is just powders that are
that are designed off whatever but plant
fats if you're eating too many avocados
olives olive oil nut butter sesame oils
peanut butters almond butters if you're
doing too many of that with the vegan
diet you're not going to get your
psoriasis but your excellence rises
better if you're doing animal products
and it's too much animal print get the
pork just too much fat in it too much
chicken too much chicken fat so you just
want to keep down your fats if you're
gonna get excellence rises better that's
one of the key components see there's no
belief system here it's not about that
it's just about the right information
it's not about the diet belief system
that everybody banks on and starts
believing and then they fight for when
they don't even know why they're even
fighting for it about what causes
illness so it's not about that it's
about making sure your fats come down
when it comes down to healing something
like this and and then it's been crazy I
mean I'm I'm about to be 37 I just met
you so yeah I haven't known you or any
so I thought you're in your 20s I mean
that's a major compliment but I'm 20
anyway well that's a Google set yo
that's like a thing that likes Kreutz of
people it's like that now he's talking
to five forty years okay sure he's 20
years already a liar right there
yeah yeah anyway I just haven't felt I
haven't felt this good in my life I mean
just in terms of energy strength I mean
I'd like to think that I have I'm a
pretty athletic person with sorts of
awesome please surf sir
I played ice hockey club soccer but I do
JIT Amelie the energy levels the
strength that I feel I don't have a gym
membership so I'm not working out
regularly I'm an active person of sorts
yeah and I really really chock it up to
the fact that I've incorporated Mike
that my diets completely been flipped on
its head and I've completely reversed
the bad habits that I was doing for such
a long time and I really really think
that the anchor of this regiment
foundation your your insights on diet
have provided the strength that I'm
experiencing a moderate here it's being
a member coming on yeah thank you so
much and thank you for all the people
that are listening out there and you
know hopefully my stories has helped you
relate to that and you know other
people's stories in the metal commune
community helped me so if Mike can help
others like yourselves and obviously
that's kind of what the whole purpose of
this is in the first place so what what
I believe is you're saving lives
okay because because you know when
you're kicked down like this and you're
just I mean and you're hit hard yeah I
mean it takes people in bad places
definitely and um I'm no stranger to
knowing the hell people have been
through in their lives you're saving
lives you guys are too out there and and
but I have to tell you right now that
I'm blown blown away man and I just
appreciate you coming on that's all that
your story it's not easy to share your
story it's not easy to talk about these
things and I read I know that I don't I
don't take it for granted say hey man
just come on here I feel like I blacked
out at least three times during this
I mean 100% I think I'm scared even
rewashed you know that's how I feel
about these things I can tree watch I'm
like what did I say you did amazing
listen subscribe I know everybody says
that but I don't know anything about
tech but I'm saying subscriber alert I
know someone who knows about tech and
like and hit the like buttons too you
know yeah you don't you yeah you're you
know the inside joke okay yeah I love
you guys so we're gonna go and I'm gonna
click this button here thanks guys