[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello this is Anthony William the
medical Medium you're listening to the
medical medium radio show where each
week we bring you the most advanced
Health healing information out there
decades ahead of what's out there now in
so many ways and um today or talking
about the medical medium 28-day cleanse
the medical medium 28-day Cleanse This
is a big show because there's it there's
so much to know there's so much to
understand and um and learn to heal and
really help to get miraculous results
and move forward in your life and give
the body what it needs the body is
unforgiving in some ways that's what we
always we've always you know heard out
there that it's unforgiving in some ways
and uh meaning like it can give you a
forewarning when it's not happy but it's
also the most
forgiving forgiving of all in the sense
that if you do the right things then it
forgives you then it forgives you it can
be unforgiving when you're doing all the
wrong things for too long and then boom
it could be the most forgiving thing
there is in
existence and it's working for you
forgiving forgiving you I mean it's
unbelievable how it works and that means
reversing conditions and illnesses and
and symptoms and everything else when
you're giving it the right thing you're
doing your you're giving your body the
right thing and you're giving the body
what it needs it's amazing what it can
do it's absolutely incredible so the
medical medium 20-day cleanse 20day
cleanse is actually uh really important
to assist the body to assist it in what
it needs to move it forward so people
can push through and get through their
healing process and recover and move
forward and grow and heal and Prosper
with their health and everything else
that they need to do and that's why the
28-day cleanse was created originally by
spirit and you know somebody said hey
did you just tell me about this 28 day
cleanse when did you just come out out
with it or what happened well spirit's
been giving me this 28 day cleanse since
I was a child for anybody that needed it
for anybody that needed it you know we
go through life our livers get Mucky
gunky sluggish stagnant
problematic um our become all kinds of
different problematic in all kinds of
different ways and and what that means
is toxins from all different levels from
all different genres of toxins
everything solvents chemicals gasoline
uh petrochemicals of all different kinds
aerosol sprays plug-in sprays you name
it everything um I mean our liver has to
take the brunt it's a big part of uh
what people do to get you it's a big
part of why why people even get sick and
then and then tack on some viruses tack
on some different viruses the up SE bar
in the liver shingles in the liver other
viruses in the liver and you tack all
those on and they're all sitting inside
the liver and they're having a field day
because they're feeding off of all the
toxins so when we when we say medical
medium 28-day
cleanse that's the medical medium 28 day
cleans clean out the liver too clean out
toxins away from viruses away from bugs
away from bacteria that could be feeding
off of it giving you everything from
fibromyalgia you know multiple sclerosis
r itis Lyme disease it just goes on and
on and on and on and on so it's
important to know what you're doing I
mean you if you have an ache and pain if
you have a certain symptom if you have
tingles and numbness if you have Tremors
you know shakes if you're freezing cold
all the time running too hot you know
hot you know burning skin burning mouth
burning tongue jaw pain head pain eye
pain headaches migraines um problems in
the back problems in the legs feet
hurting Morton Norton's Mora and and um
um Morton's neuroma and planter
fasciitis and all the other things that
that people have in their feet and
everything else and digiti everything
else with their toes and the nerves and
all these problems and gout and yeah
gout and eimos orasis right and eimos
orasis I mean it goes on and on and on
and on top of that I mean diabetes
diabetes I mean blood sugar issues up
and down all over the place and think
about it brain fog confusion I mean the
list goes on and on hemorrhoids I mean
you could just you can just go on and on
and on constipation bloating whatever I
mean if is this hitting you guys is some
of you guys have some of these things
and the 20D cleanse was designed to
actually help assist people so that we
can start getting the body to back down
back down and forgive and forgive will
the body ever forget the body is like
people right people always say hey I I
could forgive no problem but I don't
think I can forget you know how when
people say that all the time well the
body you know it for forgives you I
don't think it forgets either so once
you start you know once you start doing
all the wrong things long and long and
long enough the body might say hey look
come on we need to go back there I you
know I haven't forgotten I haven't
forgotten here we need to go back to the
start back to the beginning back to
where we need to go and um it's just
amazing how how the body works the power
it has the power of healing is within
all of our bodies you need to know that
that is important to understand our
immune system the power of healing the
power of our immune system what what it
can do what our body can do it's
incredible and knowing the right
information knowing what to do knowing
what to eat knowing what to you know all
the things you need to support your
immune system and your and your your
body your digestive all your different
body systems endocrine system I mean
cardiovascular system everything that
you have it's important nervous system
central nervous system is a big one
especially that's a big one really
important to support really important to
heal really important to move forward
really important to get better is that
old central nervous system so we want to
keep that in mind all the time and
that's a big part of everybody's
symptoms when you got aches and pains
neurological when you have yeah nerves
when you have anxiety that's
neurological people don't know that I
just have an anxiety attack I have a
panic attack that's central nervous
system depression that's central nervous
system so depression anxiety all central
nervous system um that's what these are
um you know ringing in the ears nerves
those are nerves right jaw pain nerves
all headaches migraines all nerves the
so many things we have are nerve related
tingles numbness I mean Twitches spasms
cramping cramps you know when you're
when you're at night you're trying to
sleep somebody gets a leg cramp that's
the neurological that's the whole
nervous system sending that signal down
to cramp up a leg so you know when you
think about it I mean how much is is is
connected to the nerves a lot and of
course all the neurological fatigue
people have where they think it's just
fatigue or a doctor diagnosis them with
just fatigue and they think that's all
it is or just adrenals when meanwhile
they they have neurological fatigue
which is central nervous systems
burdened down by viruses you know not in
a scary way or anything but the normal
way people just walk around they're sick
they're not feeling good or in a chronic
chronic chronic way but the point is is
it's nervous system and so the 28 day
cleanse was geared in a big way to help
support and also repair the nerves give
somebody a jump no matter what they
believe in what here's the deal you know
what you'll find is in the in the
medical medium 28 day cleanse what
you'll find is that you know it it's
going to be set up a certain way it's
going to be set up a certain way with a
guideline of what and this is all from
book one just so you know medical medium
Secrets behind chronic and mystery
illness and how to finally heal so
that's book one and so if you want to
know every detail about the 28 day
cleanse you have to grab the book if you
can't afford it go to the library and
get a book um I'm sure you can get one
there and but it's really important to
look at the book someday and get the
guidelines cuz I'm going to run over
some different things and everything
about it but it's always important to
have the book so you have there have it
as a guide so you know what to do you
know what you're trying to do to get
better so that's a that's a big thing
there um so the power of the 28 day
cleanse what's it trying to even do
what's it trying to do it's trying to
get your liver healthier clean out
toxins stop it from being so sluggish
and stagnant it's restoring the nervous
system that's another thing the diet's
trying to do and it does it's rest helps
restore the nervous system okay um helps
to clear out the cardiovascular system
helps the liver so low low um high blood
pressure everybody that's walking around
with high blood pressure um low good
cholesterol High bad cholesterol
everybody walking around with all these
different things the 28-day cleanse is
there to help assist and get things back
online now what what you'll find is
since it's all set up is hey look these
are the things you need to do and we're
going to cover that a little bit of
course we're going to cover it but
you'll notice that you can go back to
healthier other healthy diets as long as
it's not you going back to you know
jumping into the bad foods jumping into
all the pork and jumping into you know
all the corn syrup and jumping into um
you know all the dairy products and and
all the milkshakes and you know whatever
and all the bacon and said pork right
and you know as long as you're not
jumping into all the fried food and all
the fast food and all the processed food
and all these other different things as
long you're not jumping into all of that
and that's the key to understand like
that's a thing to focus on but if you're
jumping into some paleo healthy
conscious diet you're jumping into some
healthy conscious vegetarian diet you're
jumping into some other high protein
conscious diet or whatever it is or even
some you know uh even if you're jumping
into a cooked vegan diet you always have
the option to go back to the 28 day
cleanse for a reboot to get rebooted
you're going go back to the medical
medium 28d cleanse to get Juiced back up
again and and that's the key and listen
everybody's different everybody has a
different issue going on different like
toxic load somebody else might have more
petrochemicals because they had gas
spilled on their hands when they're
mowing the lawn 10 years ago somebody
else might have something else in their
liver inside their body somebody may
have more pharmace euticals inside their
body from taking a lot of
pharmaceuticals to you know and that
happens too and so there's some people
that have a lot of anti-depressants
sitting in their liver and other parts
of the body some people have um a lot of
antibiotics they took them for years
that's sitting in there so you got to
always keep in mind that everybody's
different and you don't always get the
same results instantly you're never
supposed to get Clockwork Clockwork
results in a cleanse than somebody else
does how can you because everything is
different the toxic load is different
the organs are different in different
ways somebody else may have some kind of
high viral load somebody else may have a
real low viral load somebody somebody be
may be filled with a lot of bacteria
some people may not all these things
matter some people might have really
really low hydrochloric acid in their
intestinal tread in their in their
stomach and their dadum some people may
have really really low bile bile
production in the liver and so
everything play but the but the whole
point is everybody's going to be getting
something done in their body that's
going to be moving them forward that's
the whole reboot that's the whole thing
that's the power of it that's the magic
you can do the 28 day cleanse not just
one time not just one 28 day
round you can do the 28 day
cleanse two times in a row three times
in a row four times in a row you could
do it six months in a row you can do it
a year in a row miraculous benefits I've
seen people heal from everything under
the worst cases of exmos psoriasis to
all kinds of different problems with
high cholesterol high blood pressure to
neurological problems to all kinds of to
ra to Multiple Sclerosis I've seen
people turn around they're they're
turning around by the thousands and
thousands and tens of thousands actually
and even more than that hundreds of
thousands around the globe the 28-day
cleanse medical medium 28-day cleanse
really is that helpful now don't get
confused and go on the internet and be
like okay 28 day cleanse you'll probably
find some other 28 day cleanse out there
and it's not GNA be it's not going to be
this one it's not going to be this one
so you know so they always got to keep
that in mind get the book so you have it
on hand so you have something there and
that's really important um and yeah yeah
it's a big deal it's a really big deal
and so it's time to just learn what to
do you know and and and it's going to be
easy breezy it's going to be fun I mean
there's nothing easy about changing your
diet in a lot of ways but this we're
going to try to make it as easy as we
can to get it working for you so you can
do something so you can do something to
heal so you can work on it and if you
can't do the 28 day cleanse maybe you
can take some of the goodies out of it
like the celery juice like the celery
juice maybe you take the celery juice
and that's what you take every day and
you're not doing the 28 day cleanse but
you know look if you really need this
28d cleanse like most everybody does for
a reboot get things cleaned up Move
Yourself forward you should do the 28
day cleanse and you shouldn't just hey
I'll just do celery juice and mosy on my
way I mean but if it's all you can do
I'm I'm there I'm with you okay I'm
right there by your side I'm right there
along with you I'm with you so we can we
can do that's fine now now the deal is
once you start the 28 day cleanse if you
have to you can stop you don't have to
do the full 28 days some of you are just
going to be like no I'm doing the full
28 I'm doing it I'm doing it do it when
you get to the 28 you're like oh I'm
going to keep on going I feel great I'm
feeling a lot more energy I'm feel feel
my blood sugar feels a lot more balanced
everything starts feeling a little bit
better I got through any kind of really
you know mild detox that I felt come on
and got through it and whatever and some
people they don't even they just feel
better and better and better and that's
it some people get like couple good days
and one day they're like oh yeah I
remember this you know I kind of kind of
get a little like this every couple days
anyway and they start feeling funny and
then you get somebody that might be like
oh yeah I'm detoxing a little but the 28
day cleanse is going to be cleaning up
everybody's different people have
different toxic loads different
environments in their body different
problems in their body so every single
person is different but it's going to
help that's the point I've seen
miraculous benefits miraculous
unbelievable benefits but guess
what I'm not even just talking about the
benefits I'm seeing from when medical
medium the first book came
out I actually I actually am talking
about the years and the years and and
the years and the years of working on
people day in and day out day in and day
out day in and day out like total like
decades and decades and Decades of
helping
people and making sure they're getting
to where they go and I've seen people
who walked into my office okay with
walking sticks and braces on their legs
walking sticks braces on their legs or
being wheeled into my office I've even
seen situations where I've seen people
carried into my office over the decades
and uh and and I'm telling you the power
is unbelievable about what can happen
when you get fruits and vegetables and
the right kinds of fruits and vegetables
in your diet the power the power is is
is is you know just amazing it is and
that's what I'm talking about and that's
what matters that's what
matters and so you take it one day at a
time it's not to be scary it's not to be
like frightening when you hear about a
cleanse when you hear about what can I
do to change my diet you know that's
that's it's more than that it's better
than that it's better than any of that
there's nothing scary about it if you
can only do it for one week then you do
it for one week if that's all you can do
and you do it one week at a time then
hey I'm doing the 28 day cleanse I'm
doing it 7 days because you know what's
going to happen you're going to end up
doing it two weeks someday you might
even end up doing two weeks after your
one week so you go so you go two weeks
two
weeks and um and that matters and you
might even go three weeks you might even
go four weeks so think about that and
that's what used to happen I remember
years and years and years ago and over
the years I remember people coming into
the office and I've watched what the
28-day cleanse watch what the 28 day
cleanse has done for them I have watched
it and I've seen things you wouldn't
even believe that people are
experiencing now all over the world
world but I've seen things you wouldn't
even believe and that's what I'm talking
about quite quite an amazing amazing
amazing story that goes on out there
with people's healing in their body and
what they can do had people that have
done the 28 day cleanse for 6 months in
a row got them out of wheelchairs got
them out of multiple sceris got them out
of ALS I've seen people do the 28 day
cleanse for 3 months got them out of the
worst cases of Xmen psoriasis where
their body was just riddled with Xmen
psoriasis I mean yeah I've seen the 28
day cleanse
turn people's neurological systems
around so they could start talking again
functioning again getting out of bed
dropping the fatigue I've seen the
28-day cleanse turn lives around like no
other over the years and the decades
I've seen people walking in with the
worst cases of neurological lime
starting their 28 day cleanse at home
doing it for a year and then getting
stronger than they ever have there's
people now that are 75 80 85 years old
that healed 30 25 30 years ago go from
doing the 28 day cleanse and they they
they never turned back they never turned
back and I'm saying that that's the
power of the body that's the power of
the body and what the body can do it's
quite extraordinary and quite unique
everybody's unique their body's unique
their immune system is unique but what
transpires is just unbelievable and you
have to know that when you're putting in
the fruits and vegetables when you're
putting in the time and energy when
you're putting in the dedication what
can happen you have to always keep in
mind you're doing something good for
yourself and how that matters and what
happens there it really makes a
difference in your life when you have
something in your hand and you can start
using it and you can start getting
benefits any kind of benefits any kind
is
amazing and that's what matters so let's
go into this a little bit what are you
eating now what are you eating now are
you eating cheese are you eating any
cheese we're going to take that out
we're just going to have to cuz the 28
day cleanse doesn't have it are you
doing butter we got to take butter out
that's got to come out too and that's
okay I mean come on a little butter out
that's okay and we can take out some
other things too going to take out some
fish and seafood if you're doing fish
and seafood you might be totally in it
we're going to take out that this is not
scary the 28 day cleanse is fruits and
vegetables in their raw form and that
might be that might be spooky for some
people that might be spooky fruits and
vegetables in the raw form might be
actually terrifying for some it's not
it's not a terrifying thing that's why
you can do the 28 day cleanse for 7 Days
Raw fruits and vegetables for 7 days and
we're going to do it a certain way and
we're going to talk about how we're
going to do it in a certain
way we really are we really are and
that's what's going to it's going to be
really fun to get through this and
that's why I say someone said to me and
many people have said said over the
years well can I do the 28 day cleanse
for 7 days I said yeah you better
believe it and you know what happened
they ended up going 8 Days 9 days 10
days because they're getting results 11
Days 12 days 13 days 14 days 15 days
next thing you know it they're in their
third week next thing you know it you're
in your fourth week it's like that's
what I mean hey do it for three days you
might end up at seven
days that's what you that's okay there's
nothing wrong with that if that's what
you got to do I'll do it with you so
it's really important so the deal is
your body doesn't have to process any
cooked food your body doesn't have to
process any cooked food which actually
is a little bit more of a burden on the
body sometimes than raw food is that's
the whole point the raw foods filled
with all the enzymes all the fresh
enzymes and living enzymes it does help
digestion there's no question about it
so even if you're you're doing paleo why
would you eat salads if you're doing
paleo if you're doing high protein diet
why bother eating salads just eat meat
three times a day just eat meat five
times a day never touch a vegetable you
touch a salad because salads have those
living enzymes in them you touch a salad
because it actually helps your animal
protein digest there's nothing wrong
with that and when your liver gets
stronger and stronger and stronger
because you do say a 28 day cleanse
where it's all raw fruits and vegetables
and that's all it is raw fruits and
vegetables there's no Meats there's no
Dairy there's no there's no eggs of
course there's no fish but when you're
doing that and your liver starts
building up and your liver starts
getting stronger and next thing know
your bile production gets stronger it
gets increased it gets more powerful
next thing you know your hydrochloric
acid in your stomach gets stronger and
stronger and stronger and that gets
increased and now you're able to digest
better and better so when you bring on
your vegetarian diet and you happen have
fish in there you're breaking that stuff
down better you bring on your paleo diet
you bring on your animal protein diet
whatever fancy name is on the animal
protein diet and next thing you know it
you're actually breaking down the animal
protein better than you ever did before
the 28d cleanse is not just a vegan
thing it's not just a plant-based thing
it yes it's raw fruits and vegetables so
it is raw plant-based but it's not about
that if you're into doing the high
animal protein what you're doing is
you're getting a reboot you're rebooting
your liver you're actually redirecting
your liver you're actually giving it a
chance to recover you're actually bring
it around and then you're also doing the
same for your HCL and your hydrochloric
acid you're actually bringing that
around and what's Happening Here is
you're making it so yeah you want to
forge away Forge away and Forge ahead
with your your trendy diet of any kind
that you guys or whoever wants y on or
whatever your doctor whatever you're
going to have more power to do that
you're going to have more actually more
steam in the engine you're going to have
more steam in The Liver More Steam in
other places it's going to be remarkable
it's going to be remarkable think about
that think about the power of that it
matters that
much it matters that much all of it so
if you're totally into some diet of any
kind you're totally into whatever you're
doing
doing just realize what you have in your
hands you got the reboot tool you got
the tool so you can maximize whatever
diet you believe in you can maximize
whatever diet you have if you believe in
the fast food diet if you believe in
100% fast foods that that's what you
want to do you want to go to all the
fast food restaurants I can name a whole
bunch of them you can go to all the fast
food restaurants and you just in that's
your diet you want to get this chili
cheese steak you want to get these these
you know you want to get these tacos you
want to get you know these burritos you
want to get all the fast food you could
ever think you want to get these double
double cheeseburgers with bacon you want
to get all these different things you
want to get the cheese you want to get
the ice cream you want to go out to get
ice cream want to get whatever it is you
want to get a banana split which the
banana is actually really healthy in a
banana split really you just take the
banana off The Banana Splits throw out
the b throw out everything else to just
keep the banana the point is whatever
diet you like if you like the worst
greasiest trashiest terrible High greasy
fried worst abominable diet you can
actually imagine and that's how you live
and that's how you're always going to
live let's get you to do the 28 day
cleanse for a month let's get you to do
the 28 day cleanse for month because
guess what's going to happen you're
going to be able to ma maximize that
diet better you might start digesting
those trans fatty acids that are in the
fried oil you might start digesting that
lard grease from this fried you know
from like whatever the fried eggs and
and and some Diner somewhere and the
bacon grease and everything else you
might be able to digest it better but
you know what I'm trying to say you want
to go to healthier diets you don't want
to go to that diet but that's what I'm
trying to say is in general is that if
you're into like a good diet like say
you're into a healthy paleo diet right
say you're into a healthy ketogenic diet
I'm not a fan of ketogenic diets I have
to be honest say say you're you know
you're a fan of what whatever it is
vegetarian or however it is or all
cooked or whatever an all cooked diet if
you're a fan of all these this can get
you to a place to maximize your
bioproduction so you can break down and
get the nutrients out of all those other
diets that you live for or that you love
or that you were told is the best for
you and they seem to be healthy because
they have no processed food no processed
foods in there and they seem to be
healthy because they have no no junk in
there and all this other stuff so hey
but you can maximize and get all the
nutrients out of those Foods that you
wouldn't normally get out of it before
unless you did the 28-day cleanse
because the 28-day cleanse is
reestablishing your liver for the first
time and probably your whole life the
20day cleanse is rebuilding your
hydrochloric acid faster and better than
anything could better than any HCL
supplement which doesn't work and never
worked for
anybody think about that so now you can
go hey I really believe in in this
trendy diet I always have I've been on
it but now you're going going to
maximize the nutrients in that trendy
diet that you like you're going to
actually get more out of the diet that
you like or whatever like you like and
you if you don't want to go to your
other diets you want to stay with the
medical medium stuff you want to stay
with the 28 day cleanse long term if you
want to stay with the foods and also the
90-day cleanse in the thyroid healing
book if you want to stay with the foods
and life-changing foods and all the
different recipes and everything else
then you do that you can do that that's
fine you can totally do that and you can
start beating down and beating down your
illnesses and start beating down your
conditions and start moving yourself
forward because look if no one ever got
better from the 28 day cleanse if no one
ever got better from the 28 day cleanse
I wouldn't even be talking about it and
I don't mean two people getting better I
don't mean four people getting better in
a practice of hundreds of people I don't
mean anything like that I mean we're
talking the thousands now we're talking
the tens of thousands and over the years
now we're talking the hundreds of
thousands across the country and and and
across the globe are getting some kind
of benefit from the 28 day cleanse
they're getting a benefit of some kind
from the 28th day
cleanse and that is a miracle because
anything you can get out of anything and
and it's not just you take out processed
foods you're on a trendy diet you take
out processed foods you take out
something and you start feeling a little
better no this is different this is for
people who really struggle who really
need healing who really need to get rid
of illnesses who tried all the different
trendy diets of all them the elimination
diets everything last one this is this
is one of those things those tools that
Spirit gave me a long time ago when I
was a kid that actually got people out
of the worst trouble in the worst jams
and because it has the power to do so it
has the power to do so but you got to
work with it and you got to start with
it and you got to see where you can go
with it maybe you can do it for a week
maybe you can do it for 6 months
depending on what condition you have
I've seen people where they're just
Gravely ill and it took four years of
doing it but they were Gravely ill for
20 years and the four years they did it
straight consecutively got them right
out of the woods they lived their life
for the first time ever in year and
decades but either way some people it's
fast some people it's slower some people
they instantly start feeling better hey
oh my God I'm not Les I'm less achy I'm
less painy and that's what people say
all the time like oh my God my digestion
I'm not bloating as much and somebody
might say oh my God for some reason my
doctor said my liver enzymes are down
and my blood pressure is down a little
bit someone else might say hey look you
know my Gout symptoms are down somebody
else might say my sertic arthritis is
actually better it's it's like that and
everybody has a different load different
things different viruses different
problems different bugs it's important
to get the medical medium book one or
any of the other medical medium books so
you can also see what other kinds of
things like supplements for different
conditions and everything else in case
you are one of those but the 28 day
cleanse speaks for itself in so many
different ways
it speaks for itself so many different
way so many different ways It's
amazing And you the bottom line is it's
all about you healing your loved ones
your family it's all about you guys
that's what it that's what it's all
about it really is and see when you
think about that hey who can I get on
the 28 day cleans let me just see if I
can take a couple of days out of 28 day
cleanse and get my family member to do
it a little bit let me just see if I can
get somebody to do the celery juice out
of the 28 day cleanse the original
original source of celery juice by
itself is in book one medical medium
28-day cleanse it's in the book that's
the original source and before that
there were other original sources that I
put out there going back teaching people
how to do Straight celery juice and
being the only source for that and the
reason why is cuz Spirit knew what
helped people heal and how to get them
healed and how to get them better and
how to give them a chance in a break in
life when all seemed lost and hopeless
and all seemed down and they weren't
getting the right information that
celery juice has been the miracle the
miracle along the way and it's in this
book for a reason Spirit wanted it in
this book it wasn't just for me helping
people in in in in in the medical median
practice all these years helping out
clients over and over and over again all
these decades it wasn't just for them
and it was for everybody and it's yours
so let's talk about the morning what can
we do it's this is that we're talking
about raw fruits and vegetables don't
get nervous though we can also curtail
it we can shift it a little bit we can
do that we can curtail it we can shift
it a little bit we can make it a little
bit different if we have to so don't
panic yet when you hear raw fruits and
vegetables do not
panic so we start out let's just say
we're doing the raw fruits and
vegetables version of 28 day cleanse you
start with the with the cleansing
beverage in the morning celery juice is
one option cucumber juice is one option
lemon water is one option coconut water
is one
option that's an option all on its
own so I mean you just if that's what
you got to do for the 28 day cleanse
that's what you got to do so that's an
option all on its own and you can do
this you can actually get in some of
this you can do a cucumber juice if you
can't do that let's get a coconut water
if you can't do that let's get a lemon
water meaning lemon squeezed in a glass
of water let's do that if we have
to let's do
it and we can do that that's really
important so you could start the day
with a cleansing cleansing beverage
celery juice cucumber juice lemon water
coconut water with
spirulina I mean we can do that too and
I mean we have so many options herbal
tea um you know the barley grass juice
powder that I love so much you know if
you want to know which one look at look
you know you'll see which one you go to
my directory the barley grass juice
powder in water that could even work but
you have the option of doing some
different things for a cleansing morning
a cleansing morning breakfast really
important so let's go it's basically the
early morning that's before we start any
kind of real breakfast but we prepare
for that breakfast the breakfast is
going to be we make us we make a fruit
smoothie for breakfast a good Baseline
would be like three bananas two dates
and a cup of berries a cup of wild
blueberries get the Frozen wild
blueberries if this doesn't fill you up
add more berries add two cups of Frozen
wild blueberries or add another banana
don't deprive yourself when you're doing
this don't go hungry when you're doing
this also throw some papayas in there
can throw some mango in there you can
even throw some pears in there in that
smoothie if you really had to and you'll
notice that smoothie doesn't have all
this whey protein powder all these nut
Butters all this other all this other
heavy fat or all this other heavy
protein that you don't want it in it's
the whole point you're not trying to
burden your digestive tract down anymore
for a while you're trying to give it a
break so you can heal you're not trying
to burden your liver anymore you're
trying to get you're trying to give it a
break so it can heal see how it works
another healthy smoothie smoothie you
can
do is you can include greens you can
include greens you can you can include
different like spinach kale a little bit
of cilantro two stock of celery or a
spoonful of barleygrass juice extract uh
powder in there you can put you know and
and all this you can do and it's not
even just you can even curtail it to the
Heavy Metal the detox heavy metal detox
smoothie medical medium toxic heavy
metal detox you know the smoothie and
you can curtail it to that you can bring
that in and that's in the other books
you can totally do that if you're
removing heavy metals you can have that
in the 28-day cleanse
so these are some of the options the
midm morning make another fruit smoothie
if you're really hungry or starving you
have the option you don't have to go
hungry you actually have the option you
could also make two servings of your
first one and bring that in nothing
wrong with that at
all
lunchtime okay we'll talk about
lunchtime can make a salad with spinach
lettuce cucumbers as the base you can
put fruits in there papaya chunks you
can put papaya in there grapes in there
oranges grapefruits sliced mangoes in
there you can put berries in your salads
you can make a dressing with a little
bit of avocado you don't want to do a
lot because the 28 day cleanse is low
fat it's low overt fat so you could do a
little bit if that's what you
need so look other options you can chop
up some red cabbage throat in a salad
you can put Sal celery in a salad
cauliflower raw cauliflower arugula baby
kale sprouts and scallions so these are
all options so here we go now you know
that's what you can do for lunch I mean
I know
that you know that I know it seems like
it could be overwhelming for some but
honestly a salad with some with some of
these very things on there is really
delightful really delicious really
delightful and you know it it's it's
it's incredible what can happen it
really it really is and I need you to
know that it's so important to know that
so let's talk about a mid midafternoon
snacks if you're hungry could snack on
some fruits of your choice now if you
have fruit fear this is really a good
book because you can read about why you
shouldn't have fruit fear fruits are one
of the most healing cleansing Foods on
the planet that's why they're on planet
Earth that's why they've grown for us
the human race for thousands of years
how we've survived so it's a really
important food do not be afraid of it so
and that's that's important you can't be
afraid of fruit when you're doing the 28
day cleanse you're going to have to kind
of release some of that fruit for you
you might want to get the book the
medical medium book one just to just
read the fruit fear so you hear a little
bit about or hear the fruit fear radio
show and that might be something too
that can really help so afternoon snacks
of your choice apples pear slices dates
apple slices oranges grapes munch on
celery sticks alongside of these and you
can even have a spoonful of raw honey as
a great pickup too you can totally do
that if you need to so so the deal is
we're running into din now here here we
go we're heading into dinner I like a
spinach soup for dinner for the 28 day
cleanse it's really been amazing for so
many people I remember using that for so
long ago to get people better it's like
a creamy it's a creamy dinner it's a
suppertime spinach soup so you take two
bunches of spinach three medium to large
Tomatoes you can even use you know
cherry tomatoes grape tomatoes and you
can get all the details in the book to
really have it down right you can
squeeze Orange in there use a stock of
celery and add some cilantro and a
little bit of garlic if you like you put
it on highe speed in the blender and you
blend it up and it comes out nice and
creamy nice and delicious you can chop
tomatoes and put it on top you can put a
little Atlantic Sea dolls on top some
chopped scallions these are some of the
things you can do that spinach soup if
you eat it every day the things that it
can do for you people say oh I eat
spinach I eat spinach that's what people
say they'll be like oh I eat
spinach that's what they'll do I'll eat
spinach
and and and I'll say really what what
what what do you mean tell me about it
okay well I had some spinach I I think I
had some spinach on my salad it was
mixed in in the greens it was last week
I'm like okay the difference here when
you're doing the creamy spinach soup the
raw spinach soup every single night for
a little while and you can change it off
if we want to do modifications and I'll
talk about that in a minute but every
night what it can do is UN it's it's
unimaginable actually because what what
happens is I've seen it turn people
around conditions you can't even believe
skin conditions acne I mean it's just
it's endless I've seen people with eye
problems start to disappear because
they're doing the spinach soup the kotes
literally the spinach the power and the
vitamins and spinach to that degree
blend it up so your body digests it so
easy including all the different enzymes
that are in it it's really that amazing
and the thing is you're not adding in
all these bad foods cuz people will say
well I had spinach with something else I
had spinach with my whatever and that
whatever wasn't that great it was
burdening the liver giving people
problems it was giving them have a hard
time they weren't able to heal remember
this is about clearing the air giving
you some Freedom getting you better so
you can actually do this and heal that's
what this is all about very
important so moving into the evening if
you're still hungry after dinner you can
snack on an apple and a date now listen
some people who do the 28 28 day cleanse
a lot of them because it's it's a
cleanse they end up eating like hardly
anything so you need to know that that's
not where you go with this you just you
just don't say oh my God I'm on to
cleanse because I remember I did a
cleanse from some other guy I did a
cleanse from some other place some other
doctor I did a cleanse here I did a
cleanse there and what happens is they
end up not eating and they're like wait
a minute I'm going to cleanse though uh
let me just drink lemon water I don't
want to eat I'm on a cleanse and they
start doing that next thing you know it
they're starving they're hungry next
thing you know it they're crashing
because they're back on some weird
cleanse that's not the medical medium 28
day cleanse and that happens all the
time okay it doesn't happen like it is
not everybody that goes through that
everybody there's a lot of people that
say no I'm doing it to the letter no I'm
doing it the way it's supposed to be
done no I'm doing it I got the book I'm
doing it so what it means is if you're
still hungry have a snack have an apple
have a date afterwards in the evening
you don't want to go without food you
want to go and buy enough fruits and
vegetables and have a stock you don't
have to make a complicate it where
you're in the in the grocery store not
sure what to buy you grab the book and
you you get the things that are in the
book you start there and that's that
makes it even easier it's an easier
guide it's an easier way of doing it
it's really a great way of doing it
let's talk about
modifications if you don't want to eat
this exact menu I just kind of ran by
you and I didn't give you every detail
in the menu I'm only giving you some of
them if you'd like swap out the lunch
swap out the lunch and dinner dishes by
eating two salads if you want to do and
you can do two salads and have a little
bit of like a quarter of an avocado you
know you can make a dressing out of
avocado you can squeeze oranges and you
can you can put it over you can make a
mango dressing with a little bit of
avocado you can put it over your salads
or you can just you know have your
salads with all the fruit in it so you
can do two salads a day if you really
want to or you can do a smoothie for
lunch and dinner I've had people do that
all the time they're like you know I
love the heavy metal detox smoothie can
I have it twice a day i' be like go
ahead absolutely get the metals out or
somebody say well you know I really like
the 28 day cleans smoothie can I do it
twice a day can I do it three times a
day you know what you can you can as
long as you're eating I know it's not
about a starvation diet this is not a
starvation diet this isn't about
stopping eating this isn't about eating
no more it's about eating
more so that's that's the whole thing
here so you could cycle through
different salad greens so salad soup
greens if you need to as well I mean
that's the whole thing don't pay any
mind to the myth that spinach will harm
you when it's raw it's the opposite
cooked spinach is the one where the
where the the oxyc acid actually tends
to run and become
destabilized that's the problem right
there I can't believe to this day the
spinach myth has been flipped and it's
flipped where raw bad and Cook's
actually the way to do it for spinach
it's the opposite raw spinach is this is
the way to do it to get the miraculous
benefit without any harm at all on any
level and you know and that's something
to really really understand so that's
misinformation out there you want
spinach in its raw form it's not like
other vegetables you can steam you don't
want spinach cooked or sauteed if you
eat raw spinach soup every day for a
month it will be the best thing you ever
done for yourself I'm going to repeat
this if you eat raw spinach soup every
day for one month it will be the best
thing
you've ever done for
yourself don't be afraid to eat as many
greens as you'd like too and this is
this is all important to do it's okay to
to eat an entire meal of just fruit if
you had to perfectly fine actually if
that's what you want to do so these are
some of the different options you can
balance it with a few celery sticks and
maybe even some celery juice in the
morning which would be amazing I never
told anybody in my life to only eat
fruit and fruit only and that's it where
it's fruit only with nothing else never
have I ever told anybody in my life to
do that but yet misinformation goes
around hear people like oh he's all
about fruit you only eat fruit yeah sure
sure sure never said it in my life I
mean you could eat only fruit you could
but in the medical medium 20day cleanse
you'd be doing celery sticks you'd be
doing the other options too it would
just be fruit for dinner see this is
what I'm talking about and very
important to understand you can do
alternative meal you can do an
alternative meal making a mango salsa
put it on put it on salads if you need
to could chop up mangoes tomatoes
cucumbers don't be afraid of tomatoes
whatever you do do not get suckered in
to propaganda against Tomatoes you just
be cheating yourself and you know what
when you cheat yourself out of the truth
and you cheat yourself out what your
body needs and you cheat yourself out of
the very things that reverse disease and
illness and conditions and symptoms it's
a disaster it's it's just horrible it's
horrible don't cheat yourself out
because of somebody wanting to make
money on some grandioso idea out there
and starts to slam something that
actually heals the body just be careful
out there so you can do that mangoes
chop up mangoes Tomatoes cucumber celery
cilantro and garlic you can do that you
can make a delicious mango salad you can
throw it in a food processor and chop it
up in there serve it on cucumber boats
you can scrape out cucumbers you can do
cucumber noodles you can put spinach
soup over cucumber noodles something I
forgot to tell you earlier see all the
amazing things you can do and in the
place of avocado orange dressing which
is in this book by the way an avocado
orange dressing for the 28 day cleanse
try mashing up some
guacamole top that on your salad
sprinkle it with some lime
juice so another great detox dish is a
food processor grind up so you're doing
a food processor grinding up apples and
cauliflower and even a little cabbage in
there the point is you have options just
remember your Mantra though raw fruits
and vegetables 28 days of it and that's
what matters right there it matters
right there now hey wait a minute what
if you can't do raw what if you're
nervous what if you don't want to do raw
what if you're scared because you hear
about you know raw Foodies and you hear
about stuff like that
you know and and some people get
intimidated and some people just get
they get spooked by it if you hear
something like that don't get thrown you
can there's what you can do if you
really have to if you really have to add
in a cooked
option add in a cooked option I'm trying
to work with you for sure add in a
cooked option like a potato so a steamed
potato not baked potato a steamed potato
steamed only you have it chopped up and
thrown on your salad as a dinner
option now if you're not getting you
know the greatest results ever it might
it's don't think it's because you got
the potato on there which you you've not
getting the greatest results ever you
just got to do the 28 day cleanse as
long as you can you can do it for a week
you can do it for two weeks you can do
it three weeks you can do it four weeks
and that potato is going to do great for
you because it is healing and it can
help you heal so it is an option and I'm
saying don't blame the potato if you're
not getting a result quick or anything
like that because there's potato
propaganda trying to destroy the the
healthy potatoes that actually help us
heal and get us better and everything
else it's just that the 28 day cleanse
I'm trying to maximize all the raw food
enzymes but the potato will be perfectly
fine if you need that option so giving
you that option the other option would
be butternut squash or winter squash of
some kind steaming it not baking it with
olive oil steaming it and having some
slices of it or having some of that um
some pieces of the butternut squash or
cut it up in squares whatever you want
to do and steam it and put that in your
salad so that's another great option too
so you feel like hey wait a minute I can
actually do just you know a couple
little cooked options at dinner it has
to be at dinner time it really
does so if you need and I'm talking
about this if you need to pull back the
rains on this diet by swapping out
spinach soup dinner for a meal of Simply
cooked vegetables Steam and roast them
it's not going to be responsible for why
you didn't get a result after the first
day of doing it don't be like oh no I'm
doing the steam cooked vegetables and
maybe that's why I'm not better in 3
days no no no no no you can do you can
pull back the rains you can swap things
out if you're really have to you're
still going to get benefits you're still
going to move forward you're still going
to be doing some great things but I
still would like for you to maximize the
quickest quickest quickest the most
powerfullest of course doing it raw 28
Days Raw but you have these options and
they're not going to get in your way
they're going to help you so you do some
simply cooked vegetables you can you
know you can even you know do some other
things too you got the winter squash I
talked about you got zucchini you can
play with too by steaming that potatoes
yams even some broccoli and califlour
and even steaming asparagus you can do
that if you need to put it on your
salads at night at the end of the day
that's how you do it so you put it on
and that would be really you know that
would be a great way of doing it because
I know so many of you might be like hey
wait a
minute no way it's you're many of you be
like no way I can't do the raw I can't
do the raw cleanse and I know many of
you guys can so but the but but if you
feel like you can't don't don't feel
pressured you know bring in what I just
said as the dinner option put a little
bit of those very things I just said the
steamed vegetables steamed potato
steamed butternut squash put that on top
of your salad or your spinach salad or
even your lettuce salad at the end of
the day and have that for dinner and
start back up all over again in the
morning and keep on going you might even
find you might even find yourself
actually eventually saying you know what
I don't need to do the steamed vegetable
at the end of the day I'm actually good
just give me the salad give me the salad
and I'm good you might actually head in
that direction you might be there how
amazing is
that you might even be there on that
level so the body is forgiving the body
is forgiving it really is when we're
giving it the things we need when we're
giving it the things that the body
really truly needs and loves so let's
recap what is the power of the 28 day
cleanse the medical medium 28- day
cleanse what is the power what are we
talking about what's the deal that we're
talking about here okay first of all
we're rebuilding our hydrochloric acid
in the stomach that's the gastric juices
the seven blend that I talk about in
medical medium book one we're restoring
and that's the Undiscovered hydrochloric
acid complex that's actually in your
stomach that science of research hasn't
even discovered yet we're restoring that
to help break down food digest food and
to move you forward what else are we
doing we're we're cleansing and cleaning
out a liver that could have
Pharmaceutical in it old antibiotics
anti-depressants who knows what else is
in there any kind of drug it can have
anything recreational drugs from 2030
years ago it can have um petrochemicals
you know air fresheners all kinds of
toxins everything else on the sun could
easily be in their perfumes colognes
they're all inside the liver you don't
think they are in there they're in there
you want to live in denial we can live
in denial but they're in there the liver
takes it on all of it every last bit of
it heavy metals included and what are
you
doing you're you're actually getting
your liver back taking it out of
sluggishness taking it out of fatty
liver restoring it making the bile
production stronger and that bile goes
right into Theo digestive tract and what
does it do it breaks down rancid fats
that have been making you sick for years
and years and years putrified rancid sat
putrified rancid fats that have been
literally along the lining of the
intestinal tract and colon and even
bottom of the stomach and it starts to
break all that down and eat it up 20th
day cleanse is going to do a lot for
your liver your body it's going to help
feed nutrients to your central nervous
system so you can start repairing from
all the different neurological symptoms
we suffer from that I covered and many
more at the beginning of the
show it's going to help support your
adrenals make your adrenals uh Stronger
because when you're eating like the
snacks in between and everything else it
helps to support your adrenals if
someone tells you you should only eat
twice a day once a day no no no no no
actually no it's not that's not how you
restore your your adrenals it's not how
you st not how you do
it I mean you can do some intermittent
fasting you know along the way there's
other ways of doing you can you can eat
light you can do some different stuff
but it's not good to be doing that long
term forever you got to make sure you're
supporting the adrenals and and in
medical medium I talk about all about
that making it better and better so
you're restoring your adrenals you're
actually helping there you're also
lowering your viral load because you're
not eating foods like eggs and cheese
and other things that feed and gluten
that feed viruses to make you sick
because that's why people are sick
someone said to me I mean just recently
hey uh medical medium I got pain here I
got pain here my something hurts over
here um and and you know and I don't
know what it is it's just the doctors
can't figure it out they ran me through
CAT scans MRIs they've done every test
in the book every blood test in the book
they fixed all my nutritional
deficiencies they gave me $2,000 $2,000
of uh uh every two weeks of supplements
I had a person purchase but I'm still
hurting and what the hell is it Go did
they tell you you got the Epstein bar
they're like no well they said they
might have tighters for it they said
it's not the problem though and they
said I go yeah it's the problem and the
28 day cleanse helps starve out the
virus without starving you starving out
the viruses without starving you so you
can start getting better and better and
better and that's what
matters the 28 day cleanse the medical
medium one don't go out they looking for
one you're going to be to land on some
weird 28-day cleanse it's going to have
you like gobbling down all kinds of
bottles of olive oil or something and
hot pepper cayenne pepper and olive oil
or something listen the bottom line is
it was it was created to help you and
it's not like it it was just created out
of thin ear thin air it's not like I
just came out of nutritional school or
something and I'm just now I'm starting
a little cleanse I'm creating a little
cleanse out of thin air and look God
bless anybody that does that cuz it's
going to it's going to help somebody
some way this is something that has a
history of use a history of use going
back since I was a child Spirit telling
me to get people to do this since I was
a child turning their lives around since
I was a child then a teenager then a
young adult and then a you know an older
adult and then an older adult and an
older adult it's been around a long time
it's helped people that are 20 years old
22 years old and this was around before
they were even born it's helped people
for 30 year that that that are 30 years
old this has been around before they
were even
born and that's that's the difference
and I've seen it work and it's known to
work and you take one day at a time I
stand behind you guys I love you guys
I'm really proud of all of you for being
here on this show and hanging in there
with me and uh and listening about the
28 medical medium 28 day Clans just
proud of everybody take one one day at a
time you can do it we can all heal
together I love you guys greatly and
never forget that whatever you do never
forget it okay see you next show bye
now