hey tonight we're talking about toxic
heavy metals
that's one thing we're going to talk
about there and the symptoms and
conditions that toxic heavy metals
cause yep or contribute to
that's a big deal you know and toxic
heavy metals controversial topic
starting way back when i used to talk
about it years and years and years ago
first of all people were like what what
are you talking about number one
number two it was controversial of
course
i'm going to walk you through the
medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse so i'm going to walk
you through
heavy metal detox cleanse and that's
really you know i haven't walked you
guys through
any cleanses yet so i'm going to we're
going to do a little walk through on
that that's important right there
the heavy metal detox cleanse is a
morning routine
cleanse you guys it's a morning routine
but
with an added bonus of removing toxic
heavy metals
and that's what we want metals that are
very much responsible
for many of our symptoms and conditions
that plague people
literally plague people hey everybody
i'm glad we're here because we got a lot
of talk we got
we got a lot to talk about um anxiety
right toxic heavy metals are a very big
part of anxiety
crippling anxiety conditions depression
like depression where why am i depressed
things aren't that bad life is okay
things are kind of going right but i'm
clinically depressed or i'm just so
devastatingly depressed or
no one understands my depression toxic
heavy metals involve their brain
fog a big contributor to brain fog right
how about that one anybody deal with
that you guys depersonalization
how about the personalization toxic
heavy metal especially when we don't
know why
we have that depersonalization we always
try to do band-aids out there for all
these things like we're trying to do the
meditation i've seen people do that
for 40 years i've seen people do you
know all different breath work and they
do all kinds of positive
you know everything from affirmations
all the band-aids we use to try to
push by and and spiritually grow and
spiritually get better while we're
healing and all that but
when the toxic heavy metals are there it
gets in the way
it gets in the way because i've seen
people work so
hard to try to get their lives back
and try to get out of that
depersonalization that depression that
anxiety
and then they get hung up they're just
they get and they fight for it but
they're still
sick and that's really hard for people
focus and concentration issues
that's one right there bipolar that's
one right there asperger's
another one right there toxic heavy
metals right adhd
autism parkinson's parkinson's toxic
heavy metals do you know somebody that's
getting those kinds of symptoms dementia
memory loss
als and more i mean we're talking about
toxic heavy metals
got to tell you guys something cleans
the heel this is this is actually
unbelievable i was blown away when i saw
this last night i don't know if you saw
my post all right
cleanse the heel is so low in price
right now it's it's unbelievably
ridiculous unprecedented
and i'm really happy about amazon.com
right amazon reduced it they
they make the price they want that's
what they do
and when this book first came out it was
when it first came out and it still
didn't even pay for itself because this
book is a medical textbook and it
costs more to print this what happened
is amazon lowered it and they reduced
the price they reduced the price but
just as of last night
they made it 16.99 so if you're someone
who
who couldn't afford it when it was 20
and that was 40
off if you're somebody who couldn't
afford it at 20 dollars
you hit 16.99 right now 51
off if you don't want to get it free at
the library you know if you want get it
free at the library and don't even pay
for it don't even bother
but the point is it's mind-blowing i had
to tell you guys
you know because i got friends that are
getting more of them for more of the
books because of the price right now for
their friends and they're for family and
people they know
you know a backup book whatever so they
could be in a different place with it or
something
like that but the whole point is i had
to tell you guys i'm blown away
by the way these books have street cred
because millions have healed
all around the globe with medical medium
information
got their lives back all around the
globe and that's why we've been the
largest health community for the
chronically ill and safe space
that's ever been for people to get their
lives back
and you know and you think that would
make people so happy right
they're like oh my god there's the
answers and everything but you know
there's a lot of jealousy out there in
the in the health world
a lot of haters a lot of naysayers they
just don't like
people getting better unless they're in
control of it unless
other people in the industry have
control over people
but this is the largest health community
and safe space for the chronically ill
and it's really an incredible credible
thing and it's basically because i'm
discriminated against for hearing a
voice and that's where the information
comes from if you're new here
most people in the medical medium
community started their journey
seeing multiple doctors by the way i got
some things here that i want to show you
too
so it's going to be part of the the
cleanse part of the medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse so i got a few
things with me i'm going to show you in
a little bit
most people start their journey with the
whole point with the medical medium
information the whole point with the
books and the work that i had to do with
spirit of compassion going all the way
back
was because people didn't have answers
so they came to me
i wasn't looking for them they came to
me starting back since i was a child
because
they were sick they needed answers they
saw multiple doctors you got the
specialist you got the
you know neurologist the you know
pulmonologist the endocrinologist all
the different doctors gps the internist
people see a lot of doctors and they
don't get the answer some people skip to
50 doctors that's how the community was
formed
it wasn't formed because i had a great
idea
it wasn't formed because you know
because whatever
it was informed because there were money
behind it there was no
money behind the entire thing there was
no money behind it
it was formed because people saw
lots of doctors had no answers and
needed a way out
and they found the information and they
healed and that's how it worked
and that's how the community has been
basically constructed all that
and so i was known as the guy if
anybody's new here that you bring
bizarre symptoms to that's what it was
like all these years
and i don't do consultations so if you
see someone that's impostering me and
they're
saying they're anthony william and they
offer a consultation that's not me i
haven't done them for years because it's
all been about
getting information to the masses
getting information
so people can heal so that's what it was
all about also i don't offer classes too
so if someone's trying to get 500
400 from you or whatever it is and
they're saying they offer a class and
they're me
it's not me so always remember that i've
worked with many doctors over the years
helping them troubleshoot their
difficult cases most difficult cases
that's what i was known for
i've worked with hundreds of doctors
throughout the years and more
feel feel free to bring what you learned
tonight to your
practitioner to your doctor to your
healer to your whoever's
whoever is taking care of you whoever
looks after you whoever you look up to
bring the information there and you know
if you
if you'd like for sure because we're
going to cover a lot of stuff like that
so keep in mind
keep in mind that lots of doctors read
the medical medium books
and they even say they do lots of them
across the country
and around the globe there's a lot of
doctors where they their ego
doesn't control or run them so it
doesn't control or run them
and they so they'll say yeah we we do
medical medium information we love
medical medium information
patients bring medical medium books to
doctors there's that group and there's
many doctors that actually use medical
medium information but won't admit it
because
their egos run them it's perfectly
normal so that's life it's life here on
planet earth it's how things work
but but it's originally information
published of course the medical medium
book series if you're new here in the
whole bit
uh anthony has amazing skin that defies
that's funny
um read uh so i'm gonna read
if you guys are here with me you could
read
page 179 so i don't know if you guys get
your books or anything
and if you don't have the cleanse the
heel book just
just got to get ready for this book when
it comes it's a heavy book
this book is packed it's a medical
textbook it's
it's not this is not some flimsy thin
paperback health book with some concepts
that have been regurgitated they're not
original they're not unique and they're
in a pamphlet
this is actually a real book these are
textbooks they were meant for doctors
originally so
when i came out the medical medium first
book that was
meant for doctors and it was meant for
doctors and practitioners
and then but i also made i i made it
also at the same time meant for course
people who weren't doctors and
practitioners
but doctor but what happens is books
aren't written like that they're not
written also for doctors as well that's
why the books have done so good in
doctor's offices for all these years
so i got it right here if you guys want
to open up page 179
here i am i'm going to read a little bit
about it
the whole bit and tonight i'm going to
walk through
the medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanse and cleanse the heel
so i just want you to know if you've
just came on here that's what i'm doing
so i'm excited about this because i
don't think i've walked you guys through
a cleanse
at all and i'm going to be talking about
toxic heavy metals
and how toxic heavy metals are
responsible
and the cause for so many different
conditions so many different conditions
you know
um medical medium mommy says my son was
in the darkest days of
autism and after two and a half years on
medical medium information my little
nicholas
is now taking not talking playing and
expressing his emotions
god bless aw and spirit that's
incredible that's incredible i mean
that's
that's why i wake up in the morning
right there medical media mommy because
that's the whole point it's about making
sure there's
answers and i you worked hard i'm sure
you worked hard you know it's like
there's no doubt you worked hard because
you got you know it's like okay what do
i need to do
and you're an amazing mom and i'm just
so proud of you i'm so proud of you so
um and i'm gonna try to read some
comments too along the way you drink the
heavy metal detox movie incredible
so
my son is so um i do baltrose
my my son is adhd
and with your info he's doing so much so
much better
thank you incredible incredible it's
just so incredible
um it really is so here i am i'm in
the heavy metal detox cleanse right
there so it's a heavy metal detox
cleanse i know it's like backwards
probably on here
almost nobody believes they've been
exposed to toxic heavy metals you guys
exposed to a toxic heavy metal
like and that's just the way it is and
sure
they can get sick and get their symptoms
along the way and
maybe if they're sick enough and they've
seen enough doctors or practitioners or
they lost something in their life
throughout the process like the quality
of life
or or impeded their life do they come to
that place
once they learn information like this
that wait a minute
okay is toxic heavy metals doing this
what's happening
if you're wondering if you have toxic
heavy metals and where they could come
from
these suggestions may offer
enlightenment so i just want to cover a
little bit here
have you ever had a stick of gum have
you guys ever had a stick of gum
that was wrapped in a foil wrapper have
you ever used aluminum foil at a cookout
what about that right aluminum foil have
there's some bad aluminum foils and
they're all bad
but there's ones that are so bad that if
cheese
if cheese touched that aluminum foil
in heat where there would be like a
reaction that occurred from
cheese touching aluminum foil that was
heated right so see you got a like nice
mac and cheese in the oven and you've
got
foil over the top and you've got it
bacon in that oven
flakes of aluminum foil that you can't
see and even can see sometimes it's
rainbow you can't
flakes of aluminum foil will literally
be all throughout the top of that mac
and cheese
people just don't know this and that
look it's not about being afraid
like oh my god i had that mac and cheese
whoa aw is telling me
what am i gonna do no it's about just
hey let's get the metals out
that's what it is and i'm going to show
you i'm going to walk you through this
cleanse i'm just reading a little bit at
the beginning here so
have you ever used aluminum foil at a
cookout just talked about that
eaten from aluminum takeout container
have you guys ever done that
i mean hey or used aluminum kitchen
tools which yeah look look
aluminum aluminum kitchen tools where
it's a
medley of metals with aluminum in there
too you have to remember that i'm in
cleanse the heel right here by the way
if you just got on here
cleanse the heel is dirt cheap what i
mean dirt cheap it's unbelievable right
now
it's 51 off of amazon.com
i've never seen them do that the book
book was 35
originally it's 16.99 i don't know how
long it'll be it'll probably change soon
but i'm just letting you know
if you don't want to get it free at the
library there's an option for you
so kitchen tools aluminum blend
in the metal tool what even if it
doesn't seem like it's all
aluminum have you ever sipped seltzer
sip seltzer beer how many of you guys
have beer
out of a can soft drinks from an
aluminum can once
maybe once maybe twice still
what about silver fillings i know a lot
of people don't have
them they're not getting silver fillings
you know not like the old days
a lot of people had the silver fillings
but here's the thing
what about mom having the silver
fillings
what about dad having the silver
it passes on from generation to
generation to generation
you can be 30 years old right now not
have silver fillings
have a child the child can still
have toxic heavy metals like mercury
from that silver filling
because the 30 year old who doesn't have
any silver in their mouth
doesn't have any in those malgams in
their mouth has gotten the mercury from
mom and dad who
had the mercury fillings or their mom
and dad that's how
mercury works it goes down the line just
like that okay and you guys don't have
to be scared it's not about that
and you know look it's just about
getting the metals out i don't want you
scared of pots and pans i don't want you
scared of
you know high quality pots and pans all
right i don't want you scared of
silverware it's not about that
it's literally about let's get the
medals out while we're living our life
down here
you know let's get the medals out why
we're like trying to like live
and that's what it's about it's about
empowerment you guys know this i don't
know
maybe the new people here might not be
aware of this yet but medical medium
information has always been about
empowerment in fact
when the first medical media book came
on the scene it was the only
medical empowerment book out and i'm not
talking about spiritual about
medical empowerment having answers it
was the old first time boom there was
there was actually
answers to why we're sick it's all about
that so
many people have been exposed to mercury
throughout the you know throughout those
dental fillings
having them removed you know isn't just
an easy fix either
you know that's how we also get more
mercury in this but even though we have
to get some
removed over time because they break
like i talk about or crack or the tooth
cracks or something that's when you get
them out
the extraction process can be re-exposed
you know can be a re-exposure for
someone with the mercury fillings
because it emits mercury vapor
throughout the bloodstream that's why i
recommend only having one silver filling
removed per dentist visit
and that's only if the silver filling is
starting to fall apart or loosen or if
there's a problem with the tooth
so we're gonna be reading we're gonna
i'm gonna walk you through the heavy
metal detox cleanse
so that's what we're going to do have
you ever had a fluoride treatment
yeah right how many people had a
fluoride treatment even if not recently
have you had one at any point over the
years perhaps going back to childhood
the fluoride used for treatments is a
byproduct of aluminum
a methyl aluminum neurotoxin created
from manufacturing aluminum
almost all of us have been exposed to it
in one way or another
and whether from fluoride treatments
from toothpaste or fluoridated tap water
and if we're if we have that exposure it
hasn't left our bodies unless we've
taken the proper
steps to remove it make sure if you're
worried about fluoridated tap water
if you're worried about these things in
your tap water make sure you have a
water pure
of fire not a water filter not not
a water not an alkaline water ionizer
machine that doesn't take care of these
things
most of these things it just won't make
sure it's a water purifier if you're
really worried about what's in your
water and i've been saying that to
people
forever speaking of tap water town and
city water supplies
all have trace levels of toxic heavy
metals such
as lead arsenic copper aluminum and even
mercury
they're deemed safe enough for
consumption without true knowledge of
what happens
when those trace minerals accumulate in
our body so we drink the tap water and
those metals accumulate in our body
that's what happens we drink them we
drink the tap water and
our those metals accumulate in our body
and i just don't want confusion because
people say well my alkaline ionizer
water machine takes care of all that in
the tap water it doesn't
it doesn't so it's very important to
know these things
so we you know and i've talked about
that before but i just want to make sure
since we're talking about water
that that's clear so you know ro takes
care of it other things take care of it
that's it
you know that's the whole thing so even
if you have a water filtration system at
home a good one like a purifier
a purifier you're exposed when eating
out
so we're exposed when eating out you
guys consider for example getting a
coffee at your favorite coffee shop
are you guys doing coffee drinks you
doing much tea drinks coffee drinks
anything else at the coffee shops or
anything hey let me get out there
let me start my youtube video in the car
and i'm gonna be now
doing my youtube video what's a day in
life for me you know my youtube channel
right
i'm heading off wait i'm gonna pull into
this restaurant here i gotta run in here
real quick
pull into this coffee shop i gotta get
my favorite type of coffee drink okay
i'm back in the car everybody's watching
me right
on my video now i'm heading to my
workout whatever it is
the point is is that water is not
filtered like you think it is it's just
not
so i just want to be straight up about
this stuff it's like what do i do do i
not tell you guys the truth and just
play neutral 24 7 and you guys pay the
price
or do i say it like it is and take all
the crap i get
24 7 from all the naysayers and haters
and everybody else
i'd rather have your back that's better
because then i could sleep at night
you know so here's the deal so you know
so you know
one cup of coffee made from the shops
tap water seems perfectly safe
but it's not one does you know and so
does one glass of tap water
at a restaurant seems perfectly safe but
it's not so does one
you know one ice in a restaurant that's
another thing
or a cup of tea you know cup of tea
brewed tea
or soda from a soda fountain that's
hooked up has anybody ever had that
before soda from like a restaurant
right no one thinks about what happens
after 10 years of stopping by
for your coffee every day of how many
medals accumulate right
you know it's like you know i was
thought about it i thought about it and
i was like okay do i want to drop the
medals
the talk about medals and everything and
i'm like yeah like
aren't they supposed to know isn't
everybody supposed to know
because okay live in denial or be afraid
or
learn and learn how to get metals out
and heal i mean
right it's the only thing that makes
sense
um so you know we get accumulations of
lead aluminum
arsenic mercury copper and what happens
when they get in our brain over time
as they get in our brain if you just got
on here i'm gonna be walking you through
the medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanse and cleanse the heel
i got my items over here they're already
pre-made though
because you know it's i'd be hard right
now to get a blender get everything else
go in here but i got everything here
um so what about bathing water
brushing your teeth all that with the
tap water have you ever used water that
flowed through copper pipes in someone's
lifetime
you know eczema eczema psoriasis
unknown to research in science and and
only known to the medical medium
information
copper plays a role copper inside her
liver plays a role
to eczema psoriasis do you ever eat out
consuming food cooked food that have
been used
metal utensils oh my god so many
restaurants
they beat the crap out of the bottom of
those
pots with metal tools and they're making
and they're doing the sauce in there and
they're
doing this like that and all these pots
i know people that i know people that
own restaurants i know people that
worked in restaurants
and the pots i remember being at my
friend's restaurant and standing there
in the back kitchen
and i would look at the pots they were
high quality but
the amount of gouges that were on the
bottom of that
pot i'm like where did i said to my
friend where do you think all this went
it's like what do you mean those are
high quality pots those are 150
a piece i'm like where do you think all
that metal went
it went into everybody's meals everybody
not at my restaurant no in everybody's
restaurant
um so anyway isn't this fun
it's probably annoying right all right
so restaurants are one of the most
common sources of toxic heavy metal
exposure
not that it's anybody's fault the
well-meaning restaurant
you know owner of course we just need to
work on taking the medals out if we want
to play
if you guys want to play reindeer games
out there right
if we want to play reindeer games and
live you know we want to be a roman
live like what all the romans and we
want to do that then
we got to also be proactive about taking
care of ourselves
or we just end up with dementia way down
the road or memory problems
or or whatever everything i was talking
about you know
wild blueberry kiss medical medium
protocols have significantly shifted my
psoriasis
after 30 years of trying everything else
wild blueberry kiss
i believe you in trying everything else
like 30 years of trying everything else
and
i love when people want to pin me down
as
oh everybody knew about fruits and
vegetables he's just another one of
those fruits and vegetables
guy no processed foods and that's why
people get better isn't that an insult
to you because think about it
you knew to take away processed foods
you knew about
fruits and vegetables right blueberry
kiss you knew about
fruit fruits and vegetables you knew
about these things but i love
how the haters they just love to try to
pin me down as generic like
he doesn't know anything different than
everybody knows oh no
meanwhile some of those haters actually
healed from only medical medium
information that's the irony to it but
i'm proud of you because that means you
got information you didn't have anywhere
else if it took 30 years and you tried
everything else and i'm not going to
insult you i believe
you tried everything else and i believe
that
and you know i mean it it's incredible
how it works
um people who keep knives in their
households right
knives how does a knife doll
how does a knife get dull how
well i i have a friend that's got a
knife so like half the knife is missing
it's like
my favorite knife favorite knife for 40
years
you know right i'm like favorite knife
for 40 years that knife is inside of you
i was like dude that knife is inside of
you
it's all you know on your cutting board
for 30 years you know and you're
sharpening it and all the
stuff on it and then you're cutting your
cut and you're cutting you know and and
then the knife is wearing down the knife
is wearing down i was like dude
you got half a knife inside you when do
you want to get it out
when when do you want to remove that
half a knife out of you because i'm
going to help you do it
anyway the minimal medium cleanse the
heel book if you just got on here
and i'm gonna be doing the medical
medium heavy metal detox smoothie you
guys
all right okay we got a cruise we got a
lot to talk about i have to work you
through this glens right
there's a i gotta you know i gotta be
quiet
all right what about the what about the
tuna roll
you've enjoyed from your favorite sushi
bar you guys ever done the sushi bar
thing
right it's fun yummy right yeah lots of
metal comes from that
no joke lots of metals that's just
straight out i'm just being straight out
have to be with that one and you know
when
you know and what about just tuna fish
all in its own have you eaten that
look you don't if you think you're
eating grass-fed beef instead so you
think you're in the clear
think again grass-fed beef
i'll tell you right now they use all the
tools
to cut the cow up how did the how does
the cow
get magically cut up
in sections and pieces and oh i have a
little the tenderloins i'll have this
i'll have whatever it is
you know uh filet mignon whatever it is
right
and how is that happening and how
are like bones cut and other things
machinery
grease on machinery i've seen i know
that when
gras and i'm not making fun of grass
said beef i'm not making fun of anything
i
we got animal protein people here we got
vegans plant-based people here
because this is about answers not about
what diet belief system is better or not
right
and when they're cutting up the cow
they're using machines
you know bone broth people don't know
that when to cut that
bone there's grease which has metal in
it
with a saw blade like one of those saw
blades
that cuts through those bone pieces so
you can make your bone broth
the amount of metal people get in bone
broth is unbelievable and no one knows
it so let's do something to get it out
nobody knows this stuff
and um and and you know and all of that
you know it's the whole bit you wouldn't
believe what they have to do for tools
when when they're cutting grass-fed beef
up you wouldn't believe
because those knives dull so quick
going through all that it's unbelievable
it's just to resharp and resharp and
resharp and metal metal metal and then
the grass fed the grass is still got
metals on the grass
it comes out of the sky it's in jet fuel
it's dropping from all over the places
it's in it's in ddt that floats around
the atmosphere
it's in it's in uh chemtrails
metal is dumping out of chemtrails
pouring out of chemtrails
on everyone okay it's not about being
afraid
i'm not afraid because i have the tools
to get the medals out
that's the whole point as simple as that
and listen if you guys think i have an
ego you know people are like oh he's got
an ego it's just for saying nobody knows
this
this what am i gonna do am i gonna what
am i gonna do am i not gonna be truthful
okay am i not gonna be truthful about
unique published information
in these books that my publisher knows
these books aren't cited for a reason
i can't get away with doing medical
books without citing
every single thing of where it came from
and there's no citations in these
the reason why there's no citations in
these it's all original
and unique so am i going to just pretend
that everybody knows all this so you can
go get information over there
the problem is when you go over there
you don't get the whole story
or you don't get all the information you
need and then you end up like blueberry
kiss she tried everything for 30 years
until she got rid of her psoriasis
through the medical medium information
but if i don't let people
know that how are they going to know how
are they going to know
all the things that that are original in
here how
you know and it's kind of sad it's like
it's like the whole thing is like one of
you know the whole thing about that is
really interesting is
how are people going to find their way
to get the answers so that's what it's
about
so let's go here um i'm reading a little
bit more
and what about pharmaceuticals the
metals that are in pharmaceuticals
i just want to cover that too and i
could go into that all day
about pharmaceuticals i can go into all
the metals
when it comes down to that and in the
air we breathe the toxic heavy metals
are coming out of exhaust
that too i mean listen there's so many
places you guys can get toxic heavy
metals it's
unbelievable unbelievable and
and um but yeah if you want you can call
it an ego i don't care that's fine with
me
i call it just you know hey i'm gonna
say the truth of where it comes from
i've helped 30
for 35 years i helped over 250 000
individuals one-on-one for 35 years
before publishing the medical medium
books i didn't appear
out of social media thin air like boom
and that's why when you look here
and you'll see millions of copies sold
of the medical media book series
millions around the world
that's because the platform isn't social
media
it's everywhere around the world in
almost every country in the world
and that's how many people are healing i
just for any new people because i know
they're going to come across
and say wait a minute my this other
person i know talks about medals
well we're going to talk we talk about
things and what's happening like nobody
does it's important so let's go
here we are and um
i want to go into a little bit more here
too there's so much information
truth is many varieties of toxic heavy
metals build up in us
over time they build up anus over time
and these are only some of the
opportunities we have in us for toxic
heavy metals
for collecting toxic heavy metals in our
bodies toxic heavy metals are hidden
and unseeable we don't see it we don't
think we have a problem
technology is not up to par for finding
out about toxic heavy metals
technology can't see the decaying
flesh inside our brains with alzheimer's
from oxidative material byproduct
oxidating and rusting off of pockets of
toxic heavy metals
and then leaching into adjacent tissue
and and making it impossible for someone
to heal
with alzheimer's unless they get metals
out hair testing doesn't do the trick
it doesn't hair testing doesn't do the
trick because
the metals are in our organs that's
where the metals go unless you just got
brand new exposure a heavy dosage and
then you can
check it in the bloodstream and but
that's only for a day or two after
a day or two boom it's in organs and
that's where it goes
so toxic heavy metals are hidden and
unseeable it's impossible to witness
that they reside within us you guys
it's hard to see that no technology has
been created yet to truly determine the
toxic heavy metals inside our organs the
need
for such technology isn't even on
research and sciences radar okay wait a
minute here
research in science doesn't care about
metals inside of us
you guys know this you guys know how
controversial medals are
so many of you guys do right season you
know like you guys are seasoned
and research and science doesn't care
about metals
they don't care about metals with
anxiety depression
all the different conditions i talked
about focusing concentration brain fog
they don't care
well so let's go into a little bit while
direct exposure to a large amount of
heavy metal
such as lead can be detected in the
bloodstream temporarily
all the other exposure that we get just
goes and goes and goes
into organs that's the whole point
instead medical research and science
tends to blame chronic illness on our
faulty bodies and genes that's how it
works the research
research of science doesn't want to know
it's toxic heavy metals
research in science wants to think it's
your genes
your body attacking itself
alternative research in science
alternative wants to believe it's your
body attacking itself
when you crack down to it it goes right
down to conventional did you know that
that alternative medicine
still is is is basically the puppy dog
for conventional medicine in so many
ways alternative medicine will still
be like no it's your fault in the end
and then spiritual medicine will tell
you that you created
created it with your own thoughts and
that's why you're sick spiritual
alternative medicine and that's not the
way to go i mean plans to heal right now
if you guys don't know it's 16 it's it's
off at amazon.com i've never seen that
before ever it's really amazing so let's
go into this a little bit more
what toxic heavy metals do to us let's
go into this
and then i'm going to walk you through
the medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanse
much as we may not want to believe it we
all have toxic heavy metals inside our
bodies
mercury aluminum copper lead nickel
cadmium barium arsenic
and toxic calcium accumulate in
different areas of different organs
the two most popular places that gather
are in the brain and the liver that's
the spots they gather that's where it
goes
toxic heavy metals carry a disruptive
charge that interferes with the
electricity that travels through your
brain
toxic heavy metals interfere with the
electrical impulses all that electricity
that runs to our brain that's swimming
around
so really important to know
neurotransmitter chemicals
are meant to use the electrical neural
highway there to carry information
and life force to every cell in your
brain
when toxic heavy metals such as mercury
and aluminum are
present or present electrical impulses
weaken
as they hit these deposits electrical
impulses
weaken as they hit all of these deposits
so important to know electrical activity
becomes diffused and that's why we get
that depression
why am i depressed why do i have
depersonalization
why do i have anxiety what about brain
fog focus and concentration issues
why do i have all these problems
electrical activity becomes diffused and
that leads to a host
of symptoms and conditions that can
develop over a lifetime
brain fog memory issues confusion
anxiety you guys dealing with any
anxiety that you're like well i don't
know why i have anxiety i shouldn't
this other person is also stressed out
and they don't have anxiety but i'm
stressed out and i do
got to get the medals out depression are
just a few toxic heavy metals in the
brain can lead to
alzheimer's disease dementia als
parkinson's and even die
and even diagnosis is such bipolar mania
and schizophrenia so it's important now
this is advanced
unique information people don't know
that out there that's not
out there so um and i have to tell you
because
it's not it it all these illnesses and
diseases and metals being the cause
is actually originally all medical
medium information and just letting
people know
and and it's important you know a doctor
friend of mine tells me
your information's unique why aren't you
telling them that because then they're
kind of like they don't know they think
it's somewhere else or they think that
everybody has this or
and then they get lost and they can't
they can't heal because they're just
going to go spinning around
and a doctor friend told me that by the
way i'm going to have um a doctor friend
on
live coming up and i'll let you guys
know when it is but i'm going to have a
guest on and we're going to split the
screen and we're going to do this it's
going to be great
anyway there's so much good stuff coming
i'm so excited by the way
so let's go into a little bit more here
it's not only that heavy metal deposits
themselves can be a problem so having a
heavy metal deposit in our brain can be
a problem all right toxic
heavy metals oxidize inside
our body they oxidize
they actually oxidize and
that's the problem and they discharge a
byproduct
that's why we get sick is a big piece of
it
that's why we get sicker in so many ways
you guys
because not only do we have the metal
deposits
inside our brain and inside our body in
other places
it starts to get old it starts to
oxidize
it starts to discharge and when it's
discharging
we get sicker the memory starts going
starts going more
starts going more anxiety starts getting
worse starts getting worse more
all these things because the metals are
oxidizing and then
if we learn how to eat better we can
kind of curve it a little bit okay
we can curve it because we're doing
something to help at least get some of
the oxidation out but not
enough so let's go in here a little bit
more okay
okay so we're heading to the heavy metal
detox cleanse
i'm gonna cleanse the heel right here
i'm glad to be here you guys okay
and by now you can see the value
of getting toxic heavy metals out of
your body i'm just reading straight out
of here
all right the heavy metal detox cleanse
is critical for anyone struggling with
the above symptoms and conditions and
also critical for eczema
psoriasis critical for eczema
and psoriasis because nobody knew
that copra was the problem like one of
the big
issues with x-men psoriasis until the
medical medium information
that's why there's miraculous excellent
psoriasis stories
thousands of them around the world
thousands of people healing it
and no one's seen that before it brings
me a lot more hate though
brings a lot more associations and
groups
and medical this and this and this they
don't like that
they don't like people healing to that
degree
that they just don't like it it's not
just about fruits and vegetables that
game is
that game is is cute and all oh just
fruits and vegetables and no processed
foods um
no it's not you can do fruits and
vegetables no processed foods and i've
seen people they can't even put a shirt
on their ex was so bad they're
suffering suffering unless they know
about getting
the copper out so important you guys it
really is
ex excellent psoriasis or signs of
someone dealing with
an elevation of toxic copper inside the
liver
where epstein-barr is also present
because you need a pathogen such as
epstein-barr to feed
off of the copper and the copper
by-product
and then when the virus that everybody
has inside of us feeds off of that
copper it releases a dermatoxin
so the people with excellent psoriasis
have the copper
unlike somebody else who doesn't have
the copper somebody else could have
chronic fatigue syndrome
because they have the epstein-barr okay
but they don't have the copper
and somebody else will have the copper
and the epstein bar is feeding off the
copper
releasing a poison when the poison's
released it's called a dermatoxin
that's a advanced information ahead of
science and research and doctors are
actually looking to these books
because of this now and then that
dermatoxin
goes to the skin especially when the
liver is toxic sluggish
and it goes to the skin and it creates
those eruptions and the rashes and
everything else
the dermatoxin is pushed into the
bloodstream and that's what happens from
the liver so
i'll talk about some other thing
vitiligo is an
overload of aluminum
over a load of aluminum inside the liver
that's vitiligo so you might be a
vitiligo sufferer
and you've already had damaged pigment
in your skin the melanin you've already
had that
but you know it'll keep on continuing on
and off oh sure if you eat better take
away processed foods and
eat cleaner eat clean paleo eat clean
plant-based eat clean
high protein keto whatever you want to
do and you can slow it down
because you're at least giving your body
a chance for the liver to
to clean a little better the bloodstream
to flow a little bit better
but the vitiligo can still not only not
heal but keep on getting worse as the
years go by until you address the
aluminum inside the liver
and young children with levels of
undetected mercury and aluminum inside
the liver and brain often deal with
attention deficit hyperactivity
disorder adhd difficulty regulating
concentration and focus
learning differences and behavioral
issues obsessive compulsive disorder ocd
toxic heavy metals you guys i'm reading
out of cleanse to heal
okay um yeah
corella i'm going to talk about that in
a little bit no don't do cruella
it's not a good thing i don't want
anybody doing the corella when it comes
down to this i'll tell you why
so toxic metals can create symptoms
symptoms can shape who we are they
become part of
who we are and you know in so many ways
and they become our story
but we don't want to live with symptoms
forever and we all that stuff so let's
go into this
i'm in the heavy metal detox cleanse now
here we are
okay i'm going to cleanse the heel um if
you're interested in this book
amazon.com has an incredible sale right
now on this book
um this book specifically 51
off it's just it's crazy really i i'm
actually really happy about it i just
want people to have the book
um get it free at the library of 16 is
still still too dicey for somebody you
know at these times
um so okay let's go
what is the heavy metal detox cleanse
it's part of a
it's like part of a routine a morning
routine
with the addition of having something
that's removing
metals because that's what it is so at
first
drink 16 to 32 ounces of lemon water
okay that's the first thing you want to
do
16 to 32 ounces of lemon or lime
water upon waking i'm just i'm reading
the book where i'll be walking you
through this right now okay
and you can see a recipe for this
there's a recipe in back okay chapter 23
you can see the recipe back here and you
can see the recipe for the proper
ratio and okay so that's the first thing
you want to do that
prepping that's what this is it's
prepping so
why drink 16 to 32 ounces of lemon water
how come like why drink it that's the
question right there on its own
you'll start the day with let you know
you'll start the day
with lemon or lime water to prime
the toxic heavy metals in your system to
be more
easily removed you're priming
the toxic heavy metals in your system to
be more easily removed
it's imperative that you're hydrated
enough
that when the heavy metal detox smoothie
goes
into your body into your system it's
able to
gather things and pull them out of the
body
if you're dehydrated it's a harder task
this has to be done a special way so the
what
in the book is 16 to 32 ounces of lemon
water right here
there's a recipe in the back of the book
there's 75 recipes in the back of the
book
there's a recipe of what of proper
ratios and all that okay
inside plans to heal right here if you
guys are on right now
so that's important to know and the why
drink
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water how come
how come he wants us to do this
it's because you're priming the toxic
heavy metals in your system to be more
accessible
more easily removed that's why it's
imperative
that you're hydrated enough that when
the toxic heavy metal smoothie starts
uprooting uprooting metals
when it starts to uproot them and trying
to remove them
it's easier you've got adequate flushing
adequate hydration to flush them out
that's the key right there so let's keep
on moving on so we're in the heavy metal
detox cleanse
you see all my little notes here i
always love i love post-it notes
love them love and love them so you know
because i could i just love quickly
going to things let's go down the other
part
okay the next part drink okay
15 to 30 minutes later 15 to 30 minutes
later roughly is fine
you know or you can you can wait a
little bit longer
you know it could be a little bit longer
if you need that's fine too right
so drink 16 to 32 ounces
of celery juice right here celery juice
on an empty stomach i talk about why
it's on an empty stomach
uh medical medium information is there
the whole thing is the um
what it's the originator of the celery
juice movement in the world if you're
brand new and you don't know where
celery juice started from came from
and never said ever someone never
juiced a stalk of celery with their
carrots or juiced celery
therapeutically as herbal medicine um
and how to do it
16 ounces on an empty stomach how it
works what it does in our body
it's all incredible it's all unique
information spirit of compassion that's
what's
a beautiful thing started recommending
celery juice in the early 70s
so if you want to know how that whole
thing started it starts from here
so let's go let's go into this right now
drink 32 ounces of celery juice on an
empty stomach wait at least 15 to 30
minutes
that's what you need to do so let's go
into this a little bit right here okay
celery juice comes next to loosen
up metals preparing them to be gathered
up by the heavy metal detox smoothie
so it takes more than just the lemon
water
to loosen these up okay the celery juice
is the next
phase to loosen up these toxic heavy
metals getting them
prepped for the heavy metal detox
smoothie
that's really important okay celery
juice also helps restore areas
where the toxic heavy metals cause
damage they cause damage
metals sit and rust and rot
that's what they do and they sit and
they hurt
cells they hurt tissue that's what
metals do
okay well you remove the metals you
still got the damaged tissue you still
got the cells in it you know they still
got the neurotransmitters
electrical impulse problems still got
all this stuff but what's fixing it
what's helping fix
it that's the whole point and so celery
juice
also helps restore areas inside organs
that have been damaged by toxic
heavy metals while the sodium cluster
salts
not sodium sodium cluster salts which is
a subgroup
of sodium undiscovered by research in
science i talked about it
all through the medical medium books
okay you can look into it
sodium cluster salts the undiscovered
subgroup of sodium that science and
research has not
uncovered yet and i don't think they're
going to care to look to be honest
because mainstream media just loves to
say sorry juice doesn't work
meanwhile we know what happened with how
the whole world has changed because of
it
um so that's it's amazing basically the
sodium cluster salts and celery juice
you guys
helps disarm the toxic heavy metal
charge metals inside our body
have a destructive charge aluminum
lead mercury arsenic all of it copper
has a destructive charge the celery
juice the sodium cluster salted celery
juice
help to disarm that charge to make them
less aggressive
and make them more malleable malleable
for the next phase of the heavy metal
detox cleanse so let's go into there
15 30 minutes later or a little later if
you want longer too if you want a little
bit longer you drink the heavy metal
detox smoothie and i got one right here
that's the one right here heavy metal
detox smoothie okay
you'll find the recipe on page 300
let me show you real quick what that
looks like
so heavy metal detox smoothie recipe
it's 175 recipes in here right there
there it is
right there so we got that okay
so that's important right there so let's
talk about why
do we need that medical medium heavy
metal detox movie okay
and you know the the this heavy metal
detox smoothie just so you know
is worldwide famous okay legit what it's
in stores
it's not it's not me i'm not putting
them in stores
i don't own all the you know all the
different stuff people are trying to do
with it
people are actually meaning people are
actually like put this is in juice bars
and stuff where they
say hey the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie people talk about it
around the world you might even be
seeing it out there
it's incredible and that smoothie right
there
is in millions of people's homes right
now in in almost every country in the
world
and you know it it's really important to
know this all right so let's go
so i saw a comment i think about okay
someone earlier or somebody earlier said
that spirulina
has too much copper okay it doesn't
that's the whole thing
and what happens is here is that there's
bad copper bad copper that's the
difference right there okay
hard bad copper from copper pipes
from other sources that we have copper
passed down to us
from fungicides that's on your clothing
so here's the difference
the copper inside a fungicide
that's on your brand new clothing that
you try on
that gets into our body and inside our
liver is not the same copper that's in
fruits not the same copper that's in
vegetables
not the same copper that's in herbs not
the same copper that's in spirulina
it's not the same copper that's trace
mineral that's trace mineral copper
that's in
all of our foods so i just don't want
that confusion
so it's really a good question right
there there's trace minerals in
all of our foods that's different than a
copper pipe
that's decaying with hard toxic copper
destructive charge that's not a food
that's getting into our bodies
from all these different on all these
different levels you know
and a high quality spirulina like you
know if you look at the directory you'll
see in the back of the book and the
medical medium.com you go to directory
you'll see high quality spirulina you
don't it's even
even better no matter what all the way
so let's go into this a little bit i
know the vimergy uh one
the vimergy spirulina has been tested
tested they actually test it
independently
for toxic heavy metals they test it
independently of energy
and that doesn't happen everywhere else
that's really rare
so that's what's incredible and it's not
grown it's not grown
in the ocean either so that's another
thing so not only is the
vimergy spirulina tested independently
for toxic heavy metals they pay for that
the amount of cost that is other
companies they don't do that the amount
of cost for that is unbelievable
it's not grown in the ocean where you
have toxic heavy metals in the ocean
either so it's another thing too so
let's go into this a little bit more and
these are all important things and
that's why people heal um
so let's go into this a little bit okay
heavy metal detox smoothie
is the main event here you guys the only
heavy metal detox protocol available
with the right combination of
ingredients
to extract deep seeded toxic heavy
metals
from your organs and round up
free-floating metals and oxidative
runoff that's why people have been
healing around the globe with
the medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie it's if you do it right make it
right at your home and talk about the
ingredients
you'll find much more on how this works
and why it's important on the pages to
follow when you go in here
cleanse the heal okay so after your
heavy metal detox smoothie you guys
you might get hungry again okay before
lunch time if you're one of those people
that's hungry again
before lunchtime stick to snacking
on apples okay have one
that you maybe one favorite one you like
some people like randy smith some people
like fuji some people like different
apples
pink lady there's all kinds of different
apples braeburn
um gala whatever apple that you guys
like
you know that would be amazing okay so
snack on apples
you're welcome to chop up the apples
create your own raw
applesauce you can do that too i mean
that's what i like to do i
take apples i chop it up i throw it in a
blender and i throw it in you know food
processor and i actually
i actually make my own applesauce i love
that and
if you don't want to make your own fresh
applesauce you know and you want to find
an applesauce that has no preservatives
a cooked one
that's in a glass jar that's fine too if
you can't find apples write pears for
snacks
so that's important too so let's go in
here a little bit and i'm going to go
into the why with the apples
if you're hungry later in the morning
apples are an
excellent snack because they're a
powerful medicinal cleansing food i'm
reading right of the book here
the pectin in apples helps absorb bile
coming from the liver into the
intestinal tract
bile that may have traces of toxic heavy
metals
in it due to everything that we're
dealing with
a liver filled with metals all of it a
liver filled with metals you name it
and the heavy metal detox smoothie is
uprooting metals
everywhere so if you have traces that
are in the bile because the heavy metal
detox smoothie is uprooting it and
taking out of the body
the apples is a great snack because it
even helps to absorb that bile that
could have
some of that you know extra metal but
that's what's incredible about it so
there's a reason
you're keeping your morning free from
radical fats that's a whole other thing
that
that's happening with the medical medium
heavy metal detox cleanse is you're
keeping your morning free from radical
fats because you want to keep your blood
from thickening so that the toxic heavy
metals can detox more easily
so okay what's in here by the way you
got you know you can look at the recipe
that's in cleanse the heel i got my
heavy metal detox smoothie right here
and you got the wild blueberries the
you know um that you got that wild
blueberries you got the spirulina
okay the best spirulina you got the
barley grass juice powder you got the
fresh cilantro and you got the atlantic
dolls check it out how to do it
all of that um so yeah and by the way
i answer so many questions you're gonna
have so many questions about
cleanse about all this stuff in the book
how everything works i mean i walk
people through the whole bit so
um so uh tonia says how long after
how long after the celery juice sorry
okay how long after celery juice do i
drink the heavy metal detox smoothie
um go with 15 to 30 minutes unless you
want to wait a little longer
you're welcome to do that i mean i like
15 to 30 minutes you could wait
if you feel like whoa i just had 32
ounces of celery juice and i want to
wait a little while fine it's perfectly
fine
um you know there's nothing wrong with
that at all
there's one thing i have to tell you
about the heavy metal detox smoothie
make sure the key ingredients are in
there if you want to change up the fruit
because you want more banana in there
and you got that's the fruit you have
where you got you know you got another
you got a mango you want to put that in
there
or you want to put something else in
your heavy metal detox smoothie that's a
fruit
okay you know make sure though you still
have those wild blueberries
if you can't find frozen wild
blueberries then then the vimergy wild
blueberry powder is the best on the
market
but make sure though that you you have
those key ingredients in your smoothie
because that's the key and you can if
you need to change up the fruits
because that's all you have and that's
what you want to put in there you want
to put a little bit more orange in there
you want to put something in there
then that's what you do so i cover over
200 symptoms and conditions
and what the true causes are and how to
address it with supplementation and
dosages read the whole supplement
chapter 2 with along with it
you guys it's 16.99 right now on
amazon.com 51
off i almost can't believe it when i say
it you know the whole bit
um
okay so katri
katrina hi anthony i was the thing's
flipping constantly so it takes me a
second you guys
hi anthony i was doing the heavy metal
detox movie every day but i felt
suddenly sickened by them
you were doing it every day for how long
quite a while
it could have been something else that
easily could have tripped you up i was
having symptoms of too many minerals
is it possible that one teaspoon of
spirulina and barley grass juice powder
could be too much no that's actually the
minimum
and it's a tiny amount um what else were
you eating that day
the day before what was happening during
that week are you up against any stress
any emotional stuff happening um what
products are you using um all these
things matter
and and how would you know the minerals
are tripping you up
like where'd that information come from
um
all these things matter the the smoothie
is so gentle and benign
um it's unbelievable compared to what's
out there it's incredible
i mean anything i mean there's so many
different things that could have got you
could have got you down for a little bit
so what i'm saying is don't give up
um and you know bring it back in when
you get a chance or
you know or talk to your practitioner
your doctor or however bring it back in
slowly
if you'd like which i tell people to do
is you bring it back slowly if i ever
see something like that
what happens is too is we we have other
things happening
in our body and it's good to actually
always know that hey wait a minute here
i've been doing the smoothie for a while
um didn't have any problems with it so
make sure you
you can always try to bring it back
another thing is do a small amount
you can do small amount do a half
teaspoon do a quarter teaspoon do a
much small one and the heavy metal detox
smoothie can't cause neurological
symptoms so that's one thing it can't
cause
um pathogens cause neurological symptoms
so katrina justino read the
medic the cleanse of heal book if you
already have pathogens cause heavy metal
detox
sorry cat pathogens cause symptoms heavy
metal detox smoothies uh don't
um anyway i'm heading over to facebook
you guys i'm jumping off quick because
if it ends in
uh too close to time we're gonna be
we're gonna lose the whole hour
love you guys see you over at facebook