okay we're live right now you guys day
one
of the medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanse
challenge we're doing it this is it i
got all my stuff you guys got all your
stuff
i got the celery i got the cilantro
right there i got the vimergy spirulina
vinegar barley grass juice powder
i got the wild blueberries here i even
have the
wyman's wild blueberry juice i got
apples i got lemons i got oranges got
dolls
we're rigged right here people with
crippling anxiety panicking anxiety they
have and depression depersonalization
bipolar ocd
ticks spasms tourettes adhd autism
right and then memory loss and brain fog
that's just to name a few
when it comes down to toxic heavy metals
i'm excited this is day one of the heavy
metal detox challenge cleanse
it matters because it's about getting
metals out of us you guys mercury
aluminum cadmium lead arsenic
you name it everybody has it in them
copper they got it in them and it's
sitting
in our brains that's where it sits
and then if you've got toxic heavy
metals
toxic heavy metals plus viruses you've
got the neurological line you've got the
hashimoto's thyroiditis
you've got the mecfs you've got the
autoimmune
you got the ra you got all the different
autoimmune conditions right
because metals play a role there this is
a big day i'm glad we're live facebook
youtube
we're live on tick tock we're live on
clubhouse sorry about the tech problem
we're here i'm excited you guys i got
my celery right here i got the cilantro
i got the bananas i got the mangoes i
got the
lemons i'm excited so you guys how how
is everybody doing
you're you're doing your heavy metal
detox lens you're day one
i'm pumped up so excited excited excited
this is incredible really
so look you guys metals are in the way
of a lot of people's lives they
shape how they think
metals take over they
actually are like an alien in someone's
brain
they make people make decisions that
people wouldn't even make in their life
did you know that metals when they're
inside the brain
can control people control
people metals inside our brain
can control us that's something you
haven't heard right
metals inside the brain can trip us up
make us say things we don't want to say
in times of our life
metals in our brain can throw us off
our game in our life
that's what they can do they can give us
diagnoses that are brain related they
can cause us problems they can give us
brain fog
they can take us off our game like i
said
of life right and so
metals do some things with people they
do
they can get people depressed
when they're not supposed to be
depressed sad when they're not supposed
to be sad right
think about someone who spent years with
severe depression
think about that severe depression
because the metals inside the brain are
creating that situation
so think about how that shapes someone's
life
right toxic heavy metals
inside the brain and brain stem
shaping someone's life into something
that they may not have wanted to be
or something that was happening severe
depression
crippling panic and anxiety for years
that too
right so this is important this is so
critical to get metals out of us
so we can live free because you can't
live
free metals do shape things that we may
not
want shaped in the way they become
shaped and we don't like that
we want our lives free we want to be
free of this toxic heavy metal problem
that everybody's got
and where do you get metals you get them
from all kinds of places
you guys so i'm excited let's do some
lemon water
okay this is a great great day
i'm pumped up we got some lemons right
here almost lost that one
why do i like to throw things in the air
let's do this okay so
i'm gonna get some water in this glass
right now so i'm excited
you guys we're day one of the medical
meeting heavy metal detox challenge i
hope you guys are doing it with me
do you have the book critical
do you have the book if today you didn't
start but you're coming on here live and
you're wondering what is he doing
what's happening and you don't have the
book make sure you get it
amazon.com us 51 off right now it's
16.99
it's an incredible price costs more to
print the book
so this is cleanse the heel page 179 is
the heavy metal
detox cleanse it's in here
this is a book saving lives around the
world make sure you have this book in
your hand you can go to your bookstores
wherever you need but this book is
critical right here
important you guys are clubhouse do you
have cleanse to heal
guys on tick tock you have cleanse the
heel so we're gonna do the 16 to 32
ounces of lemon water i'm going with 32
ounces
lemon water why
why lemon water lemon is a
cleanser cleanser
that's what it is okay it's hydrating
on a deep cellular level
hydrating you guys on a deep cellular
cellular level
so important to know okay do not
use hot water you can use warm water
don't use hot water you kill
the activity that occurs with lemon when
it's living
this is a living water right here inside
this lemon
okay it's calcium rich it's alkalizing
this isn't a real this is a really
important thing to do but you don't want
this hot now of course you can have a
cup of tea tonight
you can have a cup of herbal tea you can
put lemon in there it could be hot
that's fine but this is about cleansing
and this is about flushing
and this is about hydrating 16 to 32
ounces
empty stomach upon waking is a great
time to do it by the way
okay cool
not just eight ounces
not just six ounces of lemon water i
mean if you have to
and that's just what you feel like you
all you can do that that's what you do
then okay
but but if you can you want more you
want to get it up there to 16 to 32
ounces you guys that's what you want to
do
you like your lemon water daily amazing
so right there
16 to 32 ounces lemon water in my hand
the beginning of the heavy metal detox
cleanse challenge
this is day one i'm excited for you guys
you're empowering yourselves
you guys are truly empowering yourselves
there's a difference when you do things
like this because what's happening here
is you're taking out
something out of your body that's
foreign it's a foreign invader
you're not supposed to naturally have
toxic heavy metals interfering with your
life
accelerating disease as you get older
you're not supposed to have that
that's that's literally like having some
kind of alien
inside your body that's what toxic heavy
metals are
and the industries they they make sure
you get plenty of those toxic heavy
metals okay
and so you want to take control
you want to empower yourself and that's
what you do when you're doing the heavy
metal detox cleanse if you guys just
came on here i'm just reminding you
right now
you got to have the book so you can
learn the details matter it's so
important
millions of people around the world are
doing a heavy metal detox smoothie every
single day or the
heavy metal detox cleanse they've
learned how to heal
they're doing it every day they got to
cleanse the heel book
and they're taking metals out of their
body got to have the information page
and cleanse the heel the heavy metal
detox cleanse so
important right there okay so make sure
you grab a book when you can
don't don't say well someday i'll get
the book you know someday
or someday i'll heal right someday i'll
do something
someday i'll get the book maybe someday
whatever
i'll procrastinate and just yeah i'll
get the book a couple years from now
let's let's work on healing it's
important there's a question right there
what is the heavy metal detox
smoothie is that the question going to
make it pretty soon what is
hmds we're getting there so wait 15 to
30 minutes
after your lemon water
and we move on to the next part
they kept my lemon water right now if
you guys don't mind
okay we move on to the next part what do
i have right here
i got some celery right move these over
some celery here we're gonna do some
celery juice really quick we're gonna
knock it right out
pumped up excited let's get a little
celery juice going
right boom
next 16 to 32 ounces of celery juice
tick-tock
yep that's next
you're preparing to remove the metals
that's what you're doing you don't think
you got metals in you
i think i hear that
i hear a few people saying i don't have
any toxic heavy metals in me
and you're wrong you do you do have
toxic heavy metals everyone does we're
born with them they're passed on
from our family they're passed on sperm
egg
utero metals are passed on
by the way that's how babies get birth
defects
they get birth defects because of toxic
heavy metals
that's what creates birth defects okay
that's what creates problems
toxic heavy metals cause these problems
the mercury being one of them
guys encourage other people share your
stories
you know medical medium
if you're on instagram also do you know
tag at medical medium or share your
stories around the world
share your your uh so i can share your
posts
so i can see it and share your posts and
your stories
i'd love to do that good to see you guys
we're
in day one of the heavy metal detox
cleanse challenge
and it's free which is actually exciting
awesome so i'm running some celery right
now through the juicer because this is
the second part we did the lemon water
[Music]
[Applause]
now we're doing the celery
so you guys not only tag at medical
medium but hashtag medical medium at the
same time when you're doing your stories
and your posts because then i can see it
if you do bold
if you tag at medical medium and hashtag
medical medium i can see the stories and
the posts
and then i can repost
[Music]
we want to help others we want other
people
to know how to heal we want other people
to learn we want other people
to get what they need in life we want
them to rid metals out of their body
so important and so many of you guys
have been doing the heavy metal detox
smoothie for years so many of you guys
have been doing it for years
many of you guys have been doing it for
a long time
heavy metal detox smoothie heavy metal
detox cleanse right you guys have been
doing that for a while too
is day one i'm
extra excited i am
so what you see in front of me just so
you know you see spirulina
that's the vimergy spirulina it's the
best one it's so one that i trust i
don't trust
pacific spirulina anymore for a lot of
reasons
a lot of reasons i've talked about it's
terrible
and what you see is barley grass juice
powder not barley grass
right it's the vimergy stuff i'm not
sponsored by beemerjeep the stuff's
amazing
right and then
you also see some wild blueberries these
are frozen wild blueberries i defrosted
right so there's a frozen wild
blueberries that are frosted
now you can't find frozen wild
blueberries
to do this cleanse then maybe grab
another wild blueberry food
like right here that's the wild
blueberry powder from vimergy so maybe
grab a wild blueberry food
right that's the wyman's by the way um
the wyman's juice is back in stock which
blows my mind because
i've been praying it would come back to
stock and
it's incredible you know there's a
discount on cases
so when you get a case you save more
money too on top of it
so that's at shop.wymans.com
um i'm going to show you how i use it
i'm excited about that
this is just such a great day all right
so here we go we got our celery juice
right there i'm going to remove the
juicer
thank you for being patient right
remove that
how many ounces of celery juice do you
guys do
okay you gotta strain the celery juice
right don't add anything
you guys know that you guys know that
not to add anything
don't put ice in there don't add water
don't do any of that so no water no ice
right no apple cider
vinegar god forbid that's a tragedy
to actually add that in here
okay
so we got our celeries use 16 to 32
ounces celery juice that's the next part
of the heavy metal detox cleanse if
you're sensitive and
you all this is a lot because you're
really toxic
your nerves are really sensitive from
all those
metals and all those pathogens and
there's someone that's sick with all
kinds of stuff going on
maybe do a little bit of celery juice
four or eight ounces
maybe do four or eight ounces of lemon
water maybe do that maybe do four or
eight ounces of the smoothie we're about
to do
and then you build up and you build up
and then you can feel like whoa i could
do more
i could do more you're getting the junk
out you're okay you're okay
you can do more you can do more and it's
incredible so that's one way of doing it
you guys so i have a celery juice right
here so 16 to 32 ounce celery juice
is a great thing there's a question on
tick-tock right there why is adding
water bad because you dilute the sodium
cluster salts the very thing that
magically helps us heal celery juices
phytochemical compounds that have to
stay
suspended in a living solution right
here
you don't want to dilute it you don't
want to add anything if you hear out
there someone adding lemon to their
cellar juice
they just lost what celery juice does
for them they just lost it
boom they just lost it another thing too
don't do hpp so when you go into the
store
and you see a celery juice that's in
like a brand
and the brand is in the cold section you
guys of the store the health food store
right
and it says fresh or just not just juice
but
it says fresh celery juice or something
and it's in a bottle
and it wasn't freshly juiced that day
instead it was manufactured right
off an assembly line okay that's called
high pressure pasteurization
you don't want that kind of celery juice
it doesn't work high pressure
pasteurization which is hpp
that's a trick so you just get full what
happens is in the health movement
everybody gets screwed over constantly
they don't know it
they throw away their money they get
they don't even know what's happening
they're buying hpp products that's not
fresh celery juice gotta make it fresh
or a juice bar makes it fresh for you
and that's a different story because
that's how you make it work
and then you might be somebody that says
hey i did celery juice and it didn't
work it's like well you've been doing
hpp
you've been adding lemon to it or you've
been doing something else
you're not doing the way it's supposed
to be so we're day one medical medium
heavy metal detox cleanse challenge
we're going through day one right now
i'm excited
what kind of juicer is that that's the
mm-900 hds
that's the one it's the celery juicer
model it cuts your celery
cost literally almost in half i've saved
thousands of dollars with that juicer
it's the only juicer that pays for
itself so that's the mm-900 hds
at omegajuicers.com if you're interested
i get asked that
question all the time all the time but
that's the specific one if you don't get
that one it's not going to do
what it needs to do so 15 to 30 minutes
right between let's do a recap really
quick so we got the lemon water okay
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water right
there empty stomach
upon waking what you're doing so you
know you're preparing to remove metals
the lemon water hydrates you have to be
hydrated in order to get metals out
efficiently critical you guys
have to be hydrated in order to get
metals out efficiently that's
how it works so you get the 16 to 32
ounces
of lemon water wait 15 to 30
minutes and then you're off to getting
your celery juice
got to strain your celery juice can't
add anything into it into it like i said
no water no lemon no nothing no ice
no anything no apple no nothing then you
got your celery juice
once again you're hydrating
but celery juice the sodium cluster salt
starts to
dislodge metals like it gets it
prepped it gets metals prepped it helps
to loosen them
in their spaces and places getting them
ready
for the heavy metal detox to help pull
metals out
and pour into know uh someone said i was
doing it wrong
a whole time oh my god my god thank god
you didn't write a post saying medical
medium doesn't work
medical medium doesn't work and i'm
going to tell a bunch of people and then
a whole bunch of newbies go it doesn't
work
okay i won't get the book oh it doesn't
oh no i won't get the book i was about
to buy the clenched heel book who cares
if millions of people have healed from
it already around the world
i'm not gonna get that book that person
said it didn't work for them
so thank you for not doing that amazing
i'm so glad and i'm glad you're about to
learn
how to do it right so you can heal
you guys just a little reminder heavy
metal detox cleanse is in cleanse to
heal it's on page 179
you gotta have the book not someday i'll
get the book
okay someday you'll heal someday you'll
get the right information
uh someday you'll know what the details
are someday you'll like
do it okay all right someday
okay amazon.com us 51 off
16.99 and get it to get at the library
if you can find it there i know there's
a waiting list in the library so it
might not be able to get it the second
but that's that's the book right there
so we're heading into the next part
anybody's asking about kitchen tools or
anything just go to medical medium
directory medicalmeme.com check out the
directory and you can see kitchenware's
in there and
see there's something that that hits you
um okay let's move along you guys
we talked about hydration we talked
about the celery juice
loosening the metals
those micro deposits those
metal micro deposits celery juice
getting them prepped and ready so they
can be removed
by the heavy metal detox smoothie
the next part of the cleanse okay so
let's talk about that
boom the wild blueberry
that's the star of the heavy
metal detox cleanse heavy metal detox
smoothie
no one knew the wild blueberry removes
toxic heavy metals
no one knew about toxic heavy metals
causing problems before medical medium's
35 year journey of
teaching people and practitioners and
healers and professionals and everybody
else under the sun
but nobody knew what removes them
there's guessers out there that guess
that chlorella might but it doesn't
they guess that bentonite clay does but
it doesn't
they guess that charcoal might but it
doesn't those don't remove metals
so in order to get the the benefits in
order to get the results
you are looking for for anxiety and
depression
depersonalization nervousness
ocd bipolar
adhd autism brain fog
parkinson's als right
dementia memory loss
right in order to get results from any
of those and much more
you need to know a couple of things you
need to know how they're caused
toxic heavy metals right if you heard
this before it came originally from the
medical medium books
it came originally for medical meme
information toxic heavy metals are
in the way so wild blueberries
are the star that's the star here
you guys that is the star
if you want if you're interested in the
medical medium books that's cleanse the
heal
the medical medium cleanse is in here
but medical medium new edition is a
critical book to get to
if you're somebody that's on a healing
journey you want both
for sure heavy metal detox smoothies in
here
and plenty of different conditions to
heal from and here you go the cleanses
in here
right so why are wild blueberries to
start
what did they do what do they possess
they possess something that
regular cultivated blueberries do not so
what you see
here okay are tiny blueberries
tiny blueberries that's what they are
it's important to know
right tiny blueberries that have
phytochemical compounds that remove
toxic heavy metals this is a powerful
adaptogenic food
right here in my hand truly one of the
greatest adaptogenic foods we have
on the planet surviving thousands of
years
okay of environmental torture and
surviving
these they could be burned down to the
ground and they can grow back
it's the only thing on the planet that
can really do that tick tock anthony
you've helped me anthony you've helped
me
stop my my progression of als i've been
doing this for a month
thank god incredible on tick tock the
thing is people don't believe als gets
better but it does
you can get als better you can recover
from als
you can reverse it and you can move on
and heal okay because i've done that 35
years
when i'm in my office and people being
carried into the office
with als people traveling around the
world coming to the office with als
and and so it's really good i'm so happy
you're doing things i'm so happy you're
stopping the progression of that
condition proud of you so proud of you
don't even know what to say thank you
for being here so exciting
so the wild blueberry is the star you
guys
it does so much right so
nutrition in the wild blueberry is
understudied so they don't even
they don't even have really the
understanding of why the wild blueberry
is so amazing
cultivated blueberries are weak they're
still good for you but they're weak so
the big cultivated blueberry in the
store
is actually a weakened version of this
right here
this is the original this is not just
heirloom but this is a wild food
and medical medium information is about
wild foods and it always was about wild
foods
medical medium information isn't fruits
and vegetables
it's wild foods that's something to know
and it's so important
okay susan says the book has so much
info that changes lives you're really
missing a lot if you don't have it all
of anthony's books are valuable
reference books that will help you stay
healthy
or regain health thank you for sue thank
you for susan for saying that thank you
for that so let's get the blueberries in
here
blueberries can cross the blood-brain
barrier when they're wild
wild blueberries cross the blood-brain
barrier
important to know right there cultivated
blueberries
don't cross the blood-brain barrier
critical information right there to know
right so let's scoop some in we'll talk
about wild blueberries a little bit more
and a little bit more
right so these are frozen wild
blueberries right here
can't do lemon water even a tiny amount
do water in the morning if you can't do
lemon water
not even a tiny amount do regular water
that's okay let's do that right
or squeeze a tiny amount of lemon in
your water
if you can't do lemon now you might not
you might say you can't do lemon because
you've been told by your dentist that
it's bad for your teeth
don't stop it because of that reason
because that's not true
you might not do lemon because you think
it's
uh acidic and it's bad for you
it's not true it's alkaline lemon
is alkaline pretty cool right you guys
this is about information powerful
information important information
two cups of wild blueberries that's what
we're doing in here putting a little bit
more we should have that
two cups of wild blueberries inside the
smoothie
so we're gonna put this down okay
let's start putting the rest of this
together bananas
important to have the glucose now i got
substitutions
for people who are afraid of bananas or
maybe they don't do good with bananas or
somebody that might have allergic
reaction to bananas sure
it's it's very possible right now
with the wild blueberry okay let's just
finish the wild blueberry information
though okay i was going to do it
add it a little later but i'm going to
do it now
all right so if you don't have frozen
wild blueberries
then pick up a wild blueberry powder
that's the vimergy wild blueberry powder
right so that's one option because some
people they can't get the frozen wild
blueberries
depending on where they are around the
world what they can get the vimergy wild
blueberry powder
so that's the best one right there that
i use okay so
i what i do anyways i put a little in
anyway with the frozen wild blueberries
so i'm gonna put some of that in that's
right there
i call that gold
got that right there i also put
the wyman's juice they got a new stock
and you guys know i work with wyman's
right
i'm making sure this product stays alive
stays out there
um because people don't realize what it
takes to harvest wild blueberries
and then actually squeeze it down to a
juice it's an incredible process
it's an incredible process so i actually
support
uh wyman's 100 with this juice it's and
it's an incredible product
you're if you're ever interested it's
[Music]
shop.wymans.com
they have it there i buy it by the case
you get like 13
discount off of each bottle when it's
that way so i put about two ounces in
here
right two to four out look if you don't
have wild blueberry frozen wild
blueberries you could do two to four
ounces of this in the smoothie
you can do that i just throw two ounces
in with my wild blueberries
and my vemma g powder but you know
the blueberry powder right but the point
is is you can do
um you can do two to four ounces of this
no problem
if that's all you have is this
so it's good to find other options in
case you don't have the frozen wild
blueberries
so here we go we've got that covered
let's go into banana land
two bananas right
one banana down another
we're talking about glucose right here
right now glucose
carries the properties
in the wild blueberry and the properties
in the rest of
of um the smoothie that we're going to
talk about carries the properties the
glucose carries to enter the cells
if someone's on like no carb
no sugar from fruit i'm scared of all
that
then how are you going to get the metals
out because
glucose is what carries every nutrient
into a cell
do you know how you can age really fast
you want to age really quick
don't eat any fruit don't ever eat any
potato
don't have any kind of critical clean
carbohydrate that's what i call
medical medium in the books critical
clean carbohydrates
don't have any of that be afraid of that
completely just do some vegetables and
some animal protein or some vegetables
and nuts
or whatever if you know people do and
and they like stay with that whole thing
where they they're afraid of sugar and
you will age so fast down the line
because you need the glucose to carry
the nutrients
in so now if you're afraid of banana i
got alternatives right here okay
i got mango i'll crack one of these open
right
so i got mango that's an alternative
papaya's another one
so i'll have to get that out a little
bit but i got the mango
and you can do frozen mango so that's an
option too he's putting frozen mango in
here that's okay if you do that
you guys just got on here we're talking
about day one
of the medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanse challenge it's going on three
days
do you have the book get it from
amazon.com us 16.99 51
off right there or try to find it in a
local bookstore or barnes noble or
something
or try to get the library but the
waiting listing libraries are here is
like it takes times that might not be
that beneficial right now while we're
doing the cleanse
but get a hold of the book page 179 the
heavy metal detox cleanse is on here
critical to have the details the details
matter the information's right here
we're doing this cleanse we just talked
about the wild blueberries now we're
adding the bananas
let's move on to something else cilantro
let's get cilantro in there now even if
you don't like cilantro
but you you you'll you'll put a little
in that's okay
put a little in then if that's what you
that's all you can do
right put a little bit in there can you
blend the papaya with the seeds i
wouldn't no way
no way the seeds are edible i've been
teaching that for years since i was a
child the seeds
are edible but you don't want the seeds
in the smoothie okay
if you want to eat a couple of teaspoons
of the seeds while you're eating the
papaya
right you can always do that but they're
spicy
and they're gritty very gritty you don't
want them in here there's no need to
have them in here
so we're putting some cilantro in here
let's do that
i like putting a lot of cilantro i like
having a cup of cilantro
right you can do less if you want you
can do a little bit more if you want
cilantro works really well
in removing toxic heavy metals
when it's got the other four
players involved that's
critical to know you want the cilantro
fresh and raw because it's got the
living
water inside of it if you don't like the
taste of cilantro
that means you're high in toxic heavy
metals all these tips are really
important
got the cilantro in there now we're
doing bananas so we don't need to crack
open the mango
i can maybe cut it open a little while
but we don't have to do that right now
so let's move on a little bit
what about cilantro tincture marcy nope
it won't do the same thing
not even close it won't be enough it
won't be enough with one dropper full
you'd have to use the whole bottle and
that's not going to work and be enough
so cilantro tincture is not the way to
go
i mean it's real listen if you don't
have the cilantro you can't get the
cilantro keep it out of the smoothie
i'd rather have you keep that out of the
smoothie i'd rather have you
not do the cilantro tincture
okay then meaning like i'd rather have
you just not do any cilantro at all if
you're gonna use the tincture is what i
mean
so yeah so um try not to do that so we
got the cilantro in here let's move on
to a little bit more
let's get into the barley grass
juice powder now huge mistake
barley grass is not barley grass juice
powder you guys
powder huge mistake made
you can't get the full benefits right
so this is the vimergy barley grass
cheese powder right here you can get it
at vimrgy.com these are victor i
am as marye rgy.com i'm not sponsored
but it's the stuff i use and it's
incredible there's a lot of a lot of
incredible reasons why it's good
right this means it's been juiced
it's been juiced this is the barley
grass juice
powder it's the only way to make it work
in the heavy metal cleanse
important details really you know let's
put a teaspoon in there
it's fine we got that
so what are the players we have in here
right now we got the wild blueberries
boom right the wild blueberry juice the
blueberry powder right we got the wild
blueberry
we got that one right the kingpin the
wild blueberry
that's in here then we got the cilantro
that's another important one now we got
the barley grass juice powder that's
another one in here
what's next spirulina spirulina
don't get this confused
by the sales people who are pushing
chlorella
don't get that confused don't be like
whoa i hear about heavy metals
aw is talking about it let me go and
check into oh chlorella
hey claire clarell is good you know
don't get confused by all the admin
the thousands of them and the chlorella
trolls that are being paid
by the thousands of them being paid by
chlorella companies to try to
get that stuff out there don't get
thrown off the track
chlorella is dangerous for a lot of
people
how it's caused them to throw their guts
up
for weeks at a time hugging onto their
toilet
it's not properly checked with bacteria
chlorella
harbors bacteria it's a bacteria harbor
not to mention even in a perfect world
the best chlorella out there
without bacteria will not get metals out
of the brain
so important chlorella is irresponsible
it drops metal even if it picked it
up important to know drops it that means
if chlorella
is moving metal it moves it into more
tissue
it doesn't carry it with it all the way
out of the body
do not get confused with chlorella which
doesn't work
with spirulina which does work very
important to know
okay and to answer a question i just saw
barley grass juice powder is gluten free
barley grass juice powder at least the
let me correct that
at least the vimergy barley grass juice
powder
is gluten free i can't speak for any
other barley grass juice powder
companies okay or whatever right
frozen cilantro another question frozen
cilantro is okay
but use it right after meaning use it
right when you
pull it out of that freezer don't let it
defrost and turn into yuck muck
don't let the cilantro come out of the
freezer and defrost
in a bag or on the counter and turn into
yucky muck
it won't work it can only work when you
throw that stuff in there while it's
still
frozen frozen state you throw it in
there
that's important to know all these
details matter
spirulina is critical
for the heavy metal detox smoothie it's
another star
in the smoothie it's another star in the
heavy metal detox cleanse if you're
somebody that can only do a little bit
do a little bit
if you're someone that's you know that's
someone that's sensitive to a little bit
i mean a lot of sense of people do a lot
but if you're someone you can just do a
little bit of the smoothie a little bit
of this
a little bit of that in here a little
bit of cilantro a little bit you can you
can baby step it if you need to right
and that's okay could do a quarter
teaspoon instead of a teaspoon
so there's the spirulina it's the best
spirulina out there it's the bemergey
spirulina by far
the best stuff on the market i used to
like the pacific many years ago this is
the only thing
that was out there that was decent
enough but this supersedes it
problem is pacific ocean has gotten real
nasty
i wouldn't swim in there if someone paid
me to and someone said
hey medical medium go surfing in the
pacific ocean
you know we'll give you ten thousand
dollars every time you ride a wave in
i'll be like no way am i letting that
pacific ocean water touch me it's so
polluted at this point with dioxin
and metals it's out of control so anyway
um keep that in mind that's that i don't
recommend
pacific spirulinas anymore not to
mention i found something
one of the pacific spirulina companies
uh jar
that i actually contacted company to
talk to and they blew me off and it was
dangerous what i found in one of their
jars
bottom line anyway spirulina right here
got the vimergy
so let's go let's keep on moving along
we're not sponsored by bimergy but your
stuff's amazing
all right juice from one orange
one orange here's a question that comes
up all the time
some people say can i put the whole
orange in there don't put the rind
don't put the rind in there yes you can
put the orange inside in there you don't
have to just do the juice from one
orange
i do the juice i look sometimes you guys
i'll do juice from two oranges
i like two oranges in there and the
juice in there okay you can do that you
can add a little bit more banana a
little bit more
orange a little bit more orange in my
smoothie you can do that right
okay i'm squeezing this in just like
this just juice from one
orange going in my smoothie
love a little extra vitamin c a little
extra calcium
oranges are extremely alkaline inside
the body
which is great to do when you're
removing metals extremely alkaline right
if you can't do orange juice do a half a
cup of water
or coconut water half a cup of water or
coconut water if you guys just if you
guys just woke up and you got here you
turned on your
computer and you are here with me now
you are
at the heavy metal detox cleanse
challenge day one i'm pumped up
reminding you right here do you have the
cleanse to heal book make sure you grab
one as soon as you can
important make sure you have that page
179 heavy metal detox cleanse we're
doing the cleanse challenge right now
if your coconut water is pink toss it
if your coconut water is red toss it
another scam
in the world of health all right
everybody just gets
totally jaked over it's a major scam
going on
pink and red coconut water went bad it's
rancid
but the problem is okay coconut water
companies
lie and say it's good for you and it's
the good stuff
because if they don't lie and say that
then they're not going to be able to
sell as much coconut water because their
coconut water is going bad
that's what that means when it's red and
pink that means the coconut water went
rancid
that's what happens so don't do the pink
and red coconut water important to know
okay so let's see
amen it's helped me with my hashimoto's
and i haven't done the full cleanse
until now
amazing so we're doing the heavy metal
detox cleanse incredible on tick-tock
i'm proud of you
so we just put the orange in there
you guys what else am i missing
something i want to see how tuned in you
guys are
am i missing something in here uh let's
see
i got the cilantro i got the wild
blueberry i got the spirulina
i got the barley grass juice powder um
put the wild blueberry juice in there uh
what else uh put the orange in there i
got the banana what am i missing you
guys
ashley kevin dolls
at me dolls that's what it is atlantic
dulce right here you guys i see dolls
coming up everywhere
you guys are on it seriously you guys
are on it because i actually did forget
for a second
[Laughter]
and you guys are on it okay so we got
the dolls right here
um okay here's something important to
know if you don't have the atlantic
dolls
you can still do the heavy metal detox
cleanse without it
smoothie without it
it's a home run when you do it with it
but you got four out of the five
four out of the five without it
that's okay that's okay
four out of the five now dolls helps to
remove it on the way out
with the intestinal tract right the
intestinal tract
but you can still get the job done in a
great way without it
but i like having it in it because it's
the home run where you actually do get a
little bit more out
a little bit more out boarding now so
let's get a little dulce in here it's
just that a lot of people have a hard
time with dolls they can't find it
everything else atlantic golf let's get
some dolls in there
boom boom boom boom
you guys if you just got here if you
just arrived
we're making the heavy metal detox
smoothie we're doing the medical medium
heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge we're on day one
and i'm
pumped very pumped because you know why
because i see something disappearing
i see something disappearing
i see hey i see anxiety in there
disappearing i see depression
years worth of depression disappearing
in here
what i see bipolar disappearing
i see tourette's yeah tourette's
disappearing lots of people got rid of
the tourette's
medical medium information i see
parkinson's disappearing parkinson's but
yeah lots of people heal their
parkinson's
i see als disappearing uh-huh
i do i see memory problems
brain fog disappearing i see a lot of
things disappearing
migraines disappearing that's why i love
this
i think we got it let's cap it
let's cap it right let's send it through
here hopefully this is plugged in
which i think it is this right here
i'm excited
here we go
coming along right here elizabeth
legendary it's a legendary smoothie
there's all kinds of imitators imitators
trying to sell you charcoal and zeolite
imitators trying to sell you bentonite
clay and chlorella
imitators trying to put their own blends
together imitators that learned about
toxic heavy metals because of medical
medium books and information
and then they turn their back on the
medical medium community
and they try to make their own blend of
something that's toxic and doesn't work
and that's what imitators do
so what this is here
is an incredible smoothie right here i'm
very excited about this
okay
very excited how much dolls
look you got the option tablespoon is a
great amount but you can put two
teaspoons you could put a teaspoon
if you're joining in the cleanse give a
thumbs up
hit the like button i don't know do a
[Music]
right that would be amazing you guys if
you could
[Music]
we got the smoothie right here i'm
pumped
let's get a jar
and then we'll pour that smoothie right
in here
incredible
boom amazing
heavy metal detox smoothie for the heavy
metal detox cleanse but we're not done
we're not done we did the lemon water
we did the celery juice we're doing the
heavy metal
detox smoothie what's next
what's next peach snow says is it still
effective if
after you make it you put it in the
freezer then eat it in like ice cream my
daughter won't do smoothies
perfect perfect yes effective
popsicles popsicles
so we got the smoothie right there you
guys what's next that's what i'd like to
know
something that's
and i'm going to move this over
so what i'm going to make
something a little different here right
so i'm gonna do the apples next okay
apples
are important in the heavy metal detox
cleanse right
but let me use my food processor for
this one
you don't want to do fats in the morning
with a heavy metal detox cleanse you
don't want avocado you don't want oils
you don't want nut butters you don't
want nuts
you don't want any of that in the
morning because once you do radical fats
like that
you just shut your cleanse down you just
shut it down
you're doing all that work the heavy
metal detox smoothie only can take out a
portion
a small portion of the metals when
you're doing all that fat
because if you're doing avocado with
your smoothie i'll do the heavy metal
detox smoothie but i'll throw a half an
avocado
in here too because someone said healthy
fats are good for me let me mix it in
here boom you just blew it
blew it you can't get the metals out
you got to keep the oils out of the
cleanse you got to keep the fats out of
the cleanse
you can't put those in you can't no mct
oil no way no coconut oil you put that
in cleanse over
cleanse over boom what a waste what a
waste
you gotta have fly in the wall is the
over there on tick tock
you gotta be a fat free morning with
your cleanse
you can't fast yourself to death while
you're doing the cleanse you've got
you've got to wait you've got to do the
fats if you're into fats you got to do
them later on
they got to be later on during the day
you got to do you've got to keep them
later on
if you're an animal protein then you eat
animal protein at night at the end of
the day
you can't do it in your morning you
can't do bacon
while you're trying to do the heavy
metal detox cleanse
you put bacon in there it's over game
over you just ruined your cleanse
can get the medals out so we're doing
apples now
that's what we're doing now apples i got
some beautiful apples right here
let me cut off the stickers right
cutting the stickers off real quick
[Music]
two apples before noon would be great
if you can do two one apple before noon
can you do one apple before noon
that's great half an apple i'm okay if
you do a half an
apple but the pulp of the apple
the pulp the pectin of the apple helps
to carry out some of the metals
that got excreted out of your liver
let's head there now we're in the heavy
metal detox lens we're day one you guys
this is really important information
have your notepad ready do you have your
cleanse to heal
book around too keep it around page 179
is the cleanse
make sure you order the book when you
can okay let's go let's talk about this
for a couple of minutes
[Applause]
right that's your liver right there
okay your liver produces bile
you're doing the heavy metal detox
cleanse
your spirulina your wild blueberries
your cilantro your barley grass juice
powder
everything your celery juice all of it
is working
on getting those toxic heavy metals out
of you to free you
up free you up of conditions and
symptoms
right when all that enters
into the liver it starts to loosen up
the metals and grabs onto the metals
and when it grabs onto the metals
the bile spews up the pipe
and goes into the intestinal tract that
bile has toxic heavy metal in it
keep that in mind that bile has toxic
heavy metal in it
so and and the smoothie that you're
doing in the heavy metal detox cleanse
is already circulating throughout the
entire body including the brain
taking metals out of the brain right
but the liver is gonna volcano
volcano that metal out into the bile
the bile is gonna drop back into the
intestinal tract
right you guys and then the apples
help to carry it out the pectin
the pulp of the apple helps the bind
onto that bile that's contaminated
with toxic heavy metals and pull it out
of your body you see how important this
is
see how details matter so important
right so important okay so keep that
keep that in mind right there
here's something to to note make sure
you write this down you guys if you can
no coconut milk no coconut oil
inside your smoothie you can't put a fat
inside the smoothie you put avocado
coconut coconut milk coconut oil mct oil
any kind of thing that's out there you
put
whatever olive oil anything in that
smoothie
almonds in that smoothie walnuts and
that smoothie seeds in that smoothie
you just ruined it oat milk you just
ruined it almond milk you just ruined it
boom you ruined your whole your cleanse
in your smoothie letting you know keep
that in mind
question what brand for barley grass the
only one i trust in the best one
that works the best is the vimorji v
is the victor i am as amerig.com
it's barley grass juice powder it's the
best company i'm not sponsored but it's
the best stuff
right there okay so i wanted to talk
about the liver and but why
the apples are so important how come the
apples are
so important you guys so let's just i
like making an
apple sauce from for me for
for the cleanse right a quick applesauce
just apples
though right for this that's what i like
to do so i take the apples i'm cutting
them up right here right
so i like doing this during the heavy
metal detox cleanse
for me you guys can just eat the apple
if you want don't worry
you can eat the apple if you want if
that's what you want to do that's fine
i could totally do that right i toss the
core
you know i don't want to grind up the
core so i toss the course if there's any
questions there
right you can do a half an apple you can
eat a half an apple you can eat a
quarter of an apple
you can do that if you can't do the
apple if you're somebody that's allergic
to an apple if you're somebody that
doesn't like an apple if you're somebody
that just can't do an apple or you can't
find an apple
realize that your atlantic dolls
is part of getting the metals out of
that that bile
out of the intestinal tract too you
don't have the atlantic balls
right then you're still you're still
doing the frozen wild blueberry which
helps to get it
out of the intestinal tract you're still
doing the spirulina which also helps to
get it out
right so let's bring this over
i know on tick-tock you guys don't see a
lot when it's when it's
set up like this but let's so let's
bring this over here so what i'm going
to do is make a quick applesauce is what
i'm doing
so i'm chopping up two apples i'm gonna
have an apple sauce before lunch
that's what i'm gonna do you guys i'm
excited
right so that's what i'm doing let's see
if it all works out remember we're live
all kinds of disasters happen when we're
live yep what's going on
there we go averted disaster
here okay
do a little pulse action here
anybody who just got on here i advise
you to watch this from the beginning to
the end
watch it on youtube or or a facebook
allows us to see it because because i'm
censored there a lot
watch it on facebook can do that too
so i'm making an apple sauce this is a
fresh living applesauce right here
that's what i'm doing i'm going to eat
this before
12 o'clock every day during the cleanse
right you're not going to see any nuts
in here
no almond milk in here nothing like that
because if you do that
you're blowing the cleanse you've got to
be fat free before noon
to get the metals out if anybody's on
here right now stay tuned because i'm
about to do
um a little display on where you get
your toxic heavy metals which i think is
important because no
no one believes they got battles in them
by the way a lot of people are like i
don't got metals it's got anxiety
but i don't got metal they got anxiety
right
just made myself an applesauce right
let's get the blade out of here so let
me do that
the blade out okay
all right i'm going to move this out of
the way too
right here get a little bowl
okay get a little get the applesauce
got the living applesauce right there
what if you can't
get it all in before 12 can i stretch it
out as long as i don't have the fats
absolutely octop
octoporp totally you can totally do that
you can stretch it out
as long as you want you can make a big
smoothie and stretch that baby out and
just keep on going going going
absolutely
great question thank you for asking that
question it helps
right apples used to make
my gums hurt after several 369 cleanses
i love them
you're cleaning up you're healing you're
cleaning up your healing your nerves
the 369 cleanse is healing your nerve
like nerves throughout the whole body so
you can actually then not get hurt by
something because your nerves are
getting better
right there so this is the apple sauce
right there so this is a fresh apple
sauce i just made
okay there you go free even better
results avoid troublemaker foods
going to cleanse the heal learn about
the troublemaker foods
better results you can keep on going
going going
the results are endless with the medical
meme information the details matter
all the information matters you guys
know so let's talk about those
almost lost my book so let's talk about
where you get their medals because
a lot of people don't believe they have
toxic heavy metals right
so anytime you've ever touched this
eaten anything out of it cooked on
anything on the grill
been in a restaurant done any kind of
takeout you've got aluminum in you and
lots of it aluminum is also
in pharmaceuticals antibiotics
antidepressants
cold medicine loaded with aluminum
that's just to name a few
right you guys love tuna
right well i don't eat tuna out of a can
i eat sushi
i do it's so much more healthier well
it's all mercury
mercury mercury mercury right how many
times can you say it three times in a
row really quick
mercury america bright mercury there you
go
so sushi boom how many people are eating
sushi
copper you guys there was a question
by the way there was a question
yesterday that said well 14 karat gold
18 karat gold why not 24 karat gold
because 24 karat gold breaks
it breaks it's not strong enough it's
too soft that's why
24 karat gold jewelry i mean you just
you lose it
you're on the beach and boom there goes
your earrings gone you hit one wave and
boom there goes your necklace
gone you know you're on your paddle
board boom you just lost your gold chain
if it's 24 karat it just falls apart
so that's why so 18 karat is the way to
go
14 karat if you can that's fine too but
copper
copper pipes copper's passed on in utero
okay mommy and daddy pass copper on
sperm and egg
copper's in our system anybody who has
eczema has copper in their liver lots of
it
anybody that got psoriasis it's copper
in the liver lots of it
copper right the whole bit a whole bit
plastics don't cause the same problems
as metals just so you guys know they
come out easy
spirulina alone with wild blueberry
juice wild blueberry juice and spirulina
can knock all plastics out
literally plastics aren't a problem
they're really not that big of a problem
if you're doing something about it they
just you just get rid of them
copyright you do copper iud absolutely
copper iud a lot of women with the
copper iuds all get eczema psoriasis
later on
yep copper if i had a copper iud in me
okay um i would take it out but i know
that a lot of women they can't
their their husbands demand that they
have it like
i've run into that so many times where
they have no choice
um they they they literally have no
choice
but i get it if you don't have a choice
then then just work on doing the cleanse
so you can
because it's it's we can't avoid copper
all the time we can't avoid
metals all the time stay away from
copper mugs stay away from copper
jewelry
stay away from copper copper mugs copper
thermoses
you're being poisoned by a bad trend a
bad
trend okay you guys need to know that
do not get fooled by all the marketing
for bad
trends copper thermoses copper mugs
copper
terrible you guys are just getting
copper poisoning just give me the
rundown where your copper is okay
[Music]
metals copper clothing's not good either
pots and pans and restaurants you guys
pans and pots are scraped to death
in restaurants divots are in them
scraped to death audrey says holy [__]
i had an iud when younger and now live
with psoriasis
absolutely only medical medium
information knows that though only
medical medium information
knows that metals cause psoriasis
and only medical medium information
knows that copper is the specific one
that causes psoriasis
and mm info only knows that that can
happen
um so yeah and if you've heard that from
somewhere else it was taken from here
by copycats without citing back to where
info is so people can heal
okay back to this you guys people scrape
those pots and pans and restaurants
restaurant food so loaded with metal tap
water in the restaurants
oh my god loaded with coffee shops
loaded with metal
uh food from all kinds of restaurants
loaded with metal right
but but i'm not saying don't live your
life i'm just saying what are you doing
what are you doing are you getting the
medals out
are you doing the heavy metal detox
cleanse challenge it's free we're doing
it for three days
do you have the book order the book
instead of saying someday i'll get the
book someday i heal
someday i'll get medals out someday i'll
get my anxiety better
someday i'll uh take care of myself so i
don't pass medals down to my children
and sperm an egg someday i'll get the
book when i don't know i don't want to
get the book i heard the book is bad
from somebody who hates anthony williams
so
i don't know if i should get the book
even though it's healed millions of
people
so get the book if you can 51 off
amazon.com us
so look i have i have different things
that you know i have housewares and
stuff like that like
cooking wear and all that at
medicalmediumdirectory.com
if you're interested okay dental work
i'm not just talking about mercury
amalgam fillings i'm talking about
dental work i'm talking about fluoride
treatments everybody's saturated with
aluminum in their system fluoride
treatments
even composites that aren't mercury or
metal based have metal in them
copper too they have copper in them
right insect killer
every single dorm room in every single
college and university around the world
is sprayed before the before the kids
enter the dorm room
it's sprayed every single year every
single door room
dorm room is treated with some of the
most deadly insect killers insecticides
so then when you're a college student
you live in your dorm room
you're living in a box it with
pesticides and insecticides that's why a
lot of a lot of um
a lot of college kids lose their hair
while they're while they're going
through their loot they gain weight
their liver gets filled up
with all that insecticide poison the
universities and the colleges are one of
the number one ways insecticides get
into every single person
you guys have no idea no idea so that's
the insecticides right there that's just
one thing
perfumes colognes let's get some
colognes and perfumes
let's get some clones and perfumes
smells nice
smells nice smells terrible it's loaded
with toxic heavy metals too
important scented candles toxic heavy
metals
scented candles air fresheners and
scented candles
toxic heavy metals big time you breathe
in a scented candle
boom toxic heavy metals boom toxic heavy
metals pharmaceuticals
toxic heavy metals antibiotics
antidepressants to talk about that
thyroid medication all of it toxic heavy
metals
you get it everywhere you guys fish oil
fish oil toxic heavy metals
in the fish oil capsules that's right
fish oil
toxic heavy metals mercury methyl
mercury going to your brain
that will give you alzheimer's years of
taking fish oil will ensure someone when
they're in their 50s and in 60s we'll
rush some serious alzheimer's and
dementia
boom and some depression in somebody
who's younger
absolutely what else do i have here soda
soda sipping off that aluminum right
here and the liners
and i hope no one says oh but there's
liners in there oh really
because when that can constricts from
being cold in the fridge the liner
breaks
when that can expands because it's metal
because you hold it in your hand and
it's warming up at a cookout
the liner expands and liner breaks
there's there's not even liner and half
the aluminum cans out there
you don't know what brand has a liner or
not most of them don't
oh just sip off of it too okay
pencils i love when someone tries to
stick it to the mm on the pencil thing
there's no lead medical medium in
pencils
so you're just wrong no but i've seen
too many people
bite the cap which is aluminum bite the
cap
chew all that cap right there until all
the teeth marks are in that cap
how many people did that oh my god
probably more than half the population
bit the hell out of the cap and got
shavings of aluminum in them
yeah ashley kevin says always a biter
health with lizard you were bitter t you
like bite you never might think pencils
and pens right
i know so many people to bite the
pencils and pens everybody does
it's crazy right so ashley says she's a
biter
she bites the pencils right
lorraine did you ever bite the pencils
i've had so many friends that bit the
pencils i see them bite the end of the
aluminum i'm going to be telling them
when you're getting all the aluminum in
you
it's incredible so that's one thing
right there
and then whoa
do you guys ever have a cup of coffee
out in your favorite restaurant
coffee shop coffee chain yeah
that's right i see people every day when
i'm on the road
i see people going into the coffee chain
the famous
one the famous coffee chain i see them
going into you know the most popular
famous coffee chain
right elizabeth says i may have a few
times don't think so
it always gross me out that's actually
really funny
and then you get your coffee and your
soups and these chains right
well that water is loaded with toxic
heavy metals that's tap water straight
out from the city
piped in not monitored and loaded with
toxic heavy battles you get your coffee
out you've got your metals
let's recap
do you have the medical medium
information do you have the details
heavy metal detox cleanse page 179
critical to have you guys i'm not just
trying to push
a book it costs more to print this book
out to what it's selling right now on
amazon.com us
so think about that so where's the money
in that
it's priced at 16.99 there is no money
it's priced at 16.99 amazon.com us
it's 51 off learn how to heal the heavy
metal detox cleanses in here
so boiling water makes no difference
boiling the water doesn't get rid of
toxic heavy metals it just makes the
toxic heavy metals hot
all right let's go back to this i'm
getting distracted you guys
okay we're talking about the heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge let's move into
it lemon water 16 to 32 ounces
empty stomach boom we got that right
after that wait 15 to 30 minutes you got
your celery juice
16 to 32 ounces empty stomach
boom got the celery juice right
then you're working on making the heavy
metal detox smoothie you got your
spirulina that's the vimergy spirulina
you got the vimmergy barley grassroots
powder
you got the the um the beverage
blueberry powder you've got the wyman's
wild blueberry juice these are options
in the wild blueberry world right
by the way um you guys i know a lot of
you guys drink the water blueberry juice
from wyman's
uh they got a big stock back in have a
stock back in i know that so many were
having problems with getting the juice
the stock is backing at wyman's it's if
you buy it by the case
you get 13 off each bottle when you more
13 more off each bottle if you buy it by
the case
so right there shop.wymans.com
i'm pumped you guys know i'm working
with wyman's to make sure this stuff
stays out there
because it's one of those life savers
it's incredible
so let's see what else okay
now here's an option for you guys here's
an option that brings me to this
[Music]
all right here's some coconut water
right here
so i got coconut water in this glass
okay
now here's what i do if i can't get a
smoothie together
if i can't do a heavy metal detox
smoothie for some reason i'm traveling
i'm having a hard time or anything like
that right i can't
or i don't have bananas i don't have all
the things i need i don't have cilantro
then i try to get three
out of five three
out of five is what i try to do
that means three what's one spirulina
that's one of the five that takes the
metals out together
right one teaspoon boom barley grass
juice powder
one of the three out of the five so
that's the vimergy barley grass juice
powder right
teaspoon of that in there okay
okay i do the weinman's wild blueberry
juice
i do two ounces in there boom
incredible
three out of the five or the powder it's
the vimergy powder right there
or the powder right why blueberry powder
three
out of the five this is important okay
mix it
if i can't do the full smoothie
i got the coconut water version right
there and the three out of the five
right sure it would be ideal to have the
cilantro but try to get the cilantro in
your diet later on during the day
or maybe later on if you're not doing
all the fats yet
you're not doing those fats and try to
get a little dose in there maybe later
on during the day if you're not doing
all the fats
then you get the five out of the five
during that day
right if you're keeping the fats away
you can do three
out of the five add the cilantro later
tik tok
add the dose later how bitching is that
it's really cool really cool
a friend of mine used that term all the
time so i talked to them for an hour on
the phone the other day and they said
that term like three times i was like
hey that's actually really funny
so this is awesome you guys this is an
option right here this is a really cool
cool option um okay so
let's go back to everything we got the
applesauce later on before noon but if
you stretch out your heavy metal detox
cleanse
throughout the day and you're not doing
fats you can do the apples later you can
eat the apple you can have a half an
apple you can make the applesauce
ashley kevin isn't funny
lemons make sure you have your lemons
the lemon water in the morning you've
got that we're heading off to ig we
talked about metals we talked about
conditions and symptoms
that metals create we're going ig in a
little while just give me a couple of
minutes to clean up you guys and we're
going to have some fun you don't want to
miss the instagram
version we're going to try to have a
little bit more fun hopefully
incredible love you guys i will see you
m skye good to see you see you guys over
on ig
and tick tock i'm going to turn you guys
right back on on tick tock i'm excited
to do that clubhouse i'll turn you guys
back on too
all right take care