okay are you guys coming June 15th June
15th I'm going to be there signing books
unbelievable the heavy metal detox
smothie is on the menu at airan June
15th it's the launch party there's going
to be speakers there free merch I'm
going to speak hopefully there's some
some more surprises and everything else
anyway are you guys going to be there
cuz I'm going to be there this is
serious stuff I am pumped the whole bit
medicalmedium.com for the details
register there are four places to park
four places to park four locations okay
that's number one piece of information I
want to drop okay number two try to
carpol if you can use ride share if you
can or Uber or something okay but there
are four locations to park on top of
that this is a big deal yes there's
going to be bathrooms people are like is
there going to be bathrooms AWS are
going to be bathrooms you know the
medical medium crowd we're drinking our
celery juice we're doing a lemon
water we're doing hey I'm going to have
probably like three or four heavy metal
detox smoothies so I'm going to probably
buy three or four of them whatever five
of them they're not free for me I'm
going to buy like five or six of them
because the proceeds that go to me for
the heavy metal detox smoothie are going
to charity 501c in the community to give
back to the community anyway I'm going
to buy like four or five of them I'm
going to be guzzling them yeah I'm going
to need a bathroom at some point I'm
pretty sure okay unless I'm super human
and maybe I can hold it in the entire
the entire day okay on June 15th maybe I
can hold my bathroom in the entire day
on June 15th no probably can't so there
you go anyway you guys there's going to
be bathrooms so yes pretty cool right
exciting anyway this is going to be
incredible all right so I'm letting
everybody know a couple of things
medical.com get the details right four
parking locations use ride share if you
can car pull if you can right it's going
to be killer it's going to be fun it's
going to be amazing just letting you
know so um a couple of details which is
incredible in the aan stores guess what
that's right Wyman's wild blueberry
juice in the aoan stores
yep that's right High antioxidant grade
right there high grade that's right high
grade fuel right there incredible okay
vimergy in the airan locations vimer G
in
Awan boom that's incredible so you go in
there you need vimergy vimer is
inan that's all I can say that's
incredible all on its own okay I'm
excited all right all right all right
all got to calm down got to calm down
now we're making the heavy metal detox
smoothie I got my blender right here
here but I got to got to calm down oh
you guys use the airan app too thank you
very much here there it is okay use the
Awan app can you see that awesome okay
Awan will have fresh celery juice but
get this listen to this airan app listen
to this awan's going to have steamed
potatoes steamed potatoes for the
medical medium crew for the people on
June 15th how sick is that steamed
potatoes and fresh celery juice is the
app still there whoa click it on there
it is there's the app okay so you could
order on the airan app but steam
potatoes heavy metal detox smoothies
fresh celery juice edone just use the oh
my God I can't believe it all right I'm
just going to tell you right now all
right I happen to be extremely excited
for a couple of reasons one is proceeds
that go to me aren't going to me they're
going to the community back to the
people who need the money who need the
car who need things okay that's one
thing that's right that's right the
other reason why I'm excited is I got
speakers there on the 15th guests that
are going to be speaking uh-huh that's
going to be really cool too are you guys
going to be there you don't want to miss
this you want to be there you definitely
don't want to miss this all right okay
on igw will you sign Wyman's and vimergy
Bottles huh let me think about that I'm
signing books but let me think about
that because that's pretty cool right
there on its own but I got I got to
think about that got to run it by my
team too you wouldn't believe you
wouldn't believe how much we're doing
and what we've done to get to this point
it's actually really you're freaking
excited Fabian freaking excited so am I
you're on YouTube amazing okay we'll be
there with bah and Alexandra incredible
all right all right all right all right
all right all right pull it together
pull it together pull it together I know
you're coming from Denmark
boom boom
Denmark yeah incredible just what I said
I was going to pull it together the
Denmark thing just blew my mind that's
really what it is yeah Dr Fawn there
will be speakers and a microphone indeed
there will be not messing around and I
am going to be one of the speakers whoa
it's going to be cool all right you guys
and like I said before if you need the
vimer gy it's there at Awan need the
Wyman's wild blueberry juice there at
iroan now it is it's even there now all
the stuff is there
now and get the heavy metal detox
smoothie I'm going to be getting a bunch
of them all right good to see you guys
back on here we had some tech problems
earlier let's roll let's roll I want to
make this Lisa coming from Connecticut
with my daughters who's been doing
medical medium for
years for
years
incredible oh that's amazing Czech
Republic what no way from Czech you're
coming from there me and my wife are
coming from Czech Republic can't wait I
can't wait either that's a distance man
thank you for coming whoa Lara over
there on YouTube I'm coming from Germany
I am so nervous you're making me nervous
I'm nervous you're coming all the way
from Germany I better do a good job I
better be I better be a good speaker
hopefully I got some surprises too but I
better be a good speaker Arena this is
going to be amazing I am so excited
coming from Germany to meet you
Germany what
incredible yeah lra I'm coming from
Germany amazing uh us two from
Connecticut living light over there in
YouTube incredible I'm coming from
France whoa on YouTube there wealth with
Tom Tom thank you for coming from France
I'm actually excited I'm very excited
about this completely you guys are
coming I will cry on the 15th anunt
studi says over there on YouTube I will
cry on the 15th June because I am not
coming unfortunately ah ah I feel bad I
feel bad oh my God God and somebody has
a question on IG will there be security
at the park yes there will there's going
to be a lot of security not just
security there's going to be a lot of
security because we want everybody safe
everybody happy because I know that
that's a concern people have like
there's going to be security there we're
not going to have one guy there we're
not going to have two guys there we're
not going to have three guys there we're
going to have a lot of security yes
because we want everybody safe we want
this great we want this fun it's going
to be really fun it's going to be
amazing here's the thing you know the
the it's going to be about 9 to 3 I
think that's the timing of the day 900
to 3 but I'm going to show up earlier
too I'm going to pop into
Awan that's what I'm going to do
probably pop in there earlier um but I'm
going to be signing books and everything
else let's make the heavy metal detox
smoothie you're coming from Texas
driving from Dallas Texas God bless
bless you God bless you that is amazing
all right let's get some wild
blueberries in
here the medical medium heavy metal
detox
smoothie is famous it's famous why is it
famous lives were
changed lives were changed there's never
been any money behind the heavy metal
detox smoothie what I mean by that is it
wasn't like there was this massive
rollout marketing plan and PR plan for
the heavy metal detox movie all these
years okay there wasn't it was an
organic movement of people getting out
of wheelchairs getting better getting
getting freeing themselves from chronic
illness that's what it
was it was it was about that okay it was
about literally freeing themselves from
chronic illness healing recovering
miraculous stuff happening in people
lives that's what went down with the
heavy metal detox smoothie okay people
got Metals out of their body people got
Clarity people moved forward that's what
happened it is the most known yes the
most known the most known of all Heavy
Metal detox around the world it is a
famous heavy metal detox because people
healed not because there was this
massive millions of millions of dollars
of roll out and PR nothing of the sort
nothing people healed people need to
understand this this is incredible over
there Dorene over there in IG heavy
metal detox movie saved my life saved my
life that's a big deal saved my
life I mean that's right there that's
incredible incredible meaningful lemon
bomb love hey lemon bomb Love Heavy
Metal detox movie saved my life I'm
going to start getting choked up I'm
going to start getting choked up that's
that's incredible truly
incredible uh Monique over there in IG
where exactly is this event Culver City
La Culver City Awan Culver City La
medical me.com check out the details
register seriously I mean you don't want
to miss it you should be there Lea um
been drinking your heavy metal detox
smoothie since 2015 15 life changing
life changing 2015 you've been drinking
the
Smoothie yeah incredible all right let's
start let's start doing a little bit
here let's start getting some
ingredients here let's get some bananas
in here you guys
bananas I'm going bananas right now cuz
I'm so
excited I am it's it's taking like some
time to get to this point you guys it's
taking some time to get here June 15th I
am pumped I can't wait um it's going to
be so fun there's going to be some cool
stuff going on you don't want to miss it
you don't all right let me just put a
little bit of the vimergy spirina right
here it's right you guys know I work
work with these guys right here
okay incredible stuff I endorse because
yeah there's nothing better I don't care
who spirina what spirina I don't care
where where it's not the same thing and
that's the barley grass juice powder not
the barley grass but that's the vimergy
barley grass juice powder right there
okay that goes in here as well now
here's the viy DL liquid that has
changed my life changed my life the do
liquid I can't tell you how incredible
how easy it is to use and all of that
okay and um going to pop in some I
already put the Wyman's wild blueberry
in there too Wyman's wild blueberries at
ear onean that's
right wild wild blue W's wild blueberry
Wyman's wild blueberry juice at irwan
that is incredible I love when
lifechanging products incredible
products you know get to uh a new place
how incredible all right we got that in
there let's put a little bit of the
Wyman's wild juice in the Smoothie right
here there we go
popped a little bit of that in
there
nice really nice okay we got that
cilantro so many of my friends have been
asking to have the um juice available at
Awan and so in in La so that's what
happens like friends of mine will be
like when is it going to be an aan I
want to go in there and I don't see it
in there and where is it but now it's
there so it's going to be so easy for a
lot of people I know and many other
people too I'm going to put some
cilantro in here you can put it in like
this you can break it apart I want to be
able to purchase my heavy metal detox
smoothie at airan people say that all
the time they're like I want to purchase
it I want to purchase it at Air1 myself
personally that's what I want to do you
know what happens is when I'm traveling
and I'm doing things and everything else
I don't have the the time and everything
else to just get everything out and make
it myself in a lot of situations I would
love to just go into aoan and be like
I'll take one two three four I'll take
five of them for the next couple of days
a lot of my friends are pumped that
it'll be so convenient too so it this is
just so great all right I'm going to
squeeze some orange in here now remember
it's the five key ingredients though
five key
ingredients okay the barley grass juice
powder one of the key ingredients you
ready the spirulina
one of the key another key ingredients
ready the do that's the dols another key
ingredient right the wild blueberries
another key ingredient the
cilantro another key ingredient
five five key ingredients now if you
know about the medical medium heavy
metal detox you want three out of five
baby three out of five keep that in mind
okay five five for maximum benefits it's
key five for maximum benefits right and
you want that five maximum benefits
ingredients either in your smoothie as a
smoothie or in a smoothie bowl or on a
salad or throughout the day but you want
to get the five in remember that
information right here medical medium
Secrets right behind chronic illness
Myst remember this one
yes so um we got the five key
ingredients in there let's also put a
little bit of orange in there too let me
just grab a blade if you guys don't mind
LM bom love my doctor said she is coming
to the launch too
whoa okay that's cool that's really cool
I'm excited about
that very excited about that actually
I'm going to put
[Music]
some I'm going to put some orange in
here wondering wishing over there on
YouTube aw our family is coming oh what
kiddos have been doing heavy metal detox
smoothie since out of school when I
asked about changes they all say they
sleep so much better through the night I
didn't even know that was an issue wow
these things matter they matter greatly
this is what it's about this is why I'm
even here this is what it's about it is
it is all right
okay cilantro in here key ingredient
barrass cheese powder key ingred key
ingredient sorry spirulina key
ingredient and yeah I had some celery
Force earlier and I don't every time I
have it I'm like I'm actually talking
really fast so I got to slow it down a
little bit plus the wild blueberry
that's in there the dols that's in there
five key ingredients
critical for the heavy metal detox let's
get it Blended up let's roll I'm going
to pop this on here I want you guys to
be able to see
it okay come on Natasha we're so excited
to meet you coming from
Nebraska wow
Nebraska it's a great place
too amazing all right let's fire this up
you guys okay with this let's roll
all
right cilantro come on moving cilantro
let's
go cilantro
[Music]
cilantro there we go boom cilantro just
got got eaten up in
[Music]
there
yeah using cilantro as a leafy green
using cilantro as a Leal
[Music]
dream right we're
good okay so Body and Soul over there in
IG ask the question does airwan have
doul too yes it does yes it does the
bimy douls liquid right there in my hand
incredible product incredible product
all right we got our smoothie made
uh-huh let's see if we have an apparatus
to put it
in or an Implement to put it in either
way here we
go I am so pumped about this can't even
tell you Anna over there on YouTube I
Love The Heavy Metal detox smoothie I've
been drinking it for 9 years and I
healed my migraines that I had for over
years healed my migraines that I had for
over 25 years think about that everybody
oh my God also there is a birth mark on
my leg that is disappearing I so
grateful to you in s so you know I've
talked about this years ago too birth
marks heavy metals are involved with
birth marks toxic heavy metals yes
passed on from generation to generation
are involved in birth marks okay and
I've seen this before you're doing the
hmds or you're doing the heavy metal
detox right and you got those key
ingredients in there and you're saying
staying consistently with it
consistently birth marks start to reduce
and they start to disappear in a lot of
people seen this over the years that's
incredible really is
um all right yovana over there on
Facebook without heavy metal detox
smoothie I wouldn't be able to function
for my three kids it stopped my vertigo
celery uh Squad going to the event we
are excited from horse toown us uh
California Norco Horsetown USA
California amazing incredible um you
know what's exciting irwan is going to
have steamed potatoes that Day June 15th
they're going to have steamed potatoes
and lots of celery juice and of course
the heavy metal detox smoothie I am
going to purchase some steamed potatoes
while I'm there and I'm going to grab
some celery juice when I'm there and I'm
going to grab the heavy metal detox
smoothie I can't wait I can't wait I
don't even know what else to
say all right heavy metal detox smoothie
healed my
depersonalization that's that's intense
you know depersonalization is so hard on
so many people it's brutal Arena you
know right I mean God you suffered with
it heavy metal detox movie healed my
depersonalization my
depression whoa my anxiety whoa a lot of
OCD I can't say enough about OCD and a
lot of PTSD already healed all within 5
years oh my God the hmds healing OCD
healing the PTSD the anxiety depression
it means everything
it means everything right there it just
does it just does Can I taste
this the flavor so
good why does it taste so good more more
more
mhm and
more oh God it's
refreshing I haven't had anything in a
little while now I've been busy working
on all kinds of stuff this hits the spot
like nobody's business it hits the spot
but it really
does think about that
okay when we heal depression anxiety
depersonalization OCD bipolar out there
so many people have that when we're
struggling all kinds of different aches
and pains and different symptoms and we
reverse this what what does that mean
someone was asking about ingredients
which ones are in it I saw that too and
I have to go and run run by this again
if you guys don't mind barley grass
juice powder that's one of of the
five barley grass juice powder now don't
get this confused with barley grass cuz
people just go to the store they buy
barley grass that ain't going to do it
uh uh uh it's not going to do it it's
not has to be the barley grass juicee
pattern that this is the vimergy barley
grass juicee pattern it's the one I
endorse it's the one I work with and
endorse because it's incredible it's
that good so I stand behind it
wholeheartedly stand behind it I know
how good it is I know there's no binders
in here there's no agents hidden in here
did you know they do that in all the
powders out there they have all these
secret binders that aren't on the
ingredient list did you guys know that
they so so that it doesn't Clump up do
you know like no one realizes this they
go and they buy powders and different
things and it's all got these
anti-caking agents in there so that it
doesn't Clump up I don't care about a
clump I don't want garbage in my
products I don't care if there's a clump
like if barley grass cheese powder
clumped together and so what who wants
anti-caking agents that no one even
knows what it is it could be anything it
could be GMO corn powder I mean think
about that right anyway this is one of
the five ingredients right here the
vimergy barley grass juice powder all
right the vimer spirulina that's another
one of the five ingredients right there
incredible all on its own the vimergy
douls liquid that's the vimer douls
liquid right there incredible look at
this huh it's amazing okay that's
another one and then the wild
blueberries the Wyman's wild blueberries
which you can get at
airan yep and you got to be careful with
low quality products you have to be very
careful with lowquality products and
that's the Wy men's wild blueberry juice
this stuff is inane like insane if I had
a shot glass I'll get one in a minute I
just want to show you that right there
um be careful with low quality products
be very careful with lowquality products
out there they have all these different
agents in there all these different you
know um binding antibinding agents they
got all these different caking
anti-caking agents and they have more
than that that's hidden in there more
different ingredients all hidden in it
and all around it anyway irwan is
stocked with vimergy they're in there
now go ask them about it Wyman's wild
blueberries and wild blueberry juice and
then um let's go into this
dols right now you can do you can you
can buy dols in its whole Leaf form it's
a sea vegetable you can buy it that way
what I love with vimergy did is they put
it in a liquid form that's pure and
amazing I love that and then let's not
forget about the fifth key ingredient
right here guess what this is good old
cilantro using it as a leafy green now I
don't just do this right I'm going to
put cilantro in my
smoothie here we go I'm going to put a
sprig of cilantro in my smoothie right
that's not what what you do you put a
decent amount in if you can you put a
decent amount in you can put a cup of it
two cups if you like right half a cup
but I like putting around a cup of it in
there
amazing
amazing okay Nico says we're so excited
we are coming from Belgium for the book
signing and to meet Anthony and the
community community is going to be there
a big hunk of it for sure thank you so
much can't wait to see you I'm so glad
you're coming down from Belgium amazing
Sylvia Grayson over there on YouTube
healed my husband's fibromialgia so
awesome these things matter people
healed and I talked about this before
you guys right now in Social if one
person gets one person better you know
somebody selling a brand or doing a
brand or something like that they get
one person better they like roll out the
red carpet for him they praise them
they're God they're God they got one
person f with like pre-diabetic better
their sugar numbers are better they like
literally like they bow to them like I
have somebody who got better it's
somebody who got their blood sugar
better that's what happens out there
right and all those YouTube ads out
there people saying do this and your
blood sugar get better it's like all
that the medical M Community has people
that have gotten out of wheelchairs
people getting getting rid of fibro
multiple sclerosis people getting rid of
OCD bipolar people getting rid of the
worst conditions with PTSD depression
anxiety EX
osias chronic fatigue syndrome all kinds
of different problems brain lesions
liver problems fatty liver all kinds of
different stuff people have gotten rid
of with medical me information it is the
most healing Community around the world
the most healing Community around the
world if you can go um if you can go
show Iran some love for supporting the
medical medum community please go to
their social media and let them know how
we appreciate them can you guys do that
if you get a chance you can go to aan
social media and and check it out right
can you do that and just let them know
that you know that we appreciate what
they're doing they're putting the heavy
metal detox on the menu there and then
just show them some love if you can
because that's incredible that they're
doing this and and what they're doing
with everything so if you can do that
collaboration between aan and medical
medium and I'm rolling into aan I'm
going to be there that's right I'm
excited I'm going to be in that store
I'm going to sign some books then I'm
probably going to run off to the park
eventually at some point it's just going
to be I'm going to be back and forth to
the store to the park store to the park
store to the park crisy perspective over
there on YouTube hey good to see you I'm
excited Mindy I'm coming from Sugarland
Texas
whoa
incredible incredible
I don't know I'm just excited and I'm
blowing away
777 that's a good number
777 that number's up here 666 numberers
down here okay 777 numbers up here 666
numbers down here okay exactly
exactly yeah 144 that's right 777 new
podcast dropped to today by the way
check it out also medical medium
telegram check it out I talked about
Mars again on the medical medium
telegram are you guys interested in Mars
at all because I've been asking s so
lots of Mars questions and I was talking
about how the oceans on Mars before they
annihilated that planet before they
literally blew that planet to hell right
the greed and the wars and everything
did you know I was talking about how the
oceans were brackish they weren't like
the salt water here right they were
brackish it was too much fresh water
with the salt water it was really
brackish which they had all these other
different sea creatures and stuff buret
over there 144 we are coming we drink
heavy metal detox smoothie before our
flight because of radiation nice we try
to get the pet down looking forward
meeting you in person incredible you're
going to try to get the pet down here
too it's amazing you're going to try to
travel with your
pets incredible I drink the heavy metal
detox smoothie anytime I take a flight I
drink it pre-flight I drink it after the
flight if you can't drink it pre-light
drink it after the flight June 15th when
we're all together jazella aw what you
teach us works it is the best with heavy
metal detox smoothie I cured memory loss
and much more thank God I found you
thank God you're here thank God I found
you guys amazing I am so incredibly
grateful to all of you guys n says aw
can you reveal to us about other
speakers yet surprise surprise surprise
I got to have some surprises I mean
right I've already told you guys there
free merch already told you guys I'm
going to be there already told you guys
there's going to be plenty of bathrooms
also told you guys there's going to be a
lot of great things but yeah got to have
a surprise here and there right I can't
help it um I got some friends popping by
to do some speaking and I'm going to do
some speak look I'm saying I'm going to
speak but I also got some other
surprises too but I'm going to speak you
guys don't mind if I have a little bit
more of this incredible heavy metal
detox
smoothie so
good can I get a bigger spoon are you
guys okay with that excuse me over here
you guys over here don't worry over
here all
right
M A so good
so
good I still to this day can't get
enough of the hmds the hmd I Can't Get
Enough put on putting all these
ingredients on my salads in my salads I
can't get enough of like all of it I
love
dolls I love cilantro I eat cilantro
every day every
day incredible you know he guys on
another note I mean if you see somebody
out there that's just like
I mean they'll say stuff like all kinds
of crazy stuff like cilantro is not good
for you really it's
not cilantro didn't help me it almost
killed me really okay so everybody's
cilantro and everybody's guacamole for
the last freaking 50 years 60 years is
going to kill them um sorry but that
leafy green herb is healing people
around the world it's incredible and
healing people around the world sorry to
say don't use cilantro for any thing it
can kill you the stuff they say out
there is insane oh really okay so oh
don't put cilantro on your guacamole
anymore tell every
restaurant tell every restaurant on the
planet to not use cilantro for no reason
cilantro is a miracle and when you put
it in with when you put it in with the
spirulina when you put it in with
everything else mind blowing when you
put it in with the barley grass ju
powder the spirina The Dol liquid the
wild blueberry then something happens
inside the body I talk about this in
detail in the medical medium book
series Alicia thank you aw and SSC for
the steamed potatoes at Iran I'm doing
monoc
cleanses incredible please let aroan
know how grateful we are for the steamed
potatoes okay let them know on social go
to their social let them know how
grateful we are for their steamed
potatoes and everything else they're
doing seriously it's that incredible
they'd be amazing let's let them
know
definitely yeah Michelle Williams says
hmds safe with titanium rods please I
got a friend who's a doctor who's got T
titanium rods from an accident all in
both legs from a really bad accident
they had years ago they're doing the
hmds and they're a doctor a medical
doctor leave them a comment on irwan
social you know let them know how we
appreciate what they're doing they're
doing the steamed potatoes for June 15th
I mean how incredible is that they're
doing the celery they're making sure
there's celery juice there for sure
because I'm going to be grabbing celery
juice I'm not going to have time to make
any celery juice I'm just not going to
have time that day first of all I'm
going to be doing so much getting
prepared for this event June 15th so
much Tik tok's got a little hangup right
there so much that I need to make sure
that that I have my celery juice where I
can just pick it up at Iran I want to
make sure I got some steamed potatoes
I'm going to get hungry I'm going to get
hungry signing all those
books I'm be signning in those books and
then I'm going to be hungry and be like
steamed potato
please steamed potato please heavy metal
detox Smoothie Please you guys
incredible
um yeah yeah I'm reading some of the
comments anyway so as I was saying
before just a little reminder sign up to
medium.com okay register it's a free
event but register so you can get
information you need that would be
incredible the information there are
four parking locations try to use ride
share try to car pull okay cuz there is
limited parking because there's going to
be a lot of people there but there's
four parking locations check out those
details so you can be prepared and ready
please know that Iran has steamed
potatoes and the celery juice and
they're going to have the heavy metal
detox smothies lots of heavy metal detox
Smooths
okay they're going to have lots of it
there know that as well know that VII is
in aan in all locations please know and
and pick some up it's easy you can go in
there and get some at any time so please
know that vimer is in there and please
know that yes and tell other people
that's what I wanted to say please tell
other people that Wyman's wild
blueberries and the wild blueberry
juices in Iran as well I got to see the
free merch Yesterday by the way so I
just want to tell
you this is actually really good just
want to tell you guys this I got to see
the free merch yesterday I did and I am
so excited to see you all because boom
when this free merch is going to be in
your
hands it it's it's going to be really
cool because it's really good stuff it's
really high quality I am excited bar
Lynn says which store are you going to
be at I'm going to be at Culver City
Culver City
irwan in La Culver City please know that
heavy metal hippie really cool it's a
cool handle man on YouTube coming from
Chicago can't wait the windy city coming
from The Windy City whoa whoa whoa it is
going to be an incredible event Courtney
it is Courtney ma oh my God the best
event ever it is going to be it is going
to be incredible it's going to be fun
like I said there's going to be speakers
I'm going to be speaking it's going to
be fun and I'm going to see what happens
it's a surprise surprise Arena so tell
us aw more about the free merchandise
what's what is it it's a
surprise free merch is a surprise it
is I'm
pumped yep I can't even tell you
guys all right Mila says can we have a
dance party with a
DJ there happens to be a DJ
there there happens to be a DJ on June
15th at the medical medium launch party
there already is a DJ there already done
we don't have to make it happen cuz it
already has been put together and there
will be a DJ there how do you like
that oh my God incredible you guys yeah
I'm pumped up yes I want to have a dance
party OMG Amanda
says there's going to be a DJ
there and did I say there's going to be
speakers there I did all right listen I
want to tell you
guys all right okay anybody who can't go
I I feel really bad and my heart's with
you okay maybe there'll be another time
where where you do and and we do this
again in a whole bit just know that I I
feel for anybody who who can't go okay
and just they can't be there or they
don't have a means to get there or they
have a way to get there just know that I
understand
right incredible you guys yep Marissa
spiritual whoa on YouTube good to see
you will Dr Nesbit be in charge of the
playlist Dr Nesbit may make an
appearance how do you like that at this
medical medium launch party um Mr
pumpkin says you be in Iran in Culver
City question mark yes I will be in Iran
Culver City June 15th I will be there in
person uh-huh I'll be in the store I'll
be in the store Allison cool haha that
sounds like it's going to be fun and it
is going to be fun you guys I am beyond
excited seriously Carolina laugh out
loud that's hilarious I love us I love
us too seriously
incredible there's going to be bathrooms
there anybody who's worried cuz I see
people asking that question a lot like
where are going to go to bathroom
there's going to be bathrooms there
going to make it happen and we're going
to be in the park and in Awan Park Awan
I'm going to go with airw early in the
morning I know things are probably going
to get pretty intense so we're going to
make sure you know everybody's there's
going to be lots of Staff there's going
to be lots of everything there be lots
of bathrooms out there we're going to go
to the park we're going to have a nice
setup there there's going to be stage
there there's going to be a DJ all kinds
of things and I'll be probably back at
Iran I'm going be getting my lunch there
getting my steamed potatoes
it's just gonna be crazy I'm gonna sign
books just I'll have my Pen in Hand I'm
just gonna be signing I mean come
on oh my God lra says I am screaming in
my kitchen right now I'm so excited 10
exclamation
points I'm on the edge of screaming
myself right now but I have to dial it
down because I'm so excited I almost
want to start screaming see if I was in
the kitchen with you right now I would
be screaming too link
link to register for the event on June
15th is in the profile Link in profile
medical
medium.com incredible you guys you came
on late where's this happening Culver
City hi raw Vibe do you know about this
go to medical.com get all the details
there seriously Culver City La I'm going
to be there it's a big event it's free
you don't have to buy a ticket uh but
there's going to be incredible things
like free merch speakers there and
everything else I mean seriously you
don't want to miss out incredible you
guys optimal over there on YouTube I am
very excited
a I saw 10 A's very excited a very
excited lopus free with celery I am
silently screaming in my
head hold on you guys just hold on
I'm silently screaming in my head right
now I don't want to pop a cork I just
silently screamed in my head too because
I want to not silently
scream but I have to silently scream in
my head as well you heard that educating
myself educating myself are you coming
are you going to be
there um aana there's no words for how
honored I am for this information and to
be able to meet you I'm honored I can't
wait Marissa spiritual Papa cork yeah
papa cork okay Snider over there on IG
incredibly Greatful to Medical medium
info for this life-changing tool thank
you Anthony for changing my life thank
you for being there thank you for
working on it I'm so happy you worked on
things you took the information you used
the information thank God
mhm amazing
mhm so
good thank you guys for saying
like just the amount of Integrity you
guys have and the the like the how you
guys are deep souls and old souls and I
know
that and probably older than me older
than me way older old souls man old
souls here in the medical M Community
for
sure you know probably like ancient
souls okay ancient Souls much older than
than my soul I'm sure there's people
here traveling I will be loading up on
immune
support what is this in my hands you
guys know because you guys know that
this is helping you guys so much so many
people have said like it has changed
your life with oral health it's changed
your life in so many ways so many people
have talked about
this if you like this is what I travel
with right here okay right here I will
take a
photograph at some point during my
travels and I'll post it okay and that
photograph will have me drinking this
down right here because this is what I
do for my immune system when I'm
traveling this is propolis pure vimer g
v as in Victor i m as in Mary e rgy
vimergy.com get your propolis okay that
is an
extremely valuable valuable you know
product in my hand and I can't talk
enough about it with Pro this type of
prop listen what this is and how pure
and how incredible this is but this is
propolis pure I travel with it I take it
every single day and when I travel I'm
taking more of it because you know you
know exposures radiation exposures for
flood everything every exposure that
wants to knock your immune system down
right cuz that's what happens exposures
want to knock your immune system down
you get you get a little bit exposed to
this or a pathogen or exposed to
radiation or exposed to fragrances or
exposed to some type of toxin and and
your immune system takes a hit right
well guess what that's why I bring the
propolis with me right here just keep my
immune system Strong Rock Solid Rock
Solid immune system is I'm traveling you
know and working and you know freaking
out cuz you know there's so much to do
so much going on and I'm just like my
God is there something else that can be
thrown at me right now is there
something else that can be thrown at me
right now
propolis right here this is propolis
pure from vimergy that right there I
know so many people use and it's helped
them so much you use it every day too
you use it too incredible I mean the
stuff is just incredible it really is
okay I can't get into my cupboard here
cuz I got the the dummy in the way but
um maybe I do have something here I Cano
that's a noise oh who who I don't know I
know
n
tried crispy perspective you would
choose propolis over the immune blend
well if you're only going to take one
thing and one thing only like if you
just there's just one thing only and
that's all you're going to take I would
take the propolis for me personally but
I'm going to take the total immune and
the propolis cuz I'm going to take more
than one thing okay there's a lot of
people they don't have the room they
don't have enough room in their bag they
can't pack enough they can't take all
their supplements I got friends that are
just like I just need to take one thing
tell me what it is I'm traveling right
now to Europe I just need to take one
thing what is it I'll say take the
propolis take the propolis it's great
it's so great it's so great
so I'm going to put some propolis right
in here if you guys don't mind I am
going to do that
now okay little purpl right here if you
guys don't mind right there see dropping
that in there all right okay I'm going
to try not to spill it everywhere I'm
going to do the best I can I'm going to
put another one if you guys don't mind
right there ahuh indeed there we go oo
nice stuff is so amazing I'll show you
what it looks like
I'll pour some more in and just directly
okay so let me just pour some more in
directly if you guys don't mind I want
to show you what it looks like here okay
and I'm going to show you up close a
little bit let me just get some in
here what what I'm going to have to do
now cuz I probably won't put that back
in the bottle is I'll probably be
sipping that throughout the
day and tomorrow and so forth right okay
clean up my mess right here let me see
if I can put it right on my hand right
here let me see the best way to show you
what this looks like don't don't drop or
anything
please huh cameras aren't working so I
can't really do that zoom in on it you
guys it's Liquid
Gold it's Liquid Gold that's what that
propolis is right there it is liquid
gold it's hard to say okay total immune
is so good such in first of all I take
take total immune every single day okay
but I'm just telling people if they can
only take one thing and one thing only I
I I would probably take the
propolis and
um but if but if it was the total immune
fine it's so powerful it's also so
incredible it it's hard to say it's hard
to say it depends on what's also going
on with you too like you could ask your
doctor like what's the best best thing
for me right now but yeah I mean golden
seal okay here's what I'm taking okay
I'm taking golden seal I'm taking cats
claw I'm taking zinc I'm taking micro
I'm taking propolis with me and I'm
taking total total immune that's what
I'm taking with
me that's going to be my bag but I won't
go anywhere without that
propolis anywhere I have one in the car
you name
it yeah the glasses are Mars Vibe Tom
Thomas I'm going to be talking a lot
about Mars on my tell
a lot about Mars man did you catch the
last one and did you catch the one
before that you guys yeah are you
talking about these Mars glasses on
[Laughter]
me party sunglasses that's why I'm
wearing them okay I hope it's okay kind
of embarrassed
now kind of shy and embarrassed uhoh you
guys spotted my glasses these are party
glasses that's what it's about because
June 15th is coming up I'm wearing my
party Shades and you guys I'm excited I
really am all right so
um that's the liquid gold propolis right
there
incredible yes we want to hear about
Mars indeed I'm going to be talking
about Mars in so many different aspects
of it so many different on so many
different levels of it it's it's all
coming from so cold white spring laugh
out loud as
well yeah I'm I'm
excited medical medium podcast keep your
eye I got some more episodes coming now
I'm going to give
you just a little bit of a how should I
say
this
um you guys might want to keep an eye
out on the medical medium
podcast
[Music]
um guys right listen you guys know about
medical me podcasts at Apple podcast
right okay you know you know I've been
doing the health episodes right the
incredible Health episodes you know I
launched one today right you guys you
know how I did the chemical
sensitivities right and today's now the
food sensitivities you know you know
that episode released it today
but I'm just saying and you might want
to tell everybody else if you can to
kind of keep an eye out on the medical
medium
podcast because
holy
crap follow on telegram um event updates
and so forth on the day of the event and
I'm going to be on there so I'm going to
be on telegram doing like event updates
and everything like that so follow my
telegram because I'm going to be saying
all kinds of stuff and
everything Uma a Jesus podcast isn't
coming not not with what I'm saying here
but a holy baby Jesus moment podcast is
coming Uma mhm and and Uma I have a
feeling you're going to appreciate it I
have a funny feeling you're going to be
like this was
needed yeah I'm not doing a Jesus
podcast right now no but a holy baby
Jesus
moment is probably gonna
happen during the
podcast I'm trying to tell you in a
bunch of different ways you might want
to be kind of looking out for the
medical mem
podcast
yeah my 11-year-old says you look cool I
am honored greatly honored
seriously love your Mars talks
fascinating yeah the Mars talks are only
going to get more fascinating and more
fascinating because that's something
that I do on my five minutes of spare
time I ask SSC about Mars I can't help
it so I may as well share it with you
guys I mean of course
Angie my husband and I will be
celebrating our 25th wedding anniversary
with you on June 15th oh my
God congratulations by the way 20 years
it's 25 years
Uma you're going to be like okay yeah
he's got her back yeah I
do all you
guys
incredible over there
IG awesome can't wait for more Mars
education I can't way to be educated by
S so with more Mars education as well
because that's the whole point I'm
learning just like you guys Vicky over
there in IG love your Mars talks
fascinating yeah um I'm going to get
into the wars on Mars I'm going to get
into also the wildlife on Mars I'm going
to get into closer to the ending times
on Mars because Mars had an ending times
that's what happened just like planet
Earth
is constantly in in trouble and things
are getting sketchier by the minute out
there Mars had their day and some going
to talk about like different eras of
Mars right Lena do we get the tickets on
mail there are no tickets I'm not
charging anything it's free the June
15th event is free with free
merchandise and um and free talks I'm
going to have speakers and I'm going to
speak and I'm going to sign books and
everything
not charging anyway I love you
guys I love you guys all
right many blessings everybody take
care I'm honored honored to know you
guys
in um I'll see you there June 15th okay
I don't know if I'm going to be live
right now between now and then I I
really don't know I probably am at some
point but um I got to pack my
bags and get my crap together so I can
get out there so if you guys are okay
with
that you know wish me luck I'm going to
be packing up I want to tell you guys
something
okay I'm getting choked up a little
because I can't believe it all of us are
going to be out there that's going to be
incredible really
incredible am I going to
cry when I'm out there signning books am
I going to cry when I'm out there
speaking on June 15th am I going to cry
when I'm picking up my heavy metal detox
smoothies and grabbing my my steamed
potatoes and my celery juice I might cry
there's a good chance I might
cry already getting choked up all
right okay you guys I love you much I'm
going to have some of this