challenge medical medium morning cleanse
i got all my stuff
out here this is really exciting so i'm
going to run through the morning cleanse
with you guys
i got the juicer because i'm going to
make celery juice i got the blender over
here because i'm going to be making the
medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie right okay
i got the lemon water i'm gonna make
over here too
and i mean i got all kinds of great
stuff here i've got the cilantro
for the heavy metal detox smoothie which
is really awesome right there
i got the frozen wild blueberries in
here too
you'll see a lot of different stuff i
have around here um
later on i'm going to be making a fruit
bowl
and i'm going to be doing that on tick
tock so i hope later on you guys meet me
in a couple hours at tic toc but there's
going to be a lot going on
going to be doing a lot and i'm excited
glad you guys are here
so i'm going to be actually making
waffles on tick tock later too so
going to be doing that making waffles
homemade waffles
i'm really excited about that i'm
looking forward to it i hope you guys
are there with me then
um and so yeah waiting for you guys to
come on before i start
great to see alexandra drinking your
heavy metal detox smoothie right now
i can't wait to make mine i'm excited
about it awesome
and uh good to see you guys glad you
guys are here
hello from costa rica awesome so um
the morning cleanse is really like a
life
savior in so many ways because when we
head into the holidays
we end up eating a lot of things that
get in front of us and we can't help it
many of us are under stress during the
holidays
a lot of pressure during the holidays
are you guys under pressure at all
are you guys under any stress at all
especially what's happening and what's
going on
and so you know the holidays are never
that easy for a lot of people some
people it's it's fun and easy
a lot of people it's it's more than that
and what happens is we end up eating a
lot of different things we indulge in
different things
more so than usual and then we say you
know what
i'm just gonna come january 1st i'm just
going to start fresh
and we end up just you know eating
whatever that's in front of us
doing a whole bunch of different stuff
and so what's incredible
about the medical medium warning cleanse
is that it's there to protect you while
you're running into a lot of different
food
um food potholes food obstacles
you know food mania whatever comes your
way during the holidays
so it's it that's something to think
about there all on its own so
and and you know people are like
georgina says yep work stress so yeah so
even work stress during the holidays as
well
so that's a big deal too and so
there's a question there will uh celery
juice help with the liver
yes it does i talk about why and that's
why i'm gonna be making some celery
juice i'm gonna be making
the heavy metal detox smoothie too if
you guys just got on here
um 8 p.m here in england huh lorraine
wow so yeah and i'm excited about this
because
this is the check and balance this is
the benchmark this is what keeps you
strong while going through the holidays
and trying to and you know because it's
hard to dodge food
it's hard to like not not eat certain
things that get in your way
it's it i totally understand there's
friends there's family
people are making things people are
baking cookies
i just talked to somebody the other day
that you know a neighbor is baking one
of my friends cookies every day
and the cookies are filled with things
that aren't so great but my friend is
just gobbling them down
and you know and and the neighbor keeps
on making more
and bringing them over and their
christmas cookies and you know
you know those christmas christmas
cookies and when they get to you
what happens right so you know the
bottom line is
so what can you do for yourself like
what
can you do that can really help you
help protect you move the needle help
move you forward while you're going
through this kind of thing in the
holidays so that's what we're talking
about that's why i'm here i'm excited
about it and
i'm going to start with the lemon water
in a minute but first of all i just want
to tell you
you guys have your cleanse the heel book
right here so that's cleanse the heel
that's the book right there um if you
don't have it's on sale right now a
killer sale on amazon for this book it's
off it's 16.99 cleanse the heel
has 75 recipes in here and these recipes
have a lot to do with the morning
cleanse because these recipes
don't have any fats in them so they
protect your liver
so that's the morning cleanse right
there so we're gonna do the morning
cleanse
and that's it and this is the morning
cleanse challenge so there you go
and so in the morning cleanse so i'm in
cleanse to heal right now
in the morning cleanse it starts out
with the lemon water
first thing in the morning so every day
okay you're eating things indulging in
things
that come your way every single day the
liver just gets bombarded more and more
the reason why
people put on weight unwanted pounds
during the holiday okay is because their
liver is maxed out
and it's being it's being basically
compounded with lots of fat
so what happens is if you're eating some
pizza over here
even if it seems like a healthier pizza
or vegan pizza there's all this fat in
the pizza
and it's that fat that gets inside the
liver and
even if you're eating you know so if
you're eating other things too if you're
eating you know a few more eggs somebody
made you a nice breakfast and it's a
bunch of eggs scrambled eggs
maybe you got butter on some toast maybe
just doing avocado on toast and look
that's a healthier fat
but we do a lot of fats and our meals
consist
of fat every single day and so our liver
is already bombarded by all this fat
and when we eat fats in the morning
like peanut butter almond butter coconut
oil
even i know somebody that eats chicken
every morning like by like
mid-morning they're eating chicken or
bacon in the morning right
or eggs in the morning or milk cheese
butter all of that fat
stops your liver from cleansing so it
stops your liver from dumping out the
trash
it stops your liver from removing the
toxins and poisons
that actually keep us down as we get
older and older and older the unwanted
pounds come on
the weight comes on really easy that
happens like because the liver gets
maxed out and one of the cool things
about the morning cleanse
is you can do it every day or you can do
it now with the challenge right that
we're doing
and you're protecting your liver you're
protecting your immune system
you're protecting your lymphatic system
because that's an offshoot of the liver
you're protecting everything in your
body in so many different ways you're
protecting your pancreas because your
pancreas gets burned down with fats too
that's why people get pancreatitis and
during the holidays a lot of people get
gallbladder problems they get
pancreatitis
they get upset stomachs they get acid
reflux
because they're eating just a little too
much of this they're having some cake
they're having some cookies
they're indulging in a little too much
you know fats in different ways and
different foods and so
it's incredible about cleanse the heel
there's 75 recipes in here
and they're fat free and that's a big
deal because you can incorporate them
when you want but the morning cleanse is
great because
i'm not saying you shouldn't have
something that you like and i'm not
saying you shouldn't have avocados or
guacamole i mean i make a great
guacamole i love guacamole
i'm not saying you can't have any of
that or you can't eat a lot of chocolate
okay
all that fat in the chocolate and all
that caffeine i'm not saying you can't
have it during the holidays or anything
if that's what you want to do
but what i am saying is let's do the
morning cleanse
let's let our body heal while we're
in this holiday madness of foods and
eats
and we're we're living with all these
different foods
around us and friends and family are
making it for
for some of us or we're just indulging
more than usual because there's
something that comes around the holidays
i was talking to another friend and they
get really sad around the holidays they
get like depressed around the holidays
they get
depressed around christmas and around
new year's
and when they get depressed next thing
you know it they're eating a little bit
more and they're eating a little bit
more and they're having some bagels and
then they're having some bagels and
cream cheese then they're having some
donuts
then they're having a few cookies and
then they're having some ice cream
and that's another thing too is that so
many people are having ice cream
even the vegan ice cream is still high
in fat so
even the coconut ice cream is still high
everybody's kind of indulging and some
people they get sad during the holidays
some people get depressed so we end up
eating more so you know what
there's a way to protect yourself
while you're going through the holiday
season and that's the medical meeting
morning cleanse and
and if you don't have the book look
we'll still do it i got everything here
i got the lemon water i'm about to make
i got the heavy metal detox smoothie
which i'm about to make pretty soon
and i got the celery juice and later on
on tick tock i'm gonna be making waffles
and gonna making some other stuff too
so anyway let's start it out let's get
going here so that's cleansed to heal
you guys are 75 recipes in there i'm
going to run down a few of them
in a minute with you but we'll start
with the lemon water 16 to 32 ounces
of lemon water first thing in the
morning
when you wake up that's the best
time to do it if you can so right when
you wake up
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water upon
waking that's the key and it's as simple
as this you get your water
you have it in your glass all right
that's what i have here
taking the lid off now right all right
so that's the lemon water there
and so
i got a lemon right in front of me there
we go
i'm gonna cut that lemon in half
so that's your lemon there it is so you
guys got your lemons
and look if you're somebody and you only
want to do half a lemon
and 16 to 32 ounces you can i like doing
the whole lemon
i take it with my hand and that's how i
do it so you you can
you know do a different way you can do a
citrus reamer if you want or something
else in order to do it but i take my
hand
and i squeeze it just like this and this
and i'm making the lemon water right now
and that's how i do it
so
so that's a half a lemon and you can do
a half a lemon if you want and if
that's something that you feel like
doing that's a half that was a really
juicy juicy juicy
lemon is what that was it was a very
juicy one
so that's that right there because that
lemon was so
juicy that works all on its own so
that's a lemon water right there
now i like doing the whole lemon no
matter what
so i got the other half so and i'm gonna
squeeze a little bit more
so
and there you go so that's the lemon
water right there
so let's talk about what it does real
quick so
all night long your liver is working
really hard
to protect you it's gathering toxins and
poisons
and when you hear somebody talk about
toxins and poisons
what does that even mean it's like oh
toxins
that's all that is you know like what is
toxins what
what are you talking about well
petrochemicals
plastics pharmaceuticals did you ever
take a pharmaceutical have you ever
taken a drug
have you ever done a recreational drug
because
all those toxins and poisons from
pharmaceuticals
recreational recreational drugs
petrochemicals from plastics solvents
household cleaners fungicides that are
on new clothes
scented candles when you're breathing in
all that scented candle toxin which is
really one of the worst by the way
just so you know scented candles is a
life
shortener that means if you were
supposed to live to a hundred
scented candles throughout your whole
life will make it so you live to be 90
and you'll lose 10 years that's what
scented candle
candles will do air fresheners are life
shorteners and so we're breathing in air
fresheners when we go to do you know
appointments or you go somewhere or you
go you know you're in a store
and you're breathing in air fresheners
so if you have air fresheners in your
house pull them out of the walls
if you have the plug-ins and toss them
out if you're doing scented candles
toss them out because chemical scented
candles
and air fresheners are quintessentially
their life shorteners is what they are
so if someone was supposed to be 80
and and and we and they die at 80
okay well they're good we're going to
lose them
at 70. we're going to lose them at 72
we're going to lose them at 68. and
that's how dangerously toxic air
fresheners
and scented candles are so that's just
one example of how many poisons
we we we actually
ingest we actually breathe in we
actually get in our system
so when you think about toxins what kind
of toxins are we talking about
talking about um uh
like cleaning supplies we're talking
about fabric softeners we're talking
about
dishwashing detergents we're talking
about all those different things that we
might be exposed to we're talking about
water
in restaurants we're talking about toxic
heavy metals in water in restaurants
that's another thing right there too
so did you ever eat in a restaurant did
you ever drink water in a restaurant
that water in restaurants is just
city water that's filled with all kinds
of stuff it's filled with pharmaceutical
residue pharmaceuticals it's filled with
toxic heavy metals
so we have a lot of poisons and toxins
and then pesticide exposure insecticide
exposure fungicide exposure and i talk
about it in cleansing heal i mean if you
guys if you don't have this book
i mean look i i would get it and if you
need to get it free at the library get
it free at the library take it out from
the library okay
um but amazon's got the 51 off on this
book
16.99 for it it's it's easy to get it
through amazon if you ever want to get
it someday
but i talk about all the different
pesticides herbicides fungicides the
pharmaceuticals we get exposed to
and just so you know if you guys just
came on here and you're just on here now
i'm gonna make the
heavy metal detox smoothie pretty soon i
made the lemon water we're doing the
medical meeting morning cleanse it's in
cleanse the heel just so you know so
that's the book right there cleanse the
heel
and i'm also going to juice the celery
juice too as part of the medical medium
morning cleanse
so that's all in here so these
troublemakers i call them are
in your system so herbicides pesticides
insecticides fungicides they're on new
clothing
they're in the air and then the
chemtrails that float out down from the
sky
you guys heard the chemtrail episode
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
right i told you all about the
chemtrails and how they really work and
the truth about them well we breed them
in every day and during the holidays
they drop chemtrails on us more so
than ever before during the holidays
because they know people are going to be
out and about and outside more in a lot
of different ways
so when you look up at the sky you'll
see more chemtrails than you've ever
seen before
and all of these poisons and toxins get
into our system
we inhale them we ingest them we eat
them we breathe them in
it's plastics petrochemicals
pharmaceuticals toxic heavy metals
insects
insecticides and pesticides so anyway
that's in us so keep that in mind so
every single and then there's foods then
there's the foods we eat
so there's lots of different foods we
that have
toxins in them too and not good ones so
if you've ever eaten conventional dairy
if you ever eaten conventional meat if
you ever eaten conventional chicken you
got the antibiotics in your system
if you had a piece of chicken that
wasn't organic that wasn't
path you know that wasn't free range or
whatever it is if you've had a piece of
chicken from 10 years ago from a
restaurant the antibiotics in that
chicken still sit inside your liver
and i'm not saying not to eat chicken
i'm just saying those antibiotics are
still inside your liver
so that's how it works if you took an
antibiotic it's still inside your liver
if you took cold medicine from 10 years
ago
15 years ago it's still inside your
liver
but what happens is we cannot
get this out of our body out of our
brain
out of our liver and restaurant food is
a big thing right there that's how we
get a lot of this
we can't get these toxins out of us if
we have fats in the morning
so if you have your nut butter in the
morning which is like a healthy thing
you got your almond butter you're making
your smoothie you put some coconut oil
in your smoothie
you're never going to get the poisons
out so you can't get the toxins out of
your system
you see how it works so the medical
medium morning cleanse is not just great
for the holidays
it's important to do whenever you can so
you can get these toxins and poisons
out of your body old ones that are deep
seeded in there you know
antidepressants that people have taken
in their life they sit inside the liver
thyroid medications
sit inside the liver anti-inflammatories
sit inside the liver a cold medicine
sits inside the liver antibiotics all of
it sits down in there so great okay
it does but let's do something about it
so to begin with you just got on here
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water or
lime water right in the morning upon
waking is the best time to do it if you
want to add a little bit of honey
to this lemon water you can you can add
a little bit of honey to this lemon
water if you really want to so that's
okay all right
and um but give yourself 15 to 30
minutes before having the celery juice
and that's where we're going
next okay we're gonna we're gonna have
at least 15
to 30 minutes we head into the celery
juice okay
so that's the next part we're going to
go and um
so and then we're going to make the
heavy metal detox smoothie pretty soon
so we're gonna do that we're gonna head
there too so
i'm gonna get some celery sticks
so i got some killer celery sticks right
here look at this you guys
i got a really nice big batch of them
right here
so i'm going to place them here for the
moment
or actually i'm going to place them
right here actually it's a nice little
spot
and we're going to need the celery juice
next i don't know if you guys did your
celery juice yet today
um but we're doing the morning cleanse
i'm gonna pop this on
so
celery juice is an herbal medicine
[Music]
lemon water
is a medicine
that's what these are these are
medicinal
it's not that you're doing
[Applause]
celery and you're like okay i just had
some celery no
you just had straight herbal medicine
really important to know okay
and
if you do it every single day your life
will change there's a lot of reasons why
your life will change one is because if
you do it in the morning on an
empty stomach 16 to 32 ounces
okay janine you're doing yours i just
saw that drinking cj right now
amazing when you're doing 16 to 32
ounces on an empty stomach
you're not only helping your liver push
those toxins out
but you're neutralizing the poison and
toxins
it's phytochemical compounds
sodium cluster salts in celery
juice okay that neutralize
the charge the toxic charge that toxins
have
old pharmaceuticals have a charge to
them
that interferes with your body's
frequencies
keep that in mind toxic heavy metals
interfere with your body's frequencies
right i know that everybody's like
totally into the spiritual thing these
days
you know everybody's doing spiritual
work they're doing you know they're
doing spiritual growth they're doing
spiritual techniques they're reading
stuff they're doing stuff
listening to podcasts all these things
right
but what happens is these poisons and
toxins
interfere with our spiritual makeup
they interfere with our physical
body our energy they interfere with our
energetic frequencies because
what happens is these these toxins and
poisons
they run on a very negative charge
so they run on a very very toxic
charge they actually have a life a shelf
life
toxins and poisons have
a shelf life that becomes damaging to
cells
inside our body so it's important to
know when you're doing your celery juice
you're neutralizing those toxins
is what you're doing you're disarming
them because
those toxins are on the offense they're
out there to be destructive and damaging
to the body
pesticides inside your body
fungicides herbicides toxic heavy metals
petrochemicals
pharmaceuticals
solvents that come from carpet cleaning
have you ever had your carpets cleaned
ever have your carpets cleaned all those
solvents and poisons
from the carpet from the carpet cleaner
go in to the bloodstream and they have a
charge on them that's damaging to our
body
okay celery juice when it gets into
contact with all of these poisons and
toxins
disarms them breaks down their charge
diffuses them so that's what it's about
so when people think well i did my
celery juice
i guess it might have helped it might
not have helped whatever
well guess what it did help and it is
helping that's
that's a part of why it gets people
better that's why with people with
eczema and psoriasis
and skin problems vitiligo they have the
charge of copper and aluminum
[Applause]
um
carmen says i can't stay out of the
bathroom and i have to work i stopped
celery i'm assuming it's celery juice
because i can't stop
going if you're someone that has more
bacteria
in the abdomen if you have more bacteria
in the abdomen
you're going to be it's going to be
shocking that bacteria that bacteria is
toxic so when that bacteria
explodes your body's going to want to
rid it so
if you're if you have that kind of thing
going on i would consider
a small amount of celery juice is what i
would do i would consider a real
small amount of celery juice
and a smaller amount you could take baby
steps you can just go a little bit at a
time you can just go
um two ounces you can go four ounces you
can go a little bit at a time
and that's what you can do so that's
something that that's something that's a
way of doing it
the other thing is what else is
happening with your gut
that's the only thing you don't have any
bloating you've never had any gut
problems
you've never had the runs before or they
happening when you do other things
keep that in mind too always kind of
remember that if it's if everything's
perfectly fine
your stomach's fine everything's great
you never had a problem with any of that
then you drink some celery juice and you
have the runs well that's shocking the
bacteria that's what that is
um but keep keep that in mind but if
you've had other stuff too if you've had
the runs before
if something else triggers it other
things are going on
the liver a lot of stuff going on inside
the liver so you do baby steps just to
live this bad bacteria so you do a
little bit at a time a little bit of
time you start with four ounces
you can start with that right there so
you guys we're doing the medical medium
morning cleanse
and over time you'll be able to do a
little bit more and it's a little bit
more
and a little bit more and a little bit
more and that's what you can do over
time
and then eventually you'll be at 8
ounces
12 ounces 16 ounces 20 ounces
and you won't have the runs anymore
because you got rid of that
much bacteria that much of the bad
microorganisms and that's a big thing
there too
don't substitute you guys celery juice
with celery powder
whatever you do and it's either you get
you get the
fresh celery juice from a juice bar
watch out for
celery that's already been juiced in
containers not containers in bottles
they got the cap on them and they're in
the cold section of the health food
stores and grocery stores
and their hpp high pressure
pasteurization and they have a long
shelf life a long date on them
don't use those either those are
terrible um
so so just keep that in mind right there
if you can't
if you can't get lemons you can do a
ginger water
you can do that um if you can't get
celery
you can do more lemon water you can do
some ginger water medical medium ginger
water you can do some aloe water these
are all recipes in here too
so if you're somebody that can't get a
hold of celery juice you don't have a
juicer or you don't have a way to get
celery juice
all in here you got the recipes right
here for all that i'm gonna
i'm still gonna make the heavy metal
detox smoothie so bear with me guys i
got everything here i got big pile of
cilantro right here
i don't know if you guys can see it and
i got some other stuff too so i'm gonna
make that
the recipes in here are really really
helpful
um there's so many great recipes in here
that that you can work with and so much
good stuff so
i'm just going through so many different
recipes right here
but celery powder does not work i'm
letting you know i'm giving you the
4-1-1
you guys just came on we're doing the
medical meeting morning cleanse i'm in
cleanse the heel right now
so you might wanna get that book someday
put it on your wish list or something or
try to get it free at the library right
now it's 51
off that amazon uh it's 16.99
in us so look i'm looking at all the
different
recipes right here
and
and what's incredible about all the
different recipes and there's 75
different recipes in here there's a
cucumber juice which it actually is
really a great option for many people
too
there's a great cucumber juice recipe in
there of course there's the celery juice
right here
and here's the lemon ginger
i don't know if you can see that lemon
ginger
and honey water right there that's a
great substitute if you can't do celery
juice or you can't find a way to do
you know juice celery and you don't have
options
um there's the lemon lime water by the
way that we just made we just made the
lemon water but there's there's a recipe
to do it a little differently too
right there in the book so doing the
medical medium morning cleanse
there's the book right there so i'm
gonna um
pour the celery juice out right now
if you guys just came on there we did
the 16 to 32 ounces of lemon water we're
flushing the liver that's what we're
doing we're cleaning house we're
cleaning up everything
and during the holidays it's a great way
to heal by doing this medical meeting
morning cleanse
at the beginning of the day so then when
you're doing other foods and other foods
are happening
and the other foods aren't aren't so
great for you and they're they might be
toxic
all of that this is this is an awesome
so i'm going to put this down so that's
the celery juice right here
i hope you guys had some this morning
it's great it's so good
i'm gonna put a cap on it i'm gonna make
the medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie
just letting you know but you've got
other options too you can do
fresh fruit if you if you don't want to
do the heavy metal
uh detox smoothie you can do fresh fruit
breakfast
um that's an option too if you want
something more denser you can do steamed
potatoes if you're somebody that wants
something more denser
just don't put oil don't put cream
butter milk on your potatoes
you can do winter squash you can do
steamed potatoes you can do that as well
you can do millet you can do oatmeal you
can put maple syrup in your oatmeal
that's an option but fruit
is the most healing for your
medical medium morning cleanse morning
fruit is a big that's the most healing
part right there
that's like another big healing part
especially when you do it all together
you do your celery juice you do your
lemon water first you do your celery
juice second
okay and then you do some fruit
i'm gonna do the heavy metal detox
smoothie but still
you can just do chopped up fruit you can
eat chopped up bananas
you can make one of the recipes and
cleanse the heel
just capping the lemon water right here
so i have that there
so i'm going to move the juicer out of
the way you guys
this is what i'm going to do right now
just give me a second
so moving it out
and just cleaning up these lemons right
here
and i'm going to bring the blender in so
just bear with me
i got a nice orange for the heavy metal
detox smoothie i'm excited about right
there
brain of blender so
you guys got to remember this okay
what happens is that when you give your
body a chance to cleanse every morning
and you're taking a break off the fats
you're giving yourself more years in the
future
you're giving yourself a chance to live
healthier you're giving yourself a
chance to rid
conditions and symptoms that you're
dealing with so
there's all that involved too but during
the holidays
this is a great way to keep the extra
unwanted pounds from coming on
this is a great way to protect your
immune system to keep a strong immune
system
every year with all the holidays i've
seen this over
the last 30 years i've seen people get
the flu during the holidays
it's always somebody in the family
somewhere out there and somebody's
family that gets the flu they get kicked
on their butt
they got a fever they got a bad cough
they get it around christmas time
their immune system runs down and they
get stuck with the flu
and flu season starts up around that
time and of course now we've got the the
new problem that we have now on top of
it so everybody's immune systems they
get lower during the holidays
they're eating foods that lower their
immune system whether they know it or
not
they get more susceptible to you know
the virus that's going around now they
get more susceptible to
flu virus they get more susceptible to
their own viruses
their own epstein bars shingles viruses
that give you chronic fatigue and
trigeminal neuralgia neck pain back pain
migraines
fatigue tingles and numbness floaters in
the eyes ringing in the ears dizziness
vertigo so they get ex
you get susceptible to your own viruses
that people have
like the epstein barr causing
hashimoto's and hypothyroid
and all the different thyroid conditions
and hyperthyroid and
cysts and nodules and pcos and
endometriosis so people already have
enough to deal with and then you got
outside viruses
okay you got the covid and you got the
flu and you got other viruses that are
happening on the outside that
aren't happening just on the inside of
people so then you got that in the way
out there
and then the holidays come and we're
under stress we're under pressure
we're eating the foods we shouldn't eat
and then our immune system
drops drops drops our liver gets
stressed out
stressed out to the max and then we go
into the winter feeling more
sick and a lot of people it's really
hard so that's some something right
there just think about
and i'm glad we're getting a chance to
talk about this so if you guys just came
on
medical medium morning cleanse i'm
making heavy metal detox smoothie right
here
i'm excited i'm glad we're here glad
we're doing this so if you just came on
here just did the medical medium
lemon water 16 to 32 ounces
i just did the celery juice 16 and 32
ounces right
and now it's time
to make a smoothie that's what we're
gonna do now okay
so we can do a couple of things we could
start out by throwing the wild
blueberries in there
it's two cups of frozen wild blueberries
right there okay so i'm going to pop
that in there
now nobody knew what wild blueberries
were until mm info
and i
i mean nobody knew they're just like
blueberries
no not blueberries wild blueberries yeah
blueberries right
no wild blueberries the little wild
blueberries and now i'm hearing it out
there
it's out there on podcasts it's out
there on youtube people are talking
about
wild blueberries you know and medical
medium books
actually blew up the whole frozen wild
blueberry thing the whole wild liberty
thing around the world
so because millions of books went around
the world
it's the number one health books there
is globally
hands down for six years running i think
is the medical medium book series
and that's come with a lot of good stuff
but it comes with also a lot of
a lot of uh people that you know they
don't like seeing
they don't like seeing you get too many
people better out there in the world
because millions are healing for medical
media books
and that disappoints i think uh
big pharma and stuff because then that's
less pharmaceuticals more people get
better on celery juice then less
pharmaceuticals get sold
you know you guys know the drill out
there how it works so i got the frozen
wild blueberries this is the heavy metal
detox movie and what this smoothie does
blue and l i didn't know wild
blueberries existed before mm info
indeed
loon you're awesome i'm glad you're here
incredible and um
good to see you good to see you i'm
still thinking about the potato poem
that you wrote
the night sprite that goes in there the
potato poem you wrote that you put in
the comment section
it was actually a really good poem um it
was
it was really good okay so i got the
frozen wild blueberries right here
and um i'm gonna put
two bananas in here you guys really want
to do one banana and you can do one
banana
all right it's okay bananas are an
incredible food great for the digestive
system great for the liver
glucose for the brain potassium for the
brain
if you hear somebody go like oh too much
potassium too much potassium
if you hear that you got to know one
thing
potassium is one of those little
powerful minerals those little powerful
electrolytes
critical for the brain to function so
take potassium out of the equation and
your brain goes
short circuits that's how it works so so
when you hear someone
that's that's kind of misinformation
that's always out there there's just
so much bad misinformation it's like
bananas are bad
potassium too much potassium too much
this okay sure
whatever okay just stop people from
healing
just keep on stop people from healing
it's unbelievable so yeah so there's two
bananas in here right there um
a cup of cilantro i'm just gonna put you
know
big hunk right here which is going to be
like you know my cup
version so you can do that so i'm
putting that in here
so you throw some cilantro in here
that's what you do just breaking it up a
little bit
i'm really you know the thing is is that
the heavy metal detox smoothie has is
responsible for saving lives it's
responsible for getting a lot of people
out of wheelchairs
that were heavy metal in their brain
aluminum deposits
mercury deposits in their brain keeping
them
down keeping them sick multiple
sclerosis
als parkinson's high anxiety disorders
depression
bipolar depersonalization
um you know and if you guys if you guys
just got on here you might want to get a
copy of cleanse to heal someday it's a
medical textbook and it has all those
conditions plus
a lot more 75 recipes we're talking
about the medical media morning cleanse
which is in cleanse the heel
i'm letting you know powerful way to
keep yourself healthy
it's 51 off on amazon i can't get any
better than that 16.99
get it free at the library if you want
to but that's cleanse the heel but
the heavy metal detox cleanses and
cleanse the heel
so there's a cleanse and it's the heavy
metal detox cleanse by the way so
to personalize and there's over 200
symptoms and conditions in here
and um true causes to what causes the
sickness and conditions so you can learn
what the problem is and
so you can figure it out so there you go
and you can learn how to heal there's
supplements and dosages
of like the different supplements at
different dosages so you can get a head
so you can do healing so you can recover
all that's in this book but
depersonalization depression anxiety
bipolar
um schizophrenia is toxic heavy metals
schizophrenia is toxic heavy metals
so all of the different conditions
emotional conditions brain conditions
that are all
you know that are all mystery medical
medium information has been teaching
this for 35 years so what happens is
that
the information gets out there someone
might take a little piece never cite it
back to medical medium and then people
think it's already out there but it's
not it was
it's all in the books too first
published in in many of the medical
medium books but
this is the infamous medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie that brought
lives
back the recipe is in cleanse the heel
the information is inclined
to heal so let's finish up with the
recipe
and what i mean by brought lies back you
tell me if this matters
okay you're suffering from the worst
depression okay
you don't want to live anymore you're
hopeless you feel hopeless you feel like
life is hopeless you feel like you're
hopeless you feel like nothing can work
you feel like you can't get ahead of
yourself
and you're doing the heavy metal detox
smoothie
and you start coming around and you
start getting out of that and you start
getting inspired
you start getting you start feeling like
you're getting in touch with yourself
again you start being able to see
straight you
you start feeling relief out of the
depression something that no one can
even understand
and next thing you know you're working
again next thing you know you're living
your life you feel like your purpose is
back
and that's the heavy metal detox
smoothie is that a good thing i think
that's a good thing or how about this
you got alzheimer's and you're destined
to die as far as the doctors believe
okay and then all of a sudden you're
you're your spouse or your sister or
brother puts you on the heavy metal
detox movie i've seen this 100 times out
there
and the alzheimer's starts to actually
reverse and reverse and reverse to the
point where you know your name now
does that matter well yeah that's what
i'm talking about
lunelle um
you're saying all i can tell you is that
the info is real the real deal i'm not
supposed to eat
cold foods either yet i'm healing with
the mm info
i also stopped being chronically cold
see belief systems
i gotta tell you something about belief
systems okay belief systems
in health i have nothing against them
but when someone says well
there's this and then there's this and
there's this out there well people don't
know like there's
fodmap and then you know you're not
allowed to eat cold food because someone
tells you that you got dampness
you know because that's that's you know
a traditional chinese medicine
concept whatever the concept is out
there whether it's western eastern
it's all man-made it's man-made medical
medium information is not man-made
um i'm just a messenger so i'm just
letting you know so you know what this
is about so
and here's what's crazy as far as
medical medium information has become a
law
in natural health there's so many pieces
of it out there now
that doesn't come from a study or
anything it comes from these books but
yet doctors
consider it law now it's like holistic
law
so there's so many tools being used
celery juice being one of them
that doesn't that wasn't out there
because of any study
it's out there because millions of
people got their lives back and they
healed and people got out of wheelchairs
the heavy metal detox smoothie
is legendary for recovering people and
giving people their lives back
and there's something to be said about
that so you guys i got bananas
wild blueberries frozen wild blueberries
in here i got cilantro in here i
squeezing some orange right now like
this in here
i love putting some orange in here this
is so great
and um and so it's not a belief system
medical medium information
it comes from above since i was age 4
i'm just the messenger that's why more
people have healed of medical medium
information
than anything else in holistic health
yet in our history
that's a fact i can't change it you
can't change it
nobody can change it it's just a fact
more people have reversed their
conditions and diseases with celery
juice and other medical medium tools
than any other place
on the planet i'm not boasting i'm just
talking about
the fact and the results and the street
cred
that's all i'm talking about um you know
so i mean you can call it what you want
it but
it's what it is and it's really a great
thing
it's really a great thing you guys have
put orange in there and now i'm going to
put a little bit of dolson here
a little strip of dulce right here so
this is atlantic dulce
it's part of the five things in here
that get you better
this is the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie you're looking right here
it's already saved lives and change
lives
it's around the world and people are
using it so i'm also going to put a
couple of other things in here this is
barley grass juice powder now this is
the vimergy barley grass juice powder
it's the only one i trust
v is in victor i m as in mary e-r-g-y
okay that's the only one i trust it's
the best one there ever is out there if
there was a better one i would use it
if there's a better one i would use it
simple as that putting a teaspoon of the
barley grass juice powder in here
because it's part of how you get the
metals out
so there's the barley grass juice powder
right there
so now i'm going to do the spirulina now
i used to like uh pacific spirulina
i don't like it anymore because it's not
the best quality
in my opinion it's not the best quality
i've ever seen
is the kind that vimergy has and that's
the best quality spirulina i've ever
seen
so i'm putting a teaspoon of spirulina
in here too if you don't know the
company is v is in victor i
am as in mary e-r-g-y go to vimorgy.com
i'm not sponsored very important to know
not sponsored by any of the companies
that i show like these product companies
like these supplements and all that
stuff i like lots of supplements out
there
different supplement companies i like
out there and um
then i'm not sponsored so i just put the
dolls in there i just put the spirulina
i just put the barley grass juice powder
i'm going to put a little
uh even though i put wild blueberries in
there i'm going to throw a little bit of
the
vimergy wild blueberry powder in here
too
but by far the best stuff on the market
i've ever found out all the companies
and brands
that i've actually vetted this is the
best one there is
just for the record so i got the heavy
metal detox smoothie what
is going on here i'll tell you okay
frozen wild blueberries
that gets metals out of the brain
that's what you have to realize why do
people get focus and concentration
issues
why do people get anxiety and depression
depersonalization alzheimer's dementia
bipolar schizophrenia emotional
emotional ups and downs everything brain
related why
and it's wise and it's a mystery toxic
heavy metals
mercury aluminum are the dominating ones
inside people's brains
eating up their brain okay discharging
oxidizing inside their brain what i love
about the medical medium heavy metal
detox movie
is its reverse conditions fact jack
fact it has it has and that's the most
incredible thing about it it's a
wonderful thing
anyway i got in here i'm excited
i'm gonna start blending it up
so i like having in the medical media
morning cleanse as an option
it's like a favorite thing because i
know it's doing so much
it's getting metals out you got the
cilantro in there you got the wild
blueberries
you got the barley grass used powder you
got the dolls you got the spirulina
all metal removers working together
so that metal doesn't get displaced it's
so
metal actually pulls out of the
you guys just got on here
you guys just got on here with 16 ounces
of lemon water right here
16 to 32 ounces of celery juice
making the heavy metal detox moving
so i'm excited about this
so i'm going to get something for it too
now if you guys just got on here
heavy metal detox cleanses and cleanse
the heel i mean if you don't have the
book you might want to get it
have it in your library you know just
have it in your hand someday
75 recipes it's incredible book
um so much information in there i mean
if
really what happens is there's so much
in there
making the heavy metal detox smoothie
right here
you can spoon out the rest you want
so i got the heavy metal detox smoothie
right there powerful
and what i would do during the medical
medium uh morning cleanse
i would do like 16 ounces of water too
maybe during the morning at some time i
would do coconut water as an option too
so that's something you can do as well
you guys later
on tick tock first i'm going to go to ig
i'm heading over to instagram first but
after instagram i'm going to be at tik
tok
at two o'clock pacific time five o'clock
east coast time i'm going to be on tick
tock making waffles
and fruit cereal keep up keep your
notifications on
or at least be there at five o'clock
eastern two o'clock pacific on tick tock
we're in the medical media morning
cleanse challenge you just saw a medical
medium cleanse to heal it's something
you might want to pick up when you get a
chance okay
75 recipes over 200 symptoms and
conditions
check that out when you can supplement
dosages how to heal
medical medium tools i'm going to go to
ig i'll see you there so i'm looking
forward to it you guys if you want to
come over to ig i'm going to do this
again
but at tick tock i'm going to make
waffles just can't wait so anyway
all right you guys um bless your heart
take care