or give it a like or subscribe or follow
if you can share it with other people
because we're going to cover a lot of
questions and important ones
so um and you know food questions too
so throw those at me as well you can
throw the food questions
um got health and health questions as
well and
and all that so any kind of insight i
can and bring i want to do that
so waiting for the comments to come up
and as soon as they arrive i can start
answering some questions
number one new york times best-selling
author anthony williams the medical
medium if you're new here
and i even have cleanse to heal with me
right now by the way i hope you got this
book
you can go to the library get it for
free it's an amazing sort resource
hey hi soc spirit of compassion
great glad you guys are here hey
stephanie you're amazing too
um
so a lot of great questions coming
through already i'm seeing them fly up
so i'm trying to kind of get them
getting the questions to slow down if i
can
you know it's a good one era food
question hello
what are your thoughts about coffee so
okay
my real thoughts about coffee matcha tea
chocolate the caffeine industry the
caffeine this
industry just they really want to
control
people and that's their like that's
their mission
it's get people addicted get people
hooked and own their soul
that's what the caffeine industry wants
to do and i'm not talking about really
good heartache good intentioned
people who start up you know a coffee
shop
a coffee business um you know whatever
they want to sell a really good matcha
tea i'm
not talking about that that kind of
thing where it's that i'm talking about
the industry above them that gets
them addicted too it's it's an addiction
caffeine's a drug
okay it sounds harsh it's all good but
what happens is women get hair thinning
and it comes from years of caffeine not
every
not everybody the hair thinning can
happen for a few other reasons a couple
of other reasons but
but for the most part the caffeinated
beverages
the chocolate what it does is it beats
down women's adrenals and women
need their adrenals super strong for
pregnancies
for birthing babies for the reproductive
system
for the fact that they handle so much
and they do more do more
they do so much more than even men do in
so many cases women are actually
you know they have it much harder in
many ways um i mean i know women they
have
20 jobs i mean 20 jobs and
and they're doing 20 jobs from the
minute they wake up in the morning to
the minute they go to bed
they're raising children taking care of
their family they're working you know
two jobs they're doing all these things
combined
and the caffeine is kind of like it's a
scary thing because it burns out the
adrenals it gets
it actually starts to beat down the
adrenals
hormone blend the one that keeps hair on
women's heads
and and so you know caffeine is a big
part of that another thing it does it
causes chronic dehydration over time
it beats down the liver it breaks down
the liver it gets it weak it gets its
stagnant and sluggish
um and it causes adrenaline surges for
people to be in fight and flight every
day so that's that's the whole thing so
what do i think about coffee
if you're look if you've got nothing
going on there's no so you have no
symptoms you have nothing wrong
you feel great everything's good and you
want to do coffee drinks and you want to
do much tea and you want to eat
chocolate vine i mean
it's you know it's not that i'm like
freaking out or anything about it
it's just if you got fatigue if you have
symptoms if you got
some some brain fog if you have issues
of all kinds of different kinds let's
get down to the bottom of those issues
let's get down to the bottom of fatigue
and brain fog and anxiety and depression
and you know and but the chains of
addiction
or the the caffeine industry it's a
monster
that has shareholders at the top and
those shareholders want to make sure
every girl and every woman every
man too is addicted in every way
possible to caffeine that's the industry
they want them all hooked and they
wanted to own the person's soul
and they wanted to the caffeine industry
knows that if they can just control
women
on a caffeine addiction they got them
they're set they're set and they can
they can make trillions off of
off of caffeine you know caffeine from
there on out it's it's really
it's a really important topic um lisa
says coffee is my biggest obstacle
because it's it's it's a tough one it's
like it's it's an addiction
and i listen i don't blame you one bit
you need to know this like when when the
industries get us hooked on something
and they don't teach us otherwise and
they don't give us opportunities and
we don't get these opportunities to find
out what's going on with why we have
brain fog or why we got fatigue and why
we don't feel good
and the industries don't want us to know
how to fix those things they want us
hooked on that coffee so lisa it's not
like
it's not like it's your fault on any
level and plus it tastes good when you
put sugar in it
and you put you know you know if you put
sugar in coffee and you put whatever
soy cream or soy you would have soy
creamer or cream in it or whatever you
want to do
it tastes good right and so that's the
whole thing on its own
but but it's not your fault if it's your
biggest obstacle
you're a good person you didn't do
anything wrong not at all
it's it's the industry is evil i'm just
gonna be straight out the coffee
matcha tea caffeinated industry i don't
care how
woke or evolved it all seems with the
cutest coffee you know
um like coffee campaigns and matcha tea
campaigns out there
i have respect for for owners of these
companies as far as not the
not the industry itself but respect for
coffee shop owners and uh
majesty brands that are trying to get
their first match of tea out to
for people like high quality i got
respect for everybody good chocolate i
got respect for
people who want to get their first you
know what they wanna they wanna
get into you know start a company in a
business and sell chocolate i get
respect for everybody
that's not it that's not the people i'm
talking about above them
is this hierarchy is this evil giant
and that evil giant is downright
despicable and
that giant needs women especially women
hooked on coffee they want them hooked
on caffeine they want them hooked on
you know the teas they want them hooked
on everything and
it's really sad and they want to own
women's souls
and that's what that industry wants to
do i know this for a fact
this is what they do and um
and it's you know it's one of those
things
hey brandi you're awesome too um there
you know
so i briefly saw something you talked
about with the dangers of diatomaceous
earth by the way
so diastomace diatomaceous earth
particles
um and someone said i didn't know this
but i took it i took it for about two
weeks
straight as did my sister now we both
have issues with their joints being way
too loose and they feel like they could
easily just come out of their sockets
plus my knees start to feel like they're
tearing for no reason just
walking and standing makes them hard
start start to tear
um have to sometimes wear a knee brace
now shoulders hurt
and everything pops will this ever fully
heal is there something i can do
with the whole diatomaceous earth thing
and
and the side effects so that's
diatomaceous i've
i've i've been anti-diatomaceous earth
particles from the beginning um not a
big fan of it
from you know what i've seen and what
spirit of compassion some
say soc right spirit of compassion has
told me is
it's just not great for the immune
system not great for the immune system
and it's hard on the digestive tract so
it's those two things here so if you
have something going on like
an epstein barr and your sister has an
epstein bar
and you've got the sepsis bar sitting
inside of you and it's probably about to
come out and do its thing
and low-grade viral infection i talk
about you know and cleanse the heal when
people have the epstein bars they have
fibromyalgia and they have all these
other
you know joint pain and all these
different symptoms
and you take the diatomaceous earth
particles or you take you know what
however in what form or you breed them
in
it it it kind of it's hard on the immune
system
and when it's hard on the immune system
anything else can creep up
anything can creep up so um everybody
has a chance to heal everybody has an
opportunity to get past whatever
you know adversities they're up against
their health and have a chance to heal
you know and the angels are always on
our side
they're always looking out for us you
know um and i'm going to talk more about
that every now and then too
but yeah there's but but i just i always
tell people you know stay away from
diatomaceous earth
but i tell people to stay away from a
lot of things the caffeine i tell them
because that will knock
knock the immune system i've seen
caffeine make people so sick
so sick and and you know it's
unbelievable really
and then the same i tell people stay
away from nutritional
yeast i tell people to say a lot of
thing away from things that people
don't know about bentonite clay stay
away from bentonite clay
stay away from apple cider vinegar i bet
you i just angered a whole bunch of
people just now right
you guys are probably like all upset but
stay away from apple cider vinegar
it'll just pickle your liver it'll
stress out your system all that talk
about all what it does
so going through the questions right now
deborah says i'm so addicted
you know what you know the thing is with
the caffeine industry
it which is really sad is even when you
know you're addicted
and you can't break it that's how
powerful that is
and chocolate's all fun and all you know
you see influencers eating their healthy
chocolates wanting to put their healthy
chocolates out their cacao
and they're just they're sucked in
they're sucked into the madness
to the industries controlling them in
their soul so it's all about
like it's amazing how it works
um so here's a question here
charlene i just want to i just want to
thank you
the divine and the angel compassion for
turning us onto celery juice
i i think spirit of compassion all the
time about celery juice
once i began doing the protocol
correctly
the course correction was fast anthony i
thank you for being a
superb instrument and helping us bless
your heart so you're working on the
protocol properly i'm so proud of you
that means you probably read
cleanse the heal you're learning this is
a heavy medical tech this is like a
heavy book it's a medical textbook it's
packed it's comprehensive
um go to library get free or amazon has
51 off sale right now 16.99 it's
unbelievable sale
on amazon.com u.s um
sema any chance on bee venom
therapy specifically to treat lyme or
other chronic diseases okay
so my opinion on that any opinion
on that sorry on the uh venom therapy so
um here's the thing with b venom therapy
okay i'm not trying to take away
somebody's therapy
if they really find relief or they
really find something out of that they
really like but i can talk about it here
on
what i know about it and what spirit of
compassion has taught me about it and
what i teach doctors about it too
is that what's happening is with with it
it's an adrenaline response is what
occurs so when you get stung by a bee
when you get stung by a bee on your leg
or on on your body somewhere and usually
with
uh with with b therapy when they do this
is
they you sting the thigh or you sting
the knee
and in the arm too but but what happens
is it prompts the adrenals
to flood so instantly your adrenals are
flooding and flooding and flooding it's
it's a it's a serious adrenal surge
when you get stung by a bee adrenaline
is pouring in
just from your adrenals okay and so when
that's happening you guys
what you do is you get steroid relief so
you're getting steroidal relief
so that's how the therapy works so when
you have neurological conditions
like any kind of neurological condition
you have aches and pains
tingles and numbness ticks and spasms
you know like you you know uh limb
weaknesses
you know people with multiple sclerosis
or they have ms or they have als or they
have other kind of condition whatever it
is
and they're doing the bee sting therapy
it's prompting their adrenals
their self-treating themselves with with
steroids
they're using their own steroid to treat
their condition now what i don't like
about this
is that the adrenaline is corrosive
and it's it's agitating so we have
somebody with multiple sclerosis or
somebody with a neurological condition
that the doctors don't know why they're
sick medical research and science
doesn't know why people are sick they
don't have answers
if you want to know why people are sick
well these autoimmune conditions you
get cleansing heal so you can read the
true causes medical medium information
this only source that has that
information out there
other than that everywhere else is just
a game of like a cryptic game of
nonsense but anyway the bottom line is
that when your adrenals are flooding
because you're doing bee sting therapy
you're self-treating using your own
adrenaline
as a rush as a steroid
and then what it does is it gives you
relief it's the same thing with
like the same thing with some other
things that occur now
um it could be a temporary fix but
you'll notice with neurological
conditions it's only temporary
it only the relief only lasts for an
hour or half a day
or a quarter of a day or a day or two
days
depending on how much adrenaline was
released and so if you had a lot of
adrenaline released
i noticed that bee sting therapy when
you first get it
gives you some relief because a lot of
adrenaline gets released but on your
10th therapy
or your 50th bee sting you don't get the
response is the same and you need more
bee stings and you need more bee stings
i'm not a fan of it i don't recommend it
i don't recommend bee sting therapy
i never did and i'm not a fan of it um
but that's that's what i know about it
if it helps
anna gosh i started to drink a little a
little of coffee again
and my alopecia started to get worse but
i didn't see the link i
you know it's incredible that you you
understand this now
because of the medical medium
information about that but that's what
it does it's it's the
the industry actually is training
women to be addicted to the to the
caffeine
the caffeine kills women's adrenals and
nobody cares
nobody cares and then you get these like
fake doctors that
that have their podcast and they're just
like oh yeah matcha tea is great it's
got healing benefits and it's got
oh you know it's like you know your
dummy you know it's like
you don't get it you want to keep women
addicted too and then they just burn out
their adrenals and then when it's
pregnancy time
you don't have it here's the here's what
caffeine does
caffeine um makes pregnancies
harder and makes birth burn giving birth
harder
because you blow out your adrenals early
on in your life
and then then you get pregnant and then
you have a baby
and you in in the giving birth process
is much harder because your adrenals are
maxed out
and sometimes shot from coffee and all
that and this is medical medium
information nowhere else is this
information like all the information on
here if you're new here it's all medical
medium information
it's not somewhere else it's not
somewhere at so-and-so's it's not
wherever
and if it is they took little tidbits
and didn't incite it back to medical
medium information
um cindy after eight years of whole
foods and clean eating
i cannot lose weight i need help losing
weight
30 pounds to get me back to pre-baby
and i have autoimmune issues please
please please help the first thing is
autoimmune issues you can go to the
autoimmune section and cleanse the heal
and you can see back there
and you can see there's a protocol you
could take that protocol to your doctor
or practitioner if you want or just work
with it if you want to do
and you'll see there are different
supplements what to do take it slow one
little thing at a time but what you
learn is what was your autoimmune
disease name
that a doctor gave you too and you can
just go straight into autoimmune or you
can find that name specifically in the
book
but the point is is that what they don't
know
is what's behind autoimmune is a viral
condition and
i talk to doctors about this all the
time and you know and i teach doctors
this information if it's classified
under autoimmune
that's a viral issue and where do
viruses go and where are they
throughout a person's lifetime inside
their liver
and their liver gets stagnant and
sluggish and has this viral these viral
issues in there
and then when it gets stagnant and
sluggish and you can eat clean
you can eat whole foods your whole life
but it's not fixing the problem what i
would
what i would do is i would look in i
would go to the library get the book for
free if you want or
on sale at amazon right now and an
amazing sale actually
and what i would do is i would look at
the 369 cleanse
maybe the 369 advance cleanse maybe
the mono eating cleanse one of the mono
eating cleanses take your time to look
and what you're doing is first of all
you're getting rid of fats what i would
do if i was somebody that was battling
weight for many years
i would bring down those fats bring them
down in the diet you can learn about
that in here give your liver a chance to
recover
and clean things up and if you got the
autoimmune issue learn
what the causes of that issue learn what
viral issue with viruses responsible
for your autoimmune problem so then you
can take action
start getting the liver better start
lowering the viral uh
load start dropping the viral issue down
and boom all of a sudden the weight
starts coming off maybe did 369
periodically just give me any
suggestions
are you doing lemon water 32 ounces of
lemon water every morning
that's something to consider are you
doing 32 ounces of celery juice every
morning
are you keeping fats down throughout the
morning maybe do the morning cleanse
all these things matter you can get
weight off you can
and it's it's it's important so
dina says it's divinely guided
information thank you soc and anthony
bless your heart
deanna you're amazing um
and yep so true michelle
um so
manic mike uh monique my my daughter
is suffering from chronic headaches and
blurry eyes with burning
so chronic headaches and blurry eyes
with burning stabbing pain for
past few months which book is best for
healing um
so when it comes to chronic headaches
you can
you can look at the headache section
right here so if you look at cleanse the
heel
what i like about cleanse the heel it's
so comprehensive
there's so much information to customize
protocols take the book to the doctor
to your pediatrician or to to you know
whoever your caregiver is for your
daughter to and show the book
but headaches um and migraines that
little section it talks about
supplements and dosages that's one thing
you can do
the other thing is you got all the
different cleanses
what i would do okay if she was my
daughter i would
i would be focused on toxic heavy metals
maybe do the heavy metal detox smoothie
heavy metal detox cleanse in here i
would consider that as a possibility i
would look at the headache section in
the back
and you don't have to jump right in you
can just do
16 ounces of celery juice in the morning
on an empty stomach every morning that's
all you have to do just start with that
some lemon water
and you take it from there slow and and
you can just take one step at a time
how can i speed up the healing so i
don't get bloated
at all anymore so what happens with the
bloating
um jubilee is that um
there's a couple things you're doing
like what are you doing like what are
your foods
you're staying away from the dairy
products staying away from the eggs
right staying away from the gluten those
three are so important
because bloating for many people and i
talk about it in the books
is the streptococcus bacteria that sits
inside the intestinal tract
okay and that coupled with low hcl so
the gastric glands get burned out
another thing back to the caffeine thing
for one second
well that's another thing all the
caffeine beverages do when the chocolate
does the caffeine
it burns out the stomach glands so then
you get bloating later on in life that's
another thing too so not only do women
get their hair loose
lost later on they get their adrenals
get shot
so they have difficulty giving birth
they get bloating later on down the road
i mean the caffeine industry just does a
number on women
it's it's despicable really
but you want to get the hcl the stomach
glands build up you want to get your
liver bile function
better it sounds like it's hard but no i
mean you can literally just take cleanse
of heal look at the liver section there
work on getting that going on there
um and
so ann margaret um oh my i am a clinical
nutritionist
amazing and i cannot believe what i am
seeing
all these questions on things don't work
on all these questions on things don't
work so many of this not
evidence-based folks be careful oh
really really good question right there
um so you know
did you do you don't think any of the
folks here went to two three four five
doctors
um doctors not just clinical
nutritionists but actual
specialists and neurologists and medical
doctors
that's one thing ann i wanna i wanna ask
you so i wanna ask you a couple
questions because
a lot of people most people the medical
medium community they've actually been
through
20 doctors and three specialists
three neurologists psychiatrists because
they get told to go to there for for
things
because their neurological symptoms are
driving them crazy and
all of that and they've seen also
nutritionists and they tried different
things and
i think that insults people so it's not
going to insult me
i like you saying that because it gives
me a chance to just talk about the topic
in general
and but you're insulting people who
they're not stupid so and um people
go to doctors and they've been to a lot
of doctors
and they're still stuck with all their
different symptoms and conditions
so and they're suffering and they're
struggling so i would say ann
have some respect and they've seen their
nutritionists
and they've seen their health coaches so
i would just say
consider them and maybe not just think
about yourself
and think about me kind of what i do is
i'm thinking about them so i'm thinking
of the person who's suffering with the
worst trigeminal neuralgia where they
want to kill themselves
okay i'm thinking about the 20 year old
who can't go to college
and can't even look at the computer
screen because she can't
see properly because she has brain fog
and blurry eyes
i worry about and fatigue and she's and
her mom
has taken her already to 20 doctors
i'm worried about them and i'm worried
about the people who have
you know who can't get into a car
because their anxiety is so bad they
have a seizure before they get to their
car
and they can't even leave the house um i
worry about the people that are going
through all this
and the thousand and and here's in the
thousands and thousands of people that
are going through this
so and what i would do is instead of
being concerned about
your credentials and my no credentials
okay because i never said it was a
doctor be concerned about all the people
that can't find answers in their
suffering and then be open-minded to the
thousands of healing stories
that medical medium information is
brought and
and think about the street cred if you
look at the gold level label on this
book
okay you won't see that gold label on
um other books in health and and if you
look at the gold
label it says millions of copies sold in
the medical medium series
worldwide millions of copies and
millions of people with the street cred
and have reported that millions have
been healing and healed of medical
medium books so
i i'm just saying i hope you're doing
good with your doing and the work you're
doing in your practice
but just so you know i'm about to sick
and the suffering and people who
can't get answers
kelsey would like help understanding why
i get debilitating panic attacks
randomly triggered by fear or not
um being able to sleep once i start a
panic attack then it's nearly impossible
to stop
without taking conventional
pharmaceuticals i've been healing with
mm for two years and i got the panic
attack
and i got the panic attack shortly after
trying the advanced 369
for two days was off b12 for two months
recently
maybe that could be related so a couple
of things too
so um you get debilitating panic attacks
they're triggered and and been nearly
impossible to stop without taking
conventional pharmaceuticals so
the thing is with panic attacks is
that's with panic attacks and anxiety
you get all that is your trigeminal
nerve stuff so phrenic nerves trigeminal
nerve you got your you got your um
trigeminal nerve you got your phrenic
nerves you got your vagus nerve
so all those nerves work together so
they're all part of panic attacks vagus
nerve is the big one for panic attacks
right there
all on its own and so what happens is
that nerves get inflamed
and they get hypersensitive and when
they get hypersensitive
then you know you can be susceptible to
a panic attack at any point
any time and and fear can trigger one
at any moment i know when people have
severe anxiety and they got
they got um they're very sensitive they
can have a panic attack
really easily anything can trigger it it
could even be trying something new
i've seen people try something new for
the first time no matter what that is
i've seen people say well i'm going to
try coconut oil but i never tried it
before let me try it they have a panic
attack as they're trying it
or someone who's trying something new or
someone who's trying even a new
pharmaceutical they have a panic attack
while they're trying a new
pharmaceutical
and what happens is when the vagus nerve
gets so
hypersensitive and you end up getting
ptsd because of it
so you end up getting the whole ptsd
issue then we we run
into trouble so then it's like a vicious
cycle we got the hypersensitive nerves
the vagus nerve and phrenic nerves and
then
we have the ptsd associated with it
because then we get
we it just it turns into a vicious cycle
it's so hard for people and i'm so sorry
you're suffering with that and all that
so if you go into the book if you go
into medical medium you can take the
book to your doctor you'll see that
there's an anxiety section there
and that's a great place to start and
um and another thing too is
is that with anxiety you can also have a
low-grade viral infection with toxic
heavy metals
creating that inflammation with the
vagus turbine phrenic nerve so with the
vagus nerve and phrenic nerves you can
have
the toxic heavy metals mercury's the big
one so
mercury is definitely the big one with
anxiety that's a huge
huge piece of a lot of people's
anxieties
and then anxiety conditions and then the
other things low-grade virus is like the
epstein-barr
what happens is epstein-barr tends to
feed off of mercury
tends to release a neurotoxin the
neurotoxin floats around
it saturates itself on a nerve once it
saturates itself on a nerve like
like a vagus nerve or phrenic nerves
they get hypersensitive
and then we have a panic attack so if i
had anxiety i'd be in the anxiety
section i
there's so many ways to go about it what
i would do
is i would do the model eating cleanse
that's what i would do something really
simple because um when it's simple and
basic like that
and you keep your fats low and you're
doing the mono eating cleanse
like the potato monowing cleanse of the
celery juice and then you have
then you have the steamed potatoes and
then you have the smoothie and so forth
and the lemon water and
and when you do you know when you do
that kind of thing
when you're doing like the moderating
cleanse it's so easy and gentle on
sensitive nerves and that's what i would
recommend for myself if i had anxiety or
a friend or a loved one had that
go to your doctor ask them what they
think about the book
and and i don't know what you have been
doing for the last couple years or so
you know and what's happening so i don't
know like what what you've been up to in
the last two three years what you're
eating what you're not eating
all of these things play a role if you
do nutritional yeast that's it
that could really really build up in
your system with all that msg
create a lot of anxiety because the
nerves can't handle msg
um you could also you know there's also
different bugs we we
share and we pick up and and you know we
we just end up
in contact with that along the way but
what i but i what i would recommend with
anxiety you see the anxiety section
take a look at the supplements you can
customize it for yourself you can talk
to your
doctor about it too and a little bit at
a time
maybe do a mono eating cleanse 369
cleanse is still amazing for that of
course a lot of people heal
that from another thing too you know
when you're doing
something new did you know
it's coming out of it what are you going
back to
to eating something to where you used to
eat are you
what are you doing forging ahead and all
these things matter i talk about it in
detail here
but for anxiety though i talk about what
supplements
what is that are really critical you can
customize your protocol
for it i talk about the heavy metals um
another thing too you can just do the
heavy metal detox cleanse
so that's another thing i was talking to
a doctor a couple of weeks ago
this doctor's all about anxiety just
nothing about anxiety just nothing else
all about anxiety panic attacks and
different rides of anxiety and
they're really intrigued and invested in
the medical medium information and they
want to learn
and they were saying you know what
what's really helping with my patients
they were telling me is the heavy metal
detox cleanse because i told this doctor
toxic heavy metals like mercury
are responsible for so many anxiety
cases and
his doctor said it's doing wonders for
so many different cases of anxiety and
panic and everything else so maybe that
would be helpful too information
okay here's the question here please i
pray you could talk about numbness in
body from insect bites like spiders
absolutely terrified um if you
did you have it a spider bite did you
have one i mean i know the black widow
can cause
full body paralysis if it's not taken
care of if you don't get emergency
medical attention
or or medical attention you know black
widow spider can be really annoying
and and cause that you know when you do
get bit over time
the brown will wreck loose is really
annoying too these these fighters are
annoying i mean were you diagnosed with
a spider bite
was it an official spider bite or are
you just getting numbness in the body
and nobody knows but you thought you had
a bite like there's so many different
avenues and
i'm not trying to insult you at all or
throw you off that's not it you might
have got you might even seen this by
spider bite you
and then and then the doctor said yes
you had a
a brown recluse spider by yes you had a
black widow spider bite yes you had a
wolf spider bite
so that's one thing there but spider
bites yeah they can be really annoying
they haven't they have a neurotoxic
effect so you get numbness
that could last for years or just last
for the moment
you get numbness because of neurotoxins
because spider bite venom
is neurotoxic to some degree in a lot of
cases so
meaning like to some people they're not
that sensitive some people are more
sensitive i've seen people get spider
bites it's like it didn't even happen i
i got a friend who can have a black
widow bite their hand and
they're just aggravated for a week and
then it's gone but but no but it's
serious stuff
and but numbness you know it's
no matter what the trigger was say it
was a spider bite then i would go into
tingles and numbness neurological
symptoms and cleanse the heal
because you got sensitive nerves i would
go into neurological symptoms take a
look talk to your doctor
you can take a look at the different
supplements to help with it
maybe focus on the foods i would i would
focus on
um maybe the anti-bug cleanse and so
forth in the book
but yeah there's but i understand
danielle says i healed my severe anxiety
and panic attacks thanks to mm danielle
that's really inspiring for anybody with
panic attacks
anybody going through so much um
you know all that that's michelle just
said
that's a really that was a really good
one for michelle right there
we have soc no bogus studies here well
you know what michelle you know you're
not
you're you're not you're not green at
this
okay you know that you can have all the
studies
out there all the food studies all the
whatever studies and you can have all
that galore
but there are 250 million people in the
u.s alone that have symptoms that
doctors can't
figure out how to get rid of or they
can't get rid of
and and then you get you can there's the
not so sick with some symptoms and then
they're really sick
and they've been to 50 doctors and um
and with all the studies that you can
find and do
so you know this i don't michelle what's
weird is i don't know why
it's just some of the people don't know
this that are
professionals like how do they not know
that like is it because they've never
been sick yet and they just don't
understand what it's like to be sick so
they just believe
in this very land tale that the answers
are out there i don't know how they can
do that
you know you know the difference you
know what it's like to be sick
stay sick after 20 doctors and 20
nutritionists
and then not have answers until you find
answers
but you know what that's like it's the
bubble people are in
it's confusing me it still does um
actually what helps with acid reflux um
you know first of all i mean you can go
really simple
actually you can go so so gentle and
simple you can
you can go with eight ounces of celery
juice just eight ounces of celery juice
you can do aloe vera and i talk about
that in here you can do a little bit
maybe aloe
water you can just do the aloe water
where you blend a little bit of the
inside gel to a fresh aloe leaf
and i talk about that in here and you
could do just a little aloe water each
day and see what
moves it because what happens is we get
a little bacteria in our gut
we get a little bit of that the old
strep in our system everybody has it
nobody doesn't have strep we all have it
and a little bit of strep in my system
and then you know and then the liver
gets a little stagnant and sluggish even
in younger people
um stomach glands get get tired even in
younger people all these different
things
but it's really simple as like okay let
me just start out with maybe a little
bit of celery juice
eight ounces maybe start out with 16
ounces which would be ideal
every single morning 16 ounces of celery
juice on an empty stomach
and take it from there one day at a time
and talk to your practitioner tell them
what you're doing
but that's something just to start with
and do a little bit of aloe water and
you don't you know and and of course
stay away from processed foods of course
i mean
everybody's doing that right now but
um but yeah so
me tube 787 i have been to over 25
doctors and spent tens of thousands of
dollars over the past
17 years and i'm now and i'm now i'm
finally healing thanks to medical medium
information thank you
so me tube i'm a monitor here i'm
honored you found the medical medium
information
god bless you i'm so happy i'm proud of
you 17 years of going through hell and
back i call it
hell and back and i caught and now
you're rising out of the ashes
that's what that is exactly and what's
strange youtube is that
isn't that strange that but yet a couple
of nutritionists or some dietitian or
some other doc doesn't know
like that exists they don't know that
and that tells me they're just not
experienced or something and they live
in a bubble
but exactly you've been through hell and
back well that's the world i live in
i live in the world of 35 years and even
going back before that with my gift
of receiving information spirit of
compassion hearing his voice as of age
four
and knowing people suffer that when i
was age six seven
eight years old told people suffer every
day
from spirit of compassion told how many
people are suffering
and how they can't find answers and how
they're on mattress island
and some are losing their lives and
nobody cares and how science research
doesn't have answers
i've been taught that by spirit of
compassion since i was a child
okay and so it's amazing someone just of
course wants to discriminate against me
and step on right on my face and walk on
over all the people chronic and spit on
all the people with chronic illness
it's amazing how it works it's actually
really sad
um so
okay rowan france aloe water considered
a supplement during mono cleanse
i want to continue taking fresh aloe
during yeah you can't fresh aloe you
absolutely can there's no question
i would if it was me i would if i wanted
to absolutely
it's great i'm glad i'm answering
questions tonight you guys so good
spirit compassion talk
i want to say this okay people don't
realize how hard it is for me
i have to hear spirit of compassion as
i'm sitting here talking to you guys so
i'm hearing a voice here perfectly clear
like someone's yelling in my ear or
talking my ear loud i
you know it's like having an earpod in
of of of
of a podcast or an earpod of music or
something somebody talking and so i have
to do that and read comments
and deliver my information all combined
and so it's funny when someone says oh i
don't like it he's jittery today or
something on there he's not easy to
watch are you kidding if you only knew
what i had to juggle
um lisa pitman drinking my lemon water
at the end of the second day of the
original 369
and taking it easy wow that's fine
trying to be compassionate with myself
in the process in this process thank you
anthony and soc
lisa i'm proud of you i love the fact
that you're doing that incredible
incredible i'm proud of all you guys too
like all you guys are working hard
um so natasha
help me prevent migraine during my
period what can i do
natasha i'd love to talk about that for
a second because what happens is the
reason why the migraines come
during menstruation is because are
not our because i'm a man but women's
immune systems drop all women this isn't
you but all women's immune systems drop
eighty percent of their immune system
goes to the reproductive system so when
you have your period
eighty percent of your immune system
goes to your reproductive system
to protect it that's that's and that's
medical medium information it's it's not
out there you can't google it or
whatever nobody knows that
20 of your immune system is left
covering the rest of the body
taking care of everything else in the
body so that means if your
uh migraines okay or are because of a
little bit of strep that's in your
system all these years a little bit of
strep inside the sinuses
um a little bit of epstein bar inside
the liver or however or
nerves are sensitive or a little bit of
toxic heavy metals all of it that i talk
about through migraines and things like
that
and sensitive nerves like vagus nerve
frantic nerves
trigeminal nerves and you get the
headache you get them like the
neurological migraines
so when it happens that happens during
menstruation
and because and it could happen during
ovulation a little bit too so it can
happen there too because 40
of a woman's immune system goes directly
to the reproductive system during
ovulation leaving
only 60 percent everywhere else so it's
it's
because of that you're not when women go
into their cycles and ovulation they're
not running on 100 immune system
and then anything they have that's what
happens with women that's why acne
breaks out that's streptococcus during
cycles
or shortly after cycles or so that's why
when women have fatigue they get more
fatigue during their cycles because
they're dealing with something else
and their immune system is going all the
way to the reproductive system instead
of watching everything else it's it's
the difference between men and women
it's one of the
one of these differences between men and
women men's immune systems just
unless they burn themselves out their
immune system stays
just level it stays level it's it's so
unfair to women women
their immune system has to has to
actually juggle
and and take care of the reproductive
system which is how life is going to
move forward here in planet earth
um um yeah so and
um so what i would do is like when you
look at the book take the book to your
doctor
with the migraines too you can take the
book to your doctor you can look at the
protocol for supplements in the back of
the doctor for headaches and migraines
you can look in the back
of the book you can see all the
different supplements you can see the
protocols you can take that
i mean i would if i was getting the
migrants i would consider the
mono-eating cleanse for sure and look at
the supplements in the back
um shelly ann i've healed chronic acid
reflux with drinking celery juice every
morning
i had it really bad so that's incredible
so your chronic acid reflux already got
better you healed it you're drinking
every morning
and i've been drinking it for two and a
half years now oh my god shelly that's
incredible
that's incredible two and a half years
drinking celery juice
you healed your acid reflux i'm like so
proud of you
it's like you know what it is you like
you you and you probably went to a lot
of doctors for that acid reflux you
probably went
went through a lot and sometimes it
takes time to heal some people
shelly some people want to be healed in
one week you know they want to be healed
in one week
but then they don't do enough of the
protocols or customize it right like you
did and
it's amazing
so i'm looking through more questions
you guys
so staccata oh my goodness thank you for
the period answer
so for exa right suffered for
a very long time with different things
but that's what happens when you have
your periods and then all these
different problems happen and when your
periods are coming
everything feels worse because you have
these other conditions
and then the immune system can't be
taken care of all that so it
it goes to your cycle only and when it
goes to your cycle only oh my god
everything that you deal with
rises up that's what i you know and i
like trying to
get people and women to work on their
conditions get down to the bottom of
their conditions so when their periods
come they're not
they're not mortified or scared or ptsd
out that their period is going to come
and cause
more trouble
folklore family you and spirit helped me
recover from lung cancer
bless your heart i'm proud of you you
worked hard for it
nothing um hi anthony my mom's nails are
going brown and coming off do you know
what this could be
so um good question nothing
what happens with fingernails they're a
big indication of the liver
so big indication of the liver so what
would
you know what would mom like to do would
she do a little bit of celery juice
you know it's funny with her with her
mom's you know it's like
it's like you know it's some moms out
there they'll do everything and some
will just be like well i'll do a little
bit of celery juice now and i don't
really want to do this but i'll try that
i would consider a little bit of celery
juice because instantly that's going to
start going to the liver a little bit
and i would consider you know some b12
you know that's you know one thing i
would consider but when it comes down to
nails
um and and she can go to the doctor she
can take the information
too so nothing she can go to the doctor
she can take the information
and see what the doctor wants to do or
anything and you can look in the back of
the different stuff back there
but but foods are a great way to start
and you can talk to the doc
talk to your mom's doctor and find out
what
which you know find out what your doctor
feels like for different things
i know that's spinach and i talked to
another doctor recently about nails and
stuff
i recommended spinach and spinach soups
so you take raw spinach
you put in a blender you make a spinach
soup i talk about the recipes and all
the medical medium books
and the spinach soup really does help
with that with the liver and the nails
and
coupled with a little bit of celery
juice and you know
aloe water lemon water these are just
little basics and she can talk to her
doctor about what she
likes or not to do what the doctor likes
carolyn says i bought all the books yay
you're awesome thank you thank you you
know because i know that if you're
buying all the books then you're going
to tell somebody else
hey look you know then you can give
information and you can help somebody
you can help a family member you can
help a friend
and then it's all that matters it's like
the people that are in your life and
people that you love you want them to
have an answer
and um and healing so
so anna says i pray my daughter would
start listening to you now
her her periods are horrible and she has
brain fog i remember being like her in
my 30s if i only knew this stuff
and anna i know it's it's
that's what happens it's like years go
by and decades go by
no one everybody forgets what happens
you don't forget you know what you've
been through in your life but
i noticed that the younger people that
aren't so sick and they don't know what
everybody went through
and they're just kind of experimenting
for fun on all these fun things and
doing their health channels i get it and
but honestly i mean ever the history
gets forgotten
like history like just who cares if
millions of people suffered from lyme
disease many of them lost their lives
because of bad
treatments who cares if people suffered
the worst
endometriosis and and periods like all
of a sudden you know
and i care and i know you care and you
know you know that
you know what matters
yvonne can you please mention food to
focus
on for liking uh plano players so
um i'm not look the funny thing is
someone will say well he likes celery
juice for everything that's
it's one of the medical medium tools and
millions of people
hundreds of millions of people are
drinking celery juice now and there's a
reason because it really does
it is one of those incredible medical
medium tools
that spirit of compassion brought here
and it should never be underestimated so
anything with like in plano planaris
polaris it's great you could use a
little bit of celery juice that's one
aspect what i like to do with that
condition personally if i had that
condition
is i would be on low fats really low fat
so if you're an animal protein person
and you like animal protein
maybe once a day only do animal protein
once a day and i would
i would do it at the end of the day i
would never do eggs i would stay away
from eggs i would stay away from
dairy products completely butter milk
cheese
kefir yogurt i would get rid of if i had
that condition
and so and i would stay off of the
caffeine if i had the condition if you
possibly can so these are some of the
things i would do i would stay off of
fermented foods if i had that condition
so i'm just giving you
what to stay away from what to bring in
um
well leafy greens are important can you
do some
lettuces some mosh a little bit of kale
if you can some spinach
the spinach soups are great can you do
that can you do the lemon water in the
morning
do you like any fruit at all are you
afraid of fruit there's so many people
afraid of fruit it's so sad
do you like any fruit you can do the
smoothies so with lichen plantal
plenaries with
polaris what you want to do is is you
want to do like the heavy metal detox
cleanse it's something i would focus on
um that's a possibility there you can
you can take it one step at a time with
that condition you can really look at
the book
and you can say well what cleanse you
can start with the most basic gentlest
cleanse
take it from there take it all to your
doctor ask your doctor that question too
um
what does there was a question there
that went up there was pretty funny what
does medical media mean
uh by pauline you know what's the
funniest thing
i mean and my great-grandfather he
he named me that he called me that and
because at age four
and from there on out i heard a voice
perfectly clear
and from the outside though not from the
inside giving me advanced medical
information
that i put in all the books there's no
citations in these books it's all
original and unique information that's
healing millions worldwide
and that's the name i just you know
there's there's
you can call me anything call me
anything but the gift
is all the same of what the gift is
what's happened and like spirit of
capacity always tells me
you're not the gifted one anthony your
gift is for everyone else
it's so every you're the messenger to
deliver the information for everyone
else so that they can have an
opportunity to heal
and that's what the gift is it's for
people who are in need
okay uh michaela
derman i eat only raw fruits
vegetables and greens from over for
over a year now but i'm bloating every
time i eat
so you must been dealing with uploading
problem for years and years and years
and what i would do to begin with is i
would look and cleanse the heel
get the book free at the library just go
to library don't even buy the book get
it for free
um of course you can get it on sale at
amazon right now
an incredible sale for this book
personally for this book whatever
specifically i mean but bloating go in
the bloating section
and take a look and you can start there
but what i like to do for
it's not about fruits and vegetables
like raw fruits and vegetables
is not an answer and i think there's a
confusion out there
people will say like american means raw
fruits vegetables are fruits and
vegetables it's like
no medical medium is a thousand
different protocols and
customizing for the specific condition
of what's going wrong so you're bloating
what's going on with that bloating well
find out what
causes bloating so you read that in the
back here and you find out what causes
bloating to begin with okay
and then um you learn that it's low
hydrochloric acid
so low hydrochloric acid from years ago
from your whole life
so your stomach glands just have not
returned to the where they need to be
yet they haven't got to that place of
where they need to be the other can
the other thing that happens is low bile
reserves in your liver
so you can be on only raw fruits and
vegetables and leafy greens
but are you doing fats are you burdening
your liver how much avocado are you
doing so
really bad bloating cases and i teach
doctors this all the time
you want to get the liver back so you
want to get the bile reserves back and
one way of doing that is you drop the
fats
you drop the fats get those fats down
and when you do that you drop you get
rid of the nuts and seeds for a while
you get rid of the
avocado you get rid of the oils and if
you're doing animal proteins get rid of
the animal
proteins for a while get rid of all the
fats whether plant-based or animal-based
whether you're a plant-based or animal
baser and
and what happens is you have all these
old rotting proteins on lining the
intestinal tract all these old rancid
fats that have been there for years 10
20 30 years
they're on the inside you know the
intestinal tract lining they need to
finally get
cleaned out and they will over time so
it takes a little time
then you build up your hydrochloric acid
in your stomach land you build up your
liver
all these things matter you clean out
bacteria that's hiding in the gut
streptococcus hiding in all that and
then you do you look at the book and you
look hey
you know what's going on the cause of
bloating and then you look mono eating
cleanse
celery juice is something you bring in
32 ounces once a day
so fruits and vegetables is not enough
that's all great
and and raw fruits and vegetables is not
enough that's the difference between if
you find somebody on youtube and they're
just a raw
raw foodie or something and they're
doing raw fruits vegetables and that's
their thing
that don't mean anything when you're
sick what means when you're sick
is what's wrong what's the answer to
whatever you're doing
and then how to use your fruits and
vegetables
how to use them as tools you know is the
is the bloating severe bloating and and
mono eating is something i look at when
it's severe bloating so like
gastroparesis severe bloating all these
different
conditions mono eating is really
important so
i hope that that helps in celery juice
like 32 ounces
every single morning you can do fruits
and vegetables but if you're not doing
32 ounces every single morning and
you're aloe water
and and doing and knowing what's wrong
so you can do that say the monolithing
cleanse
see how all these things matter all the
different ways you can heal and the
different
tools you can use and somebody could be
like raw fruits and vegetables it
doesn't mean anything
but but i'm proud of you though that
you're eating that clean
it's just what i mean but it doesn't
mean anything it means you have to know
what's wrong
then be able to customize it using
healing tools the only place i've seen
that
still to this day whether anybody likes
it or not is the medical medium books
and information
but that's from spirit of compassion not
because i'm smart i tell you guys all
the time i'm not a smart guy
you know yeah i talk to doctors every
single day and i teach doctors every day
for years and years but i'm not a smart
guy it comes from up here
um so it's all about knowing the cost so
it's like well
what's the cause you can be a fruit and
vegetable expert out there on youtube
you can be this person on youtube that
person on youtube but do you know the
cause of your condition that's another
thing too on all its own but i'm proud
of you
proud of you
check out this book cleanse the heel you
get it from the library yay
totally can get it from the library
that's so cool i love that i want people
to get it for free if they can with the
library
um stacy can you talk about detox
reactions
whoa it's a question right there detox
reactions i've been drinking celery
juice
for four weeks and it just had a nasty
bat of shingles pop up
can this happen not from celery juice um
like there's people with shingles and
they use celery just to get rid of
shingles that's there's people
out there that they they have conditions
caused by the shingles
so um if you weren't doing your celery
juice the shingles were still coming
um that's this is how it works it's just
if you were doing
if you were doing oil pulling for a
month
and you had your shingles it would be
the oil pulling that caused it it's just
a normal
assist life it's like it's like that's
how we think when we're trying something
new or anything and it happens to be
around a time when something's already
out in order for shingles to come out
it had been in the works for the last
six months to a year so shingles doesn't
just
come out it's in the process of coming
out so
it's in the process it's usually you get
it a year before
you get it six months before and then
it's in you
and it stays in you until it
proliferates and proliferates and then
you have the rash
so so um four weeks
and the shingles coming out well it's
more like four months and the shingles
comes out
so stacey what i would do is look into
the shingle section here and jump on
this
because get the book out for free at the
library
jump on it in a sense where you want to
take the protocols to your doctor
that's in the shingles protocol so you
can protect yourself from
post shingles post shingles is the
problem celery juice is helpful
uh i i just i wouldn't i mean i wouldn't
stop the seller issues
but there's so many things you can do
for your immune system and what else are
you eating
were you eating something else you're
drinking celery just but were you eating
something else that feeds shingles
because aids
because eggs feed shingles so it you
know that's what happens with eggs
they feed shingles and what they also do
they feed all the different bugs
so that's what they do so when it comes
down dairy products
feeds shingles you know eggs feed
shingles
so breezy hi i am wondering what to do
for whole body twitching
most in the chest thighs and head any
suggestions would be great
so all the years i mean 35 years of
helping so many people
and helping so many people to doctors
doctors patients and so forth because i
was always the guy was the bizarre
symptoms guy
that's what it was so um back going back
35 years
he's the bizarre symptom guys if you
have a guy and what happens is doctors
would be like
okay i know this guy um
talk to him let's get him on the phone
so doctor would contact me have a
patient on the phone
we'd all be on the phone together and go
ahead tell anthony your bizarre symptoms
and let's see what spirit of compassion
has to say and so spirit of compassion
would give information to the doctor and
what happens is with twitches and spasms
and all that
would always would come through for the
most part outside of some different
viral issues and other things
would be the toxic heavy metals so
mercury
that's a big one for twitches and spasms
and
all that stuff so you know what take
take the book to your doctor look at the
heavy metal detox cleanse
and take a look and you can go to the
neural neurological section and you can
see twitches spasms
all that jerking all that so yeah
um
so so many great questions just reading
questions along the way
such a great night to have you guys on
here tonight a cup
janet's got an interesting question
right here if i don't if i don't plant
based fat
so that means i think you're saying if i
don't eat plant-based fats
my blood sugar is not balanced what do
you suggest
well it's it's like this it's if that
means
here's how it works if you it
okay if you stop your plant-based fats
that'd be nuts seeds avocado and all
that your most
those are high-calorie foods you're most
likely stopping those and not getting
enough calories on the opposite end
so here's how it goes so you're eating
your plant-based diet
you stop the highest calorie part of
your diet which is the fats
so you stop eating two avocados a day
you stop eating uh
you know handfuls of cashews you stop
eating oils
you stop those high calories okay once
those are gone
you're under calorie now without
realizing so you don't know how to like
all of a sudden bring in enough potatoes
enough sweet potatoes winter squash
enough bananas enough you know a few
dates or
you know and you have to also get in the
mineral salts
critical so you can't just go off
of all these fats and then not get some
mineral salts in
you'll go under calories you won't get
enough mineral salts plus you'll have
fats in your system so here's how it
works
you've been eating your fats all your
life the minute you stop your fats
you know the fats don't go away they're
in the liver
they're in they're in the bloodstream
for three straight days after that
then they're in the bloodstream for
quite a while because you start
you start getting rid of toxic fat
storages
so then you get all of sudden you got
still more fat going into the
bloodstream
so what it is is what i'm suggesting
which is probably what's happening is
you're going off your high calorie fats
and
you're under calorie for the moment and
you're getting a swing because you're
under calories so then you're getting a
little bit of a blood sugar drop
so you want to consider you want to make
sure you're doing enough of the
you know enough things like you're doing
the celery juice for the mineral salts
you're getting enough in your smoothie
you're getting the wild blueberries
you're getting the bananas in your
smoothie
you're doing the steamed potatoes and
leafy greens and you're not
like giving up calories
and that's what happens to try that
that's one angle right there it could be
really helpful i love that food question
um you know papaya banana more of that
in there
more the celery juice more of the
lettuce is and you
keep that balance while you're getting
rid of that old fat storage and the fat
that's been in your bloodstream
for three days because it's still going
to be in your bloodstream for days after
you go off the fats so you're going to
be swinging you're going to be like what
is this
so you guys thanks for being here um you
know if you found this helpful
uh thumbs up if you can like if you can
subscribe follow whatever just you know
share if you can please share help
others it would be amazing if you do
that i would love you guys for that
um and anyway i stand with you totally
i believe in you i believe in your your
ability to heal
um i got your back you i know so many of
you have been
through so much struggling as many of
you been through hell and back with your
symptoms and conditions and seeing a lot
of doctors and
gone through a lot just that my heart
pours out to you and
i believe in you and and tonight when
you're sleeping
you let your body heal okay tonight when
you know right before you go to sleep
you ask the angels to come
and have them by your bedside okay and
they'll be sitting there with you they
love you they'll stay there
and they'll help you just you'll keep
some peace around you you do some
healing
you sleep okay and just know that you
know that healing is a process
but you have everything in your body
everything in your
soul it's all there we just need to do
the right things take one step at a time
do some tools go three steps up two
steps back keep on climbing up keep on
healing
and know that uh that i care greatly
i care greatly and uh love you guys and
okay um and uh
yeah so i will see you guys the next q a
bless your heart