why in our everyday lives do we
experience so many
heartaches a lot of people are suffering
they don't understand why horrible
things are occurring in their lives they
feel something must be behind this it's
important to understand the realm that's
very rarely seen by the
eyes in all these decades I've been
asked about angels asked about the
afterlife I've asked about
demons to understand demonic forces is
to understand Injustice and deception
and
trickery by the end of this original
audio you're going to understand the
forces at work in our lives you are
going to be awakened and you're going to
understand how to regain your power to
help protect yourself and your loved
ones so we can play our part heart in
stopping demonic forces in their tracks
like never before