Anthony William Anthony William the
medical medium an incredible day right
here have two really special people here
we're going to be talking about the
healing stories Aaron Hudson Elizabeth
Stassen this is a special day I'm so
excited to be here so I have you guys
here we're gonna be talking about all
kinds of stuff I can't believe I'm here
you know I mean Elizabeth has a powerful
healing story erin has a powerful
healing story medical medium healing
story and it's it's it's one that hits
down to the core I mean really does
because there's so many people like that
I talked about that are on mattress
island where they're sick and then they
got lime and they got different problems
and they're seeing doctor and doctor and
doctor so you got a hang on because you
got it you got to hear everything we're
talking about I'm already getting a
little a little emotional about it
um but Erin Lee Catholic you know I want
it I want you to tell a story how anyway
how it all happened right here it came
about where but so my husband and his
sister are doing a podcast and they were
talking about the people they want to
get on the show and one of them was
going to be Anthony Williams and of
course you know my fingers were crossed
himself I saw this happened this would
be incredible Kate was really curious um
and we were so fortunate for him to come
on the show and do the podcast and kind
of get a little insight on who you are
as a person and just your whole story
and everything and it was amazing and
incredible and of course I wanted to be
there and I got the chance to meet him
and truly it was because of Elizabeth
and I couldn't believe it was really
happening but I did get to meet him and
see how and you know just genuine and
kinda incredible he was and immediately
the first person that I called was
Elizabeth because you can call me 30
years
oh my gosh you know I got to meet
Anthony Williams and the reason I was so
excited it was because she had
introduced me to him years ago when she
was going through an extremely dark and
scary time and as a very close friend of
hers it was hard it was hard as a friend
feeling so helpless seeing your friend
in so much pain and discomfort and the
unknown and the fear of what was
happening to her and her diagnosis of
Lyme and how it was affecting her and
seeing her you know go through all these
different phases and and things that she
was trying out anyways eventually a
little tiny shift happened and there was
a little hope in her voice and I was so
relieved and so I remember her saying
it's this book and it's the medical
medium and and this was years ago this
was 2015 no one early two-thousands was
talking about it and it wasn't getting
in the fight for truth I always say the
trends don't they don't save lives it's
it's it's one of you know my smartest
most passionate you know friends that I
know and extremely smart when it comes
to nutrition and healing and that's her
background for her to find something
that really resonated with her and gave
her a glimpse of hope I was like what is
this and send it to me and I want to
hear about it so I was lucky enough or
not lucky enough but I wasn't dealing
with anything as severe but I was having
pretty significant GI issues which is
the loveliest thing to talk about but
like I don't have it
fine and it takes over everything
because anything that you're eating and
anywhere you go you're constantly like
oh no how's this gonna affect me and oh
I can't go to this and you know you're
just I was you know I naturally fin
anybody that knows me from growing up I
like crap I've wonderful genetics I'm
thank God but I have this distended
crazy stomach that no matter what I ate
I thought oh I'm gonna shift and start
to eat healthy but I was eating this you
know kale salads and you know trying to
not eat the junk food and it was
actually making my stomach worse I was
finally diagnosed with SIBO which is
small intestinal bacterial overgrowth
and this was about eight years ago and
there wasn't a ton of information out
there I kind of just grasp onto it
because of a few of the symptoms that I
had and anyways she I eat have started
reading his book after she had told me
and it was this page turning I couldn't
put it down
highlighting stuff I'm waking up Oliver
my one small area that I was dealing
with and it really it shifted the game
for me when I saw her starting to heal
and the things that she would tell me
and the belief that I had because I was
witnessing it firsthand and so of course
for me I said well my gosh I'm going to
try this this is and after years of
struggling and nothing sticking and kind
of just settling into the idea that okay
this is going to be this is it this is
my my battle and of course it's not the
end of the world but I'm gonna have to
deal with it and then I tried celery
juice in my blender with a nut milk in
the earlier crazy yes sir
and it was a big you know juicer was
expensive I was like I'm gonna try this
out anyways it was such a game changer
for me it and it was instant and so I
like it's one of those things where you
know people say oh that's hilarious and
I want to try it and I'm gonna you know
do this and that when you really have
something that is an ailment that
nothing else is working for and it seems
so simple yeah yeah it's not simplistic
because the book breaks it down and what
it's doing and what it's replacing and
replenishing and if that really made
sense to me for SIBO but it was instant
and it was amazing and I committed I was
pretty good more people that just it was
it was so simple meaning I didn't have
to do some crazy you know take all this
out and only do this and do that it it
was tangible does that makes sense
and of course yeah coming up in February
will be a year he was announcing his new
book which was coming out and so in the
title if you can see it does some Siebel
on it it was the first thing that came
in my direction yeah you know we'll see
what information on it and that got in
healing and deliver and so when I got
went on to order my book of course it
said oh it's not coming out until
October and I was you know pre-ordered
it and it came and into Christmas
literally yeah I know every book on here
I've read them all they're all
incredible this one really resonated
with me and I know there's the new one
coming on I can't wait for that I feel
like there's just more information and
more knowledge and people want it that's
a little bit of my story which obviously
led me to to your story which
you know with the in the digestive
problems and it it can take over your
life like really people don't realize it
dress and you know lack of sleep and
you're worried about it and what am i
eating and what am i not even and I also
ended up doing the detox movie as well I
always have to have one cuz I always
have one every day again super easy to
make super tangible and really good and
that for me and like those two I would
say together was a game changer and a
lot of the stuff that happened along the
way I can talk with Beth too but it just
made sense and so for me it was let me
read this book does it resonate with you
are you you know where are you in your
journey I wasn't in the depths of where
but I was struggling and it was hard and
there weren't a lot of answers and but
we don't want a person to go into the
depths of work Elizabeth you know where
Beth was we don't want anything that's a
thing you're struggling as it was that's
a thing if we don't get the answers we
need we can go backwards more and then
something else happens and some you know
and it all kind of falls apart one thing
when you're doing one thing you know you
you want people to pay attention to
their bodies what when symptoms start to
come up and not sort of you know ignore
them and just you know stay on the
standard American diet and not do
anything these are warning signs that
your body is giving you that it's
unhappy with the status quo or you know
your current diet and so for me mine you
know if I really look at it I was sort
of set up for being taken out by disease
I was sort of emotionally spiritually
mentally and physically broken down and
and then it just kind of woke up
something in me and overnight I was in a
completely different body but I look at
people that are dealing with you know
things that were you know painful and
uncomfortable and you know
Sol and I really want to implore people
to pay attention pay attention to your
body now before you end up in bed like I
was oh yeah that's no way to live yeah I
mean that's like real like yeah here's
what you went through it's unbelievable
and if you want to share with everybody
and I think I think it's it's the Lyme
disease world yes would always when when
you're talking to me about it it just
brought me back to Lyme disease being
still nothing but a confusion out there
a wake of 40 years almost of people
suffering yeah and not getting answers
and getting bombarded with antibiotics
and so I had to get the truth out I
risked my life doing it but then people
don't realize that but you know you know
and now it's actually changed the
movement so ingre in a great way the
people human but I'd love for you to
tell a story because I think people can
learn from your healing experience and
your story how it started when you just
got hit with it yeah it's so
overwhelming and I don't I'm aware of
how much time it would take to tell the
whole story but I'm going to try to try
to focus well I think it really started
when I was an exhausted mom with a baby
who was one and a half at home and I
found myself pregnant again and I went
through a miscarriage and I had to have
a surgery following it and I was really
down at that point I was really I was
exhausted I was still you know nursing
my baby I found myself like pregnant was
you know another pregnancy and then I
lost it and I you know I'm I was a whole
I was already a holistic health coach
and a nutritionist I barely ever took it
I'd film before and all of a sudden I'm
getting this surgery you know I'm you
know having all these drugs pumped into
me and stuff in
and I'm really sad and grieving and just
kind of upset you know mad at the world
that this happened and it that parts a
little hard to talk about but I know
that when I woke up the next day I was
in a different body
I had pins and needles and I had heart
palpitations and I had massive anxiety
and you know insomnia and burning skin
just a different a completely different
body and I thought oh this is just like
you know I'm everyone says like oh
you're grieving you know you're you're
anxious you know it's hormones your
hormones you know I had had hot flashes
I had night sweats it's just it's gonna
go away it's gonna go away when you know
the drugs wear off it's gonna go away
when you you know you just need to cry
about this loss that you went through
and you know just get back to your life
and it didn't happen I spent about a
year running around to different doctors
I went to you know all sorts of doctors
and then about at the end of the year I
got a Lyme diagnosis and I had had Lyme
disease when I was a college student at
21 and I had had a diagnosis then and
but I've been it been dormant for you
know 18 years and I'd lived a really
normal life so it was really kind of
surprising to me I was like well there's
no tick I didn't get bit again is it a
reinfection was it there the whole time
you know I didn't really have the
answers but I know that for the next
really you know several months I was
running around everywhere searching
going to different doctors going to
different Lyme doctors going to
different healers you know New York LA
like different parts of California just
the way that I can describe it is just
panic just you know can you help me can
you help me can you help me can you help
me and I would get these large protocols
back of things that I was supposed to
take and I I couldn't put it together I
didn't have the mental capacity to
follow it and I know that sounds crazy
but I I couldn't like follow the
doctor's orders because
I needed something very simple and I did
eventually go on one protocol that
really really made me go downhill very
very quickly and I wasn't really able to
use my legs in the way that I always had
I couldn't get out of bed and I would
just sit there I had to have someone
come take care of my daughter
I had a cane at one point briefly but
you know there was to help just to help
walk but I I it was really getting that
getting the cane and look seeing at my
house that I was like instinctively
thinking you know I'm a young woman and
I would see people in the doctor's
office like that were you know stage for
a neurological line which was what I had
and I remember my doctor saying like oh
you're not in a wheelchair yet you're
fine
and I remember thinking oh there's so
many things but I remember saying like
okay you know there's there's got to be
another way there's got to be something
I can do and I think because it was I
had already gone to nutrition school and
I already like you know already love to
cook and stuff I I was just sort of
praying I guess for something else and
then they never dry joining this um
Ellie Lyme support group and there was
this guy on line and in the support
group that was very controversial and
people were fighting about it and
they're probably still fighting about it
but I just remember you know I kind of
had that personality of like when
something is frisky I want to know about
it
you know what is it I just want to
decide for myself and sort of bring in
the information and go how do I feel
about this does this make sense or can I
read between the lines or you know so I
that's how I you know started searching
a little bit and so I just I bought this
book this was the first book but if I
say the guy online controversial I'm
sorry but so so I just I Amazon this
book and I remember reading it and
literally crying and telling my husband
same thing like
No oh my god no yes yes this sort of
intuitive knowing of like this is
explaining what I am feeling inside and
I don't care what anybody thinks I don't
care what's normal I don't care what's
being taught or told I know that what
I'm doing right now is making me go down
down down and I would call my Lyme
doctor and say I really don't think this
is right and he would say you get you
get much worse before you get better
you're gonna get worse before you get
better and maybe there there is you know
detoxing and stuff on any protocol but
you're not you're not supposed to get
much worse
we have to get better that's only
because they don't know anything you
know I had to basically shut out all of
that and just go I know my body I've
been in this body for you know a long
time and I know this is not right
and maybe that work for someone and
that's their story but this is not
working for me and I remember literally
like walking and going like God give me
a sign if I'm supposed to get off the
you know standard protocol and get on
this give me a sign and I had I was
taking a walk and I went back to my car
where I was walking and one of my best
friends Chris had texted me a picture of
this book and was like I was just
thinking about you have you checked out
this guy I think you should check it out
and they just asked for a sign so it's
like okay I am getting it on getting off
of that today and I'm switching to this
and within about four weeks I was out of
bed I I was making I started slow it was
like you know okay I can start my
kitchen I'm just going to do the celery
juice I'm just gonna do this purple
murky looking it's actually quite
delicious oh yeah um I made it
religiously for two years actually and I
just like I was like autopilot I just
got up and I did
because you knew you knew you knew the
truth was there
you knew somewhere in your heart that
this is yes this is the right track but
I had to stay with the face of it like I
had to faithfully kind of make it even
when I wasn't feeling like it I had to
just faithfully make it and my healing
really came in shifts you know there was
an immediate like oh my gosh I have more
energy oh my gosh I can get out of bed
oh my gosh I can make stuff in my
kitchen but you know when you lay in bed
for a long time and he tells so many
people this that yeah once you start
getting better though you're gonna get
tired again because you're using all
these muscles you didn't use yeah now
you're in the kitchen and you're being
able to function but then BOOM
whoa now I'm doing so much more than a
happen I'm not yet ridden but you know
yeah then you get kind of kicked back
and it gets scary but then you're moving
forward even more did that happen oh
yeah there was at least a year
if I'm honest there was Italy because my
healing was like two and a half three
years there there was at least a year
where I my my mind it was like I woke up
from a 20-year nap my mind was sharp and
clear my spirit was so excited to get
out there and do the things that I
wasn't able to do even before I got sick
and you know I think I was like you know
just didn't know you know and and my
body was just like nope you're not doing
it today like you so I was sort of and I
think that kind of helped me because
mentally and spiritually once I had that
hope for healing I could kind of like
vision myself in the future like just
one in college stuff I'm gonna travel
I'm gonna you know when you're in bed or
even just not feeling well for so long
it's like you're in your own prison if
you have amazing which I did but you
still it was this feeling of like I'm so
lonely because no one else knows like
what my body's feeling you have the
elements that we're going on and you
don't you let your soup or something
that people would be like we look good
yeah you're standing up yeah you look
good in a photograph
actually just took me six hours to get
up and out of bed and function to get
myself showered and dressed and I have
like a good like three hours a day
before have to go take a nap and come
back do you know any like it wears when
you were you were on a clock and that
clock was wait a minute what can I do in
this 45 minutes in this one hour before
I'm flatlined in the bed for a while
yeah and the nervous system is shutting
down and you're just you just know
you're not you know you know you can't
push yourself cuz you you've probably
learned that if you did you just really
flat low it my nervous game is collapsed
yeah in my dream everything you know if
I did too much and the adrenals start
kicking in everything I would literally
not sleep for three days and you know my
husband would be like did you know maybe
two or three days just because when I
was stuck the nervous system gets that
weak and when you're dealing with this
and what happens is it gets that weak to
the point where you can't sleep
regardless of how tired you are it's
hell and doctors don't understand how
this works they don't know why the
patient isn't sleeping or not don't say
oh maybe it's a Hertz heimer
or maybe it's this or they have no idea
it's not the doctors fault but it's it's
the industry science the research has no
idea about anything this is just in with
this and so when you push yourself too
hard too it could even get worse where
you don't sleep even more even though
you're exhausted because every nerve in
the body hurts too for example or buzzes
[Music]
it was it was it forces you and I told
people to in the past or it forces you
have told a lot of professionals this
because they just don't understand how
you're feeling I said it's a prison when
you're laying in bed if you don't relax
the nerves and let them calm down yeah
for all the buzzing and the humming just
if you don't do that you will you will
be in real trouble yeah you you won't be
able to just get into the bathroom I
remember I went to someone's wedding in
New York and just getting on the plane
and land
I was like I looked at my husband and
every part of my body was like vibrating
and I was like I'm like the lights were
shutting out yeah
it was really really scary and I spent
the entire trip and went to the wedding
and they spent the entire trip in New
York in bed while my husband went and
did all this fun New York stuff that I
planned this with my daughter I mean
when you're young like this you're
dealing what does he must have thought
you were dying I for sure thought I was
dying I mean I yeah I told my husband
there were many nights that I said I
don't know if I'm gonna make it through
the night I think I'm gonna die tonight
that my symptoms were so bad and I would
just look at my daughter sleeping and
just say like I don't know how much time
I have with you but I love you and so
glad I got to be here with you and when
I was lying in bed listening to someone
else laugh and take care of her whether
it was my mother-in-law who was a saint
to come all the time or we hired someone
at one point to help us and or my
husband like they would take her to the
park all I wanted was to be the one to
be the one to take her to the park to be
the one to push the stroller to be the
one to make her dinner and and I I at
one point really said to my husband like
I don't I think this is it and I just I
don't know what to do I want to be here
for that and so my being a mommy was my
motivator and it's still my motivator I
mean I am now at the point where I can
eat almost anything so I just want if
anyone can't eat anything I want you to
know that three years ago I couldn't eat
anything no gluten no dairy no sugar no
alcohol no processed food no nothing I
know you're not supposed eat eggs I'm
not good thing but I do eat and enjoy
everything but I know that I'm gonna end
right back up where I started if I'm not
careful so now this died all these books
I have all of these books and you know
sometimes it's 20% of my diet sometimes
it's a hundred percent of my diet
sometimes it's 80% it's always there I'm
always working in the stuff but you
worked hard at the beginning no you
wouldn't
you knew it was right at the beginning
when you were getting those results you
just had to stay with it and yeah and
the thing is is to do that while
emotionally I mean you already went
through emotional I mean hell and back
yeah or them
I mean you already went through so much
and then to have a sickness come at the
same time yeah you know and you probably
I think my my defences were sort of
immune system came down absolutely yeah
we the goal is to know what to do so we
have the right to be emotional and we
have the right to experience a tragedy
or a loss or a hardship that we have the
right for that because it's it's it's
worse than salt in the wound if you if
you if you have to experience something
that's happening in our lives and then
we get kicked down with sickness on top
of it and then that's one salt round of
salt in the wound and then the doctors
don't know what's going on in going on
in your body the professionals
that's another round of salt and as
fears people around us don't know what's
going on so thank God you have a friend
like there and because that's when you
find out who your friends are - oh yeah
true oh yeah I I have to thank my
girlfriends and my family were amazing
they you know Aaron's been my like you
know sister and earthly guardian angel
for thirty years and you know just she
all of my friends all my girlfriends
really walked through it with me and my
mother and my mother-in-law my sisters
my husband went through so much and you
know you do realize who your who your
people are and who gets it and who
doesn't get it at the same time it's a
really personal journey and the only way
that I got well was to really block
everyone out and and it taught me
boundaries of deciding what was going
going in instead of looking outside for
answers like just being here with my
book and being with my like I have a
little like supplement apothecary now
and my my frigerator and you know just
if I could do nothing else I could eat
it
and that would be like a healing healing
thing for me I know once when spirit of
compassion when I was younger said you
know in these books when when we're able
to do these books cuz it I had to help
so many people for so many decades
before I could even do the books to get
this to you and Spirit said to me this
is medical Scripture and I was like well
what do you mean as I was writing this
down and spirit said people are going to
they're going to hold on to this and
read these words and it's going to get
them through a hard time and so I
realized even then right there that okay
this you know this is what it's about
it's about making sure that when you
were your alone in the world of sickness
because even if we have family around us
and we have friends around us and we
have good physicians around us yeah it
doesn't mean we can be saved when you're
that sick because you just where do you
go what do you do
even yeah and that's and and I said I
remember I said I my Lyme doctor one of
three that I went to I went in and I
started I must have been healing because
I was trying to get pissed off and when
you are you know suffering and you're
down and then you start to get a little
like fight and you a little like anger a
little you know that's actually you're
moving up the emotional guidance scale
and you're getting towards like you're
fighting for yourself and I remember
going in and going you know what you
need you need to treat forget about Lyme
you need to treat my fear disease
because now I'm in fear I'm in this
scary Lyme world and there's just so
much noise and they know how to block it
all out and I don't know what I'm
supposed to be doing and you're not
telling me what I'm doing and I'm not
feeling better and it was just like
fighting for myself and being excited
myself in my life and you know you don't
have all the answers and I was off about
it and I think that helped does your
same fighting for yourself because the
truth is you were really lucky to have
people around you they were supportive
and I think a lot of people don't
yeah because or whatever it is we're
grow up or who's around that people
believe they don't believe people don't
believe they think it's in their head
Oh case they don't get what's going on
they just don't understand as you say
you know medical medium a lot of people
want to be skeptical skeptical but for
me I was like this is you know you
you've learned yourself and you know
your body and if it's working I started
working for you of course and that I was
like and whatever is working for you
couldn't work for anybody that's how I
saw and literally it was like wait a
minute but that's the other thing some
people you don't have the support system
you don't have someone fighting for you
or believing your symptoms or you know
it's like just listen to your doctor you
know and of course doctors are there for
a course they're amazing and they're
always you know important I don't want
to say it's not going against but
sometimes thinking outside of the box or
trusting your body yeah
Kent helps you can help because you can
get bombarded with oh but this works for
that person and this you know this is
what my doctor says and this with the
other doctor says and there's so much
information but at the end of the day
like kind of trusting yourself I think
there are plenty of people that have
gotten well with the help of a doctor
and for me I I couldn't get organized
around what they were telling me to do
I really couldn't it was this was much
more simple for me and it was manageable
and it was it was like I always say to
like it's medicine being in food being
your medicine I remember in the very
beginning you telling me I had struggled
with Candida as well for a long time and
my kind of healing journey and I was so
scared of sugar and yeah you know fruits
and you know I was like she was talking
about the smoothing I was like I can't
really do you know the blueberries and
the thing that she was like no you need
to read this book and like understand
and it really made sense to me you know
fruit is one nature and you almost have
to you know go against maybe what what's
trendy yes it's trendy to have less
friendly blue berries people are so
scared of you know bananas and this
thing has like what two or three bananas
in it I mean I had just yet three
bananas a day every day for two years
the reason my sugar was okay the reason
why trends don't save anybody from real
sickness is because they were originally
propelled by financial gain their back
their back my money and backed by even
studies for a reason they're backed by
things purposely and then put out to
Bank and bankroll and make money okay
fine but when you're sick and you're
struggling and you're in your bed and
you're you go to three line doctors you
think you're gonna die and then the line
groups aren't a lot of help sometimes in
the old days to a story everybody's
their own story but when you try to go
against the trend in a line group what
happens you know what happens there
because you know I noticed that people
what I mean I think I don't like I
couldn't really share it I think I'd
there were a couple people I did share
it with in there yeah I mean there's
people that don't get it and there's I
mean it's so simple so how could this if
you're really suffering how could celery
juice help you how could you know we
just we love to look outside for healing
we like to go to experts and we like to
you know oh this is the top top doctor
and I'm I think that works for some
people it just didn't work for me
because it was it was too complicated
and my body's really sensitive and you
get since I got reactions from every
system and you get when you get lime
yeah thanks ultra sensitive and I would
call me though nobody has ever had that
reaction I've heard that so many times
no one's ever had that reaction I mean I
couldn't handle you know even food
nevermind like you know a drug or
something that was new that I was
introducing so you have to know and what
I liked about this was I could control
it I could kick it up if I wanted a
little more cleansing and detoxifying or
I could pull it back and like the you
know the killer stuff the stuff that
kills like the you know cats call and
the licorice root and lemon balm stuff
like that I could kind of ease off that
for a while and I would just you know do
the supportive things like if I did
nothing else I just took the support of
supplements and food it's like how could
but when it's the right things when it's
the right things it all counts that
when it really counts yeah when it's the
right things that's what you were doing
you were doing the licorice root and the
cat's claw yeah because yeah because
Lyme disease isn't isn't bacterial it's
not bacterial that's the big mistake
and that's what happens that's why the
licorice and the cat's claw and all
these work because those are antivirals
and I really felt like I was viral like
the night sweats you know and I think
that everyone has their own brand of
toxic soup and you know some people have
more viral most people probably have
more viral and some people have
absolutely have bacteria bacteria
doesn't cause neurological problems and
that's yeah that's where science and
research is either completely in the
dark or can't help anybody out or they
haven't done any of the work yet but
that's that's a thing it's the viruses
that create neurological Lyme so when
you're diagnosed with stage-four
neurological Lyme that's a really high
viral load yeah that's if it is and
that's the controversial point too that
when I finally cracked the Lyme disease
world and kind of broke it apart because
it's shifting now thank God because
because there doctors know now they're
learning that it's viral because of this
information so there they're back and
down on antibiotics and they're trying
to bring in cat's claw yeah but when my
doctor said that actually one of my
doctors said you know people have got I
will say I don't know what's his name
but one of my doctors in California had
the book on his desk and I said we'll
have you read it I would challenge him
he's like no no how do you know what
you're talking about you haven't read it
and he said you know I saw him about six
months after and he says because I would
check in I had to check in and just make
sure he talked but usually I felt like
it was just sort of like a check-in like
what are you are you seeing this and I
would ask like I would ask simple
questions like hey you're lying patients
did they all have epstein-barr - or a
past infection for epstein-barr and that
he would say yes and I would say oh hey
um you know have people taking cat's
claw and gotten better and not taking
care but you know I would like ask him
he's like he told me at one point you
can
get better with just cats cloth and I
was like why did you tell me that a year
ago I was like you know are you reading
the book or you just you don't and I
thought that that was progress and
pretty well a lot of doctors were
reading the books but but not letting
people know too because in the early
days now there's lots of doctors that
say yeah I have medical medium books in
my practice because all the patients are
coming in now across the world globally
and in the u.s. especially and so what
happens is they used to privately look
at the books and lean from the
information and you know and then they
kind of you know they say well yeah
cat's claw can help
I mean I remember thirty years ago in my
office literally my first office thirty
years ago and I had a big jar of cat's
claw drive because she couldn't get a
good quality cats because I had to have
the drive and I would just take it out
when the spirit said take this out for
the person I would say this is what you
need to do for your Lyme disease and
they got off the antibiotics and they
took it in there you know well they
would make it in a bag and this is what
you have to do and and it's finally
taking off now but but you know there's
still there's a lot of problems we have
in the line world one is you know the
labs don't want to let go of bacteria
because they just built an empire on it
you got and then you got the antibiotic
sales right Big Pharma they built an
empire off antibiotics for lives Yeah
right
I mean hail if that's the right to do
that's right to do it I'm not I'm not
really cooling it I'm just saying if
that's what you want to do but the
problem is it's viral so we have but but
it's falling apart now because the
industry the medical industry actually
took big pharma took Lyme disease and
they moved it out of the bacteria
category without telling anybody and
they put it in autoimmune which means
it's not bacterial now it's autoimmune
but they did it in a sly way without
informing too many people without
informing too many doctors it's now
moved it's now considered an autoimmune
disease which means if it's autoimmune
that means that big pharma or whoever
the medical industry or science and
research believes that Lyme disease is
your body attacking itself no longer is
it back
Tyrael that's due to the medical medium
books because millions of them got out
their doctors are using them across the
globe and they know that it's shifting
whether anybody likes it or not saving
lives but we still have the Lyme disease
groups that are just all about
herxheimer sand bacteria because there's
a lot of old dogs that call them not the
people but the old doctors that don't
want to let go of that because they've
been if you're proven wrong there's a
lot of doctors that say you know what I
was wrong yeah I was wrong I care about
people too much
I want them better darn it it's viral
and it takes some time takes personal
thing and then there's some doctors and
I'm like I'm not admitting that that the
20 years I just bombarded people with
antibiotics cuz science and research
force them to force them to basically
and and they don't want to break them
and I understand I understand if you've
been behind something your whole life
you made it your life and then some guy
that's not a doctor coating around the
Titanic it's hard to you know but you
know our message is I try to stay away
from all that because it overwhelms me
but my message is just listen to your
body listen to your know this is really
simple stuff I think when I was really
suffering and really looking for answers
I thought about like my plants and my
dogs yeah and my child and just what are
the things that a body needs to heal a
body needs this fresh air sunshine
adequate hydration and you turn
nutrients nutrient-rich foods that it's
kind of really basic and this is we're
coming i hope full circle and empowering
people to really listen to that and not
be skeptical of it I think not too
simple it's what I've ever meant to do
and if you can find a healer or a doctor
who's supportive who's open-minded all
the better you know I would I would love
to have found that and maybe maybe one
of the doctors I was talking about who
is open-minded maybe he's here now I
haven't checked in and you know a year
and a half two years because I don't you
know feel good but I I do think yes of
course there's agendas and stuff I
really do think that everyone's just
trying their best and that people
to help people and and they're not able
to really separate what's story and
what's fact and what's fiction and it's
just um well I'm it's just a murky
environment and world for everyone I
remember doctor telling me a member
doctor friend telling me Anthony you
know do you want to put this information
out there about Lyme do you want that
you know what I said I said what about
the mommy that can't get out of bed to
take her child to school and he said you
know that you're going against the
agenda that's out there you're going
you're you're trying to crack it you
know you're trying to you're going
against all the rules and he said he
said I've al you your fight he said you
sure you want to do this because you
don't have to do this and I said the
mommy that can't make food she can't get
up can make dinner and she has to rely
on her husband or anything you know and
then flee and and then and then the
husband has to then change his whole
life around and how he's working on his
life parents move next door to us and
helped us and he's he's losing sleep
over how you feel what's going on yeah
and my doctor friend said my friend said
you know what I know I see it too I said
you can't there's there's thousands and
then hundreds of thousands of mom moms
with the fatigue and the chronic fatigue
and the buzzing and the ringing in the
vertigo and dizziness and the high
anxiety and they can't panic and this
any aches and pains and then all their
or rashes when they or the hot flash
yeah and my doctor said it's this and
your doctor says well you know
experiencing the same things and that
was what really the book really got me
it's just oh there's all these different
chapters with different like this
collection of symptoms that's called
this disease in this collection of
symptoms and then you know talking to
someone that had something else like ALS
or aunt or MS or something that was
similar to neurological line I was
always like I wonder if it's the same I
wonder if it's the same I wonder if it's
a cousin of that you know and and I just
was always asking those questions and
you know that
like controversial topic people are very
attached to what their diagnosis is or
what it's called or what their doctor
said and I think that people I believe
in you know the effect in a way and I
believe that people need to do what they
feel works for them and you know that's
really really important to me but I
don't think anyone can go wrong with
more fruits and vegetables in their diet
and when I was in nutrition school we
learned something called crowding out
and crowding out is just like bringing
in the fruits bringing in the vegetables
bringing in the herbal teas and stuff
I'm just kind of crowding out the bad
stuff and you know you're just naturally
gonna you're naturally gonna eat a lot
less like cheese chocolate beer and wine
if you are you know I listen I hear I've
listened to all your stuff so I hear in
my head now it's like you know
compassion is in your ear you're in my
ear and it's literally like like well
you can have one thought today but you
would be better it's more like this you
know just like annoying mosquito can you
just steam a little asparagus on the
side with dinner straight and so I
always have that like how can I work it
and how can I make it part of my life
how can I bring it to my families of it
they don't get sick and and you know to
people that want to hear it you know
it's the little things that we take for
granted when were strong and we're
feeling good it's every little thing
it's not can I step out the front door
and get to my little herb garden so I
can maybe pluck some parsley that you
know I couldn't even plant as my husband
had to plant yes on or there's the
little things can I can I actually you
know take a shower yeah like how
hardwood or showers enzymes like I got a
lien around
shots so any kind of hot water I
couldn't breathe in the shower and I
would feel like just like I was gonna
pass out whenever he took a shower and
I'd have to kind of like sit down or lay
down I was really happy as laying down
and I know that sounds crazy but just to
get downstairs or to get dressed to hang
out with my family was really hard and
you know my daughter at the time was so
so young that you know I think just it
almost gave me more presents and
attention to be with her in the house
because I obviously couldn't work or
anything but um you know she if she
wanted to go and do something like I'm
not going do something that she wanted
to do this daddy
it was my mother-in-law Sarah it was
family or it was Nora the woman who
brought in to help who is supposed to be
like a babysitter for 15 hours a week
ended up becoming like almost full time
or full time at one point because the
sicker I got the more I needed help and
then you know not everyone has that
luxury
and you know I think if we had continued
going the route that I was it would do
it with every little thing counts when
you're and then you're your and then you
have to get into a mindset of I'm
grateful I can shower today I'm grateful
I can get downstairs and probably be on
the couch for a little while and sit up
yeah that's another thing too it's like
how long can I sit up before I have to
lay down that happens to a lot of people
for like there were short hours of the
day and then like I noticed as I was
healing like it would get longer and
longer and then I would like get up and
out the healing to me was just like it
would come I wasn't like oh I'm healed
it was just one thing than one thing
that I could do I could do more is it
three steps up two steps back like I
said on my pocket there's a roller
coaster ride and I want to say that for
people that are doing this right now and
maybe you're in year one or two I don't
know some some people you know it takes
longer some people it takes shorter but
just faithful just faithfully you know
if you believe it and it resonates with
you just faithfully do it because then
you're just gonna get a shift and then
you get another shift and then you're
gonna have a step back but if you just
keep getting back on just keep getting
back on
and believe it then that's when it
really worked for me and I also think
the emotional part of you know healing
your emotional stuff is it's all
mind/body/spirit so this is your body
that you're healing but also your brain
works better when you're eating clean
and you're able to have more hope and
you know just my spirit really when once
I healed my broken spirit I think when
you're when you're feeling good
physically you can conquer anything
emotionally when you're when the
physical is down yeah that's when the
emotional wounds are hard that's when
everything is hard because you can't
even distract yourself from you can't
even do like I'm gonna go and take a jog
I'm gonna go and take a run you know I'm
gonna go and do this because you can
distract yourself when you're feeling
good to help battle emotional turmoil
how many people go I'm gonna go and
meditate I'm gonna go on a hill on a
climb on a hike hike today with my
girlfriend or my boyfriend and I'm gonna
go for a hike because I'm battling some
stuff emotionally I went to an emotional
counselor this is not the Deacon when
you're feeling good enough you can
actually take action you can take action
you can you can keep yourself busy you
can distract yourself you can hop on a
treadmill for a half an hour I have so
many people that say you know I hop on a
treadmill to burn off my steam and
adjust me and balance me emotionally but
when you get hit with that the viral
issues and and you get hit and knocked
down yeah and now you're just laying in
a bed I tell people hang in there
there's a way there's a way up there's a
way up to heal there's a way out of the
bed and there's a way to getting back to
doing things you love again whatever
that might be it could be the smallest
things like taking a little walk on the
street yeah I mean anything oh yeah I
mean it was eating like yes that I
couldn't eat for so long I mean it's
that simple sometimes it's heavy but and
then it becomes social like you never
partake is something with people that
you couldn't do or you know
I'm not nothing but well conversing so
you're in a social environment you get
together with some friends or even
family and you can't socialize the way
you want to work stressors I would just
whelmed with the challah just the
holidays like I wanted to be there for
my family I wanted to cook and have
people and I would just be like I can't
handle this I have to be in my room
because my nervous system was collapsed
and that's around family you know we're
more comfortable when we're at war when
we're around family well what about
friends you haven't seen in a while it
could be really difficult because now
you want more work I mean forget working
it and it takes it to a new level of
being hard on the nervous system these
are all things people are going through
with their lime and going through with
their different symptoms and you you you
push through this I know and you know
you got more energy than I do today so
I'm trying to finish up a book
yeah and I'm killing myself on every
chance I can you got more energy than I
do right now you're like you're popping
with energy no I mean am I am I just
making that up but she's got the energy
seeing as the friend it was like first
of all it was just it was a heavy time
it was dark and it was scary and like we
know we talked about the fear but it's
that fear of the unknown what's
happening to me
no one really knows what does this mean
how am I gonna get better and then it
was like this little tiny light at the
end of the tunnel and this process and
the belief and seeing the shifts and
then literally just you know over time
there was one day I came to the house
and I said I was like you're back like
it was just a vibrancy and it was a
lightness and you know and and she's
literally supermom she's literally the
greatest mom in the whole world and but
you see if you see her energy and her
pouch
and she doesn't want to miss a minute
that's the gift if anyone who has
chronic illness or anyone that's spent
time down whether you're in bed or you
know some of the times I was in bed
sometimes I was just at home on my couch
pajamas like wanting to get dressed and
like you know wanting to get out and
like participate in life but it's hard
on the kids
it's hard on - you're wondering if it's
affecting your children you wonder if
it's a way to take care of your child
but you you have to take care of
yourself and you know that's I think for
mommies it's the hardest thing because
you are still even if you have somebody
helping you
you're still consumed with your child
least I was just annoyingly there all
the time and like unable to let someone
really do it as much as I you know
should've probably but you can hardly
you can't listen to what you need when
you have a crying baby a or a colicky
baby which I had and you're exhausted
it's just very hard it's hard you know
in my practice even before this like
mommy's feeding themselves like a
nutritious lunch even you know instead
of like eating like a sugary bar and
going off to do a million things for
their kids work we're a service to our
children that is what the mothers are
absurdist to their children and their
homes and their husbands and and so when
you're sick and you can't provide that
environment and value levels and that
basic nurturing that you want to it is
very very tough on everybody everyone
your spouse your kids everybody so so
the gifts of having chronic illness are
if you've spent time down then when
you're it's the motivation of I want to
get out I want to do this and this and
then once you're feeling better you're
like I'm gonna do everything it gives
you like this new zest for life like I'm
planning on these trips right now and
I'm super excited and I go to concerts
now and I I you know I've taken so many
road trips since I got well I'm dragging
my family and you succeed you'll think
about it now like I'm on a road trip I
could couldn't have done a road trip
back a few years ago yours ain't easy
[Music]
this reminds me a point - can you just
let everybody know that because I don't
see anybody anymore okay you know on
that level and I can't because I'm
writing the books and everything like
that that the informations in these
books right it's there and all
everything else because it because of
how to stop helping up people because
the waiting list was in the millions so
I had to put it in the books years ago
it's you weren't probably the last yes
and I spoke to yes I applied to win the
lottery and I had this like weird
feeling I was gonna win which I never
have because I lose but I I did actually
win and it was February of 2016 and I
was one of the last people it was that
was pretty much wouldn't stop it's not
this right I had to keep up with the
books and get the information to the
world there were there were hundreds of
thousands of mommy's in the waiting list
and hundreds of thousands of children
win the waiting list and it was it was
breaking my heart and there I had to do
books cuz I knew there was no way I can
do it alone and get to everybody yeah it
wouldn't happen and so it was a mere
this has the supplements this has the
supplements in the book but it doesn't
have what I always call your yogi and I
would do like two drops and think that
was gonna get me well
out the handed ends and it has over 200
different symptoms and conditions and
the dosages right so what you you know
theme I say through all of them is the
same heavy metals because what people
need to know is the viruses feed off the
heavy metals and and yeah all you need
is a trigger an emotional hardship you
can really I mean that's also one thing
I want to say if I won the lottery I got
to consult with them I he was supposed
to only give me 30 minutes he gave me 60
minutes I did and I never talk to him
again after I just had the books and I
had the internet and I just would listen
to the and I just would take notes and
then I think what happens is I had zero
intuition about what was good I can help
everyone else to oh I doubt that
no you know even in my practice like I
knew how to help everyone but I just put
my self-care on the bar you mean
intuition on yourself yeah self-care
eating like I mean there were years
where it was like frosting for breakfast
I mean my friends can say that's right
like old places where all you can do is
like drink in a basement basically yeah
in a basement with pizza so so no I
didn't have a lot of like it was shut
down it was disconnected so as I was
doing it and I couldn't talk to you I
had those you know three years this is
the first time I talked to you since
then so I kind of got better at being
like ah what do I need today or what you
know I would go with the basic protocol
but I would feel it out and go like
highlighted and I go back and it read
chapters and I get so you did the
highlighting oh yeah listen because when
you find something that works there and
he's watching like CNN or something with
your intestinal stuff and I was said
earlier how that could like take over a
person's life and it becomes I mean the
bloating the gas France yeah the just
going to bathroom bathroom is like you
and like where it even can give you like
aches and pains when I get so bad
because you're getting you get the look
great do you get the low-grade viral
stuff to know if there you get the aches
and pains a little bit
hands all the time everybody that knows
me surprising that I can actually be
facing you guys you know because they
remember being at Kate's house yeah with
you guys and and and we took a little
look and everything you know I don't
want you guys to think that I'm out
there doing readings now think they said
you're not leaving yes
you're not leaving Kate's house and they
yeah and they said this and I and no but
that's but it really was incredible
because there was you know the reading
came out and it was just stuff that no
one knows about anybody and you know
Oliver was job was on the floor and he
was like what I was this how's this
possible and and it just but first of
all it made sense and and to me I was
like you know this is stuff that for
years I mean you talk about your ear and
hearing yelling he was like oh I was
turning around saying huh what happened
I thought yeah so it was incredible I
felt like or question to anything it was
yeah and it's really the end no matter
what your ailments are I feel like
there's something in ya look back I
don't want anybody thinking just because
they can't have that chance exactly that
they can't get the information and I had
my complete experience literally come
just you know watching her heal reading
connecting to it saying oh my gosh this
is a it makes so much sense and be it's
the first thing that worked that really
worked and I committed to it just as
hard as I committed to any other
protocol that I was told in the past or
antibiotics which caused other problems
and this you know was a game-changer but
then and then I got to meet you so it's
the added bonus on top for me and you
know just being able to say thank you
and and just in hear your story - that
was cool I hope you guys you know when
when the podcast comes out and did a
podcast of Kate Hudson and and all of
our yeah and I hope you guys everybody
just listens to that podcast
listen stall the part that was
uncensored that was that was just you
guys just threw me down I just I was
thrown on a couch and I was just
standing there and oh oh crap you're
going to say anything
a few stupid things I'm sure I said a
few stupid and out because you it's
about there are things that you and you
know look at the end of the day no one
is out there you know making every
single person happy but you're changing
people's lives and you know I know
exactly where I would be and it was so
25th
I threw a birthday brunch for myself in
my garden and in my back like you know
we'll call it garden it's patio and and
I had all my girlfriend's there and had
so much energy to like make the food
days later
I had like this that's what gave me the
glimpse of hopes I was like well I feel
amazing and I don't know why you
working but it's working you know spirit
of compassion told me when I was when I
was younger and spirit of compassion
told me there
this information is going to empower
people I didn't know what that word
meant okay because I'm not people think
I mean I hear a voice perfectly clear it
gives me this advanced medical
information to save lives but it doesn't
mean I practice the most spiritual or or
talked the most spiritual or anything
like that
and I remember once when spirit told me
this is going to empower women moms
women and everything men too and I
didn't know what it meant I was like
what does empowerment mean what does
empower mean and then I heard it
throughout the years but what it meant
was you know when you're in the depths
of despair like that and there's no
answers and you can't even have that
brunch you can't even have that brunch
with family or friends or anything and
you can't even even do anything but then
you can take control over your life and
you can actually I'm getting choked up
and you can actually do something about
it
that's real empowerment now that that's
empowerment and that's what spirit was
teaching me like that's what this is
gonna be is gonna be empowerment for
women to be able to just to not be
bullied and spiritually bullied by the
industry by trends in the industry and
somebody might say well celery juice is
a trend Anthony actually it was never
backed or there was no agenda
besides healing and it wasn't backed by
any funding wasn't back for any science
and research science resources even know
anything about snow and you know and
it's funny it's like how many millions
to sell you just have to heal before
science research so like there's no
starting behind it's not good for you oh
come on Howard right you were in Howard
Howard and it was so full circle for me
and you know somebody said to me once
like I don't know if this was in school
or work but if you want to know what to
eat like any food that's ever been
advertised is probably something you're
not supposed to eat and all the foods
that nobody talks about that nobody like
you know advertises about those are the
foods those are the foods we should be
looking at and you're the first person
like I don't know how you made celery
trendy I don't know how you made like oh
you know I've become a
lover of vegetables wears before you
know I said she used to talk that beer
and wine where my four food groups
and I you know it's just it's wonderful
to feel to have this much energy and it
comes from the plans it comes from the
Sun that comes from the plants and then
it comes into you and you know it's a
live food from the earth it's one
ingredient whole businesses of movement
of Whole Foods it's back to basics it's
stuff that my grandmother ate you know
maybe she wasn't but you know my mom and
they were picking wild blueberries ya
know I mean I do think that there was
this connection with nature I mean
growing up in New England that we felt
with the seasons and we picked apples
and stuff like that I mean maybe that's
not too far no no you're picking out you
know what's funny you know it's funny
that elevated biotics that i talked
about in the communal that you know is
more advanced than it more advanced in
any way way more advanced and microbiome
talk even today microbiome talk is just
a new trendy word for they don't know
what's wrong with your guts though and
you know what spirits are talking to me
as a child spirit said look we're
picking you I said it on the pot because
you can probably handle it and you're a
fighter and no one even knows what I've
gone through through this journey but
but the point is those those ramps and
everything you're like okay no
I'm just trying to talk to the person
that I was supposed to get to the
information I get in my own way listen I
do get in my own way I know I get fired
up because you know when people suffer
it's no joke
that's the whole thing and people who
hasn't some people who haven't suffered
yet or been there they don't know what
it's like for the other person and
that's my issue that's my issue not to
the people that don't know my issue is
to the people out there enough to be
funny thing is is if you know the
industry is saying don't drink celery
juice you need to have all your fiber
don't juice it all these things they
tell people wrong information but what's
funny is okay you know what no one drink
it anymore I just want it for myself
because I it was it wasn't in the store
one time I had some the funny thing is I
can't go into the store anymore because
I'll be mom bar decor so I can't go in
there and water a celery juice right so
someone has to go and get the celery for
me I'm like hey aw I'm like what there's
no celery and like no I need my celery
and so so now that I hear it when you
hear an article say Oh celery juice
there's no science research I believe
good good keep the negative did you know
what I'm like I need my cell you know my
heart of hearts I wanted
it's one of these things were I feel
like a lot of people say oh celery juice
but it's sorry there's so much behind it
even though it's one of these terms
it's like seems simple yeah
the information in the books is what
really makes sense and the you know the
I wanna say the the breaking the making
sense kind of in your body yeah you know
you have to top off the fluency your car
you you know you get low on fluids you
get low on you know I'm not so the zero
diagnosis is just an idea theory that is
bacteria that's what the theory is okay
so the difference or what I discovered
along the way was a lot of kind of GI
issues are in the lower intestine and
you know it's just a different diagnosis
and there it's kind of two different
things
talent it was first and it's kind of
where the food lands we sit down it used
to be the Candida theory yeah and I took
a long time I mean I worked hard to
break that one yeah yeah I had to
actually split that world in half laughs
clearly cracking maligne world I had a I
had a you know the information of the
misinformation I mean just like the
candida right crack that whole thing
open because Candida you first of all if
you're trying to get rid of your Candida
that's how we actually absorb our
nutrients we have to have Candida to do
this so that was a theory because that
is my hard work well spirits hard work
yes but now they moved it they moved it
to see Bo yeah okay and but the problem
is with that one they don't know what
bacteria it is that's behind anything
and it's streptococcus that's what it is
and it's caused from your liver being
stagnant sluggish low bio reserves and
low hydrochloric acid but here's the
thing
and then strep we all have strep in us
and then it becomes a gut issue is what
it does now they're trying to shift it
all to this microbiome thing like
everybody's like oh there's something in
there that special they're still behind
by 2030 years it's it's the elevated
bionics that you know about right did
you hear that I'm not friends with any
farmers and I don't have okay so okay
are you able to tell people I know it's
in the boat or the countertop but like
the basics of like if you want the
elevated wrote your own parsley in a pot
in a plant where in your kitchen if you
need to yeah absolutely if you have to
so you literally just buy like organic
seeds seeds and gigantic soil grows when
you pick that piece of parsley
it's got bacteria on it it's got
microorganism on it and those those are
the I don't wash it leave it that you
don't have to it's growing in your own
it's not like you're using some
dangerous this or that or yeah I'm using
some kind of whatever it's true and so
so what happens is that that parsley
just is an example it has the elevated
biotics and on it which science research
doesn't know about either there's not
only signs in research but all the
probiotic companies that that's not what
that is that just dies in your system
you take all those probiotics it just
gets eaten off your stomach acid it just
kills it leaves that never even gets
down there because it's not really no
not in an item probiotic land but not
even in earth you know earth soil borne
work Michael Rehm ISM probiotic none of
that
it's the probe it's the it's the
elevated biotic sorry not the end
and it's that it's that microorganism
that someday they'll study about it
because we'll get them to do it and
hopefully this is good well that's that
goes into your gut but deep in it in the
ileum and that's where you produce your
b12 everybody's b12 deficient that's why
I want people are like hey eww why
you're pushing the b12 pushing the b12
because no one has those elevated
biotics yeah if you sprout your own
sprouts if you like get a sprouting tray
and you sprout your own sprouts you'll
get the elevated biotic it will just
literally be on the leaves it's coming
from the Sun it's coming it's coming
from the air the air literally it's like
the it's like the Earth's ability to
keep us healthy that we haven't even
tapped into just like we haven't tapped
into the Sun well what the Sun does for
us we still don't even know we talking
about Megane it's it's yeah there's so
much more than that and so that's what's
happening with the elevator biotics it's
it's actually in the air and it develops
literally develops there's some
connection happening around us that
creates that micro organism especially
in the garden especially outside so if
you open your kitchen door
I just in Japan you open your kitchen
door you're letting in outside air and
it's in the outside air you know if you
plant an apple tree on your property if
you if you have a lemon tree and we
rinse it am I supposed to not if it's
off your own tree you don't rinse it
like okay dirt and you can do a really
laughs you can you can get a light rinse
if you if you have you will anything
you if it has if you know it hasn't been
sprayed by pesticides right let's say
that it was a fresh squirrel pee pee and
that's what will happen but we are very
disconnected from nature you know
sterilized place with a wrapper well
that squirrel pee has less anything in
it then all the people walking around
with all the shingles in hhv-6 is HB h7
simplex is this that epstein-barr 64 I
do have smart shingles that's hiria 50
groups of strep bacteria all of it
that squirrel trust me that's only you
got to worry about restaurants bathroom
doors bathroom toilets in the white you
got you carry the spray I'm not worried
about a squirrel that's a good question
the sport listen I'm doing all this work
it's so true it's like we worry about
and it's good you wash things because
when you go to the store seriously
Elizabeth so important when you go to
the store and you get things you want to
wash them yeah so don't get me wrong
it's yes I'm glad you in the habit you
pump your lemon off the tree yes and you
rinse it stay in that habit because I
don't want you to not rinse a
store-bought lemon yeah and and for
these reasons so seriously so I don't
want people get the wrong message the
other thing is those elevated biotics
they're on an apple and an apple orchard
if you go to pick your own apples like
once a year yeah if you get that
elevated biotic once a year and you it
goes into the ileum it stays in there
for years but we never get it in us and
we don't get enough of it and then we
are the metals and all the other things
we have in our body
that knock them down right but it's the
strongest microorganism that build your
b12 keeps your gut healthy so you don't
get the SIBO which is streptococcus or
anything else but did you have to ask
them if they spray like you have to go
to a place where they're not on organic
forms now
yeah and a lot of there's a lot of non
spray forms they're not organic but they
don't spray design yeah which is fun
like the whole farmer's market in
California is right yes it's all like
that hole it's hard to get certain oh
that's hard to get certification but it
doesn't mean that they're you know GMO
or spraying and stuff like that I'm
blown away
powerful stories no I can I'll keep you
guys powerful stories of healing and and
it's no joke these stories because these
are real experiences and you guys have
gone through it there so what would you
say you guys feel like saying anything
to anybody who's struggling right now
who's in a bed right now or they're
there they're functioning but they know
they're not where they need to be and
people don't understand all their
different symptoms or you know what
they're up against if you have any if
you have something to say to the women
out there and men too and I worry about
children yes you know I've seen
daughters and sons at 14 15 16 years old
and mom's just frantic because they're
diagnosed with Lyme disease or diagnosed
with autoimmune or a thyroid problem if
you have any words to the moms out there
that anything as a mom you know we you
know I don't want to get into like
gender roles there were never been a lot
of mommies do the shopping and you know
kind of control what comes in to the
house and I think that you know I'm not
crazy we have you know we have some junk
in our house but generally we have a
foundation and a base for nutrition and
a lot of its based in this stuff and I
get it in where I can you know my
daughter she's not we're not like crazy
you know juicing and she's totally vegan
she's not but you know maybe more 80%
20% and you know it's just really to
protect her overall health going forward
and you know cold and flu season
coming up and you know might be nice to
give her a little zinc or b12 or you
know just fortify her and build her up
in a way because the world is you know
there's a lot out there
but to someone who's in bed struggling I
think I've said it all yeah I really
just I want people to there's hope
there's there's hope is we can you know
I want to say to someone who heals
because you know I used to listen to
Anthony say like you can heal and you
know I'm telling you from the inside out
that your life can get better all I
wanted was a normal amount of pain and
suffering I didn't want to be inundated
with symptoms and so much that I didn't
feel like I wanted to live and you know
I got there I have a normal amount of
pain and suffering like their fest of
people that are healthy walking around
and the ones that we take for granted
the ones that we take for granted not
you know like healthiest person in the
world but I'm not bedridden and I'm
having a functioning life and I'm
enjoying my life and I think you can get
your life back I really do and I think
just lock out the noise tune into what
you need and this is something I learned
for my friend Robin Youkilis and also
Gabby Bernstein your inner guidance
system and and ask your body every day
what do you what do I need what do I
need today what do I need today can I
block out the noise yeah what do I need
today and you'll be amazed when you're
grounded that you just make better
choices naturally and you'll also be
shown when you don't make better choices
we'll show you with the symptoms or you
know something happening so you know I
just I wanted people that kind of like
take ownership of their healing it
doesn't mean that you don't have
supporters and you don't have helpers
you don't have like doctors and you know
healers and friends but it's your
journey whose your journey and when you
give your body what it needs you can
heal you can hear you can heal
a little way and I just am honored and I
don't think without you I mean I
wouldn't know without you I mean you
know for me I never talked about any
kind of stuff going on whether it's the
fatigue or the you know just issues and
there's so many these days I always
recommend it because I say give it a
shot
read it see nothing you know just for
anyone who's suffering also to surround
yourself with really positive people who
I always ask myself like a person place
or thing
do I have a good feeling or a bad
feeling about this person place or thing
and it's really important on your
healing journey to surround yourself
with like the foods that make you feel
good the people all the places the
things that really give back to you and
and nurture you and don't deplete even
on the smallest levels even the smallest
like dragging you down not making you
feel good making you feel like no gross
it's probably not a supportive healing
food I'm happy you guys are here I'm
gonna I'm gonna let you guys go guys
everybody thank you for being here today
another medical medium live thank you
special in it I'm going to click the
button here