I don't have any words it was amazing
and the cardi gave me for the light that
stands in the way of Darkness exactly
what we needed the Smoothie is the best
smoothie I've ever had better than I
could ever do I could definitely taste
the fresh amazing tast like the ocean
love it all
of anxiety depression addiction I mean
it's countless all the things that
there's no other way people ask me all
the time like you know don't you want to
like cheat or something it's like there
is no cheating treating myself is
drinking what I'm supposed to be
drinking there's there is a way I mean a
lot of it is just not knowing the way be
patient love yourself best you can and
never give up on yourself and you can
feel good you don't have to feel the way
you're feeling