heavy metal pumped up about it
you know
heavy metals
controls us more than we know
toxic heavy metals control our mind
i think that's why the industries
are even involved with it because they
are
the more toxic heavy metals that enter
our brain
the more chances
we're gonna screw up we're gonna screw
up
toxic heavy metals
causes more suicides
than people would even believe or know
heavy metals can create a depression
that's so devastating a mysterious
depression that's so devastating where
you can't seem to see
the light on any level
where
that depression
takes over
it takes over everything there's no hope
there's no
light
there's no sanctuary
there's no
anything when you're that severely
depressed
but yet the toxic heavy metals creating
that depression
can push somebody to suicide
toxic heavy metals
really show themselves when an elder
gets
dementia
and you lose touch with that elder
that mother that father
that grandmother
that grandfather
that great grandmother that great
grandfather
you lose touch with that person or that
best friend
where the best friend is
losing their mind
toxic heavy metals
can devastate lives
but yet
you don't hear anything really about
toxic heavy metals i spent 35 years
trying to teach people about toxic heavy
metals
so they know and now you kind of faintly
hear it amongst the
alternative health industry right and
they all give all the wrong stuff for it
like
do charcoal by the way is
terrifying
internally when you take charcoal
do
uh this do chlorella which doesn't work
doesn't remove metals
and
what happens is that
that
toxic heavy metals can also change our
decisions in life
they can confuse us to make us confused
so we lose all confidence
toxic heavy metals can make it so you
don't have the confidence to choose what
road to go down
do i go if you're blessed enough to go
to a university do i go to this
university or do i go to that university
toxic heavy metals can literally shape
what college you're going to go to if
you're blessed enough to go to college
toxic heavy metals can change the shape
of the world around you too to make you
think certain things about the world
that actually aren't of what's happening
in the world and it also toxic metals
can make you not see things you need to
see in the world to protect
yourself toxic heavy metals can create
deep insecurities so you make the wrong
decisions it's not your fault
any decision you made that wasn't the
best is not your fault
it's not your fault
toxic heavy metals can alter how we
perceive things in relationships toxic
heavy metals can make it so you think
you've got a good relationship with
someone whether it's a boyfriend
girlfriend friend partner whoever it is
work part or whatever it is and then
something goes wrong because that person
has toxic heavy metals and that person's
just not just agreeable where it's just
not working and then the relationship
breaks up
toxic heavy metals can make boyfriends
cheat on girlfriends
toxic heavy metals can make girlfriends
cheat on boyfriends
toxic heavy metals can make husbands
cheat on wives toxic heavy metals can
make watching husbands toxic heavy
metals can literally
alter how someone perceives their
relationship
it also can create a problem where a
relationship is really difficult
really
difficult toxic heavy metals
can shape
so many things around our daily living
it's unfathomable
toxic heavy metals are in everyone
and they can alter
how a person sees the world
toxic heavy metals can create an anxiety
condition so that person gets tagged as
an anxiety-ridden person amongst their
family and friends
when it's not even the person's fault
that they have anxiety that they're
struggling and suffering
but all the friends and family can't
take it anymore that person's too
anxiety ridden and too anxious meanwhile
that person gets labeled that and and
tagged that by family members and
friends how confusing is that that's not
even who the real person is inside toxic
heavy metals are creating that
toxic heavy metals
can alter so many things in our lives
around us and shape and change
everything
when a loved one is getting alzheimer's
that's toxic heavy metals when a loved
one's getting parkinson's and seeing 50
neurologists that's toxic heavy metals
toxic heavy metals can get you searching
to doctor to doctor to doctor even with
your most mildest brain fog case you
guys toxic heavy metals are making you
go to ten doctors spending ten thousand
dollars spending another this doing this
driving to toxic heavy metals
can make you
confused
and then get hit by a car
on the freaking highway
toxic heavy metals can make somebody on
the highway
have a seizure
and then four or five people die on the
highway because of toxic heavy metals
people seizure all the time on highways
driving on roadways
and run off the road and hit and hit
five people
toxic heavy metals did that
toxic heavy metals can make somebody
drink
and drink get drunk and hit somebody
because metals can create a depression
and only alcohol seems to soothe it so
toxic heavy metals makes somebody
addictive and now they're drinking all
this alcohol and then they go and kill
somebody and guess what it was toxic
heavy metals that actually propel that
sure the person's at fault sure they did
they drank and all that but toxic heavy
metals made their life unbearable so
they had to do that toxic heavy metals
make kids go
and snort fentanyl and cocaine
toxic heavy metals
make people at spring break drink
themselves to death and there's always
that one person that over drinks and
they get uh poisoning and their parents
get a phone call from the morgue and the
morgue is talking to the parents saying
i'm sorry mr smith i'm sorry mrs smith
but your 19 year old daughter
got alcohol poisoning in his dead
toxic heavy metals
creates a lot of problems including
madness
to the point where
terrible crimes are committed it takes
also a bad person don't get me wrong but
when you have toxic heavy metals in a
bad person that's when it goes really
downhill
you put toxic heavy metals in a good
person you'll get bad decisions and
wrong decisions and you'll get all kinds
of issues and all kinds of symptoms and
conditions and confusion amongst friends
and family around them making their life
difficult making the person suffering
difficult but if you stick toxic heavy
metals in a madman
then a war or something can happen you
stick toxic heavy metals in someone
who's just already batshit crazy and you
put metals in them it only compiles it
and makes it worse right
you stick toxic heavy metals in a
surgeon they're going to be extra
tremoring when they're cutting you open
okay but they don't want to retire
because they can't retire because they
need the money because surgeons still
have to work for a living so as they're
shaking a little bit and they're on all
their caffeine to control it and their
medications to control it the surgeon's
working on you and they got a tremor
condition because the toxic heavy metals
toxic heavy metals can change the
outcomes of people who are getting
surgeries done by doctors that got toxic
heavy metals inside of them toxic heavy
metals can change the outcome of all
everybody's lives for all these
different reasons
toxic heavy metals
can make it
where critical mistakes are made all the
time
so
is it important
to get toxic heavy metals out of us i
don't know
i really don't know anymore sometimes i
wake up in the morning and i'm like
gotta get medals out of people i gotta
get metal spirit of compassion i gotta
get medals out of people it's exhausting
right
it's exhausting
we're day two of the heavy metal detox
cleanse challenge that's what we're
doing medical medium do you guys have
your book right here cleanse the heel
got it right here cleanse the heel you
guys the heavy metal detox cleanse is in
this book questions are answered in this
book so important in this book there's
information it's here right do you have
your supplies and stuff like that right
so i got the wild blueberry powder from
vimergy incredible not sponsored these
guys are amazing i got the barley grass
cheese powder right there from vimergy
these are key ingredients i got the
spirulina
powder from vimergy right key
ingredients right there i'm not an
ambassador to this company and i'm not
sponsored okay and i don't own the
company okay someday maybe i'll come out
with a medical medium product i'll slap
medical medium across the label it'll be
medical medium spirulina and i'll do
that but the reason one the reason why i
don't to begin with because the best
stuff ever i've ever seen
i don't even know if i could even do
something as good as what they did
because for some reason
they're they they have the capacity to
fight for it i don't know if i have that
strength to fight for what they've done
the fight to make actually this stuff
the cleanest stuff on the planet
i mean of course i would fight but man
that's what i love about this stuff
but if this company ever changes what
they're doing boom they're gone they
change what they're doing with their
products out of here i don't wanna i
don't you know what i mean
but anyway incredible stuff right now
it's the best stuff out there and they
made promises that they're not gonna
change
so you guys we're on tick tock right now
we're live there there's a question on
tick tock what's the difference between
blueberries and wild blueberries good
question you guys so what's the
difference between blueberries and wild
blueberries okay
a blueberry
is a cultivated fruit that still has
wonderful nutrients and some
antioxidants i love regular blueberries
if i see a pint of regular blueberries
i'll eat them absolutely they're good
for you they are
they're related they're related to its
cousin which is the real blueberry like
the wild blueberry right the wild
blueberry is a wild food that means that
the difference is when you're dealing
with the wild food is is remarkable the
antioxidants are off the chart they're
much higher anthocyanins much stronger
right that's just one thing the other
thing is adaptive
adaptive
you can burn the wild the blueberries
down to the ground and they'll come back
if you go and torch the cultivated
blueberry down to the ground
you see nothing
you see nothing come back
nothing comes back
and that's one of the big things right
there what that means is the wild
blueberry's got
thousands and thousands of years of
information in it to survive to beat out
stuff and that's what i want inside my
body i want something that has thousands
of years of information in it
in it
right
for survival survival because of what
we're up against now too
anyway that's just some reasons the wild
blueberry actually has the ability
to actually help with
removing the metals i talk about
so you guys
has a great ability we're live right now
on telegram tick tock rumble facebook
youtube and probably somewhere too
and i hope the angels are watching as
well from above we're live on getter
one more i actually forgot
so you guys we're in the heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge right now we're
day two this is exciting i'm making the
heavy metal detox smoothie i'm gonna run
some celery really quick through here i
got cilantro right there which is
exciting so we're gonna have some fun so
this is gonna be a great time we're
gonna talk about mental illness
we're going to talk about anxiety
depression a little bit of that we'll
talk about the vagus nerve too and
everything else we can so how do we do
this
how do we actually do this
we take a lemon
if you can only do one part of this
cleanse
you're not gonna get metals out
if you just do the lemon water but
you're gonna flush your liver in the
morning which is really exciting unless
you all you do it like a ham turkey
bacon sausage breakfast egg breakfast
you do that then you're probably not
gonna flush much at all out of your
liver but if you start out with lemon
water first thing and it's all you do
you made a move man in your life you did
you made a big move right
so cut open the lemon
and i'm going to squeeze some lemon in
here right there
this is really hard to do
right
it's not hard to do
i'm being
hardly sarcastic i guess
i don't know what i'm being
done
that's step one right there you did it
even if it's just this at least you're
gonna get a little hydration and a flush
right in the morning especially if you
don't do any heavy fats in the morning
too so if you just do the lemon water in
the morning life starts to change
don't do hot lemon i know i did this
yesterday where no hot water no hot
you don't want to kill the lemon you
don't want to kill the
michelle l that's the best word for it
exactly
she's just yeah totally
so
you don't want to kill the living
phytochemical compounds inside
the lemon the lemon juice you don't want
to destroy that the living enzymes the
living water inside when a lemon's on a
tree or in the basket or at home in the
basket of the grocery store or at home
on your cutting board your lemon's still
alive it has it hasn't died
so when you do the hot water you kill
the lemon juice you kill it right so you
don't want to do that in order for that
hydration to happen it has to be raw
lemon juice you put it in hot water you
have cooked lemon juice which is fine if
you want a hot lemon tea so a little bit
of lemon balm tea you want some honey
you want some ginger tea you want to
squeeze lemon in there but it's doing a
different thing this is different here
adele says details matter i'm honored
thank you for being here truly
so
this detail makes her breaks it makes or
breaks so we got that lemon water right
there you guys see that i'll even show
you the lemon right there boom i'm close
up to talking just doing a little close
up over here i'm not trying to leave you
guys out we're here we're here we're
here i'll give you guys a close up to
the lemon at least so there we are
so we got that done the next thing is
celery juice right that's the next thing
before we move on to celery juice do you
have what you need to do this because i
want you to be able to do this tomorrow
or the next day so even when the heavy
metal detox day 2 challenge is over
which it'll be over today it doesn't
mean you're not starting the heavy metal
detox cleanse tomorrow because you might
be somebody just getting here and you're
like what do i got to do what what what
get the book right get it free at the
library or at amazon.com us
51 off amazon.com us right
it's a medical textbook it has the heavy
metal detox cleanse in there make sure
you have this
if you can't afford the sixteen dollars
go the library and try to get one so you
can start your cleanse someday
very important
and you can read the details of the
cleanse in here a lot of information
that can be answered
so make sure you guys get cleansed to
heal it's so critical it really is
that's what you need there the next
thing you need is spirulina right do you
have a spirulina that's the one i like
that's the best one right there so
that's the vimorcy you'll see the little
vimergy label right there
there it is right there
so that's the vimorji right see if i can
get this straight how do you get this
straight
what
what there we are
that was that was weird that was
psychedelic i couldn't tell you right
now that was really psychedelic
all right
so that's the vimercy powder right there
so you need that now if you get another
if you get another spirulina
right
keep in mind it may not be as strong and
may not be as good it may not be as
clean and if that's the case you're
still using something and so that's good
okay
but that's the best one
it's barley grass juice powder let's see
if we get a close up on that one too so
the barley grass juice powder
right there you go
so that's the emergency barley cream now
this is important to know barley grass
don't make a mistake and get just barley
grass
don't do that you want barley grass
juice powder because here's how it works
barley grass you're just gonna poop out
you're just gonna poop the barley grass
out
that's all
it's just going to come out the other
end
that's what it's going to do
barley grass juice powder you're not
going to poop out
sure you might poop some out naturally
depending on how fast you poop after you
eat and stuff everybody's got a
different time span because of
peristaltic action issues and stuff but
the barley grass juice powder will
absorb and assimilate that will absorb
and assimilate and it'll get into your
bloodstream and to your brain is what
you want right the next thing
you got the option of wild blueberry in
different ways so here's the frozen wild
blueberries right
and then you got the option of like the
vimergy wild blueberry powder i throw it
all in here's an option right here of
wyman's this is the wyman's right there
okay
the wyman's uh wild blueberry juice
you guys can see it right there okay
now i work with weimans to try to keep
this stuff around
okay so um i'm not sponsored by vimergy
but wyman's i work with them on mona
says drinking heavy metal detox smoothie
along with celery juice and lemon juice
since last summer my allergies to cats
are gone incredible no more menopause
symptoms that's amazing right there
vision improving expecting to lose
weight sooner or later diet low in fat
yeah you will lose weight that's amazing
you're doing all the things you need to
do what you're doing is you're restoring
the liver as soon as the liver starts to
restore you lose the weight as soon as
the liver starts to get a little
stronger and all that junk comes out and
that's the thing if your allergies go
down if the allergies are going down i
tell people all this time all this all
these
all about this all this time talk to
doctors too when allergies are going
down when you're doing this like the
heavy metal detox smoothie and the
celery juice and lemon water you're
cleaning up the liver too and when
you're cleaning up the liver and
removing all the toxic waste including
toxic heavy metals what happens is the
door opens the gate opens
you got less stuff
floating around your system
less stuff floating around your system
triggering allergies left and right got
less of that and less of that and
eventually your liver gets better and
better and then boom the weight starts
coming off the unwanted weight starts
coming off so that's really good
so do you guys have your cilantro let's
take a look at cilantro that's next
right here
so we got cilantro that's something you
can use now listen if you don't have all
these things and you only have three of
these things
let's do it let's do it there's the
cilantro right there okay i use it as a
leafy green i eat it all the time like i
throw it in nori rolls every day i mean
you name it i love cilantro
and it goes inside the smoothie so it's
one of the key ingredients check it out
right there right
the other one is dulse do you have dolls
now that's the vimergy dolls right there
okay
and what i do is i put a couple of
dropper folds in the smoothie i'll put
one or two
the quality is unmatched and it's
incredible by the way this is legendary
to have a doll's tincture like that it's
it's just i can't say enough about it
and do you have whole form of dolls as
an option too a lot of people can't get
the whole form
that's the whole form right there so i
got that i throw a little bit of that in
the smoothie right there so incredible
so there you go if you guys can see that
amazing right
so we're going over the ingredients now
other stuff other stuff those are the
five key ingredients i'm covering so
these are the five
key ingredients right
then you need other things for the
smoothie
you need an orange so that's something
you need right there so you need an
orange
got an orange right here okay
nice little orange
that's a big orange actually that's a
really big orange you guys
you need your you need your um orange
you need
bananas
right
we're gonna have to get some in a little
bit we need bananas and we need apples
apples don't go in the smoothie
apples don't go in the smoothie oh here
we go we got bananas
close call close call
banana scare a banana scare
we got bananas
we need bananas okay so that's another
thing we need right so that's going into
the smoothie all right you guys don't
mind if i have a bite
i still love bananas after all these
years eating bananas
i love them you know what's funny about
the alternative industry
i hate bananas so much
they create all these diets around don't
have any sugar don't have any sugar and
stuff like that when they don't even get
it a banana is anti-viral
they don't even know why anybody's sick
and they're telling you not to eat a
banana
bananas have antiviral compounds in them
anti-pathogen compounds anti-mold
anti-yeast anti-everything meanwhile the
alternative industry has been putting
people into banana fare for years now
right i did a podcast episode on it
right medical media podcast apple
podcast
they try to put people in fear of
bananas like scared to death of a banana
right
and how ridiculous is that
they're children with autism and adhd
the doctors like don't eat bananas don't
give the kids sugar
it's it's psycho
meanwhile
your brain runs on sugar did you know
that if your brain doesn't receive sugar
within 10 seconds guess what it dies
it dies
the blood going to your brain is
traveling with glucose in it if you
don't get glucose to your brain why do
you think the old keto diet used to kill
people all the time you guys don't know
many well actually some of you guys
might have experienced watching this or
gone through it so i'm actually wrong
about that spirit just said you're wrong
there are some people that actually are
in the medical medium community that did
the old keto diet in the old way and
almost died
i love when spirit uh corrects me
it's like a school teacher it's like a
school teacher on my butt
every time
anyway so the whole point is
is that we need sugar to the brain so
now here's how the heavy metal detox
smoothie works it works
where there's glucose to travel a lot of
these nutrients
to the brain
to get the metals out that's where i was
going the whole point and and so where
i'm heading here is why do we do the
heavy metal detox movie
we do it because we're trying to get
metals out of the brain and glucose is a
big part of it and we make sure there's
ample glucose inside the smoothies what
we do all right i'm gonna put the banana
down
let's make some celery juice really
quick
all right
so i'm gonna run some celery through
here it's part of the cleanse if you
don't have a juicer use a blender then
strain it with a cheesecloth or a milk
nut milk bag and that's fine you can do
that you know
this is amazing right here this thing is
running good
right
okay
you guys get the book check out the
check out the details in the book under
the heavy metal cleanse okay don't add
water to your celery
i'm gonna run some celery through here
[Applause]
right
16 ounces if you need to do less do
eight ounces if you need to do less
because you're sensitive because you're
really toxic do four ounces if you're
really toxic do four ounces then work
your way up same thing you want to do
with the heavy metal detox smoothie it's
very gentle all of the gentle
what i love about the heavy metal detox
smoothie and the heavy metal detox
cleanse it's gentle
there's radical nutty people and
alternative medicine in the cultish
alternative medicine out there that all
said well like this is how you get
metals out they make you so sick
people get so sick
sometimes it ruins their lives they'll
go and they'll get these dangerous
chelation treatments
and they'll just they're
damaged for years
lydia says facebook stops
yeah that's whoa
they're just they just yeah we're
censored on facebook for some reason
because i'm talking about bananas
somebody in facebook probably doesn't
like the bananas because they've been
taught not to be bananas so they're like
oh i'll fix that medical medium let's
hit this button a couple more times and
knock off another bunch of people
just guess it
all right
so when it comes down to the heavy metal
detox smoothie it's really gentle it's
critical that it's that gentle sarah
says i just ordered the spare of the end
of barley grass juice powder amazing
amazing
making a little bit of solar juice so
celery juice neutralizes the toxins
and neutralizes metals it helps to
dislodge that
it creates a dislodging of purging now
celery juice does not bind onto metals
specifically and carry them completely
out of the body that's not celery
juice's role celery juice's role is to
neutralize metals
lower their strength and their toxic
nature
celery juice does bind on to metal
byproduct
that makes us sick that gives us a lot
of metal conditions and symptoms and
diseases
people get better just drinking celery
juice with the brain fog i hear it all
the time it's like oh my god my brain
fog so much better i'm doing celery
juice and part of that reason is because
the celery juice is removing
toxic heavy metal
by-product
that's different than the metal itself
but it's byproducts so celery is already
helping everybody with their metal
problems every single day
that's what's incredible
michelle l says it's a team effort
indeed it is the celery juice acts as
part of that as part of that team member
so it's really important
now listen some people have more toxic
heavy metals than others some people
have them deeper in the brain
keep that in mind some people have more
metals different kinds of metals
all that's important to know you
somebody else may not be doing anything
but the heavy metal detox smoothie and
they have a really bad case of metals
and they're not reading the details in
the book
about like
adding additional customizing protocols
and stuff
customizing is critical and that's what
medical medium information it's about
it's not one size fits all because
everyone has a different level of metals
and different circumstances with with
what they're dealing with in their
symptoms and conditions right
so there we go got some celery juice
right here
[Music]
hey w can you let us know how long it
can take to get metals out exactly what
i'm talking about right now yo fruits
and
vegetables that's a cool handle eo
fruits and vegetables so yeah so what
happens is that
a lot of people may have a lot of a lot
of different metals so let's go into
that a little bit okay so i got my brain
over here
one of my brains
right
somebody may have metals in the left
left hemisphere and not the right
hemisphere somebody may have them in the
left and right uh hemisphere somebody
may have them in the frontal lobe
everybody's got a different situation
with metals more people might have more
metal
other people might have more metal in
the brain stem
a lot of different situations
someone might have metals in the
emotional center of the brain
keep that in mind so we can have metals
in different areas some people may have
more mercury more leads somebody
somebody might have more aluminum more
copper somebody might have only copper
and a little bit of aluminum somebody
might have aluminum calcium
the bad one industrialized calcium
copper
lead arsenic cadmium and nickel somebody
might have just a ton of mercury
not literally a ton figuratively but a
lot of mercury
so that's the difference right there
okay and that's what changes
everything all right
so keep that in mind i see aj
all right we got some celery juice right
here
you guys we got some celery right here
i'm gonna pour it from the corner this
time see when i'm back here my juicer's
in the way so i actually have to
pour it from the corner
smart
just laughing at myself
like usual all right so we got some
celery juice right here
how do you test which heavy metals you
have good question let's answer it
let me just cap this off you guys right
here
yep thank you for asking that question
i'm going to move this down here just
give me one second
nice how do you test what metals that
you like what metals you have here's
here's how it works to begin with metals
sit inside organs so you can't test for
all the metals and you can't test for
every metal in the body it doesn't work
like that so that's important to know
right so
if you guys just came on here make sure
you have cleanse the heel when you can
get it free at the library
um amazon.com 51 off the heavy metal
detox cleanse is in here or day two of
the heavy metal detox cleanse challenge
so just so you know what we're doing
right
so when you get a heavy metal detox test
they're testing a quick snapshot of time
they're testing your blood a quick
snapshot of time is what they're doing
they're getting some blood in the moment
at that part of the body right
so when you're getting your blood tested
okay
if you ever have an ink have you ever
had a tattoo just assume you got toxic
heavy metals in the organs
because that's what the ink is it's got
all these metals in it we'll talk about
that in a second again
but if you had your blood tested
for toxic heavy metals it's a snapshot
it's just a window meanwhile metals can
build up in your organs for years but
you don't see it in the blood test so
when they do take a blood test and they
see some that's just what's floating
around in their bloodstream in that
moment
they can't go and do a brain biopsy on
you so they can't be like hold on mister
hold on mr wilson
we're going to see how many we're going
to knock you out under general
anesthesia
and uh
we're going to do a brain biopsy on you
right now don't worry we're gonna knock
you out okay we knocked you out you're
you're under anesthesia now let's just
cut open the skull and let's do a brain
biopsy
and we're gonna get that biopsy and now
we're gonna study that on how many heavy
metals you are you have and here's the
problem even with that so even if they
could do that
they're going to pick a spot in the
brain that the metals aren't even in
your metals can be located anywhere they
can be anywhere they can they can biopsy
the wrong side they can
the metals can be anywhere inside the
brain they can't go and dissect your
brain while you're under anesthesia
you'll never come out of it if they
dissect your brain and cut everything
open and look for it it's not going to
happen
so
it's impossible to measure metals is
what i'm trying to say unless you drank
a
a gallon of lead
lead water
and you had lead poisoning and you
literally were going into neurological
seizure and coma and you're in the
hospital they know you have lead
poisoning
they can test out lead really high in
your bloodstream because you just got
the lead but you but other than that if
we don't have that kind of exposure
then what we're dealing with is we never
know there is no analysis or test that
could determine how many metals we have
in every organ inside our brain inside
our liver or anything else
you start getting alzheimer's you got
metals really bad
a hair analysis doesn't do it do the
trick either
a hair analysis is not going to tell you
how much lead you have in your liver how
much mercury you have in different parts
of your brain how many how much
mercury's in your spleen how much
aluminum's in your pancreas how much
aluminum is underneath your derma how
like nothing like you're not gonna get
any answers for that
i'm just gonna since i brought this up
i'm not telling you to remove your
tattoos i saw a bunch of comments
yesterday and everybody's like oh crap i
gotta get my tattoos removed
you don't have to get your tattoos
removed you don't you just have to be
proactive on catching the metals as they
leave your derma into your bloodstream
because for the rest of your life
they're gonna leave your derma into the
bloodstream they're gonna soak down down
through
and if you go and get a tattoo today and
you hop into like a hipster
tattoo place
you know it's real like like totally you
know i don't know hollywood boulevard
hipster tattoo place that you've been
recommended to you because they got the
best vegan non-cruelty ink
you're just completely just you know
you're you're it's distant for
misinformation because there's no such
thing
you have to have metal in the ink to get
that color to pop so light hits it and
it pops
you have to have that christie seriously
i'm serious there is none
so
what happens is that you have to have
it's all metal it's all metal
it's all minerals
but not the good kind so your ink is
filled with all metal
yeah i don't care who says we had ours
tested there's no metals in it no no no
no both i call bs
i call bs
industrialized metals and they're
they're they're
it's fine particles it's nano it's
actually under it's like septo
it's like septo right
so you need to know that
that metal is like septo size
so that's what it is that's an entirely
different size right that's crazy small
so what it is is that's what is inside
the ink and that's what makes the light
hit it so you hit the the light goes and
hits your skin and then it pops so you
guys will give you a rundown now and
everything
all right
let's do it
16 to 16 to 32 ounces of lemon water you
guys know the drill wait 15 to 30
minutes going to 16 to 32 ounces of
celery juice
wait
another 15 to 30 minutes
get your smoothie going that's what
we're going to do right now
smoothie time
let's have some fun
where are my bananas
right here
we got the bananas we're going to throw
a couple of bananas in here
okay
glucose
delivers
the phytochemical compounds and the
antioxidants and everything else that
have to get to your brain and liver and
other organs you gotta have the banana
don't be afraid of banana
unless you hate banana then okay put
mango in there
you hate banana but man
here's the thing like all these
alternatives are in here
just so you know they're all in here
on what you can do that's what's amazing
okay
all right so we got a couple of bananas
in there let's get the wild blueberries
in here here are the wild blueberries
right here
that's why blueberry time
here we go
put about two cups in here
so i'm dropping that in here you guys
right frozen wild blueberries
if you don't have wild blueberries use
blackberries but they're not going to do
the same thing but it's the closest
thing we can we can use if you don't
have an option the key is to have three
out of these five ingredients if
possible shoot for three out of five
shoot for four out of five shoot for
five out of five would be really
incredible
but if you only have three out of five
that's what you have then
we got the wild blueberry in there
cilantro get about a cup in there
let's do about a cup in there right i'm
gonna break some up throw it in here
right
elky said i love this guy
well i'm honored
all right
we got this
okay we gotta hear that
let's let's go here
we're gonna put
we got the cilantro in here now we're
going to squeeze some orange in here
okay that's next
you guys can see that going in there
all right let's squeeze some orange in
here
okay
there we go you can see it on the
close-up
some orange
whoa
okay okay
all right i'm gonna squeeze the rest of
this orange in
there we go
plenty
all right now i'm gonna drop some wild
blueberry powder in here it's a vimergy
wild blueberry powder that's what i like
to do now listen if you just have the
blueberries use just the blueberries
meaning the wild blueberries incredible
right
i'm gonna drop some of this in here this
stuff is like gold it's incredible right
drop a little bit in there
you guys don't have to do it my way
okay it's not my way or the highway here
medical medium information isn't that
it's what what can you do
i support you what can you do lemon
water and that's it
i'm with you 100
lemon water and that's it spirulina's
next i want to show you the how
incredible the spirulina is right here
okay i just want to give you guys a
little window
this stuff is incredible
i'm just showing you right there that's
going in i'm going to do about a
teaspoon right there
it's not my way or the highway
it's what can you do can you do
a little bit of lemon water what can you
do i'm gonna drop in some while wild
some barley grass juice powder next
right here
medical medium info is about going as
far as you need to go when you want to
go and when you want to do it it's about
going as far as you want to go
and when
yes let's talk about the lymphatic
system once i get this smoothie going i
want to talk about the lymphatic system
there's a lot of misinformation about
the lymphatic system out there and quite
frankly it's it's kind of embarrassing
at this point
and and and a nuisance too because it
interferes with people's healing so i
can't wait to cover that for a minute
so i'm going to put
now the dulce liquid
right there
i'm going to put a shot of that in
you could do one or two dropper fulls
i might even throw a little whole piece
in there too just a little whole piece
of
there we go
right
and then
i'm going to put a little bit of this in
here too i mean people that don't even
have the wild blueberries but they can
get a hold of a wild blueberry juice
that's that's the way to go right
you can go do that option
it doesn't mean go to the store and buy
a blueberry juice because the blueberry
juice is not going to be the same thing
it's going to be wild blueberry
now you guys know i do work
with wyman's
i do work with wyman's
okay
because the process of what they do i'm
supportive 100 i endorse them i work
with them on this important pouring a
little bit in there right
i like to take a swig of that right now
all right
i think we got what we need in here
we're loaded up
that's the smoothie right there let's
give it a blend
and we'll talk about the lymphatic
system for a couple of minutes let's
turn this puppy on
here we go
all right
let's get the blender off before we
that's why we're live
[Music]
i've been known to be a menace in the
kitchen
you don't want me in your kitchen
okay
[Music]
if you don't want to mess
[Applause]
only person out there that clarifies who
they work with the transparency and
honesty
um
starch with plant starch with plants
that will handle the brand of wild
blueberries honestly
live it
the wild blueberry powder
emergency
i love the wild blueberry powder
this thing's blended
right let's get this let's get this
plated
so i got the smoothie all made right
here i am lining it up to the nice
camera shot there there we go filling it
up
we have
heavy metal detox smoothie right there
the anti anti-madness creator
that's what this is
about getting people's lives back on
track getting them out of ocd getting
them out of bipolar getting them out of
the personalization getting them out of
anxiety depression
all of it getting them out of just
a deep sense of sadness and they don't
know why they have the sadness i've
watched for years i've watched for years
something that happens to people like
they have this deep sense of sadness
they they're not sure if it's a
depression but they don't really know
they just it's a sense of like
sadness right so then they go to a
therapist and the therapist is trying to
crack them
so then the therapist is trying to crack
them tell me about your life
like whoa i'm like this is what i do
this is what i you know this is my life
and i'm like okay well let's find out
where the problem is right there's
nothing wrong with that right you go to
the therapist
and then there's that therapist the deep
sense of sadness doesn't end up
resolving so now they're at a
psychiatrist right then they're then
then from there they're at their doctor
and that doctor's doing a work up and
taking blood out of them and more blood
out of them and making them sicker right
and then now they're going from the
doctor to another doctor but they have
this deep sense of sadness right and
then their family's like why are you so
sad why are you so sad then they go find
a psychic
and then the psychic says that they're
sad because in their past life they had
their head chopped off under queen
victoria of whatever year and whatever
whatnot or they were burned alive at the
stake as a witch or their sadness is
because they were on the titanic and
they went down the titanic went down and
they were one of the people that died on
the titanic in their past lives and
that's why they have this deep sadness
meanwhile the whole time
it's toxic heavy metals eating away at
their brain and that sadness becomes
something worse down the road unless
they address the toxic heavy metals and
something worse than something worse so
then when they have a real serious
problem down the road with their brain
20 years down the road okay and now it's
serious like some serious craps going on
no one knew it was a toxic heavy metals
but they thought all these years is
because of one of their past lives they
died on the titanic
[Music]
snack on some apples that's part of this
metal detox cleanse
okay snap on some apples we're gonna
talk about the lymphatic system let's
run across that with a little bit
lymphatic system
we're on it
oh
very careful the guts of this dummy just
fall right out
okay
lymphatic system time you'll see some
lymphatic vessels somewhere right here
say the lymphatic vessels here
some little lymph nodes some lymphatic
vessels there we are right
if you hear
from facebook groups that are not
authentic facebook groups of medical
medium where it's not the medical medium
authentic
right
facebook group and you've got these so
what happens is you get medical medium
fans that eventually create
not all of them do this but they
eventually create a facebook group right
over the years
they create a facebook group and then
they start changing everything they
start trying to indoctrinate the people
coming in they make it look like it's
all medical medium they make it look
like medical medium doesn't know what
he's talking about anymore and they just
get people in so they can sell all their
stuff right all their lymphatic tonics
and all kinds of crazy stuff and then
what happens is people go into the group
the group gets bigger and bigger and
bigger and it becomes kind of like this
half-like medical medium yeah i kind of
like them in this half i kind of hate
them
and it becomes this group that is just a
smorgasbord of like nothing but
misinformation some haters
some naysayers people don't even read
the books or the medical medium books
they never even read any of the books
and it becomes this just big colossal
cluster
and that's what it is right
and so
in these groups in some of these groups
under each other you're saying yes yes
yes you've seen this over and over again
yeah i know
so i just have to bring this up because
here's one of the colossal screw-ups
that are happening now is
you can't do the heavy metal detox
cleanse unless you cleanse your
lymphatic system get lymphatic drainage
and lymphatic massage that's the most
ridiculous thing i've ever heard in my
life
and so people will be like wait a minute
i'm afraid do i even start the heavy
metal ones meanwhile the person's
suffering they got anxiety they got
depression they got all kinds of
problems they're sick they got you mean
i can't do the heavy metal detox cleanse
unless i do what with my lymphatic
system buy your lymphatic products
okay so i'm in this new facebook group
right now and i'm gonna now buy all your
lymphatic system products too let me
spend a fortune a thousand dollars on
all of your lymphatic products because
you're telling me i can't do the heavy
metal detox movie unless i clear my
lymphatic system
and oh by the way i better pay for and
buy your program too your thousand
dollar program that i'm gonna have to
buy as well because you seem to know
more than the medical medium does
because the medical medium is not saying
that you have to cleanse and drain and
do this with your lymphatic system
before doing the heavy metal detox
smoothie
and that's the information out there
that goes screwed up happens in all
these
places dana white
says it's because they're selling a
lymphatic reset program 100 true right
so what you have is you have all these
like i used to call baby sharks but
right now i just call basically just
i don't know what name i could name them
now right i don't want to like
you know how you're just like you just
you don't want to stoop down to their
level you guys know it's right you don't
want to stoop down to your level and be
like say something really bad
right but when their intention is really
dark
and they're misleading people and they
stare people off off the deep end
instead they're the wrong direction and
they end up not helping them but they
want to sell them their whatever
you can't you know you it's it's just
crazy how it works right
but they use medical medium to bring
these people down so they're using
medical medium to bring these people
down they use medical medium to lure
them in and then they use medical medium
to bring them down right so let's talk
about the lymphatic system
the heavy metal detox cleanse or
smoothie and celery juice
or lemon water
is cleaning up your liver
when you clean up your liver the
lymphatic system automatically gets
cleaned up so your lymphatic system
automatically gets cleaned up
anything you're doing for your lymphatic
system doesn't fix the problem
it doesn't and no one even can measure
if it's helping the lymphatic system
they can't see your lymphatic system
you can take a lymphatic system tonic
it's not going to fix it or help it
there's no anything that shows
that it would or could
it's someone's idea i guess out there
that oh lymphatic system this will help
so the point is is that they'll tell you
you can't start the metal cleanse or
anything unless you address the
lymphatic system right it's false
information of the worst kind and it's
misleading first of all the heavy metal
detox smoothie that you would drink if
you're doing this to see this metal
smoothie right there
goes into the liver and it starts to
restore it
as your liver is restoring the lymphatic
system is automatically restoring
because your lymphatic system is going
to be
not great because your liver is stagnant
and sluggish it's the dumping ground so
your lymphatic system is the trash
ground for a bad liver for a liver
that's stagnant and sluggish and dirty
so when you're doing the heavy metal
detox
you're cleaning up
right your liver
so then the sewer system lymphatic
system gets cleaned up automatically
that's the whole point so by saying no
you have to buy my lymphatic program
and you have to subscribe and buy all my
stuff and products and lymphatic before
you can even do medical medium because
medical medium doesn't know
he doesn't know better i know better
than him so i'm gonna sell you my my
lymphatic programs right
and that's where the confusion gets
right there it's really terrible
and
i get it you know
there's a lot of sharks baby sharks out
there that's what it is lots of them a
lot of baby sharks in the medical mean
community that healed from medical
medium information they're still using
it now but then they leave and they kick
like they kick medical medium down as
they're leaving they step on them and
spit on them and then they go because
they're just like no i want to sell my
whatever my ionizer water machine i want
to sell my fulvic acid i want to sell my
humic acid i want to sell my shilajit i
want to sell them whatever i'm going to
mlm into
so the liver is just the lymphatic
system is an overflow of your liver so
your liver has to clean up and that's
what this does so when you do your
celery juice you do your lemon water
right here and you do your your heavy
metal detox smoothie right or if you're
just using a little bit of spirulina
every day or however you want to do it
and customize the way you want to do
you're cleaning up your liver inevitably
it cleans up your lymphatic system is
what it does
key information right there just so you
know
so
you'll see this out there all the time
and the problem is they won't get
censored but i will so facebook will
censor me but facebook won't censor them
so their group gets bigger and bigger
with the misinformation
and that's the way life works but i
think darkness just finds its way to
kind of like create these situations
and it's just it's it's interesting
but hey we work for the light and we got
to remember that okay the other thing
too is these other places they become
cults you know so what happens is they
become cults
in so many ways because they're the ones
making all these darn roles they're
making roles that are like
crazy
and you have to pay in those cults right
you have to pay that's how crazy it
works too
because now you're in fear and you
better get that lymphatic protocol
programmed for a thousand dollars you
better get something out you know what i
mean and that's how just so you think
they prey on sick people
and that's that's what happens
when your lymphatic system
when your liver gets really really
sluggish and stagnant and really dirty
and it's dumping in into your
bloodstream and it's dumping into
everything it's not just
a lymphatic system when your liver is
really dirty it overflows and it dumps
into everything and then we get
sensitive
and sensitive and people get sensitive
and it's not even the lymphatic system
causing a problem that's the other
problem so people don't realize that
their lymphatic system is not giving
them any problems
they're sick from nervous system
problems they're sick from vagus nerve
problems they're sick from neurological
issues they're sick from pathogens
they're sick from all these things
they're not sick because their lymphatic
system is an issue that's another reason
why it's so screwed up of what they're
doing they're trying to get someone kind
of mental about their lymphatic system
when their lymphatic system has nothing
to do with why they're sick to begin
with and has nothing to do with why
they're sensitive nothing to do with why
they're neurologically feeling pain and
their suffering nothing to do with their
symptoms nothing to do with their
anxiety or anything like that
nothing you can have somebody
got somebody with a real lymphatic
problem like severe lymphoedema
right some something separate
you have somebody with that and they
won't have anxiety they won't have
anything else they won't have any of
these problems doesn't mean so what they
do is they take all these symptoms and
conditions everybody's suffering with
and then they'll say whoa i can totally
i can manipulate them saying this is a
medical medium facebook group i can
manipulate them get them in and then i
could tell them that all their symptoms
and all their suffering is their
lymphatic system or something and i
could make a crap boatload of money
perfect and i'll get a bunch of
administrators in that facebook group so
the administrators traders are like yeah
anthony doesn't know what he's talking
about yeah anthony doesn't know what
he's talking about yeah anthony doesn't
know good we got you in here pay this
thousand dollars for our program he
doesn't know about this
sick all right let's give you a rundown
today is day two of the medical medium
heavy metal detox cleanse challenge
we're also having personal talks here
about all kinds of stuff
do you have the free book go to the
library for free
library for free do you how many people
go to the library
a lot
a lot i think it's like 80 percent of
the people that
get the medical mean books get it for
free at the library and that's the way i
love it right there okay you want it at
amazon it's also on sale at the amazon
right now incredible sale on this book
medical textbook
all right i'd rather do this
and you get the book for free then
charge you a 3 500 program to teach you
how to get rid of medals
which i think is just ridiculous i could
teach you for free a little bit at a
time and get the book okay and i don't
control the price on amazon they knocked
it down so low that it cost more to
print the book isn't that nice of them i
will tell you this i really think it's
angelic intervention i believe the
angels intervened with amazon
to cut the book so low in price
regardless of whatever happens whether i
can keep lights on or not
all right whether i can keep the
utilities going
it doesn't matter i really think it's
angelic intervention they made the price
51 off on this massive textbook
on amazon i think it's it's incredible
anyway listen you guys
enjoy your smoothie i shall enjoy your
celery juice enjoy everything i'm gonna
go to instagram we're gonna have some
fun
we'll head there
okay tic toc i'm turning you guys back
on and i'm turning telegram back on oh
wait before you guys go
press any likes and follows or whatever
you got you know on the videos whatever
is there i don't know exactly how it
works right the other thing is check out
my exclusive tic toc videos oh my god
i put a tick tock video out today
please everybody go and watch it i'm
asking because it's really informative
i'm talking about the vagus nerve again
i just posted it three hours ago i don't
know what it is two hours ago i talked
about nausea i talked about okay i
talked about
dysphagia nausea i talked about the
vagus nerve check it out on tick-tock
it's an exclusive video if you guys can
go watch that and then we're gonna go
live on instagram and i'm gonna put
tick-tock back on i talked about chest
tightening and i went into a little bit
more detail and after you're done there
i'm asking too much am i asking too much
you guys i'm probably asking too much
i'm really sorry like i apologize
seriously but if you can go after you go
from there
you can check out
my snapchat exclusive video okay and my
newsletter i got to this video sign up
to my newsletter too when you can i got
videos little videos going out to you
guys every sunday if you don't get the
video and you signed up to newsletter
check your promotions and your spam
it's a lot to cover
we got to do it though
okay go to your desktop computer if you
don't get the the newsletter for some
reason and check your spam promotions on
your desktop it's free it's free
it's free i'm not going to do the robot
right now
well i can do the robot i might be able
to do the robot on ig
all right guys
i love you guys and i'll see you guys in
a little while what about half an hour
or something or whatever i'm heading to
ig