excited I had to come on again today
because I still can't believe it you
know the dedication in here for the
light that stands in the way of the
darkness and boy does it ever when you
see the incredible information inside
the brain saver books you know it's of
the light you know it's battling
Darkness you know it's protecting the
chronically ill you know it's fighting
for the chronically ill you see it you
feel it you can even hear it it's here
it's that powerful the books are here
I'm gonna read a little bit about toxic
heavy metals he can't help it but
seriously you guys
I mean I'm not kidding the power that's
in your hands with these books because
it's empowerment you don't want anyone
to control you you don't want an
industry to control you you don't want
someone to actually brainwash you you
don't want someone to control your
thoughts you don't want someone to
control what you do and control your
actions you want freedom and what
happens is when we get sick
and we don't know why we're sick we're
being controlled because now it's all
about doctors appointments and you got
to have a doctor that's great it's all
about doctor's appointments all about
doing you know it's all about I don't
know what to do I don't know what's
wrong with me what's going on and then
they just basically turn us into robots
and then we're just like gotta find
another doctor another doctor another
doctor or it's all day long another
doctor I got a doctor's appointment
they're going to take more blood they
don't know what's wrong autoimmune
they've got inflammatory markers showing
this is what's going on that's going on
you get diagnosis ever diagnosis and
then we head into this place where it's
not our life anymore it's like somebody
else's life it's somebody else kind of
puppeteering us controlling us in our
life it's the system it's the industries
that got you packaged up and if the
Freedom's critical Freedom away from
that is critical you guys Austin says I
love the robot
brain saver brain saver protocols right
here
they're jammed packed now I forewarn you
this is a little disclaimer right here
when you get the books
just know that every line is packed with
information
every sentence there's no cookie cutter
fluffer butter Nutter or anything in
these books it is sentence to sentence
to paragraph of life-changing powerful
Advanced comprehensive detailed
information from above far Advanced from
anything signs of research has they're
going to be poaching the out of
these books science and research the
clinics all the clinics you know the
mayonnaise Clinic all of them they're
going to be poaching poaching taking
podcast doctors are going to be poaching
and taking from these very books it's
like they've done the other books and
that's what they're going to do they
don't have any original information of
their own they don't have any
information about the brain besides
telomere and the fact that
we're all genetically whatever and then
we'll Neuroscience but they don't know
why people are sick they don't know why
people are struggling and they're going
to poach the out of these books
because they're so ahead of science and
research so ahead of the time and that's
what we're up against and when you hold
these books you're gonna know when you
read them you're going to know what's in
here it's about protecting your brain in
every way possible I am just so excited
I can't even tell you someone to read a
little bit about toxic heavy metals in a
second
but it's good for you guys to know how
to protect yourself what you know all of
it it's in here in the books right you
guys that talk about EMF in here stuff
that people don't don't know about EMF
that's the whole point I talk about
radiation stuff people don't know about
radiation I talk about the sea Trails
people don't know about I talk about
blood drawn here I talk about caffeine I
talk about alcohol I talk about eating
disorders now that's a whole other thing
eating disorders
when you read the eating disorder
chapter your mind's going to be blown so
I'm just preparing you for what you're
up against
and what you're doing I talk about micro
dosing in these books right so let me
just like cover just a couple little
things really quick in here santara is
healing good to see you always proud of
you too by the way santara and you you
actually post the coolest stuff just did
the adrenal stabilizer shot again and oh
my God it's actually insane how quick
they work actually a miracle
Sentara
I kid you not I mean when I do those
brain shot therapies it hits me fast now
as I was telling you guys before in the
earlier live today I was trying to
forewarn you in alternative medicine
and conventional medicine it's not about
instant relief right and alternative
medicine it's not about instant relief
no one's expecting no one's anticipating
instant relief I'm trying to prepare you
first of all medical medium information
between the celery juice and all and
heavy metal detox smoothies and a lot a
lot of people get instant relief with
all the stuff but when it comes down to
the brain shot Therapies
we're talking about an instant relief
people have never ever experienced
before so I'm trying to prepare you so
what that means is you're going to be
caught off guard
that's the whole point Center's healing
says it literally feels like a happy
drug
you're it's because of the synergistic
blend that Spirit of compassion created
because only Spirit of compassion knew
about what to put with what just the
right amount just the right way so that
when you took the brain shot therapies
you get the relief and the thing is I'm
trying to tell you because you may not
be prepared for it it may not be
expecting that relief so when it comes
it catches you off guard which could be
fine but I'm just forewarning you when
you do the brain shot therapies that's
really important so I just want to go
over those a little a little bit now too
you guys
when you get your books
just know
it's a heavy box so if you got to take
one out at a time take one out at a time
all right because I see some of you guys
the books are coming the Box thrown on
your doorstep and you grab the box and
you're like what the heck is this what
is this and so you know when you unpack
them take about one at a time right I
mean
and
what's crazy about it is the information
is here in here
it's literally every single sentence and
every paragraph right
[Music]
so I'm in here
Kim possibly said I am blown away at how
much you put in into these books you are
our true savior forever grateful and
thankful to you in SOC
I'm just the messenger
I'm just you know a dummy that's
that's making sure the information gets
in here and making sure I can actually
communicate that to you guys all right
SSC is the the smart one that's for sure
and you know that's the whole thing and
there are 30 brain shot Therapies
seven brain shot therapy cleanses
it's important to know all on its own
right so I'm just going over a little
bit of this
so let me get to it now brain shot
therapy cleanses right you guys the
books are so big you can just keep on
going through and going through them
there's so much information in here it
just it's incredible I want to go over
the shifters the stabilizers and the
exposures one more time with you guys
that's an exciting moment I can't help
it
so here we are I'm just trying to bring
this right to the top
got my little postage notes on here I've
always done that you guys medical medium
brain shot therapy medical meaning brain
shot therapy offers instant relief while
you're working to fix problems on a
deeper level in your brain and nervous
system and body your brain and body have
a quick response to medicinals delivered
in a liquid form what I call a shot
designed to be highly absorbable in the
mouth and that's one of the things
things I want to tell you about the
stabilizers the brain shot therapies the
stabilizers the shifters and the
exposures these are designed to be
highly absorbable it's one of the
reasons why the relief comes which is
incredible it's not just the
phytochemical compounds mixed the right
way
right it's about the fact that it's so
absorbable but it's it's the blend of
the ingredients that make it even more
absorbent inside the mouth and then in
the bloodstream these brain shots
they're valuable healing components can
reach the brain quick so the thing about
the medical medium brain shot therapy
and you'll see when you get your book
and you look into this
one of the things that's really
important
is that these specially formulated shots
have the ability to reset and rewire the
brain one of the reasons why it gives
you that relief okay
and they're designed to be highly
absorbable in the mouth these brain
shots valuable healing components reach
the brain quick and I wanted to say that
again because that's the whole point so
when you do the brain shots
they reach the brain fast
that's one of the gifts of it that's one
of the powerhouses of it it reaches the
brain quick so important to know right
there that's a really critical piece of
it
and then these specially formulated
shots have the ability to reset and
rewire the brain another reason why you
get so much relief right there on its
own
it can shock out the patterns while at
the same time reducing triggers check
this out they can shock out patterns and
that's the thing so many people have
patterns
and the patterns can be some bad
patterns it's not your fault not judging
anybody no one should be judged on
patterns but these brain shot therapies
can shock out patterns
while reducing triggers that's a huge
point right there so many people are up
against so many triggers they're being
triggered all the time
and this can shock someone out of that
and actually stop the triggers medical
medium brain shot therapy is Uncharted
Territory so you guys it's Uncharted
Territory just like all medical medium
information but man these brain shot
therapies is a whole other level these
are special configurations
synergistically combined just right to
crack the code of how the fruits herbs
leafy greens wild foods and vegetables
can work as medicine now here's what's
insane about the brain shot Therapies
it what happened with SOC and giving you
this information it was about cracking a
code
synergistically with combining the right
ingredients out of the wild Foods out of
the fruits out of the leafy greens out
of the vegetables and the herbs to
actually make it work so you get that
powerful relief
it just blows me away while Creative
Juice concoctions have their place in
human creativity in the kitchen should
be honored and that's true people can
throw a bunch of things together and
juice it or whatever there's a big
difference here it's not what you will
find here these brain shots
aren't just tasty Delights thrown
together for a fun experiment instead
these are gifted
combinations that literally will change
your life
the healing shots of medical medium
brain shot therapy are tools that come
from above
above
these brain shots are composed of
specific combinations of ingredients
working together
systematically for specific reasons that
only a source above could know
the relationships among these
ingredients are intricate and unknown to
anyone
hands down these are the greatest books
of health history
and science and research will never
touch these besides poaching from them
but they'll never be able to compete
with this for the future this is
literally the books for The Chronic Leo
until now this knowledge from above has
remained untapped so what that means is
I sat my ass in my office chair
and spirit of compassion said it's time
because this is what's happened in the
world whom I can only do so much I'm
only one person one messenger and spirit
of compassion said with just these brain
books have to be what they are they have
to be that volume is
they have to be that jacked up
they have to have that much information
healing information
and we have to get people better
so let's go over the brain shot therapy
list
Holly's Health says I did out my old
shot glass you got out your old shot
glasses that I used to use for tequila
laugh out loud that's actually great
though I'm glad you got those ones out
it's amazing Michelle says science
research needs the ego shifter indeed
they do
so they do
the brain shot therapy list I'll give
you a little rundown on that for a
second you guys good to see you guys
we're live right now brain shot therapy
list exposures pathogen exposure brain
shot so I'll just I'll just talk a
little bit about it too let me find the
exposure shots let's just do it pathogen
exposure you ready
you feel you've been around others who
could be contagious due to the Sea
the flu or mono
you're concerned about having shared
bodily fluids with another person
through shared glasses bottles food
utensils or plates
you're concerned about having shared
bodily fluids through public restrooms
or sexual activity
you believe you might have been exposed
to foodborne pathogens and you're
concerned about getting food poisoning
that's just a few powerful reasons why
the pathogen exposure right there is
there so then boom you said you think
you got any kind of exposure and it's
like boom you're sending down the
pathogen exposure now I'm going to talk
about toxic heavy metals on the brain
hence in the brain we're going to go
into that in a couple of minutes but I
just wanted to give you guys a quick
rundown on some of the different okay
mold exposure right there so the mold
exposure shots
now
I said this the other day if this is the
only reason why you buy it by the brain
books or get them free in the library
when they're in the library or whatever
if this is the only time you get the
brain you know only reason the mold
exposure then let it be the mold
exposure like
that alone is worth having these in your
hand to know this so the mold exposure
shop a helpful shot for any kind of mold
or mildew exposure including when you
have been visiting or living in a moldy
house or building
working in a moldy office or other
workplace
inhaling mold off another person's
clothing
people don't realize it but they're
inhaling mold on other people's clothing
you go into the store you're inhaling
all their mold and mildew off their
clothing from their home right
consuming water contain contaminated
with mildew or mold spores or eating
moldy food that's when you bring out the
mold exposure shot you're like boom you
bring that out boom you got your shot
glass boom you get that quick hit that
really boom you send it down
I know a lot of people are worried about
EMF and 5G it's like 5G what about 5G aw
what about 5G I've been hearing it right
for years
so I got an EMF and 5G exposure shot
which is really powerful on its own
try this shot
if you spend a lot of time on computers
and computerized devices hmm
[Applause]
spend a lot of time on computers and
computerized devices
so it's like yeah you better believe it
gonna be doing that shot
or if you live near a high voltage area
a lot of people live near high voltage
areas
spend time talking or texting on cell
phones like
[Music]
right traveling by plane this is a great
time to take this shot send this shot
glass down right
live or work close to others while
they're using devices spend your day
within several feet of a router
live near a cell tower
all those are the reasons right there
for the brain shot therapy EMF and 5G
exposure now we're going to be talking
about the toxic metal stuff let's go
into that right now I just wanted to
give you guys just a couple of the 30
shots now we have 30 shots brain shot
therapy we have seven brain shot therapy
cleanses actual cleanses you can do with
the shots which is really cool all on
its own
so that's really exciting
so we're in the medical medium heavy
metal detox now I talk about Metals
throughout the book in various places
and throughout the protocols book too so
right there so I'm in the brain saver
book you guys are getting some of your
books right you guys are excited that's
the protocols book let me just put that
out in the front a little bit so you can
see it
both these books equally powerful
equally packed with information equally
important both of them they were one
book and they had to become two they
were too big it was too big for one book
to publish to print way too big
medical medium heavy metal detox so I
want to just mention something about
here this is mind-blowing information
from above
now medical medium information is always
the most advanced with toxic heavy
metals and always has been in fact it
paved the way fact
it paved the way for the metal
information that we have now
including the dental stuff
I remember over 30 years ago being in a
dental conference is actually trying to
forewarn and tell people about those
Mercury amalgams
and I got the crap beat out of me for it
because no one was against the Mercury
malcolms they are filling people see
they do it now they even have that for
now for people's teeth they offer it but
the point is it was considered fine and
not harmful and I really took quite a uh
bashing for fighting for that one and
fighting for that one and traveling
around the country and fighting for that
one
a long time ago so that people aren't
getting Mercury fillings today in their
teeth so medical medium was a big part
of making sure that people aren't
getting still those fillings right so
but this is really incredible here this
information here so minus that
heavy metals that we inherit have aged
to them they're old
that statement alone is critical to know
that is a powerful statement already a
piece of information and that's just one
line
of this Advanced information one line
heavy metals that we inherit we inherit
in our family lines you guys passed down
from generation to generation to
generation right
they have aged to them
just think about that for a second
the metal in your system
is old
think about that
the metal in your brain
giving you your schizophrenia your
bipolar diagnosis your OCD your
depersonalization your depression your
anxiety and all the other stuff ADHD
your autism all these things we get the
medical medium first let the world know
causes those conditions those Metals so
when you hear it out there it was
poached here
heavy metals that we inherit have aged
to them they're old many times going
back as far as two thousand to three
thousand years so that means the toxic
heavy metals that are being passed down
from generation to generation
could be two to three thousand years old
in your family line going all the way
back
you'll be hearing this once these books
are out out you'll be hearing this
everywhere you'll hear it on podcast
you'll hear it in different places they
won't cite where it comes from
check this out
depending on what part of the world
someone's bloodline stems from too so
ready
older heavy metals also have a higher
oxidative rate than heavy metals from
newer exposures that's another sentence
in this book now take a look at both
these books
and the sizes of these books you guys
are getting them now in the mail okay
I read you two sentences
that are so far advanced in information
and mind-blowing
two sentences right check this out
older heavy metals also have a higher
oxidative rate than heavy metals from
newer exposures now first of all how
would we know they even oxidized well
that's medical medium information
originally but you you'll hear it out
there now
the older Metals oxidize faster they
have a higher rate of oxidation now that
means if you have these old inherited
Metals it's oxide oxidizing faster
send you into Alzheimer's dementia
depression anxiety whatever it's sending
you into all kinds of different
conditions
the aging process of toxic heavy metals
that were mined mined meaning mind from
the earth dug out of the earth machines
digging it out right people digging it
out throughout throughout time
the aging process of toxic heavy metals
that were mined many generations ago
started when the metals were removed
from the earth now this is something
science and research has no idea about
neither does any
professional or a podcast doctor or
whoever or somebody in Harvard or
whatever they don't know this they don't
know that when a toxic heavy metal was
removed from the earth a thousand years
ago 200 years ago 500 years ago it
already started oxidizing because oxygen
hit it
oxygen hit it
it was pulled out of the Earth where
there was no oxygen it was mined out of
the Earth
you see how mind-blowing this is when I
heard this from Spirit of compassion and
I was trying to get this in the books
like I was just like okay I gotta sit
back with that one for a second oh my
God I got to sit back with that one for
a second
think about how advanced it is
so when the toxic heavy metal was mined
out of the earth like Mercury a thousand
years ago it already started to oxidize
whoa
an oxidative countdown occurred so it
was a countdown then the countdown
started one Mississippi two Mississippi
three Mississippi four it started when
it was mined out of the Earth
a countdown occurred as Metals aged
those Metals became highly unstable when
they entered and sat inside human bodies
where metals are exposed to more oxygen
acids heat blood gases electricity
outside chemicals and more so when a
metal sits inside your body you guys
it's exposed to oxygen inside your body
acids heat blood gases electricity
inside your body
and more
so the older Metals pulled out of the
Earth the countdown of oxidation already
occurred then it got into the human body
that's the whole point it got into us
what do you think the Emperors of China
they were all poison to death because
the medicine in Chinese medicine culture
was Mercury
it was Mercury
everybody thinks it was this ingenious
natural
mushrooms it wasn't it was Mercury
that was their number one medicine up
until the 1800s was mercury in early
1900s actually
so in Chinese medicine culture it was
Mercury to give you that was that was
the whole point it was all Mercury and
so it gets passed on down but Mercury
was used in all cultures around the
world eventually as medicine so Mercury
got into all cultures around the world
right
it's important to know
new Metals differ greatly from old
metals
newer Metals differ greatly from old
Metals new metal exposure you guys the
new metal exposures you're getting all
the time like copper you want to drink
out of the copper cups the new fancy
copper cups now right the thermoses
whatever that are made out of copper
it's that's NuMe heavy metal exposure
newer Metals recently mined that's new
copper
that's new steel new copper new aluminum
whatever it's just all the different
Metals it's new newer Metals recently
mined and taken out of the Earth are
still highly toxic although they are
more stable here's the thing so newer
toxic heavy metal exposure still causes
problems and makes us sick but it's more
stable it's more stable than the older
metals making them less destructive is
older Metals but you have to get this
though check out this you guys I'm in
the brain saver books if you just got
here
lock down a copy when you can
foreign
newer Metals don't break down inside the
body as quickly it all depends on how
many generations the metals have been
passed down through and how much metal
is in each individual most people have a
mix of older metals and newer metals and
it brings us to another part here most
people who are sick depersonalization
depression 10 different ways to Sunday
anxiety and panic 10 different ways to
Sunday bipolar any other kind of of
diagnosis all of it
is metals
but a blend of newer and older the
newest metal exposure is when a child
gets something
can't read that in you can't read that
you guys I have to not read any of that
out here you gotta check out the book
most likely the Mercury and aluminum
were Unearthed in the last 50 to 70
years so here's the problem too so any
kind of new toxic heavy metal exposure
that you guys are getting it's been
mined out of the earth 50 to 70 years
ago
so 50 to 70 years ago
saved in storage and eventually
purchased by a medical industry or a
place inside a pharmaceutical or some
other kind of industry many medications
have toxic heavy metals in them and at
the same time
can't read you the rest of that
not on here
anyway bottom line you guys were talking
about Advanced information detailed
comprehensive just about metals that
nobody knows science of research or
anywhere else that's critical to know
and we're in it we're in the brain saver
book and brain saver protocols book you
guys and you guys if you get a chance if
you got your book whatever leave her you
know you've got both books I mean leave
a review if you get a chance on Amazon
that would be great
you beat out the trolls
that helps
both books would be amazing so if you do
leave a review if you like the book If
you like what's in it if you like the
recipes if you open the book and you see
some recipes you like leave a review
that would be great because it helps
other people find the book so they can
get the information and I got a new
podcast episode coming out tonight I
know a lot of you guys look forward to
the podcast I do I look forward to the
podcast episodes that are coming out
medical medium podcast episodes and yeah
so the new episode is coming out tonight
I hope you actually listen to it if you
get a chance right
okay so you guys we're also in the
middle of the brain saver challenge
we're on the second day of the brain
saver challenge did you sign up it's
free free free
and I make some brain shot therapies
during the brain saver Challenge and I'm
doing the light infusion meditation
so I'm doing the light infusion
meditation
so I hope you catch that one you only
get 24 hours to listen to or see sorry
see the brain saver challenge video so
if you missed it on the first 24 out if
you missed the first one first 24 hours
are today if you don't see the second
one today then you're gonna miss both of
them
and you're gonna miss out on some really
cool stuff
so tomorrow's the third day of the brain
saver challenge
and the day after that's the fourth day
where we do the light infusion
meditation so I'm hoping you guys do
that with me because I'm going to do it
with you guys
so that's going to be really fun a dot m
dot says aw thinks you're spoiling us so
I try my best I try my best ciao
emotional brain is in
the book to a chapter on it which is
really incredible anyway you guys
so much information I can only scratch
the surface we're just talking about a
little bit about heavy metals inside the
brain we're talking about old Metals
versus newer metals and then people
having a combination and how it works
oxidation and all of that and that leads
obviously to so many conditions and
symptoms
the books have over 300 symptoms
conditions 100 over 100 recipes that are
for the brain santara thank you for
everything too
and yeah you can't go wrong when you get
empowered with information it's really
really helpful to heal
so anyway you guys
I will see you again hopefully tomorrow
keep a lookout hopefully you get the
notification and I'll see you guys soon
love you guys greatly