[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is De
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 or 20 years to
wait for answers to their illnesses life
is precious and there's no time to spare
let's get started now Today's Show is
about gene mutation the
mtfr gene mutation this is an important
show it's going to be an historic show
in many ways because what you're going
to hear is
mindblowing if you're a connoisseur of
genes or gene mutations mtfr gene
mutations and I'm not saying that it's
going to be a show with information
about genes and how they work and how
they're they're connected to us it's not
going to be there instead it's going to
be protecting you against Gene fraud
okay and that's something really it's
critical to understand Gene fraud and
what that means is things that are
created so you think your body is
destroying itself that your body is
attacking itself that your genes are
faulty that your genes are useless that
your genes are attacking you or or
melting down on you so that you don't
have a chance to heal and that's the
weakness that's thrown on us so if
you're a gene expert you hang on to your
seat you're either going to hate me
after the show or or you're going to you
know keep in one eye open and one ear
open and you're going to be like hey you
know what that makes sense because this
is that important the show totally so
that's that's what we're talking about
today remember to go to my website
medical medium.com if you guys haven't
been there go and and and there's all
kinds of stuff going on one of the you
know Facebook we I put out information
every single day Instagram the Instagram
is is really going great I mean all
kinds of people and their healing
experiences and what you'll find on the
social media that's involved with IAL
medium is you're not going to see
pictures of me 24/7 you're not going to
see oh here's Anthony doing this or
here's Anthony William doing that and
that's all great and I and I and I love
when people do that what you're going to
see instead is people in their stories
people healing people getting better
people's lives changing people making
recipes people taking care of themselves
people getting the best out of their
life people's lives that are changing
you're going to see all that because
here's the deal this is about you it's
not about me I've been saying that for
years this is about you it's not about
me and and so just know that this is
about you healing and I've been the
voice for people who have a chronic
illness who can't get out of bed who
can't function who can't do whatever
they need to do and can't get answers
and been the voice for you know you for
the people that need that voice and need
the answers and that's what it's about
so when you go to my Instagram
you'll see that and when you go to the
you know the Facebook you'll see that
and you go to the website and everything
else so check it all out look into my
healing path too my healing path is it
has amazing Audios in there and recipes
and everything else to help you change
your life the audios are from me me
speaking and talking but in the way that
you need the information you need so you
can heal and then tell others and how to
heal and everything else so it's about
you guys and that's the the key so
anyway and hey look you know if if this
the first time on the show it all
started for me at age 4 when I heard a
voice perfectly clear it led me to the
diagnosis of my grandmother I've
dedicated my entire life um to helping
people tens of thousands of people get
the answers they need so that's more
about me I hear a voice that tells me
what's going on and and we're going to
go into the whole Gene thing right now
so the so let's start so fasten your
seat belt you know get ready
fasten that seat belt hold on hold on to
your seat because um this is a big deal
today and maybe some of you don't even
know about the gene mutation thing maybe
you know you haven't heard it or or
you're just done you're not aware of it
or anything like that but the MTHFR gene
mutation is taking the World by storm in
holistic medicine at this point and if I
go with the ride
and just you know hop on that ride hop
on that
Trend um it's going to do you an
injustice it really is you need to know
this so I'm going to explain where I sit
with this where it has its good place or
it's good points and where it's
completely backwards in a way that's not
good at all for you your well-being for
your children and for your family so
this is really important to understand
so see you know I'm not against every
Trend in fad that's you know that's not
it I mean look the celery juice Trend
that started from me and everybody's
doing now and it's going everywhere it's
just it's it's crossing the Earth right
now that's a trend that came from me
okay so yeah I'm not going to be against
the celery juice Trend because a you
know Spirit created it but there and I'm
not against other trends that are out
there too that someone else came up with
somehow or figured it out through Maybe
a scientific thing that then became
trendy I support a lot of different
Trends too but there's some that there's
there's no way it it deserves the
support the support from me it doesn't
one of the things that we got here is
this gene mutation
so what what is an Mt you know MTHFR
gene mutation it's the inability to
convert folate so that's the thing it's
the inability to convert folate that's
what you're going to hear out there so
when you look into it you dial it up on
your computer or you talk to a doctor or
practitioner it's going to be this
inability to convert fate or folic acid
you know into usable forms into a form
where the body can accept it and you
know that part alone has some Merit to
it but this I'm just going to give you
what's out there now a little bit and
you hey you could be an expert on this
and you know have all these you know
details that go along with all this but
so basically the the MTHFR Gene produces
an
enzyme okay so methylene Tetra hydrolate
that's the enzyme it produces so
scientifically that's what's been
discovered out there but I'm going to
tell you right now about something about
science okay science is
incredible when it comes down to hey you
break your leg I talked about that a
zillion times you're probably like okay
I've heard that before or you need a
heart transplant okay or you need
something else or your your gallbladder
explodes because it got highly infected
or stone got caught in there because
you're doing a gallbladder flush and you
flush the stone into the duct and now
you need your your gallbladder removed
hence is why I don't like the
gallbladder flushes by the way you guys
and so whatever it is that you know
Sciences we have great surgeons got
neurosurgeons you name it that can
remove aneurysms out of people's brains
with robots and and that's incredible
that's the part of science that I love
and there's there's plenty of it there's
a decent amount of it but then there's
chronic illness chronic illness massive
you know amount of space out there
complete mystery to science complete
mystery and and you know for real
mystery illness and anything you can tag
a name onto it I don't care what it is
tag a name onto it Celiac just so you
know that's still a medical mystery um
you know Hashimoto thyroiditis still a
medical mystery until I brought the
because I've been the first one to bring
out the truth that the Epstein bar
causes Hashim Modas and now people are
picking that up now and they don't they
don't say it came from me and whatever
I'm seeing that out there out there and
fine you know as long as the information
gets out there it's incredible but the
point is is that there are all these
different chronic mystery illnesses with
no real truth to what's going on behind
any of them
and and I mean the list goes on colius
Myster illness that alone I mean you
know uh depression depression depression
is a mystery illness anxiety mystery
illness I mean especially when it comes
down to stuff like that and then you
know ra um lupus multiple sclerosis
still a mystery uh go on down the line
ALS still a mystery and you know you can
keep on going and keep on going so the
point is is that since chronic illness
is mystery illness and I dedicated the
medical medium book The First Medical
medium book to that um check that out if
you haven't seen it go check a book out
and and or pick one up or wherever you
can get one and you know you'll see
about how mystery and chronic illness
and how it's designed how there's labels
on things but technically the label
really isn't the answer um how we need
to deem these things mystery in order to
get real help and they won't nobody
won't the medical world won't medical
communities won't deem any of these
mystery illnesses because if they do
that then they'll just be showcasing how
they've been wrong the whole time um
with just putting labels on things and
that's it so and so where it falls in
here's what I'm talking about now got
all this chronic illness out there it's
all mysterious it's not mysterious here
it's not mysterious here and if you're
someone who just logged on to the show
and you don't know you don't know me or
anything like that what's going on
you're going to think oh so this guy has
all the answers big Mr medical medium
has all the answers here in this show
but all the science and all the world
doesn't have it it's not me that knows
that it's a source that I've been given
as a gift to receive whether you like it
or not I've helped tens of thousands of
people get to where they need to be
regardless so you know putting this
aside though putting this aside okay
science doesn't have the answers to why
mommies can't get out of bed and take
care of their children to why people
can't walk down the street because they
got aches and pains but all these
different things science does not cover
any of that I don't care what anybody
says I've seen the suffering I've seen
what people have gone through I see it
every day and things have to be done and
we need real information from real
sources so the whole point about The
Chronic and mystery illness is because
there's no answers we get blamed the
blame game okay the blame game yes
talking about it again I might have
talked about it in the last show might
have talked talked about a little bit in
the last show before that but here's
where it really kicks in really kicks in
so when you get told you have an
autoimmune
disease you're told that your body is
attacking itself you've heard this from
me here's how it works we walk into the
the doctor's office they don't know no
one knows what's really wrong with
anybody they don't know what's causing
Hashimoto that's just a quick example
because you know what so many people
have thyroid problems and so it's it's
easy to understand and we get hold their
body is attacking itself the blame
gamees going on okay this is one of the
great mistakes I talk about but there's
blame another blame game and it's a bad
one it's really bad it's the genan blame
game it's a losers game everybody walks
away a loser on this one it's no fun
it's it's
insulting insulting terribly insulting
it's
demeaning it's the gening because of
jees you name it it is what it is and
what the what I'm trying to say is you
got something wrong with you and you got
some bad jeans you got some rotten jeans
you got some faulty jeans your jeans
don't work that's your problem you're
sick because you got bad jeans over
there that person over there is healthy
cuz they got good jeans you got bad
jeans cuz you feel like
crap okay that person's overweight oh
they got bad genes that person you know
has all kinds of problems they got bad
genes that's where it's going because it
has to go there because medical research
and medical science whether anybody
likes it or not I'm just going to tell
you right now doesn't have the answers
it doesn't have the
answers
90% of Health and Wellness is mysterious
it's
mystery that's the bottom line and where
the gene mutation comes in this is where
you got to be careful you get sucked
into the G mutation you're going to get
in trouble big trouble because you're
going to lose you got to be careful and
I'm saying that now now it's pretty bold
to go against a trend that's catching on
like lightning out there lightning it's
it's so so yeah so I'm being pretty bold
about this but I'm going to put my butt
on the firing line to do everything I
can to protect you your children and
your well-being that's the bottom line
and what you're going to hear is going
to make sense it's going to make a lot
of sense is what you're going to hear as
we go through this show this is a very
important show just as important as the
lime disease show just as important as
you know as as other shows that have
done and maybe even more important okay
um so let's let's run into it a little
bit so science is telling us is
dictating to us right now that our genes
become
mutated and they can't produce enzymes
that are
needed and these enzymes help you know
with glutathion production they help
with folate and folic acid um
involvement as far as easily
assimilating into the body and and it
involves chemical compounds as well so
we're told that if you have the gene
mutation whatever variety of gene
mutation you might have there's
different m th hfrg mutations now there
was used to be just one now there's two
now there's three and I'm sure there'll
be 10 more because you know why science
doesn't know what it's doing in this
it's just it it's just moving in a in a
path that's not a good place now good
meaning practitioners and
doctors is they're you know they're for
you they're for you they're looking out
for you they're looking after you they
care about you just like I care about
you I'm sure they do you know that's the
whole point we go into this because we
care and that's what it's about but it's
easy for a practitioner to get LED down
this path of genes because it makes so
much sense that that much must be what's
behind you being sick and and whoever's
sick it's behind it so it's easy to go
right down that
path and and and head there and be like
okay yeah jeans heck yeah why not we're
made up of jeans look at all the
hereditary traits we have
but the genan blame game is a tricky one
it's the trickiest of all because when
you have a child and your child takes on
hereditary traits you can't ignore the
fact that genes are not playing a role
when you have some similarities to your
forefather to your mother your father to
your grandfather it wins the case
immediately that jeans have to be while
you're sick it wins the Case Case Closed
bam
because you get it it's
inescapable you can't get away from the
fact that your mother or your father or
your grandfather looks the same or maybe
even feels the same or maybe even has a
symptom that's the same regardless it's
it's impossible to ignore so this is by
far one of the most evil miscon
inceptions there has to be because no
matter what and no matter probably what
I say here it's just easy to fall into
this
pit what this means is generations to
come are going to all think no matter
what their chronic illnesses are Gene
related and that medical research and
medical science better be up on the
genes and better be working to help our
genes and money and billions of dollars
has to go into genan Jean genan Jean
genes yep that's right and guess what
people are not only going to be sick
they're going to be sicker in the future
and that's why this is by far one of the
worst so the point is how do we escape
this and what do we do okay we're filled
with genes they have their purposes
absolutely they have their purpose they
do genes are involved in our body in so
many different
ways but your
Gene can't become
mutated it can't become mutated
it's not truly a real mutation if you've
been diagnosed with an mthf FRG mutation
it's technically not a real gene
mutation even if the gene is
under problems of some kind meaning
under some kind of um contaminant some
kind of chemical some kind of pollutants
creating a gene to not function function
is good it's not technically mutated so
you need to understand this so when you
get diagnosed with MTHFR gene mutation
it's not you don't have a gene you don't
have a gene that's mutated you don't you
don't have a gene that's not working in
fact when it comes down to mfrg mutation
the gene isn't even
problematic there's something else
triggering off the faulty MTHFR gene
mutation test tests the faulty
tests that's what's going on there the
mthf FRG mutation tests are not accurate
they're inaccurate to begin with okay so
that's what's going on there doesn't
mean you don't have to you doesn't mean
you don't stop and get one I mean you
can still get your G mutation test the
whole bit but I'm trying to let you know
they're not
Ironclad not Ironclad at all and if you
do ring up a gene mutation test gets
rung up positive I'm going to tell you
what's going on so we can really cut
into it so we have methylation problems
that's the real part we have inabilities
inability to methylate methylate is
conversion it's all about conversion
inside the body that's what methylation
is it's all about conversion uh breaking
down chemicals into smaller chemicals
breaking down smaller chemicals into
smaller chemicals breaking down those
smaller chemicals into smaller chemicals
it goes on and on and on if you look
into methylation or you look into the G
mutation out there on the trendy stuff
that's trending they'll just kind of you
know cut it clear they'll say well you
know it's an enzyme and then they'll say
you know this enzyme um you know um this
enzyme is involved with methylene
another enzyme and that they bind on
together they break down folate they
break down folic acid and it it's pretty
much where it stops but
what's really happening is we have
chemical breakdowns in the body that
science is so far away that it would
take a thousand years we're talking
about it doesn't stop at chemicals
breaking down and converting into more a
smaller chemicals or more easily viable
chemicals it keeps on going the mystery
of what our body does how many chemicals
we have is is unbelievable and I'm going
to talk about something here something
very important okay okay medical science
and research only believes the liver is
responsible for anywhere from 400 to 500
chemical uses or chemical
responsibilities okay chemical
responsibilities in your body to do
things to do things to keep you alive
and well the liver has thousands of
chemical
responsibilities thousands that haven't
even been discovered yet and these
thousands of responsibilities play into
methylation which is still in its baby
stage of understanding but the problem
is it sends you down the direction that
your Gene is mutated and that's the
problem the problem with that is the
real issue in your health is not being
seen whatsoever not being seen not being
understood but then you might get a
diagnosed well you got this methylation
issue this MTHFR gen mutation issue you
got that you're me not methylating fine
and and you know youve got some candida
you may have this oh you've been
diagnosed with lime you got a little bit
borderline lime it's a mess it's a hot
mess out there so let's talk about how
it works what what creates the test the
triggers off the test to begin with what
triggers it off is inflammation the
MTHFR G mutation test is just as good as
an Ana anti- nuclear antibody test just
as good as that test it's just as good
as a C-reactive protein test they're
just basic inflammatory marker tests but
the mthf FRG mutation test is under the
guce of a gene test it's just another
basic you got some inflammation
throughout your entire
body test that's what it is just just so
you know so where does this lead this
leads
to
misdiagnosis this leads to
misinformation less information for our
health and well-being kind of like the
anti-nuclear antigen test antibody test
the Ana test that test for
Lupus tells you if you have Lupus first
of all it doesn't tell you if you have
Lupus it's just another inflammation
test for mystery illness or mystery
issues the mthf FRG mutation test should
just be a tool to show that yes there's
something else wrong with you or going
on with you but it should not be
deciphering or defining you and saying
that you have a gene mutation or that
your child has a gene
mutation it's so detrimental to your
health and well-being you have to back
out of that and say okay you know what I
don't have a gene mutation it's not
possible what I have though is a marker
that's telling me something else is
going on and that's the part where I'm
okay about the test itself because the
test is a basic inflammatory test just
like many of the other ones that get a
tag and get a label so if you do or you
have been diagnosed with MTHFR gene
mutation one of the gene mutations and
you have been diagnosed and you have
that test has been done and you've been
told this is what's going on what you
have to do is it's okay it's okay you
just have to know your Gene's not
mutated you have to know that
immediately you don't have a gene
dysfunction but you have to realize the
test is not really accurate it's in its
baby stages I mean that you give it 20
years and you watch where that test is
and you have to realize it's just a
marker that's showing that you have
something else going on so that's how
you have have to see it and this is
where I'm supportive of the gene
mutation test it really they should just
change the name of it they should change
the name of it and get out of the whole
Gene blame game it's a dangerous game so
here's the deal you go to the doctor
you're not feeling good whether you're
not feeling good or not people get the
test and it rings off and they're
feeling fine but you go to the doctor
you get the test or your
practitioner test comes up positive that
you got the MTHFR gene mutation okay
what you have to realize right away
something else is going on there's
something happening inside the body and
let me tell you what's happening and
where it is all gene
mutations meaning the test itself
providing somebody with the
misinformation of having a gene
mutation all these lead to a
dysfunctional problem in the liver
that's where it's all going on it's the
liver second part is the intestinal
tract but the liver is where the trouble
lies see what triggers off the
inflammation that then determines if you
have an mthf FRG mutation what triggers
all of this off is byproduct byproduct
coming out of the liver floating in the
bloodstream wreaking havoc causing
homocysteine levels to rise or to fall
or become useless it's it's these these
other chemicals these toxins they're
floating around the bloodstream from the
liver from sources in combinations of
pathogens viruses inside the liver
viruses or heavy metals or both
technically it really is both most cases
of having heavy metals inside the liver
having a lot of byproduct a lot of slug
sludge a lot of Gunk a lot of junk
inside that
liver from pathogens that are producing
that also things that the liver have
collected over the years like the toxic
heavy metals and that junk and garbage
starts making the liver less efficient
stops letting it function as good stops
it from cleaning your blood when you get
your F Mt mthf R gene mutation test and
it comes up positive you got dirty blood
that's what it means it doesn't mean you
have a faulty Gene it means you have a
you have dirty blood it means your dirty
blood is preventing folate or folic acid
from converting methylating being usable
by the body so here's where the parts
more than true there's a methylation
issue correct I'm not against the
methylation issue I've been talking
about methylation for 30
years so that's how long it's been and
so I'm totally for it because that's
where it lies that's where the truth
holds it holds in there it's not that
you have a g
mutation but you do have a methylation
problem so what the practitioner and the
doctor is discovering is you do have a
methylation problem but it's under the G
it's under the hidden
roof you know that dark pit of it's your
Gene causing all this
trouble and guess what if your Gene's
causing all the trouble you can't fix
that you can't just fix that Gene if
your Gene's causing all the
trouble but here's the irony you fix
somebody's methylation problem and the
test doesn't ring off off anymore so
when you fix somebody's methylation
issue where they're methylating their
liver is getting better their blood
isn't dirty they don't trigger off the
gene mutation test anymore isn't that
interesting one week that test rings off
that you got the you got two two
versions of G mutations one one week
that test rings off that you're it shows
you got this mthf FRG mutation and it's
really bad
and then you start methylating
again and you start fixing the problem
that's creating the dirty
blood and that's inside the
liver and guess what that test goes away
the Tex test goes away I know
practitioners that are baffled because
because the person did the right thing
not offered by the practitioner but did
the right thing by finding and sourcing
the right information to to heal a meth
a problem like the adino silab balamin
we talk about like the B12 we talk about
you guys and really creating the you
know creating methylation in the body
cleaning up the liver getting the viral
load down and then the test goes away
and then literally the practitioner
scratching the head like this is
impossible this you know maybe the blood
was switched to the lab maybe the blood
was switched here maybe you know they
can't understand how it's possible you
lose the tag the label it's possible
because once you fix the real issue you
lose that inflammation the inflammation
disappears and it won't trigger off the
gene mutation
test so just recap a little bit gene
mutation test number one is really just
an inflammatory test with a fancy name
blaming your
jeans I'm just being straightforward now
if you're a practitioner you're like
that's not true I know how the test
works it's a real Gene we're looking at
no no no no no no yeah that part yeah
you're looking at that you're looking at
a real Gene but the test still comes up
wrong it's how look you can name you can
take any test and name it anything you
want in any way capacity possible but
it's going to end up being in many cases
an inflammatory test and this is a new
version of showcasing inflammation in
the body yeah rocking the B rocking the
you know rocking the boat when it comes
down to homosysteine
and rocking the boat in
methylation but nevertheless it's an
inflammatory marker that's what it is
just like I've talked about all the Lyme
disease tests all these years why do you
think Lyme disease testing is oh your
borderline it's either you have the
pathogen or you don't but for some
reason we're told oh but it's borderline
so yeah we would say you do because it's
borderline what's borderline you either
you either have it or you don't the
reason why it's borderline because it's
an inflammation test another version of
an inflammation test you listen to the
lime show you I think I talk about it
there and uh and I'll do another another
lime show in the future what you're
going to find anybody who's viral and I
talked about this Lyme disease is viral
the reason why I'm mentioning this it's
important to know Lyme disease is viral
not bacterial at read if this is the
first time hopping on the show you know
hopping into the show read the book
medical medium read the lime chapter but
same thing with ra it's viral same thing
with multiple sclerosis that's viral you
can go on and on and on and all these
different illnesses that we have there's
probably hundred I can name maybe even
200 but it would just drive you nuts if
I sat here naming a list of 200
illnesses in these 200
illnesses understand that viruses play a
role and those
viruses sit inside the liver muck it up
whether you feel good or you don't feel
good releasing poison and toxin or
filling up toxins in the liver so when
you're diagnosed with Lyme disease
you're going to have an mthf FRG
mutation everybody with lime now is
getting the Mt MTHFR G mutation test now
and they're all coming up positive
because it's viral issues in the liver
causing dirty blood and triggering off
the mtfr gene mutation test so that you
get diagnosed with a G
issue anybody with multiple sclerosis
now they're getting they're they're
saying they they got the mthf FRG
mutation everybody with lupus MTHFR G
mutation see what's happening here is
when you have a viral condition that's
causing lupus like the Epstein bar virus
that causes lupus they talk about it in
the book or you got you know or you got
the multiple sclerosis or a different
variet variety of Epstein bar causing Ms
whatever it is or Lyme disease where
it's hhv6 HH B7 or shingles or the
Epstein bar varieties or multiple
varieties of all these creating Lyme
disease whatever it is you're going to
see mthf FRG mutation eventually come up
and you're going to see methylation
issues the methylation issues homo homoy
issues are because the liver gets
clogged up clouded up filled the toxins
from having to deal with viral issues
and this flood of toxins viral viral
bodies viral casings spets that actually
are viral because casings of viruses
look like spyit you name it all of this
stuff dumps into the bloodstream along
with neurotoxins Dermot toxins that go
to the skin and create eczema psoriasis
all of this dumps into the bloodstream
floats
around and triggers off the MTHFR gene
mutation test and then you're told you
have a mutated Gene which doesn't help
you you heal from Lyme disease it
doesn't help you heal from Ms it doesn't
help you heal from eximus risis it
doesn't help you heal from SAR cardosis
it doesn't help you heal from you know
uh colitis or whatever it is it doesn't
help you heal to think and that you have
a gene mutation and if you think that
that's not true you're wrong it sits in
the back of the Mind in a subconscious
place that your jeans suck and it eats
away at the immune system so you got to
flip the switch now you got to know that
you have no gene
mutation you got to flip it and know you
don't have a gene mutation but what you
have is a methylation problem and that's
where the gene mutation test or the
philosophy or the theory because it's
all theoretical just so you know it's
all you know just know that there is
though a methylation issue cuz when that
liver gets clogged up and it gets dirty
and the blood gets get dirty and all
that's going on and stuff's flooding
into the bloodstream and into the
intestinal tract and clouding it up and
you're not eating the right foods and
that's elevating more inflammation and
feeding more pathogens and whatever's
going on just know methylation is not
going to go good you're going to get
minimum methylation minimum
conversions minimum conversions of
important chemicals and chemical
compounds and phytochemicals that come
through from food and come from all the
things that we involve come from the Sun
it come from food Sun clean
water and we're going to we're not going
to get the methylation
needed and there's this little spot I
talk about a lot it's in the colon It's
the eloel the Elum it's right there in
the Elum it's a little spot right right
after your small intestinal track and
right before your colon that spot has
probiotics called elevated biotics from
when you eat an apple you picked off a
tree not an apple you just get in the
supermarket that's been sitting there
waxed I'm talking about when you when
you that one time in your life you went
to an apple orchard because you went to
go pick some apples and drink a little
fresh apple cider that has these
elevated biotics in it it's a
microorganism that helps you methylate
that produces B12 when you pick a little
piece of kale out of the
garden that
produces B12 because it has
microorganisms that get to the Elum this
little section after your in small
intestinal
tract so methylation is a big deal we
got to clean up the liver we have to get
the diet right we have to lower any kind
of viral issues if you have a gene
mutation test that comes back positive
and your doctor says you're not
methylating then you better go antiviral
and talk to your doctor tell your
practitioner say look that means you
know I heard from Anthony that means
that I got low levels of viral issue
maybe in the liver that's what's causing
some of my symptoms my fatigue my eggs
and pains my Hashimoto and I got this
low level of viral you know viral um
activity going on making my blood toxic
and maybe that's why I don't detox good
because what the G mutation test leads
to as a practitioner then teaching
people you know hey it means you can't
detox you have no ability to detox your
homocysteine is all messed up your your
you know all this stuff is going on and
you can't detox you're not
detoxing because you're toxic because
you have a viral issue creating toxins
weakening the liver so that conversions
don't happen back to the liver liver is
responsible for thousands thousands of
of of of um of chemical activities
chemical
procedures okay chemical
responsibilities the liver is
responsible and and in this
responsibility Factor all this going
on is the breaking down of chemicals to
chemicals to chemicals to chemicals
meaning being used so that Amino and and
and the production of amino acids and
the breakdown and the combin ining of
aminos and the combining of aminos with
other chemicals all this is done in the
liver it's one of the most important
places there is and it's responsible for
methylation so if you got a viral thing
in the liver if you've had chronic
fatigue you got the Epstein bar in the
liver if you got Hashimoto you got the
Epstein bar in the liver you're
eventually going to end up with a gene
mutation diagnosis which will be in
accurate the only accurate part is is
that yes your methylation has dropped
your ability to methylate and to to you
know and to combine the folate and the
folic acid mean with other chemicals and
break them down so they're usable is
diminishing that part is correct that's
why a big part of the whole methylation
thing and the g mutations I
like but it's still got holes in it that
we're covering all in here today so you
know the conversion of homocysteine to
um to methionine okay that
conversion is something that gets
interfered with when you can't methylate
so your homocysteine levels can rise the
conversion is not there once again from
the liver being clogged up whether
you're overweight whether you're
underweight
whether you feel good whether you don't
whether your child's diagnosed with the
G mutation and you know feels fine in
the moment and then you think your child
has a gene mutation it means the liver
is showcasing signs of some wear and
tear whether it's a really early on
which happens all the time or later on
and that will give you the mfrg mutation
but like I said before if you've been
diagnosed with any chronic illness
that's still a mystery and a mystery to
Alternative doctors to and alternative
medicine still a mystery and you're
diagnosed all these different labels
many of them which we talked about
already then chances are you'll
eventually get that MTHFR mutation test
and be and be told you have
that but really what's happening is yes
you have things going on with your
health and that your health is having
you know you're struggling with the
methylation process because of the dirty
blood the detoxic detoxification issue
from having dirty blood and the liver
not being able to perform what it needs
to perform so the blood gets toxic and
dirty and you end up with the gene
mutation test so what do we do being a
positive so what do we do we can turn
this around you can change this you can
get yourself
better and clean this up so that when
you go and get your mthf FRG mutation
test you can get rid of the positive on
that test and blow the doctor or
practitioner's
mind you can because what it's going to
mean is you're going to lower your
inflammation so it doesn't trigger off
the faulty test that was created another
test that's really not accurate I mean
it showcases something it showcases a
little a little bit of elevation of
inflammation so it's accurate on that
level it showcases that leads to a
methylation problem on that level so
what can we do well first of all go
antiviral that's the first thing get
your zinc up to par it's the first thing
you want to do get your zinc up the par
start drinking some th tea a little bit
of thme tea get some oregano capsules
okay so you can find you know you can
find any of this stuff also on on uh you
know I have a little um directory of all
these things you can find so people know
the Best Brands just go to medical
medium.com and and look for this stuff
we don't sell it okay so we don't have a
store where we're selling anything but
it's there so you don't buy the zinc
that has citric acid so you burn your
stomach and and create an
ulcer okay so we so that doesn't happen
all right so you don't buy the the
tincture that has corn grain alcohol in
it so you feed another bacteria or feed
some kind of sibo problem or whatever it
is so you know you want the right
supplements so you do the oregano oil
capsules that's important Olive Leaf you
want to bring a little olive leaf in
cat's claw that's another great one you
want to have the right
zinc bring in the zinc the supplement
methylfolate this is the most critical
part of methylation right here but yeah
you might know about it your
practitioner offers it with a
methylation problem or a g mutation
issue they offer the methylfolate but it
won't work unless your B12 supplement
has adoil cobalamin in it you won't find
that information anywhere else but here
that's how you methylate regardless of
your liver condition or anything else or
the dirty blood fixed up and all that
better you still can methylate when you
combine these two so that's the
important part all the other b12's never
have adinos Sil cobalamin in it so
methylation still doesn't occur when
someone has a problem and you want
vitamin C because vitamin C helps you
detox like it gets the poisons out of
the blood so they get
removed and pushed on Down the Line
so you want vitamin C and enough vitamin
C so that's
important so keep that in your regime um
line that's a big deal line lowers viral
loads viral loads are responsible for
methylation issues viral loads are
responsible for problems dirty blood the
liver not working good so get the
lysine so that's a great one to bring in
foods get out the eggs get out the dairy
get out the wheat okay and you'll know
you go to your alternative practitioner
you go to your um holistic
practitioner and you're going to be told
to get off the weak gluten of course
you're going to be told to get off maybe
some dairy products so you want to get
off of those that's really
important so when it comes down to the
foods you want less fat in the foods
this is really important so you don't
want the dairy okay you don't want the
you know you don't want the eggs in
there you don't want foods that have
real high fat if you're a meat eater
lower the fats by lowering the amount of
meat you're eating because we're talking
about it's your liver and your liver is
creating the methylation problem it's
creating the mthf FRG mutation problem
that means the more fat in your liver
the more fat that your liver has to you
know break down the more bile it has to
produce and break down more fat in your
your diet the the less it's going to
have the ability to rejuvenate the less
it's going to have the the ability to
get rid of the poison that's actually
causing the conversion problems that's
actually causing the folate and the
folic you know the the folic acid
conversion problems and the amino acid
conversion problems you know with MTHFR
gene mutation issues so the whole point
here is if you're doing Foods whe so say
you're on a plant-based diet don't
overdo the nuts don't overdo the avocado
you know so if you're on a plant-based
diet you know more fresh fruits and
vegetables more obviously um and you
know more sweet potatoes but if you're
on say a Palo diet or a meat eating diet
you know whatever that might be like you
do chicken twice a day or something or
you do turkey for lunch chicken for you
got to break it down to once a day
because if you don't you're going to
have a little too much fat going on so
that means you know for lunch maybe do
avocado Which is less fat than chicken
for lunch so that you just knock down a
level of fat intake greatly and then at
dinner do something that you like that's
in the animal protein realm if you're if
you're big in animal protein the point
is is lowering the fat in the diet in
any way helps stop the the the liver
from declining so it can pick speed up
again so it can start to heal clean up
and so you can start using the different
things to knock out the viral load that
could be in the liver that's producing
the gene mutation test triggering it off
by producing all of that byproduct
floating around in the bloodstream so
for instance let's go over Foods the
wild blueberries really heal and cleanse
the liver celery juice cleanses the
liver so you could do the 16 ounces look
go to my blog go to my blog and check
out different things you check out the
celery juice and it's for you and I want
you to go into my blog because you're
going to see a big snap snazzy picture
of me holding up celery juice that's not
it I want you doing the celery juice you
to do it okay I'm doing it at home
that's already happening so you don't
need to see that on the blog get there
and know what the recipe is understand
do the celery juice and then you know
bring in the sweet potatoes they help
cleanse the liver because there's no fat
in the sweet potato virtually virtually
none in there and so that helps with the
liver winter squash helps with the
healing of the liver so these are some
of the foods you can do and you know hey
look if it's winter it's it's cold you
do more sweet potato do sweet potatoes
for lunch if you if you love animal
products you know Skip skip the you know
whatever it is for lunch turkey or the
chicken or the the the meat for lunch
and do the sweet potatoes for lunch
you're going to be getting your gene
mutation you know reversed you're going
to be getting things reversed and then
for dinner time you can then do whatever
it is that you do you know and if you're
and once again if you're vegetarian or
you're you know vegan or PL base or
whatever you you want to be that you
feel is good you know it's incredible
for liver problems that create the gene
mutation okay or create the false gene
mutation test that we talked about all
through here and so but the best thing
to do ever is to at least take a moment
in your life and have it really lowfat
that means you're doing lots of salads
with fruit in them or you're doing
smoothies green smoothies and we talk
about that all the time the different
smoothies and everything I mean you'll
see them on Facebook and Instagram and
all that so you'll get you get an idea
better smoothies and you'll find recipes
in the life-changing Foods book any of
the
recipes you know are helpful for the
gene mutation issue that we have that's
that's rampant out there that we're
talking about see lowering the fats gets
the liver to produce less bile and it
gets it to rejuvenate fast so when
you're doing that celery juice and then
eating some oranges in the morning
having a mango then lunchtime having a
spinach tomato you know um spinach
tomato soup and then in the afternoon
you're having um you're having celery
sticks and apples and other things like
that and then you know for dinner time
you do the sweet potatoes for dinner
it's something like that in that realm
that lowers your fats enough in one day
to purge the liver so that you're not
told you can't detox so that your liver
can recover and cleanse and when it
recovers and cleanses you're home free
with the methylation issue and you can
be freed from the test that tells you
you have a gene mutation you can
actually be freed from that over time
part of that like I said is getting the
viral load down because it's
viruses and some heavy metals that lie
in the liver that they lay in the liver
there they hide in there and they're
working on creating junk and byproduct
and garbage and this could be
responsible for your symptoms too the
whole thing the viruses that create
chronic fatigue fibromyalgia the Epstein
bar that's a big one all of these
different viruses that sit in the liver
they create whatever your symptoms are
and your additional mtfr gene mutation
you see what I mean it even creates that
so in short the viral issue is creating
your gene mutation that's that's what
I'm talking about being inside the liver
getting it clogged up getting it
sluggish getting it problematic and then
your blood gets dirty your methylation
ability drops greatly because the liver
has so much to do with methylation along
with that part in the colon I was
talking to you about you guys about and
so what do you do you get the antivirals
going on like we talked about the zinc
and you bring in some ibrite try some
ibrite too talk to your practitioner say
you want to go antiviral bring in some
ibrite bringing lemon bomb red clover
tea cleans out the blood real nice by
the way could really reverse that
inflamation that's triggering off that
gene mutation test you know and lemon
bomb the nettle Leaf the olive leaf I
talked about earlier you bring a little
bit of that in the cat's Claw is amazing
the reason why cats claw works so good
with lime patients now and you know and
cats claw has been you know that's been
something that Spirits always promoted
back since I was a child and that cat's
claw works because it's killing off
viruses and it eventually can lead you
to not having a methylation problem now
you may have already a diagnosis of
something and you don't trigger off as a
methylation problem it doesn't mean you
don't have one the test itself is not
concrete it's not Ironclad so it's
picking up inflammation sometimes and
sometimes it doesn't it's not perfect
there's no test in medical research and
IAL science that is absolutely perfect
and even blood typing is not perfect in
science and research testing sometimes
someone can have one blood type and two
months later get it tested again and it
be different that has happened in
history That's Not Unusual so what I'm
saying is even the most Ironclad what we
feel like sometimes is not lemon water
get the lemon water make sure you're
doing it every day 16 oun twice a day
can help your can reverse a methylation
problem remember the B12 I talked about
as well all these things combined keep
your fats low and you're heading in the
right direction and you will reverse the
diagnosis listen I love you I stand
behind you 100% thank you for hanging in
there on this show this show might have
gotten some people mad might have gotten
some people upset hang in there have
faith stay strong I love you and just
know that you know one day at a time you
take care
bye-bye