hi guys I'm here with Anthony William
medical medium and I'm super excited to
share from the man himself who created
this incredible celery juice phenomena
really and that I have personally been
on for the last six months drinking my
you know 16 ounces of celery juice on an
empty stomach every morning and I have
personally noticed the benefit and so I
have the wonderful man here himself to
tell you about the incredible health
benefits all drinking celery juice in
the morning one of the best things it
does is a restores your hydrochloric
acid and everybody's digestion is weak
and they're bloated or they're
constipated or they have problems out
there with their digestion acid reflux
and it repairs and heals the digestive
system by repairing the hydrochloric
acid recovering it and fixing the liver
getting the liver stronger that's the
whole point getting liver stronger and
getting people better so it's amazing
and how much celery juice do you drink
every morning I feel like 24 ounces 16
ounces on an empty stomach is like green
that's fantastic I do like 24 ounces
some people can do more but 16 ounces
minimum I'm gonna up my dose to 24
ounces
it just it honestly does help with that
kind of like energy the clearer thoughts
you know feeling good brain fog that's
one of the things that really helps with
celery juice is incredible for like
everybody being so busy being stressed
out so much on their plate their
neurotransmitters are getting eaten up
and then we get the brain fog or we get
tired because we have so much going on
celery juice gets it so you can actually
move forward faster do more things get
busier get things done because we can
think better think more clear it's not
incredible for the brain
neurotransmitters it's everything it's
amazing
I'm obsessed do you guys really need to
try it it's life-changing and you're
gonna love it and just celery juice
alone but let's show them how we do it
yeah definitely yeah so yeah we got the
juicer right here yep so this is freshly
washed celery and look okay
that's your book
and why don't you show us how you do it
yeah okay totally got it right here all
right these are really good stocks by
the way they are filled with a lot of
nutrition there's no question I mean if
you get the thinner stocks they're fine
to you but these are also like nice and
juicy delicious sometimes take the
homeless piece so it's really incredible
so yeah you know some good stuff
oh good so if you can't get organic
celery normal salaries fine yeah normal
conventional summer is fine but you can
like wash it good really well it's it's
good you can use a natural non-sentient
like unscented dishwashing soap and
basically a dish soap or something and
you can do a drop of that in a in a bowl
of water push yourself in there and
but you should be good do you do
anything with the left of a celery Pope
no I actually go I know that people are
staying out the combust combust yeah I
know people are saying you should be
eating that you should just put it in
your smoothies you should be shooting
juice celery they're just it's not the
way to go you have to it has to be the
juice in order to get usual benefits
yeah this is an herbal extraction is
what we're doing yeah so just like tea
men need the teabags you know yeah all
right so now we have our celery juice
Cheers
pretty cool here's to good health and
happiness enjoy