nice to meet you too thank you for your
generosity and your commitment this is
epic congratulations this is Monumental
um years into my journey after
miraculously healing a lot of symptoms I
had an epic setback where I couldn't
properly apply your tools okay and what
helped get that happens thank you yeah
thank you even just affirming that what
helped get me out of that was
recognizing that I was under attack from
negative entities and negative energy
yeah it can be a real Twisted world
thank you for staying with it staying
with the information healing that's all
that counts is you and your healing you
and your body okay that's you and and
your life means everything and that's
what counts not all the out
there