roasted butternut kombucha squash that's
what we're doing
we're doing
we're doing roasted brussels sprouts
maple brussels sprouts
i'm excited about that all right we're
doing cranberry sauce
this is gonna be great you guys we were
just on amazon live and there was a tech
issue on amazon
so we moved the medical medium cooking
show right here something weird you know
something different we're doing cooking
tips on here
we're going to make this dish all over
again is what we're going to do so i'm
excited and we'll make it even better
good to see you guys awesome lineup
right chris incredible so you guys work
let's get into this right now let's chop
up some stuff so this is really cool
this is the medical medium cooking show
but the difference right now i'm going
to be able to say anything i want to say
so
that's the fun part this might be even a
more fun cooking show man so i'm excited
you guys
did you see colorful incredible right
yeah
redo andy exactly we're live on tick
tock right now you guys which i'm pumped
up about we're live on telegram you guys
i know on tick tock and telegram you
can't see the whole
the whole setup right you can't see all
of it you can see some of it right
but if you need to go on youtube or
rumble
then you can see more of it right i'm
going to chop up some celery you guys is
what i'm gonna do right now
yeah hey guys how you doing you're all
coming on here i'm so excited about that
the recipes are in the books
you guys know the recipes right come on
don't you guys know the recipes check
this out right
what do we have here look at that that
is incredible i am so pumped up about
this
take a look right now
you guys see
incredible
all right
what that is is the maple roasted
brussels sprouts in liver rescue if you
don't have liver rescue incredible book
mind-blowing book okay really
mind-blowing book there's so much in
there
it's about fighting disease fighting
illness fighting all kinds of conditions
it's incredible and then we're going to
do this dish check it out i'm looking at
these whoa these carrot zucchini and
potato patties that i'm not making today
but i'm making
the stuffed butternut squash right there
how great is that tik tok what do you
guys think right pretty cool you like
the close-up on tick-tock there you go
okay i'll do that more i just saw that i
saw you just say that on tick-tock i
will do that more all right
all right let's do this
we got some celery sticks i got a pan
right now okay
which i'm excited about we're gonna get
this in the pan we're gonna chop up some
celery is what we're gonna do
i'm gonna thinly slice it whoa we got
the camera on here when have i ever done
that here
right this is incredible we grabbed some
more celery look at this this is so
great you guys i'm i'm really pumped up
about this
this is great we took the amazon cooking
show right to here for now for today how
cool
yeah i'm liking this we'll do this no
problem right
sorry about the noise i'll try to be a
little quieter like this how about this
there we go
i'm gonna cut these nice and small i'm
making the stuffing so you guys on tick
tock i'm making the stuffing all right
so this is really
exciting because we're doing this
stuffed butternut squash i want to show
you guys something
i want to show you guys
this came out of the oven earlier what
do you think close up right there in
rumble what do you guys think on
telegram how about look at that in
rumble
and youtube
right incredible came out of the oven
tick tock you like the close-up i'll
bring this closer
[Laughter]
so i'm gonna put a stuffing right on top
of those just so you guys all know
that's what i'm making right now okay
we're doing recipes out of the
life-saving books or rescue and cleanse
the heal books that have changed the
lives of millions of people worldwide
change the lives of millions of people
worldwide right
think about that
how incredible
so
the medical medium books
are the most selling books
in medical in the world right now just
so you know
right and
six and a half years running
and there's a reason for that no pr or
marketing guys do you know what that
means
no pr marketing it means i didn't take a
million dollars
like they all do
and put it into pr marketing
so that their book can get somewhere
the books no money behind them
no money behind the books being
propelled out there right i'm gonna put
this in the pan
the books
healed people
they healed people
people everybody deserves to heal even
people
who heal from medical medium and then
give me a middle finger on the way out
because they want to sell an alkaline
ionizer water machine and the medical
medium community says medical medium
doesn't like those because the metal
plates in there rot and bubble up and
everybody gets poisoned and then because
they can't sell their alkaline
ionizer water machine to anybody they
get mad and they say well even though i
healed 100
for medical medium information i'm gonna
tell everybody
forget it
i'm out of here
you know what's funny about medical
medium information you guys we're doing
cooking tips and stuff what's funny
about medical medium information is
it's
saved a lot of lives
and i don't care who's live it's safe as
long as it saved their life
doesn't matter
as long as their life is saved
i don't care
what they want to do or
sell or
believe in it's totally up to everybody
to believe in anything they want do what
they want everything
i just want you better so you can do
what you want in life whatever that's
going to be so i'm doing a pan right
here it's really exciting here with this
cooking tips as we're going to be doing
so i got the carrot so i don't know if i
showed you guys this i'm going to show
you one more time
from here on up from here on up
okay
right there
there's an alkaloid on that carrot
nobody knows this they don't know that
there's an alkaloid here inside that
carrot and that alkaloid
okay that alkaloid makes it hard to
digest
it's got enzyme inhibitors in that
alcohol alkaloid right there so i chop
the top of the carrot off because that's
an enzyme enzyme inhibitors are in that
part of the carrot give somebody a
bellyache there's people that can't eat
carrots and they don't know why well the
reason why they can't eat carrots
is because
that affected them a lot more than
somebody else but i love carrots so what
i like to do anyways i cut that top off
i mean i eat them with the tops
but i know there's people that are
sensitive
i'm not i don't have a sensitive
digestion
i mean i could you know it's not going
to affect me but it will
it will affect somebody else for sure
who's struggling with digestive problems
so what i say with carrots that's what
you want to do
so what i'm doing is cutting this and i
like that tip because that's a really
important tip
that's what that is
you cut the top off you don't have to
cut that far i probably cut a little too
far right there on that top right you
guys just came on here we're doing
cooking tips we're making stuffed squash
bakes big squash we're making roasted
maple brussels sprouts and some
cranberry sauce
this cooking show was set up for the
amazon live but amazon had a tech
problem
all right so we're cutting up these
carrot pieces getting it in the pan
that's what we're doing
and then we're gonna do some more
carrots i'm gonna make a nice size
stuffing
you always cut the top off leslie really
you guys
any of the other guys do that that's
that's amazing you cut the top off
yeah that's good that's good that you do
that's important
i'm going to show you some tips about
the squashes which is going to be really
fun i didn't even finish doing that
earlier so i'm excited to do that and
get into it so i'm cutting these a
little thinner you don't want these
carrots thick
you don't want them so thick
cut the top off again there we go i'm
excited you guys on telegram if you want
to see the show a little bit with
different you could always look look on
rumble too rumble i got the whole screen
on rumble there
same on tick tock but you guys are
comfortable to stay there stay there
perfectly fine i love it i'm glad you're
here
i didn't peel the carrots
i didn't feel like i had to on this you
know like then what i wanted to do i
didn't peel the carrots but you know
what i did is i washed them so i want to
talk about like why it's important to
wash some techniques about washing
a little bit about that what happens is
that
produce
could be
in a box and those boxes on a pallet in
the truck could be under other boxes it
happens all the time they could be under
chicken
fresh
chicken boxes
and chicken juices can be dripping on
produce this is why washing produce is
so important
it's different when you're picking it
yourself maybe in the farm or something
if you do you know like pick your own or
you got your garden or anything like
that that's different right but you got
to be careful with
with
you know you can have some in la e coli
the whole bit
right
and the thing is with chicken
is like
chicken can kill you
it can kill you
eggs can kill you
right eggs can kill you mayonnaise do
you ever think about that mayonnaise
don't leave the mayonnaise out in the
sun
why because you'll die
uh
at the cookout make sure the mayonnaise
is cold oh my god make sure the
mayonnaise is cold if the mayonnaise
doesn't stay cold everybody's gonna be
on the toilet and barfing and holding
the toilet for dear life and throwing up
and diarrhea
just don't let the mayonnaise get cold
because why because egg
egg
right didn't i i taught you guys about
the whole thing about eggs right eggs
are the food that raised all the
pathogens
in in the classified medical research
and science labs right it's all the
whole thing i told you guys about that
so the whole point is
is that eggs feed bacteria really fast
so when you bring your mayonnaise in the
sun
you bring your mayonnaise outside
and a fly lands on your mayonnaise
it's possible the fly can bring some
bacteria from somebody's garbage can
down the road right
when you're at a cookout or you're out
in the backyard and you've got that mayo
that fly can bring some bacteria from
somebody's garbage can down the street
and that bacteria
you know what if somebody threw out some
bad meat at their house and they threw
it in the can it was in the garbage bag
and it was kind of sitting there open
and the flies got into the garbage bag
and they just started you know landing
on that meat and then what happened was
that meat had all this e coli and stuff
and everything else or some raw chicken
bags were thrown in there and the fly
then landed in
somebody's cookout and then landed in
the mayo dish the bacteria that the fly
brought can proliferate in hours
in hours
and that's why
what happens is you you know
it's crazy and the same thing with with
chicken like if you eat chicken juices
they can kill you undercooked chicken
right can kill you right
all that information
citric acid i saw something about citric
acid over there yeah citric acid not
good not good
when it's in processed food and
everything else and all these other
things are you guys i just put some
carrots in the pan so i got that on on
here too so i'm gonna keep on going i'm
gonna cut some mushrooms how about that
let's do that
so i'm going to cut up some mushrooms
right here if you guys are okay with
that
i think the bottom line is you got to
wash your produce
you got to wash them
these are mushrooms right here you have
to wash mushrooms with hot water
remember that
with hot water because you might you
might eat a mushroom piece
on its own
that hasn't been in the pan so you got
to make sure you wash because there's
any bacteria on top of those mushrooms
the manure that they grow mushrooms in
manure
has all this bacteria
so you have to make sure that you
wash them with hot water to really
bind on to that bacteria and pull that
bacteria off and like i said there's all
this fresh produce it's all moved
someone left a comment reminding me
about that and i remember i've seen that
through through the years
and i'm glad that person left the
comment because reminding me i was like
yeah i know totally what happens is you
got like in the grocery store trucks and
the
trucks you've got fresh produce and you
got fresh fish and you got fresh chicken
and cross contamination happens all the
time let's get some more mushrooms in
here
this dish is for anybody who's animal
protein or anybody who's plant-based and
vegan okay so
keep that in mind i mean you can have if
you really want your animal protein you
can still have it you can still have
anything you want this is but this is an
incredible dish you can just do on its
own totally it's meant to be on its own
it's a medical medium recipe it's got no
oil in it it's it's so good for you too
i'm gonna get some more mushrooms in
here i'm making a big stuffing because
the stuffing is gonna fill up a lot of
squashes over there i'm gonna pile it
high so this is gonna be really good
maybe a couple more mushrooms
yeah
lorraine says good to have extra
awareness i saw that
so
i'm already glad i have some of the
books marilyn says need to cleanse heel
book you need to cleanse the heel book
cleansing heel book is a great book it's
incredible book that's helped so many
people around the world and i was saying
earlier that the books
are one of those global phenomenons in
health especially cleanse the heal too
that's that's one that's just
helping so many people out there
all right
so we got some mushrooms in here this is
great let's grind up some cauliflower if
you guys can see this
guys on tiktok i got a food processor
over here
okay
and i'm about to put cauliflower in
so there's my cauliflower right there
right dino good to see you amazing
camera angles on cutting you like that
incredible
so what i'm doing is i'm cutting inside
this
a little bit
i cut inside down in here i don't like
doing this let me show you what happens
when you cut the cauliflower like that
right
when you cut it like that
it just it flakes everywhere you see all
the little pieces
so i don't like to do that
what i like to do is i cut it down in
here
and then i section off so they all stay
nice and and whole look at that right
you guys see that on tick tock
there you go you guys do that too is
this something that you guys do as well
right where you do it that way
i just section it all off like that
how about that
and then i break the small pieces i put
the small pieces into the food processor
which i'm gonna do
okay so i'm gonna do that over here now
on rumble you can see this in tik tok
you guys can't really see me over here
on on telegram but i'm gonna bring it
over all right let me do that for a
second
let me bring this over little food
processor i got here
and i'm going to put these pieces right
here
now you'll do that heidi says now i will
great tip lemon balm love says live my
love danielle great tip i make such a
mess when i cut the cauliflower
it does it makes a terrible mess doesn't
it
all right this is working
this is going
great there we go
so i'm pulsing you don't want to make a
smoothie you don't want to make a
cauliflower smoothie keep that in mind
okay you don't want to make a
cauliflower smoothie right so you want
to dump this in here
there you go
all right we're going to knock some more
pieces in there we don't want to make a
cauliflower smoothie that's the last
thing we want keep that in mind
yeah
sarah says but if you are going to mince
it what is the problem cutting the other
way
well what happens is is that
most people are not going to make it
their cauliflower rice they're just
going to cut their cauliflower on the
board and throw it nicely in a salad
so that's a tip for every reason and
when you cut it the other way and you
want to put it in a salad it just starts
to break apart and crumble and then it's
not doesn't have that pretty look or
maybe maybe you want to make a crude
it's hay and you want them perfect for
your crude hay for dipping right and
then what you did was you ended up
cutting it like this and it just started
to fall apart when it was cutting these
little pieces were popping off and then
it just it ends up kind of falling apart
like it was when i was first cutting all
those big pieces so there's a lot of
reasons i was just covering that tip for
a second because it covers everything
it's a great way to really keep it
intact and you know what you get all
these little pieces on the board if you
cut it that way you got a board full of
this stuff
look you can get cauliflower rice in the
store so i want to show you guys
right that's cauliflower rice you can
get in the store you guys on
telegram you guys on tiktok
right there's the cauliflower rice
you can get that right in the store just
like that frozen frozen section or fresh
section
it could be in the fresh or frozen
you don't have to
you don't have to make your own rice
you don't have to do it this way
i'm pulsing it right here see
now remember i'm not making a smoothie
you don't want this you don't want
you don't want that
because what's going to happen you're
going to go too far and you're going to
go too long and then you're going to
have
cauliflower mush
kind of like cauliflower mush right is
what you're going to end up with and you
don't want to have that
look at that isn't that great
all right
so i think what i'm going to do is cut
an onion we're going to get an onion in
here too
so that's the plan
i'm going to move this over
you can you can save that too you can
use that you can turn that into rice too
that core cauliflower core you can
totally turn into rice that's perfectly
fine
nothing wrong with that i'm gonna go
with an onion i'm gonna go with a white
onion right here
remember how i taught you guys that
that's the sweet part the top of the
onion
that's the roots you see the roots right
there i don't know if you see those
roots okay
so
a lot of cauliflower hanging around here
i don't know if you see those roots
that's the bitter part of the onion if
you're making a salad someone's going to
get the bitter part of the onion and
when somebody gets a bitter part of the
onion
then your salad was
you know could it could throw somebody
off
and they'll be like yeah it was all
right that's the right salad
so that's the bitter part of the onion
right there so what i do is i usually
save that for other things like a soup
or something right so sometimes i just
leave that part out so i'm gonna peel
this back
a little bit
okay there you go
all right
i'm gonna peel that part back right
and then
i'm gonna cut this
so that's the sweet part top of the
onion where the greens were that's the
sweet part right there okay
i'm cutting tiny pieces i don't want big
hunks but there's a couple of bigger
hunks but they're not so big
that's the bottom right there that's the
part that's a little bit bitter and you
can cut that bitter part off like that
there you go
believe it or not when someone gets that
it's not a pleasing thing they don't
know sure you're smothering it with
ranch dressing you may not notice
but there's a lot of people that pick
subtle flavors up everywhere and or you
know flavors that are a little bit more
bitter or intense and they get thrown
off by by everything
just moving stuff over here giving
myself a little bit of room
we're going to chop up these onions
if you guys just came on
we're making stuffed butternut squash
i'm making the stuffing we're also going
to make some brussels sprouts some
roasted brussels sprouts which are
really good maple roasted right
corny mma says your hands are incredible
i'm honored
hopefully i don't cut my hand
so i'm chopping up the onions there's
different ways of chopping these onions
you know
i'm trying not to blow your ears out too
with any noise but there's different
ways of chopping them you can do you
guys have your techniques i'm sure right
so i'm making small pieces now with
onions remember once they cook down
they kind of get a little bit
translucent
they start to
break down better
there we go
let's get these in here
that's a whole nice big yellow onion
see if it gets my eyes
there we go
so
you guys let's take a look at the
recipes why this is cooking for a second
recipes are in the books i'm going to
make the maple roasted brussels sprouts
you guys in tik tok i hope you stick
around for that
you guys in rumble
i'm going to make those okay that's in
river rescue right there
hopefully you got a copy of liver rescue
someday
and then cleanse the heel
cleanse the heel
let's see what we have here
covers are slipping on me there
that's the stuff butternut squash right
there i'm making which is really great
and that's in cleanse the heel
so that's there
kendall says buy his books
or get them free at the library recipes
are in the books and there's lots of
recipes
dr von md good to see you
so this is the medical medium cooking
show we just moved it out of amazon
amazon had a tech problem now we're here
and what we're doing is we're going to
go over some tips on some squash i'm
going to let this cook down a little bit
is what i'm going to do
i'm going to get the lid
like that
keep that lid on let that cook up i'm
going to clean off the board a touch
because what happens is when you cut
this squash you want to make sure you
don't have anything on the board that's
really important to know you don't want
the squash slipping on you when you're
trying to run that knife through it
always be cautious
when you're dealing with these squashes
make sure the board is dry so i got this
towel right here
so make sure the board is dry
right
like that
make sure the board is definitely got
it's not wet because you don't want the
squash to slip when you're cutting it
keep that in mind right this is holiday
recipe right here i mean the maple
roasted brussels sprouts it's insane
it's so good i can't wait to eat it i'm
actually really really hungry right now
because we're delayed okay so here's a
couple of tips right here
on the squash this is a kombucha squash
right not kombucha tea
about your squash not kombucha tea right
so keep that in mind all right
and
what i'm doing is i'm taking my knife
right this knife right here
and i'm cutting this out
carefully
kind of putting my thumb on here
so i'm holding the knife in a special
way i'm not putting my knife under the
blade right here i'm not putting my my
hand under the blade
i'm holding the knife but i'm putting my
thumb thumb up closer to the knife like
that right
and this is how i do it okay and this is
where you don't get cut
and i'm taking out this really hard part
right there
taking that off
because i've seen it over and over again
over the years somebody's grandmom
somebody's granddad somebody's uncle
somebody's aunt sweeney's nephew
somebody ends up biting on that at the
table somewhere and then someone's
getting to the dentist with an emergency
dental problem
so i like taking that really hard part
off
so that's important there and then i
take this one off right here
this is the other part the bottom of the
squash not the stem but the bottom there
we go
take that off
like that
i do that because i've seen them the
squash is baked boom they're baked and
then someone gets that last piece
last piece all right so i'm gonna i'm
gonna put my knife through it okay so
now i'm gonna put my knife through this
squash
you gotta be really careful when you do
these really careful
right kind of go around like that
very cautious so now you got the inside
i mean is that gorgeous you want to see
that on tick tock you guys a little
close up
right
[Music]
that's the inside the squash
now here's a cool tip
okay on telegram did you guys see
right
you know some people leave the seeds in
scoop them out later after they they
baked it
i take the seeds out because for for one
i'm gonna stuff this one so i want the
seeds out most everybody takes the seeds
out
which is gorgeous and by the way you can
like
you can throw these in a pan
and actually have them pop like popcorn
you throw them in a pan and they they
start to toast up and then you can
actually eat the insides which is really
incredible the insides of these big
squash seeds
now here's the important thing right
here which is a medical medium unique
tip
so
i have to say that because someone would
say oh he's not giving any unique tips
false advertising
no
lots of unique tips for sure now what
people don't realize is that fur that's
left behind
here that fur okay not that seed get
that seed out
but that fur is bitter
and everybody leaves it in
and their squash experience isn't as
great as it should be it's not as great
as it should be so it should be a better
squash experience
but that fur is left behind you want to
scrape that out because it doesn't taste
good it doesn't taste like that sweet
squash is supposed to taste it's got an
entirely different flavor
so you want to scrape that out and i
people don't know that this is bitter
and doesn't have a good flavor they
don't know that that's going to make
their squash dish not that great
they don't know this
so what i'm doing is getting that out
there it is
that's the pulp with the fur on it
on telegram tick-tock yes that's it
that won't make that dish
taste good
it will be okay everybody will have
squash their stuff squash they'd be like
okay that was good but not boom mind
blown not like wow
marjus says new information for me cool
light culture says oh wow i never knew
that
well that's why we're here that's what
we're doing you guys just so you know
that's the whole point of the medical
medium cooking show i was trying to do
on amazon
i did not know that keaton says
there's lots of tips to come
and
this is going to be really cool
all right
so i got to give you another tip which
is really good to know
so let's find the squash
i got one right here butternut squash
right
we're live the squash left the counter
and hit the floor
and that's why we do everything live all
the time because
it's just kind of just it's just
whatever whatever happens you just it's
okay hey
that squash went flying
that's all i can tell you
all right you want to take the top off
the squash when you're doing the
butternut squash okay
[Music]
so i'm taking that off
you want that stem off
yeah that squash was too shy uh-huh
courtney's laughing frugivore there
right now you want to take this part off
too you want to cut
the butternut the back part off maybe
we'll get a
close-up in a minute but i want to cut
that off
just you don't want to cut a lot of it
like you don't want to cut all that
part off you just want to cut a thin
slice at the back of your butternut
squash
right joshua says mmm saved my life a
monitor here josh
so there it goes
that's really uncomfortable to eat right
there
really uncomfortable to eat even when
it's baked
it's not a great thing to eat right
there
and it's bitter as hell it's bitter as
hell
it just is
so
so here we go
let's get into the squash a little bit
that's what we're going to do
now you'll see a divot missing in the
squash why is there a divot missing
hold on you guys i just want to do
something
i want to i want to move this around a
little bit
maybe get a close-up on this pan too
can you guys see that up there a little
bit of a close-up
all right
this is cauliflower pulsed in the food
processor you can get the bagged
cauliflower rice
you can get the bag cauliflower rice
right there there it is
any brand you want right
yeah
i'm going to throw a few more mushrooms
in here in a minute i think we're
lacking a few mushrooms why not
let me do that first before i
move on
all right
so here we go i'm going to throw a few
more mushrooms in here really quick
there you go
gonna get a few more mushrooms in here
there we go
all right
this is cooking up nice
on the little burner so let's take a
look at this
so we have is the butternut squash
i cut off the ends there's a divot in
here
why
because there was a pretty big hole
poked into this i see it all the time in
the market
and what people don't realize
is those holes
right here's one here
those gashes
were equipment gashes
that was equipment gashes
equipment
that you don't know what's on it you
don't know what's on that farm equipment
you don't know what's on that grocery
store equipment you don't know what's on
the
the you know you don't know what's on
that
right
so what you want to do is carve out any
suspicious hole or
mark that's big enough you carve it out
now the squash that hit the floor
which i'm just gonna grab for a second
this is a squash that ran away the
squash did not want to be cut open it's
a shy squash okay
now
let's see if there's any marks on this
one because i thought there was one
there's a little one on this one here's
one right here
it's right there
wait here we go right there see that
mark
i'm gonna cut that out
i cut that off
so i'm gonna put that over here
that was on the floor so i'm not gonna
put on the cutting board even though the
floor is clean so over here
so anyway
the bottom line is what i'm trying to
say is we don't know what's on that
equipment we don't know what's on that
whatever went into i've seen some gashes
in some of the big
big squashes and other things like that
and those gashes
there's grease on that equipment
so a little bit of grease goes into like
because i've seen all the farm equipment
i've walked on a lot of farms i've
visited a lot of farms visit some
friends farms i've spent all around and
all that farm equipment there's grease
on every tractor grease on everything
and what happens is people don't realize
this so when you see when you see
injuries to things you want to cut them
out because you can have some grease and
that's another original medical medium
tip
which is really important let's cut this
open actually let's do that so
let me make sure the board's not wet
okay
so you don't want the board wet when
you're cutting your squashes you can
even put a towel down so you can
actually put a towel down while you're
cutting it too
but
this is a pretty dry board
chris says i work on a small scale
organic farm it's hard haha yeah i know
i can't
i could imagine i know i understand
right so here's the butter butternut
squash right so i'm gonna cut this one
now what i what i don't like about
squashes is cutting them i don't like it
right
because you to be really careful you got
to be really careful when you're cutting
this can't can't be reckless you got to
be cautious so here we go
same rule applies with every single
squash
every single squash you scoop out
not just the seeds
not just the seeds of the squash
right
but you scoop out more than the seeds
you scoop out the fur
that fur you don't want to be baking and
eating
it's not going to hurt you it's just not
going to make a pleasant flavor you're
going to go into this part of the squash
which is the sweetest part of squash and
then there's this bitter side to it
right there
and you're gonna be like what i thought
i had the swedish squash the sweetest
one and it's not so sweet so i'm gonna
scoop this one out too right
so you wanna get
that out
now i stuffed this butternut squash that
i that i've already cooked that we're
gonna fill and prepare and all that
okay here we go
right so what i did was
then you get this fur too out of here
so if your squash has it up here you
want it up there too you'll know because
if you cook this and you just eat this
part by itself you'll be like that just
didn't taste great
but when you get it out
when you get it out
wow
tastes amazing now what i did with this
squash because i'm i'm stuffing these
squashes
and baking them i cut a divot in here
like this
i wanted to make sure i had some
stuffing room
so i cut a divot right in the center a
little bit just a little piece is what i
did
like that
and so when i filled it
i got room
and that's what's happening with this
one right here which is a cooked one
right here which i'm excited about
lake culture says
now it makes sense why my pumpkin dishes
taste different each time gotta remove
the fur you got same thing same thing
with the pumpkin identical thing with
the pumpkin it's identical
same problem so i'm gonna move this over
a little bit
i want to show you tip we're doing
brussels sprouts i'm going to show you
that as well a couple cool tips about
brussels sprouts
right so i'm going to get this cleaned
up just give me a second you guys
so the one thing about the holidays is
that
you gotta keep a light heart when you're
making food for family and friends
and you gotta have fun doing it and it
doesn't have to be perfect
never have it never has to be perfect
but there's these cool things you can do
to make it taste better right so which
is really great
all right
so i cleared off that but let me just
see if the stuffing is nice and done
all right this is done now now i'm going
to add
some maple syrup to this
right
add a little bit of maple syrup
because i want this to taste incredible
and i'm going to add some lemon juice to
this too
add some lemon as well
there we go
a little bit more lemon
make it really pop
right
mix it up because i got that maple syrup
in there now i'm mixing it up with lemon
it's just really delicious
i'm going to put some dried thyme in
here
right pinch of dried thyme
how about that
and now i'm going to stuff
these turkeys
you know as i'm talking about earlier
these are these aren't turkeys i was
talking about this earlier you guys
that
i never liked that whole turkey gizzard
thing
turkey heart turkey gizzard because
that's what's in there i forget to put a
little garlic in there so let me get a
garlic clove going
right
i never liked that whole stuff the
turkey gizzard
like with the gizzards and the heart
because it's like you got a little heart
little turkey heart in your hand right
you know in the bag that comes in you
pull the bag out of the turkey
if you like turkey that's great i mean
it's you can still do turkey in medical
medium
but when you pull that bag out
trisha murray says me neither you pull
that bag out and it's got all that stuff
in there right it's got the liver that's
the gizzard thing it's got the liver
right
and it's got a heart
so you look at the heart you're like
well what do i do with this heart will
you chop it up because you put it in
there for flavor
i just never really like that i'm just
mincing some garlic real quick you guys
quick mince with with the knife
there we go
if you just got here re-watch i'm gonna
post it after post it on rumble post it
on youtube
post it on telegram
there we go we got some garlic in there
that'll go good when it's
when it's baking in the oven
all right let's stuff
these squashes
let's do
that you can put a little bit of salt in
here
you're welcome to do that
right so you can do that if you want a
little bit of salt in there you can put
a little bit of salt in here
i usually keep the salt out
you know that's what i do i keep the
salt out
all right so here we go
let's take a look
so
if you can see and you can get a
close-up on this if you want to there
you go
look at that it's like a pie it's like a
pie crust
right telegram take a look tic tac it's
a pie crust that's what it's like
so i'm gonna fill it
look at that
how incredible is that right
so i'm filling this
pie crust basically
okay so there's one right there let's
get another
and
i got another one right here
you don't have to make your own
cauliflower rice you can
buy the rice minced in the store
there you go look at that
that that's so good that's insanely good
i love that
i'm going to get these back
on the pan
now i'm going to bring these over here
this is the butternut right here okay
why are you cooking too long not sure if
this tastes good
if it's over or well done
well the thing is you don't want the
carrots
hard
right
i don't have the heat on too high but
you don't want the carrots hard
you want to make sure those are cooked
because the squash are already cooked
they're already done so when i'm
throwing this in at 400 heat in a minute
to just basically really you know and
you want the cauliflower to cook the
problem is is the cauliflower takes a
little longer cauliflower rice
you don't want that hard either
you want these just cooked right they're
not super soft but they're not
hard right that's that's why
so what i'm doing is popping this on
like that
there we go
all right so we got these all set these
are going in the oven
guys give me a second
i'm gonna pop these in
so that's what we have and that's what's
going on right there
maybe i'll drop this whole thing by
accident on my way it'll come off
that's what happens when you're live you
don't know what could happen
that is
an amazing pan right there
all right so that's in the oven
i'm gonna clean up the board for a
minute you guys give me a second here
so the thing is is
what you you want if you want your stuff
to taste really good all these little
tips matter too which is really great so
i'm gonna show you some brussels sprouts
i'm gonna do a little brussels sprout
dish
so
i got some brussels sprouts right here
okay here we are
now these aren't raw
i lightly steamed these
because what happens is when you roast
brussels sprouts
they'll be tough
like chewy and tough
that that's hard on a lot of people for
a lot of reasons not so easy to digest
when they're tough and chewy and just
not that fun you want them roasted but
yet kind of creamy inside a little bit
roasted and crispy on the top and on the
edges
but creamy inside like that's what you
want so those are the steamed ones right
there
so what i'm going to do is cut some of
these
right here
right and i'm going to put these right
up here in front of here for you
if you guys can see those a little bit
so i'm just going to cut these up
i'm going to cut them in half
i'm going to move them out
i'm going to cut them in half like this
so these are going to be the maple
roasted
brussels sprouts
right here
i got a couple of raw ones i want to
show you a tip on that
which is going to be cool
but i like to steam these a little
because you can roast them
all you want in there raw to start with
and what happens is they're going to be
tough and chewy they're just going to be
tough and chewy that's what they're
going to be
so i'm giving these guys all a little
bit
of a cut right here you guys see this on
telegram
all right
get some more
now i did a big batch
i steamed them for about 20 minutes
you can even steam them for 30 minutes
you can try you can check them out but i
steamed them for
20 to maybe 25 minutes is what i did
there we go
did you cut the ends off okay good
question i did it
because if you steam them
if you steam them they still come they
come out really good those ends see
that's the end right there so you're
talking about that end and i saved this
one on purpose to show you this right
here right so what's interesting here is
you got this end right here it's
sticking out right
so you got this end
and
what's happening is you can you can eat
that end
when it's cooked
but that's why steaming is really good
you steam for 25 minutes all this at
least starts to soften up if you steam
them longer this is all tender here i
know a lot of people do this a lot of
people will cut this end off like that
so they'll cut the end completely off i
keep them on even when there's that
piece right there i still keep them on
but you're welcome to cut them off
definitely right
you're definitely welcome to do that
and
there we go
do some more
i'm gonna make a nice big batch
i got the squashes in the oven i could
smell them already
if you guys don't like maple syrup
you can use honey if you want
if you're if you're somebody that just
won't do maple syrup for some reason you
can use honey and that's okay
right
let's cut a few more
and then we're
good we'll get the rest of these done
so i'm cutting these in half
did i cut the ends off didn't cut the
ends off
kept the ends i always keep my ends on
these
when it comes down to brussels that's
how i do it all right
let's get these back in the bowl and
then
make a nice dressing to put in here
heli says
healy says your
advices has been a life changer i'm 69
and i don't need glasses anymore have no
back pain no knee pain no pain at all my
whole body is stronger thanks so much
incredible incredible
what's funny is the amazon live i did i
didn't wear my glasses because i don't
need glasses
and people say well he's wearing glasses
he can't fix his eyes
i got incredible vision all right let's
make a sauce everybody
who knows medical meme information knows
why i wear them because when i'm around
people
there's a lot of light coming through
because of soc spirit of compassion and
then i squint
and what happens is you guys don't know
but i'm squinting all the time and so if
i take off the glasses
you're then gonna notice it i hide the
squint that i've had since age four
but the site's fantastic so it's all
good all
right people around me family and
friends
they see me without my glasses
and people who are close you know i'm
even close up to me all the time
i don't wear them all right so what i'm
doing is i'm getting some maple syrup
right here
i'm making a dressing
is what i'm doing
this is 100 100 pure
gotta make sure it's 100 pure maple
syrup that's really important to do so i
got that
i'm going to do some lemon now
cut a couple lemons here
squeeze the lemon in here how you guys
doing on telegram
so we're going to squeeze these lemons
in like that
dear appleman good to see
so you you're here those look like meyer
lemons cat ladoo said they're actually
not they look like it but they're not
that's what's really funny they're
actually
you know
they're actually not meyer lemons which
is great now you can add some spices to
this
which i like to do
so i'm going to add a garlic clove i'm
going to mince a garlic clove let me do
that
i got a
nice bulb of garlic right here
okay
so
let's get a garlic clove here
the maple roasted bronze courtney ian
says the maple roasted brussels sprouts
are really good i think you said are
really good
so i'm gonna get a clove of garlic
mince and put here
amy tang says good thank you for
the cooking
inspiration
there we go
get a little bit of that nicely minced
in there
let's see what else we should put in
there let's put some paprika in there
let's do that
we got some paprika right here
get that in there
okay
let's get some cayenne in there right
a little bit of cayenne in there
we don't want it too too hot right
unless you want it really spicy i mean
sometimes i'll even
go spicier
let me put some
some red pepper flakes in there too some
nice red pepper flakes right how about
that and you can go with a little bit of
salt if you want
definitely and you could easily add a
little bit of that let me whisk it
[Music]
do a little bit of whisking here
all right this is going on top of the
bowl
brussels sprouts we're going to add this
in here
right on top and we're going to mix it
up
we're going to do
a little bit of that
so that maple lemon flavor is so good
in these brussels sprouts just delicious
really incredible
there we go
let's get that on a baking pan
so i'm doing that now
just got a little bit of
parchment paper on here
show you guys
all right
so i'm getting these on the pan
what do you guys think on telegram did
you ever have these did you ever make
the recipe
right out of liver rescue
you know what happens is when people
make these recipes
so
save some sauce at the bottom of the
bowl so that's what i recommend okay
so save some of that sauce at the bottom
of the bowl i'm gonna put all these on
here
there we go and i'm gonna spread them
out on the pan look at that
strange how people get mad when you heal
sarah dylan they do get mad
and know what's really strange
is when
tens of thousands and thousands of
people
it goes into millions around the world
and they're healing from the mm info
that's not allowed
because then they'll call you a cult or
something
say oh you're a cult well that's funny
then it must be the biggest cult on the
planet because 500 million people are
drinking celery juice
millions and millions of medical medium
books are out there in almost every
country in the world
i guess we're just not allowed to heal
or something
it's the craziest thing i've ever seen
and it's all free
does that make any sense it's all free
go to library and get the book
meanwhile you got the medical colts
are scary
you got the alkaline ionizer water
machine colts you guys i got this set up
here
you got the you got the caffeine product
colts oh man that's a dangerous industry
that caffeine industry
you got all that stuff you guys
i got these ready to go in the oven okay
so what i'm gonna do
i'm gonna take a look at that squash
how about if we do that
wow
that's that's coming together really
nice
just gonna make a little bit of room
over here
amazing
cleaning off the spot
be open-hearted
don't know if you heard me but i was
thanking you in my prayers yesterday aw
bless your heart
i i see your comments on youtube too all
the time and i'm like hey there you are
incredible
yep
lamb lamb tail says yep bro
yum bro give us a shout out the spirit
of compassion
that's great trisha marie says delish
i'm gonna let these cedar for a second i
want to show you a couple tips
let's get another brussels sprout right
here
and i want to show you guys this right
what i do is i peel back the leaf i mean
everybody probably does that
i'm sure a lot of people do that right
if the leaf is yellow or yellowing you
want to take that leaf off
that leaf
tastes
terrible
terrible so when you get the yellow
leaves
on your brussels sprouts
awful flavor
it'll ruin it'll ruin the whole brussels
sprout because the yellow leaf
decayed
and so it's just got this awful oxidized
flavor it could ruin it just ruins your
whole dish so what i did was i picked
off all the yellow leaves
right i'll show you guys on a close-up
too i picked up all i picked them all
off so this is a raw brussels sprout
these are steamed in here
amber says starting the cleanse with mom
whoa incredible
so what i do is i take this off
when they're yellow or decayed on any
level and right there there's that dk on
there it's on there i know if you guys
can see it it's basically just plant
decay it's it's
it's leaves that have gone bad on here
so i kind of pull back that leaf that
one's really stuck on
but i pull that leaf off like that
there you go aj i saw you
there you go and i took that leaf off
these leaves taste terrible when they
start to decay like that
and i know people peel back their
brussels sprouts
i do know that some people do that right
but
the leaf when it's decaying or yellow it
stays in the mix it's going to ruin the
flavor of the whole dish
right
so in rumble kim marie
and cindy you know and ben ben watson
i'm glad you guys are there
glad you guys are on there
so debbie said did he say pull off the
yellow only
you can pull off the yellow only yeah
only
but if you see a leaf that's not yellow
but it's like it's decayed okay here's
one right here
you see this one's not okay here it is
right there that'll show it perfectly
good thing i had one left
see right there you guys a close-up i
know you can't see it on telegram
no maybe you guys can on tick-tock
put that close-up up there
that right there so you can do this you
can even take shortcuts and not peel
back the leaf if you don't want to
that's the leaf i peeled back you can
take shortcuts if you don't want to peel
back the leaf right like you can peel
back that leaf but if you don't want to
you can just do this
if you want
and you get rid of that because that
piece right there will ruin
that taste
of your meal it just does
those leaves when they're they when they
get nasty like that they're nasty to
your meal so that's really important to
know i'm just trying to show everybody
including the close-up right and there
you go on tiktok and pilgrim
dno says hey w i was introduced to you
last week i bought cleanse the heel and
your medical media two great books i
committed to lemon water daily and
celery juice and supplements i plan on
doing a cleanse next week yeah
[Laughter]
proud of you
proud proud proud of you definitely
tristan says you're amazing teacher i'm
sure you are too i'm sure you're amazing
teacher as well
because you know we're all teachers
we're all teachers here right that's
what it is that's what we are
you know we're all trying to teach look
the whole point though is with that
brussels sprout look out for that that's
something to know like i said before if
you're going to steam brussels sprouts
and that's the only way you're going to
make them another tip that's important
when you steam brussels sprouts and it's
the only way you're going to make them
or you're going to cook them in some way
you want to cook them till they're soft
inside until the fork goes through
so let me just show you right here right
like you want to make sure like that
these are still these are only steamed
for 20 minutes 25 minutes right but
there might be a soft one in here okay
here's a soft one
you want to steam them until that fork
goes through
because if you have any digestive issues
whatsoever that's to that's how you
avoid digestive distress you don't want
half cooked brussels sprouts you don't
want chewy brussels sprouts if you're
going to steam them or cook them and
just eat them so you're not even going
to do this roasted brussels sprout meal
out of the book
you want to make sure you steam them
until the fork goes in where it's soft
where they're creamy inside where you
can eat them and they're creamy inside
that's how you want to do it that's
important
for any kind of problems at all
kenneth says maybe that's why i was not
having it when eating steamed brussels
sprouts for three to four days during my
original 369 that's exactly why it can
it
exactly why
you when they're chewy or tough in the
center you're gonna have a tummy full of
roughage that doesn't want to break down
or digest easy
and and what i did here is i steamed
them for 25 minutes and that's not
enough if you just want to have it that
way alone but when i put it in the oven
and then i roast them for a while too
that's where it takes that next level
where they're going to start getting it
you know softer but you can cook them
not roast them you can cook them where
they're where you're steaming them real
soft if you're going to do like a mono
cleanser brussels sprouts or something
like that if you're going to do
something like on the 369 and you're
cleansing you want to cook them when
they're really really soft that's what
you want to do
yep that's important
so
all right so i have these getting ready
right here i'm going to move these over
we still have the cranberry sauce to
make okay so really
just so you know there's going to be a
cranberry sauce on its way to be made
i'm going to move this pan
over right now
i'm going to check the
squash
we are
done
i'm gonna i'm gonna take this out right
now
let's do that
you guys i'm still here i'm just taking
this out of the oven just bear with me
all right
it's really hot but i just brought it up
to you guys that's the roasted
stuffed or the stuffed baked squashes
right i'm gonna pop that right here
and then i'm gonna get these in the oven
right now
that's what we're doing
these are going in
and we're gonna toast these up
those are going to come out nice let's
start making some cranberry sauce
see that a little pan here
right what are you so what are you going
to do with all this food family's going
to eat it
it's going to be fun too i'm looking
forward to it
i can't wait
all right
so this is the cranberry sauce this is
the wild blueberry cranberry sauce which
i really love
so this is the wild blueberries right
there
that's going in the pan
oh man this tastes so good
this is i mean so good
if you guys ever had this you would know
what i'm talking about and your mind
would be blown so i'm gonna put the
cranberries
right here
so
you guys see that
on telegram you guys see that
right
we're gonna cook this down for a while
that's what we need to do
so i'm going to dice up an apple
these apples are incredible
right here
i want to give you a tip on apples
you want to have or enjoy the best apple
do you know do you want to know how to
pick apples
i'm not talking about off the tree
i'm talking about picking them at the
store right
do you want to know how to pick these
apples at the store
you want to look for apple skins
that have
that kind of design those marks you see
this
it's not a perfect
apple
right you don't want bruises there's no
bruises on this apple right there's no
bruises
but the best flavored apples inside have
the skin that looks kind of geographic
see that right there
see how it looks like it's got like
constellations or stars
and that that means that whether it's
honey crisp all the same whether it's
fuji all the same this is what you're
looking for well there's pink lady
that's what you're looking for red
delicious that's what you're looking for
you're looking for the skins to have
like
this
rough patches
where it's like what is that like what's
that rough patch
right that means you have the crispiest
sweetest apples
out of that bunch
okay and the only people that probably
have an idea about that one are apple
growers themselves that are so
they're so used to tasting their own
apples and picking them and and trying
them out and harvesting them that they
know this right they know this and i've
been blessed to know it because i've
picked a lot of apples and so it's
really a special little tip
so i want to do is cut these pieces thin
i want them
thin and small i don't want these pieces
too big because this apple's gonna cook
down
is what it's gonna do so i'm cutting
these pretty thin i want this apple to
cook down in that sauce
all right so i don't want big hunky
pieces in this right
lacey said breath bauer says i had no
idea thank you
that's what the medical medium cooking
show is here for is to make sure that we
can do these things right serena x says
whoa
you will get the best apples and then
everybody else will have these other
apples that aren't the best
lori malone says wow great apple tip
yeah i'm going to show you right here
you see i have a different apple here
right so it's not different apple the
same pineapples now i picked
purposely all these kinds of apples
where they have that geographic zone so
these are all the best apples possible
this has less see see how's this less
this look that has less believe it or
not it has it but less it's not like
that
you see the different difference there
we go
you see that
that's how you pick them in the store
guess which one you pick you pick that
one at the store
i want to show you on tick-tock you pick
the one here
right there you see all that you don't
pick that one you pick this one
yeah
[Music]
it's a tip that you will be so happy
about
along the way i promise you you will be
so happy about you will be like okay
wait a minute and if you have a basket
of apples you you bought a bunch of
different apples you'll know when you
start
trying it out like that
be open-hearted has a question looks
like a question for soc really
because
my brain can't hold
the trillions of pounds of information
from soc every second so why is that the
geographic area right
okay that means that a temperature
change happened
and that temperature temperature change
brought the sweetness out so the
temperature fluctuation spirit of
compassion is telling me right now so
you're
that's how that's because i didn't know
i forgot or didn't know but it's attempt
that means we had we had in that crop
right when it was coming to almost
getting ripe the whole batch of apples
in that crop
we had some temperature changes where
the temperature went really high or low
and most likely the temperature dropped
and went low so that means it might have
been a frost coming on or close to a
frost the temperature spirit compassion
is telling me right now the temperature
dropped to maybe 40 degrees and it
wasn't 40 degrees for a while and it's
the end of august it's the end of
september it's in the middle of october
and then often boom you get a 38 degree
night
and then the the sweetness comes out and
the skin
turns that rough color because of that
temperature shift
because the chemistry of the apple
changes spirit of compassion says it
changes and shifts and then the sugar
comes out to more it comes out of the
core like literally sugar comes right
out of the core and then the core will
be won't be sweet
the core won't be sweet and what happens
is with these other apples when that
doesn't happen in certain crops spirit
of compassion is dumb this is new
information for me i had no idea about
this spirit kabash is telling me right
now that
the core
right
is more sweeter on the not so good
apples and then all the flesh and the
apples when this doesn't happen is not
as sweet so that's a piece of
information i just learned now because
yes you asked
you know
i like learning
i'm learning a heck of a lot right now
with that new book that i'm trying to
finish and hand to the publisher
hopefully soon
i'm learning a lot information about the
human body i had no idea about even all
these years
the book is a massive book
a massive book
so i'm going to get this apple in here
and actually get this apple cooking down
is what we're going to do
so we're going to chop this up
and that's why i wear glasses because if
i answer questions specifically that
spirit of compassion is giving me new
information for in the moment like an
actual read
then
now i'm getting whited out it's called
snow blindness and i talk about it in
here
of how i lose the eyesight from that and
then i'm struggling to actually even see
anything so that's what starts happening
and that's why these are on so that you
don't see me like this
okay and the glasses kind of kind of
hide that when i need to do that like
that sometimes
all right let me get the rest these
apples in while those brussels sprouts
are cooking up
this is an incredible
incredible sauce
it really is
chop the rest of these up
i'm mincing them practically right
because you don't want these big hunky
apple pieces in that sauce because you
want them to break down that's the key
that's that's a really important key
right there so when you do it this way
like that you got it nice and minced up
right
let's get this in here
so if you guys just came on here i'm
making three recipes right smells so
good it's blowing my mind
my mind is blowing
there we go i want to show you guys can
we get a close-up right here real quick
look at that that's the sauce and
how it's just starting to break down the
cranberries and everything you guys on
telegram you guys on tick tock
let's get this back on the burner
let's get that pumping away
cinnamon sticks right you can go with
cinnamon powder
okay
you can do cinnamon sticks if you wanted
to in this
right
okay
and i'm gonna put maple syrup in here
too so i'm gonna put a little bit of
cinnamon in here
there you go
and then i'm gonna do some maple syrup
wow that's gonna be really good
i think i'm gonna put a little bit more
sorry about the
noises over there it seems to be a lot
of noise near the mic
let that cook up nice you guys
all right and then i'm gonna put juice
of one orange let's find an orange let's
go let's do some orange tips
those are my favorite orange tips
right
i like orange tips i like lemon tips
right i like
um tips on grapefruits i just like tips
on all fruits so that's why i like
fruits or fruit tips are my favorite i
guess right
so juice from one orange so one of the
things about oranges
you don't want them soft you don't want
them soft if you guys pick oranges in
the grocery store and you're picking
them soft and they're too soft go with
the hardest oranges go with the harder
ones if you see a good batch of oranges
go with the harder oranges if you go
with an orange that's starting to get
all the dense and it's getting the dense
and it's getting soft like squishy it
still could be a good orange ready watch
this it still could be a good orange
check this out looks amazing
it's incredible
it looks incredible but why did i tell
you not to pick this orange
like why
it looks great but it's got the softness
to it
that's because when you buy a bunch of
these and then you've got them in a bowl
whether they're on the counter or even
in the fridge in a week they're going to
start going bad fast that's why unless
you're going to eat them right now
they're going to start going bad quick
and when you buy oranges you want them
to stick around you want to be able to
have your oranges you want them to be
able to stick around that's what you
want to do and so what happens is is
you know when you get those soft spots
like that and it's soft all the soft
different dents and everything
you just you it's starting to get to a
point where it's shifting gears it's
starting to shift gears
right so i'm doing juice from one orange
but i cut two oranges why not
i'm gonna pop that in here
okay
my screen keeps freezing
adelina
what a bummer
are you going to rumble are you on
facebook because facebook
facebook freezes everything on me
yeah
they freeze everybody out
they hope you go away and don't come
back
so they freeze people out to make them
go away
just go to rumble stay on there
they're not going to freeze you out
there it's rare really rare
right so i'm moving this i'm getting the
sauce this sauce is breaking down
it's really really good
so i wanted to show you that orange
trick right there now you can you can
take a little bit of the skin in the
orange you ready and i'm going to add it
to here to actually give it an extra
twist you can take a little bit of
skinny orange but don't do the white
pith
can you see this you guys
don't do the white pith
right see look at that
see i took that that skin off
right there okay
and there it is i'm gonna take a little
bit more of this orange skin
but i'm not gonna do the pith
right look at that
there you go
okay and i'm gonna dice that up
donna says you're right anthony you do
not find these cooking tips anywhere
loving it
oh you're awesome
well my haters will
will beg to differ
you can bring the most unique
information ever
out
like the blood draw problem if you ever
listen to the blood draw podcast medical
medium podcast apple podcast
or
or a unique tip
the haters will say you know that tips
out there already they'll say celery
juice was out there i never said no one
ever ran a celery stick through a juicer
before
me i never said that
i said no one knew how to use it
therapeutically and not to mix anything
with it
and how to have enough of it and what's
in it that no one knows about and how to
use it like 16 ounces on an empty
stomach half an hour after half an hour
before all these things that are unique
just because someone held a celery stick
in their hand one day before i was born
doesn't mean i didn't have the
information for spirit of compassion on
how to use it therapeutically to save
people's lives right
amber marquis says these tips are
literally from source
and like gold
so
you know what i like repeating some of
the tips too in case other people didn't
see the tips i have so many of them
what's going to happen with the medical
medium cooking show just so you guys
know i'm not going to be doing the
medical medium cooking show on
on these channels here that i'm on now
right
the medical mean cooking show was really
meant for amazon live
right
but we had a tech problem on amazon
today so i took the cooking show here
but what i do here but i don't want you
discouraged what i do on these channels
is i talk about
i talk about um
the medical heavy-duty medical stuff but
we're having a cooking show for fun
right now
yeah so that's cooking up really nice
so
[Laughter]
guys if you see what i just did
i actually stained my beautiful
spatula
so
that's going to be stained for a long
time
and i was really proud of myself for not
doing that for a long time because i was
using a different tool
in there but
it looks like now i'm gonna have a red i
mean a red wooden utensil
so
you were just arguing with mom about
taking only half aisles
darcy lee said i was just arguing with
my mom about only letting them take half
files she said they never heard of that
i go of course they haven't
now she feels horrible and i'm so
frustrated
anybody who doesn't know we're talking
about medical mean podcast at apple
podcast listen to the blood draw vampire
bloodletting episode
it's
critical
critical episode to hear could save a
life could save your life
and
original medical medium information yes
it's what's really funny guys is i'm not
allowed to say oh
it's medical medium information
everybody gets mad
but what am i gonna say if it's
original medical medium information that
comes from spirit of compassion and
nobody knew before am i supposed to just
pretend that's not really it and then i
got it from somebody else when i didn't
this smells amazing by the way amazing
and it's cooking up really quick
actually it's starting to cook up nice
i'm gonna keep the lid on it because i
want the juices to be in there while
that is cooking
and the thing is is how do you help
somebody heal if you don't tell them
about the original medical medium
information right
how are you going to help them find the
rest of it someone can say epstein-barr
but not know all the things they need to
do to heal the problem or not know what
epstein-barr causes it's just it's
critical that people know where the
original information comes from
so
all right so
whoa those are cooking up nice brussels
sprouts are almost done the maple
brussels sprouts
all right so
let's move a little bit into where we're
going next you guys
we might plate some stuff up
so i got these right here
and i'm going to do some plating and i
got a nice plate right here
moving that over
so
these are really hot
putting that one here
those are hot
i don't advise you to use your hands
unless they've cooled down
but i have for some reason an ability
to stand really high intense heat with
my hands
since i was a child
i mean i could grab hot potatoes like
it's nothing
right out of the steamer like it's
nothing
look at that
so
that's the big squash which is
incredible now you can cut it like a
pizza pie
you can do it that way you can serve it
like that you can take a knife and and
cut it in pieces and serve it on
you know an individual plate
you can easily do that
so that's one one way to do it too and
i'll cut them up too in a little bit
you can do this for thanksgiving you can
do this for christmas what an incredible
recipe it really is
i'm gonna put a little bit of a garnish
on top of this are you guys okay i might
put a little parsley garnish on top got
some beautiful
leafy green parsley
right leafy greens
no one
unfortunately
knew
that you can take these herbs and eat
them in high quantity like a leafy green
and you can and it's so great so i'm
going to cut up a little bit of parsley
you don't have to have a lot
just a little bit it's fine
i it blows people's minds every day it's
like what do you mean a leafy green
a salad like yeah it's called really
having a big plate of cilantro and
parsley and eating them like a leafy
green that's a great way to heal
let's put this on here put a little bit
on here
just right on top you don't need a lot
for this
because you're not having leafy greens
in this meal really you're not do unless
you make a big salad a leafy green salad
but you're not having that kind of meal
okay alessa says
my neurologist says that i have to have
sir my neurologist says that i have to
have the blood draw drawn so that he can
keep an eye on my levels
right
you should listen to medical medium
look at the the blood draw podcast too
and you did oh wait you did
wait a minute let me
hold on you know what's funny i got this
thing cooking and cranking and i'm
trying to keep an eye on it hold on
there we go i turned the heat down the
heat was really high for some reason on
here and just pumping
this is coming out really good
what happens is doctors don't know they
don't have to take a lot of blood
i'm going to get a pop really quick i
don't usually take a prop out during the
medical medium cooking show but i'm
going to do that for now
and
so i'll give you a little bit of
information about this this will be
interesting
there we go
that cranberry sauce is going to be done
in just a couple of minutes which is
incredible
okay
so
let's just say that
let's just say that the blood lab needed
to test for something like an a a
anti-nuclear antigen test
thyroid panel
a1c
check out the kidneys
sodium levels potassium levels
a whole bit right
nutritional a nutritional panel
right a metabolic panel liver enzyme
test the whole bit
they only need this much blood
that's all they need
i'll show you guys on a close-up i don't
think i've ever had ability to show you
guys on a close-up they only need that
much blood
that's it
they can take a speck of blood
right smaller than that a speck like a
speck you can't see on here like a speck
and i'll put a speck you see i put a
little green speck right there
see a green speck
they can take dehydrated blood
from a murder scene
50 years ago on a pair of jeans that
were buried in a shallow grave
that only had a speck of blood on that
pair of jeans
way less than that
and they can do a thyroid panel
not metabolic panel a a
they could do a lyme disease test they
can do mt if mthfr gene mutation tests
they can do everything sodium levels
nutritional panels all of it
just so you know
check out medical medium podcasts at
apple podcast the blood draw episode
so important
so important and
so
they take the blood on purpose
they rob the blood on purpose
and all it does is send people backwards
and backwards and backwards so when i
tell my friends and family ask for half
files or quarter vials well i'll tell
them to ask for quarter vials
quarter vials they can fill up each tube
with a quarter
quarter tubes quarter each two quarter
amount in each two
so that you're not losing all of your
blood they don't need a lot of blood to
make a serum
so what happens is that
when you've got chronic illness and
you're sick i mean that'll trash you
next thing you know you're sicker and
then sicker and then you lose your
immune system and you're sicker and now
you catch something and then you're
sicker and then you lose your immune
system and you're sick and they take
more blood take more blood take more
blood
and that's what they do
all right so
yeah i think i added the orange but i'm
double checking i think i did i think i
added the orange i'm gonna add a little
bit more there we go
add a little bit more okay so this
cranberry sauce looks like it's getting
there i better check the brussels
sprouts let's hope they're not burned
those babies are done
all right you guys i'm gonna take these
out
here they are
right here
they're not burnt they're just toasted
up nice if i left them in there for 10
more minutes they would probably start
to burn but those are just toasted up
nice right there
[Music]
cooling those down then i'm going to
plate it up
so just give me a minute on that
and i'm gonna get this cranberry sauce
plated up too
okay
so this cranberry sauce is so insanely
good you guys i can't even tell you it's
like insanely good
right
hmm
wait
all right
[Music]
so i'm gonna get this in the jar right
here
this is just incredible stuff this this
cranberry sauce it's a wild blueberry
cranberry sauce so good i can't even
tell
i can't even tell you but i am telling
you guys it's that good
all right
seriously
like seriously
like so
good to put the little spoon in there
check this out i love this
that is really incredible it's piping
hot
so good smells so good
anything you see here i have it linked
on amazon on my amazon live shopping
spot just so you know
that's where i have it
because it's stuff that i use so showing
you guys stuff that i use so it's
awesome
all right so let's let's figure out how
to plate all this stuff and everything
let's get this off of here
i don't think you guys want to see that
yep
uh link is on previous video description
all right
i'm gonna clean this up if you guys can
just give me a couple of seconds
anthony i'm going to make the sauce no
way amanda the color makes it so good
can you tell me
all about the trails
all right
let's go
let's plate stuff up
you guys pointing to this for you this
is going in
so i'm putting these on here
these are really good because they were
steamed before
so they're going to be really really
nice and
and soft inside so i'm going to bring
this over so just give me a few seconds
here so i'm not over here
all right
there we go
guys can you see this how about that
does that work better
plating this up nice looking good
oh that's insane
that maple just shines through
look
i really love these
get as many as i can on here for you
how's it look tick tock how does it look
you guys telegram does it look okay
whoa that one wasn't cut
that one was hot
very hot
you can ask for pedia pediatric um
biles
small one
there we go
okay
i just want to show you this real quick
all right now you're supposed to have
some leftover sauce here
and i do
so i'm going to get some leftover sauce
on there we go
[Music]
and that's that right there
that's an incredible dish i just want to
tell you guys right there
so good
okay so
cranberry sauce on
for you
okay
and then you got these
right here
a lot of moving parts
and then i'm going to get these squashes
over here to you guys
now
that's what i talk about a feast that's
what i call a beast right there i don't
know if you guys see that
it's roasted kabocha squash roasted
butternut squash
man the stuffing i can't wait to get
into that stuffing i can't even wait
like i am i'm definitely gonna get into
that stuffing a little bit
amazing
brian says this man's dedication to
people's health day in and day out
forever is probably the most impressive
thing i've seen out of my living person
ever out of any living person ever
ryan jefferson i'm honored man
i truly am i can't even tell you
like that what how that makes me feel
seriously i mean i don't have words to
describe it really
and uh
hits me in the core and it hits me right
in the heart in a good way in just a
good way
anyway
so i'm moving this over in front of you
a little bit i'm going to take one off
yep i'm going gonna plate it up
so i'm gonna do a plate with a little
bit of everything
so
i'm gonna do some brussels sprouts over
here
okay and then i'm gonna get
you can even take the stuffing out if
you want put it on the dish
so good
right
i'm gonna put a few more in here
all right there we go let's get a little
bit of that going on
all right
that's one thing i want to do i'm going
to move this over for a little bit
a second
i'm going to take one of these
right
and
you can put it like this if you want
there you go
and that's not the butter that's a
kabocha one that's not the butternut
squash which is incredible you guys
i'm pumped up i can't wait to eat
and then a cranberry sauce you can put
it on top
right there
cranberry sauce you put it on top you
can put on the side i'm gonna put it on
the side right here of these it's piping
hot
hot cranberry sauce
that's the thing too it's hot piping hot
look at that you guys see the steam
coming off of that
right is that incredible it's so good
yeah so good got a little cranberry all
over my hand
all right
you guys this is amazing
amazing day
here we go
if you guys can see that up close
telegram can you see that
these all look amazing debbie gail says
cold white spring says i'm envious about
that meal
honored
you guys it's for great for
thanksgiving great for christmas great
for any time you can do it anytime you
want
proud of all of you i just want to say
and thanks for being here the medical
medium cooking show
this was so great
incredible and check out amazon live
because
that's where i'm going to be doing the
medical medium cooking show so make sure
you check that out when you get a chance
all right guys i love you greatly