hello
the doctor's ready to talk to me been
waiting for hours
okay
great he's uh he's coming up okay
doc dr joni
yeah
yeah thank you for taking your time out
for your busy day i know you got
hundreds of patients yeah
so when i left your office i didn't know
exactly what you meant
what yeah the chocolate cake how much
chocolate cake can i have
yeah was it
a slice a day you said moderation and
i'm trying to figure this out like the
moderation thing
yeah because my moderation's different
than your moderation possibly
because it sounded like to me you have
chocolate cake
on the weekends i think you were telling
me and then i realized when i came back
home that i i'm not having chocolate
cake on the weekends i'm having
chocolate cake tuesday night
yeah thursday night
and friday night
and i think if there's leftover
chocolate cake i'm gonna have it on
sunday night too
and then if there's a little left over
i'm gonna have some for monday morning
with my coffee
is that okay
the thing is i don't want to waste the
cake when i buy a chocolate cake
i have a lot of leftover cake and i
can't afford to keep on i can't throw
away the cake
so how do i freeze it
okay i could freeze the chocolate cake
that's why that's why
it's amazing i got such an incredible
doctor
you're no no you're welcome you're
welcome you are that amazing of a doctor
dr
dr joni
yeah i got another question too so
so then
so that takes care of the chocolate cake
so i also like to have some popcorn
movie theater popcorn yeah my friend
goes to see the movies and then brings
me back a whole bunch of it
when do i do the popcorn
in between a chocolate cake okay so this
this moderation thing i'm really liking
this moderation
so i can have
can i have the whole thing you don't
know what i have in my hand you can't
see it okay i have a really big thing of
popcorn right here so do half of this is
that what you're saying a quarter
i could do a quarter of this popcorn
three times a week
okay
okay i could do that but there's going
to be a leftover quarter
because that's three times a week four
times a week is four quarters
yeah so i could do four times a week
okay that's why i had such a smart
doctor
yeah thank you for helping me out with
that i
i
what
yeah
listen you know that
that
what
i i want to tell you about this other
thing i do
yeah the moderation thing just has my
head so messed up i've been sick so long
and i want to heal and get better and i
needed a doctor like you oh wait
someone's calling and patching in
i got to patch them in here
um
dr joni just hold on a second
okay
i just don't know how this phone okay
hello
my naturopath yes put my naturopath on i
got my md on the other line my
naturopath because you have to have a
naturopath too
yeah hey
hey
dr jesuit
that yes i got my md dr joni on the
other line i wish i can connect you guys
can i connect you guys
all right i'm gonna connect you guys
okay we're back we're all on
dr joni dr jesuit you guys there that's
dr joney that's my naturopath right
there
yeah he says moderation is good too
so i would
yeah moderation
so i have sausages right here these are
really good cured sausages
and they've been hanging up
in the
in the grocery store
and there's even some mold on them yeah
these are really good i really love the
flavor of these can you guys can i have
these
wait is that dr jesse with the
naturopath i can have these how often
once a week that's great
dr joni once a week is good okay i'm
glad you guys are in agreement i love
when my doctors are in agreement
that's my favorite thing i got my
medical doctor in agreement i got my
naturopathic agreement yeah wait you
guys i got another phone call coming
through
hold on
but
got another one i'm patching through
another phone call here
yep
oh what oh hold on
hello
yeah
hey oh my trainer yes my trainer exactly
my trainer really believes in moderation
i'm gonna patch my trainer in with dr
joni dr jesuit
you guys i'm patching you guys hey you
guys are all there
hey hi yeah we're all here we're all on
hey you guys my trainer i i want you to
meet my trainer yeah
we
he he believes in moderation too he says
i just have to work the calories off i
have to work the calories off if i can
keep up with the workouts i can keep the
calories off and then i can do whatever
i want moderation
i'm so glad all you guys are into the
moderation thing this is amazing because
i have the best team the best healthcare
team ever
yeah because i hear everybody's
healthcare team believes in moderation
i got one more phone call coming in hold
on you guys i'm patching one more call
wait this one came through already oh my
acupuncturist
are you there
dr dr chi my acupuncturist
okay
you guys so my acupuncturist is on board
my acupuncturist says that i can have
some moderation too but not to do a lot
of raw foods
not to do a lot of raw lettuces
no bananas right
so what is good
i could have bone broth
okay i could do some bone broth is it
okay if i have dr g
is it okay if i have a little bit of
pizza once in a while
once every week
okay
slice a pizza
my acupuncture says once a week as long
as it's gluten free i'll make sure
i can have chocolate cake four to six
times four times a week i think popcorn
four times a week i can have a sausage
every day my trainer says i need the
protein the sausage is good protein just
one sausage every day
i
yeah you guys
you guys this is the best healthcare
you know the healthcare system is so
amazing
and you guys are the best practitioners
and doctors
i just want to tell you thank you for
taking care of my health so good
i'm really i'm getting choked up now
yeah i'm just drinking the coffee right
now okay you guys got to go i know you
got a busy life and we got a live to do
we're talking about moderation okay all
right you guys
you guys are the greatest all right bye
guys we're live right now we're talking
about moderation and this is an
important live i wonder yeah
i
i think we have a delayed audience
laughter response but we're we're going
to find out where it went you know the
thing is you guys on this is that
when it comes down to moderation right
it it's it's rampant because we're
talking about autoimmune and moderation
they don't fit in they don't work
together they don't fit in together
they don't work together still waiting
for that delay and the thing is is like
when it comes down to
if you say moderation's okay
then
someone with autoimmune there it is you
guys there it is
all right all right
there we are
it's how things work here they work
really good
so
so the whole thing is so let's talk
let's take this serious though we got to
take the series we're talking about
autoimmune in moderation why they don't
blend why they don't mix they just don't
mix they just don't blend and this is an
important talk because
i can tell you right now if you're
somebody that's trying to heal if you're
somebody that wants to get your life
back moderation does not fit into the
equation it doesn't it just doesn't fit
into the equation
because
if you have to heal
everything in your body and your mind
and your soul wants to heal
wants to heal so bad
but then you get given
misinformation about how you can have a
little bit of this and a little bit of
that and a little bit of this and a
little bit of that
that's how we just get in trouble we
truly get in trouble
and we don't realize it we don't realize
how that works
because it's like the
stopper to us healing that's what it is
moderation is like a
obstacle right it's like an obstacle
that gets in everybody's way and
everybody in the health care world and
the health care providers in the health
world and the health and fitness world
all say moderation is okay have some
espresso have some coffee have some
caffeine have a donut have a
cheeseburger right have a little popcorn
hey it's organic popcorn have a little
organic popcorn right have a little
gluten-free pizza or just not even just
have pizza just plain old pizza with
gluten whatever whatever you're gonna do
right you guys we're live on tick tock
we're live on facebook i don't know
where we're live right now because we
got a lot of platforms up right now
so
anyway
we're um
so let's let's go into this a little bit
about moderation and where we're at
where we're all right we're live on
telegram right now too i know that
we're live on youtube so i'm excited
about today
so
do you ever
do you ever wonder why moderation is so
easy
to get permission for by every single
doctor and healthcare practitioner i
hear it every single day
that's why i'm bringing it up i'm
bringing it up because i hear it all the
time it's like aw i just got permission
to do this is that okay i'm like what
and you know what you don't need
permission from me you can do what you
want your life your choice but what i am
going to do is lay out what gets in the
way of our health and how we can heal
right but moderation can add
it can add years missing off your life
not adding years to your life too that's
another thing because moderation is like
that chipper away where it chips away
years off your life is what it does
and it depends on how far you go into
moderation how much into moderation do
you do do you drink in moderation like
what's drinking in moderation right
do you smoke in moderation what do you
eat in moderation right all these things
that we do
and it just it basically becomes a
snowball like this moderation snowball
and everybody's all trapped in it and
their legs are sticking out of that
snowball and their arms are sticking out
their heads are sticking out the
snowball and it's going down the
mountain is what it's doing it's like
this gigantic moderation snowball
if you got autoimmune
if you got
anxiety depression severe depression
if you got any kind of neurological
symptom
whatever that may be
moderation becomes a trap it becomes
your enemy it becomes
something that really gets in our way
and i see it happen all the time it's
like we want we're desperate for
permission we're desperate for
validation we're desperate for somebody
to say yeah you can have that
yeah you can have a little bit of that
you know yeah why not it's good for the
soul right
well you know i think about what's good
for the soul i think about staying here
longer staying here not sick
staying here
feeling good staying here you know
an optimum level right or just staying
here and functioning on a decent enough
level whatever it takes right but
staying here you know that's good for
the soul i see that as good for the soul
and at the same time
it's all about
how we perceive stuff to you guys right
i know
people that have had to heal
their gastrointestinal tract because it
was so bad off and so inflamed and
colitis and crohn's and celiac right and
ibs and they had to heal it by scaling
back on their foods
and all of a sudden doing like mono
eating right where they're doing
potatoes and lettuce or they're doing
celery juice and bananas and papaya
right and then
they
healed and they got nice and strong and
their intestinal tract got nice and
strong and then they can bring in more
things then they'll say they're bringing
in more things
now they're bringing in some avocado now
they're bringing in some you know some
more different dishes and every single
kind of vegetable and then they're
bringing some more things and if they're
an animal protein person now they're
bringing in a little bit of animal
protein
and they're and they're able to now eat
more of what they feel
is like an incredible moderation so
moderation can like it could be like one
to a hundred to have the worst level of
moderation there ever was at hunt at a
hundred
and you can have like the best level of
moderation
at like one and two and three the 97 98
99 100 the worst level of moderation
and people don't realize that it can get
like it can snowball it's like you know
what i can do this now i could do a
little bit of this let me have a little
bit of this i could have a cheeseburger
twice a week and now i can have you know
pancakes this day and now on sunday i'll
just have a little bit more and it just
takes over and then we're trapped in it
and when we get trapped in it it's hard
to get out of it especially when we're
sick so it's the kind of thing where
it's
everybody wants to heal they all want to
get better they all want to get their
lives back
but the moderation trap is real and we
have to be really careful you see it in
every article out there you see people
say no i can eat what i want it's cheat
day right
and so everybody does their cheat days
too so they think they can do their
cheat day in moderation so everybody
still has their moderation now at the
same time i don't shame anybody no
judgment on anybody if you eat a
chocolate cake tomorrow
you got my support
that's right if you eat anything
if you have a pizza
tomorrow you got my support good bacon
double cheeseburger you got my support
man i'm still gonna have your back no
matter what because it's not an easy
world it's not an easy ride and i know
it's not easy to stay healthy as far as
your foods and to keep them clean really
really hard you guys i did the amazon
live today check it out my favorite
cleaning supplies
and tools you guys got to check it out
when you get a chance you can sign up
right there you see the link is in the
profile link is in the description
so if you can you can take a look at
that and then of course sign up to my
newsletter exclusive weekly videos i'm
doing if you're having trouble
subscribing to my newsletter it might
mean that you unsubscribed at one point
and then
you have to go
to the check out the link in description
you have to re-subscribe so i give you a
process when you go to my website okay
you'll see like like you can actually do
the process over because a lot of people
are trying to resubscribe they don't
realize that they unsubscribed at one
point and so they want to subscribe now
and they're like hey i don't get your
newsletters what's going on so there's a
way to getting back into the system so
check it out
so
the whole thing about food is one thing
about medical medium
is my mechanism information right
it's never about shaming
or judging
it's always being about being supportive
with someone wherever they are with
their foods because i know
it is hard
it is hard when you're living with
family that are eating certain foods
like i know so many of you guys are so
you're you're in a situation where you
got family members right loved ones
they're eating a certain way
they're doing what they want to do with
foods and it's really hard for you
and i completely understand that when
it's really hard
that makes it very difficult and one
that makes it very difficult that i
understand so there's that alone right
so you guys so that's a whole other
thing and i know that
that it's different
when you you're alone if you're somebody
that lives alone then you could be like
okay wait a minute i don't have the peer
pressure someone's not bringing in
pizzas someone's not bringing but at the
same time it's easy to just say you know
what this is what i want or this is what
i want right so i get it you know and
it's not an easy road when it comes down
to food so
yeah it's really difficult out there
when you see somebody and they're so
good with their foods right really like
great with their foods and then you
think that they are kind of harping on
you because you're not that good with
your foods
it's it's difficult all around and i've
seen all the different scenarios out
there right but you got to keep one
thing in your in your mind one thing you
do a little bit out of time a little bit
at a time
so i like to kind of reframe moderation
it's not about
i could have this in moderation wow what
a relief right i can have a little bit
of this in moderation i could have a
slice of this in moderation i'll have
some popcorn today not about that
it's about bringing in the other foods
it's about bringing in more fruit it's
about bringing in right
more brussels sprouts more artichokes
right more asparagus it's about bringing
those in until you weed out until you
push out
like the moderation foods that's a way
of doing it that's a great way of doing
it it's a way you bring in more apples
and you bring in more oranges and you
bring in medical medium tools if you can
like the heavy metal detox smoothies you
bring in your celery juice and when you
start bringing all this in it actually
pushes
the moderation foods away
and you start getting stronger and you
start feeling like better willpower more
well strong willpower starts to take
over
and you can actually push those
moderation foods away so when someone
says no you can have that moderation
you're always like no no you can start
to feel strength coming up from the
inner core and you can get that strength
building up strong in the inner core
like your soul gets stronger
your ability to defend yourself
against the the moderation foods
starts to get stronger right you get
that inner strength and it gets better
that's because when you bring in more
things so when you start bringing in
things like
tomatoes and you're bringing more of
these and you're snacking on these
tomatoes something changes when you
start doing your lemon and lime water
every single day something starts to
change right this is when what happens
so when you're bringing in these foods
it starts to push away those moderation
traps right and you're bringing in more
onions and these are just a few things
right you're bringing in some onions
which you can't see right there and
you're bringing other things when you
start to bring in
other foods look at these tomatoes right
here look how incredible these are right
and
it starts to change the game the playing
field gets different
you can strengthen in a way because
you're bringing all these different
pieces right so what i recommend
for anybody who's struggling with the
moderation traps because i know so many
people are i'm sure you guys are i'm
sure maybe maybe some of you guys are
you guys are solid right through the
moderation
has it the moderation isn't tempting you
or the moderation trap isn't in your way
but if it is in your way okay
don't think about
the
food the unproductive foods and the bad
foods in the troublemaker foods don't
think about those as being like oh can i
eat those think about what can i eat
that's not these
and you bring in these other foods you
bring in the bananas
right you pick up some cantaloupe okay
things like you pick up some berries you
get your frozen wild blueberries and the
more and more things you bring in
every even avocado if you gotta bring an
avocado you bring the avocado in you
bring that one in right there absolutely
and then you bring in your leafy greens
now one of the ways to beat the
moderation food game
is get the leafy greens in the trace
mineral salts to get the celery juice in
which is the trace mineral salts and to
get the glucose which is the sugar you
can get the sugar in because if you
don't get the good sugar in you're going
to be getting this sugar right here
you're going to be looking for this
sugar this is the one you're going to be
looking for if you don't get the good
sugar in if you don't get the good sugar
in you're going to be trying to get this
sugar in right here this is
the sugar
that's what you're looking for can be
looking for this if you don't get
the good sugar if you don't get the good
sugar in
you're going to be looking for this
sugar right here all right that's how it
works so if you don't get the good stuff
in like the bananas okay
you gotta have the stuff around so it's
critical to have it around you don't
have
the trace mineral salt and the glucose
then you're gonna be just eating
whatever anything that comes your way
any friend any neighbor any family
member that's making something someone
scooping some ice cream out of the
freezer you're gonna eat it nothing's
gonna stop a lot of people from grabbing
a slice of pizza and then you're going
to be thinking like well wait i had it
last week or i had four days ago it's
moderation i'll i should get by
and the moderation is just going to beat
us down it's going to beat us down and
keep us down
so
one of the key things one of the key
things to remember is you gotta have
your trace mineral salts you gotta have
your celery juice you gotta have your
spinach and leafy greens
if you can just bring in spinach salads
every single day with tomatoes and put
avocado on them just put avocado on them
have a avocado tomato onion spinach
salad if you can do your celery juice
you could do the heavy metal detox
smoothie
if you can do the lemon water if you can
get your trace mineral salts and lots of
your glucose
right there you're going to be beating
the moderation trap you're going to be
winning if you can get those in because
you're going to be less
less apt to actually eating the bad
stuff when it comes your way so it's
really about bringing the good stuff in
and then you push away the bad stuff it
becomes a natural push off is what
you're doing a natural way of getting
those things pushed away and getting
them out of your life but you got to
worry about the permission granters
right got to worry about yeah health
care providers that say you can have a
little of this and you can have a little
of that you can have some of that
because they're doing it so they're
doing it and maybe they're not sick yet
but you could be somebody that's sick
you're struggling with anxiety you're
struggling with autoimmune you're
struggling with neurological symptoms
and then
the people that are supposed to be
watching your back
because they do the moderation thing and
eat whatever when they want they're
going to give you little bits of
permission and you're going to take
those bits of permission
and you're going to take that advice and
it's going to slow you down
so we got to remember that we got to
look out for that of course i always
want you listening to your doctors and
practitioners 100 but i also want you to
be able to protect yourself in any way
you possibly can and maybe you find a
doctor that doesn't offer all this other
foods i'm going off to ig you guys i
just want to give you a quick moderation
talk because it's really hitting people
hard right now
and um
i'm gonna go to ig in just a few minutes
so i hope you guys hang around for that
i'm gonna turn telegram back on i'm
looking forward to it can't wait to see
you guys soon