live anthony william the medical medium
we're live streaming right here
we always got to do it live mold the
crazy maker so episode 13
mold the crazy maker mold sickness
mold everything it is the comprehensive
episode on medical meeting podcast at
apple podcast you got to check it out
so that's an episode that really if
you're concerned about mold in any way
i'm talking about mold on food too even
mold on food
where people are worried about that
we'll talk about that in a minute too
all about mold on food and then i talk
about
things that people don't know about in
this episode about
how fungicides were created
to control mold and only made it worse
and the reason why we have
thousands of varieties of mold out there
right now that get in people's ceilings
get in the attic they get in the
basements underneath the sinks
you know and how that works how it makes
people sick why it makes people sick
what happens there so you really want to
catch this out um
jeanette says listen to the listen this
morning just gave a friend my extra copy
a cleanse the heel
awesome cleanse the heel right there
incredible so this mold episode is
really comprehensive
it's packed with information medical
medium podcasts that
apple podcast don't miss it don't miss
it so
you want to catch it did you subscribe
so then you get notified that's the best
way to actually
you know hear about it so the whole bit
so
i want to talk about mold the crazy
maker why did i name it the crazy maker
because
it could send you down a rabbit hole it
sent a lot of people down the rabbit
hole over the years
then you you know then there's a lot of
mold chasing doctors too
out there where they they chase mold so
they don't know what's going
on they don't know why someone has aches
and pains and tingles and numbness
and fatigue and brain fog and they don't
know why
someone has all that body pain and neck
pain and jaw pain
so they start they don't they weren't
taught that it's about viruses it's
about bacteria
and and toxic heavy metals and they
weren't taught about that so they don't
know that's why they
people have anxiety and you know medical
medium information so
what they do is there's some doctors out
there that are in the great pure
intentions and
they're loving doctors and are
compassionate and they look for mold
and they think that mold is the reason
why someone just can't get
better but when you get away from mold
so
say you actually were in a situation
where you were surrounded by mold or
mold was in your life and you get away
from mold
and you're still sick and still sick and
still sick there's a reason and it
wasn't the mold the mold was the trigger
and i talked all about this this is
really
incredible information and why why
would a family of five you know
not get sick from mold or a family of
four
or why would a family
you know be okay except for one member
in the family so why would like
say the mom be bedridden sick with
fatigue
and aches and pains and blurry vision
and dizziness
and and just stuck on mattress island
like many people
are and just be bedridden practically
and then the husband and the kids they
feel great
they're going out every day they're
going to the park they're going to the
beach
everything's great you know and and it's
because mold exposure
most mold exposure should make every
single person
sick if they were exposed but it doesn't
work that way there's office buildings
where you have like 50 people working in
one
and only three get sick and it's like
whoa they test for mold wait it's mold
it's mold it's mold if you're chasing
mold and molds bad
it's real bad but i talk about why it's
really really bad and why
people do get sick when they've been
around mold so
you know it's really important to know
there too um
so yeah and look the bottom line is
i want you guys to learn this
information i want you to
experience the podcast medical media
podcast at apple podcast
check it out that's the uncensored
platform that means this mold episode
ain't gonna be the same somewhere else
letting you know
so this mold episode is not gonna be the
same episode if it's on another platform
so
it's apple podcast medical media podcast
at apple
podcast that's where you have to listen
to it so you get the uncensored version
so you got it down
um artie says love the moon meditation
we'll be doing it every day until the
full moon incredible already i'm so glad
you're doing that
powerful meditation that's one of the
episodes of medical media podcast at
apple podcast
try the moon meditation like arty's
doing because what it does
is it heals wounds in the soul and
the magnetic ability of the moon the
power
that it has to actually pull and
eliminate
um pain and suffering out of her soul
wounds of betrayal and
broken trust and hardships and losses
it's so important you know so you guys
i hope you enjoy this mold episode the
crazy maker
and you know what i thought about it i
was like okay you know i got a friend
who just literally has just gone through
hell and back
because of mold and you know and she's
just like really had it hard she had to
move out of one place then she took all
her stuff with her
and she went and took it someplace else
and then you know mold
came with her it felt like and she was
really worried
and was sick and i was like wait a
minute you know you're just being
triggered
yeah it made you sick but
there's more to it than that there's
more something else inside
of us um marcilla said already listen to
it and you literally have written my
life
lost all my furniture and belongings to
mold
it almost killed my marriage because my
husband thought i was crazy
poor thing this you know i understand
i'm look you know and and i want you to
know that these episodes like
the mold the the mold episode they're
here for a reason
so you guys can actually know that hey
there are answers there is help
and number two there are things that
happen there that yes
yes it's it's understood it's understood
there's validation there it's critical
um it's really critical so anyway
thank you for listening to the episode i
hope it helped in some way
and you know it's a powerful one it's
packed with information
um jennifer said just finished listening
to your mold
podcast thank you so much
because i was sick from it because i
live in
a historical home oh my god yeah the
mold was in the faulty air ducts
it's all been replaced yeah what happens
is that
you were sick from it because it weakens
the immune system
that's how it works jennifer so it's
like really tough
that mold just weakens our immune
systems and i give all these powerful
tools there some medical medium podcast
at apple podcast that's the uncensored
platform
if you listen to it somewhere else
you're not getting the full thing
something's going to be missing
you might not seem it but yeah so the
link is in the description
that's where you listen to it right
there subscribe
so that you actually get notified and
share with everybody else if you can
share share share alexandra says she's
doing the moon meditation just saw that
fly up
um you know you guys i'm really proud of
all of you you're working so hard
and laurie says heard the mold podcast
hard to hear after been through it whoa
you love the meditations incredible
you're doing the brain meditation the
moon meditation the freeze the bird
meditation i'm gonna work hard on
getting another one out for you guys
eventually
so i want you to know that so you know
look
so many people have been through the
mold they've been through it
it's knocked them on their butt
devastated so many people you guys know
um and it's just uh trisha marie she's
here right now i just saw her comment go
up there i think you've dealt with mold
stuff from what i've seen in past
comments
you know it's like i know you guys it's
really frustrating
totally and and susan wright says
i'm living the mold life now it's
frustrating oh my god that's really hard
it's really hard
um and i hope i've given you some
some relief somehow at least or some
support with this episode i want to do
whatever i can
i do you know you could learn how the
mold today
is not the same mold of yesterday in
this episode
really important to talk about
fungicides and how
the chemical industry and the the
industries in general and the
industrial industry has changed mold
it's now something entirely different
um kelly says i'm so sick from it whoa
so you're sick from the mold yeah it's
it's really
that intense that in the episode if you
heard the episode too i talk about how
it's the trigger to get really sick
it's the trigger to get really sick so
it's important to know um
and sharon says how do you detox mold i
give a bunch of tools that are really
helpful
they're in the episode medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast link is in the
description
um dressa says can you tell me where to
get the
adenosil cobalamin um that you know the
one i use
the one i use is vimergy that's the one
i use so vimergy it's v is in victor
i m is in mary e-r-g-y i have one over
here i think i'll grab it in a second
and so um it's adenosicobalamin and
methicovalement so b-12
so i didn't talk about that enough i
know i didn't give a chance but in the
b12 episode
this is the one i use right here if you
want to know
it's the b12 right here and that's the
vivirgy brand it's
um v is the victor i am is in mary
e-r-g-y
so that's that one right there so if you
want to know
let's take a look that's it and
sabina says podcast is a life savior so
yeah the b-12 with dinosaur bomb methyl
volume
no preservatives none of that bad stuff
and then the alkyl no alcohol
no citric acid nothing like that in
there this is the cleanest stuff the
stuff i trust and everything so um
you guys the bottom line is when it
comes down to mold
you want to be easy on yourself okay you
want to pat yourself on the back
wherever you can you want to
be be compassionate towards yourself
because it's not your fault
mold sickness isn't your fault you
didn't do anything
wrong you didn't do anything to create
mold sickness it's not your fault there
so that's something that's really
important to know
and and um the bottom line is
it's a trigger a major trigger and
that's one thing no one really gets
and even the best mold doctors don't
know it's a trigger they think
the mold itself is totally the reason
why we get knocked down but really it
knocks down our immune system and then
we have more problems that talk about
that in there
so yeah um so so many people have mold
they have them in their walls they have
them everywhere
i think jenny fisher was just saying
that as the as her comment went up there
too
there's michelle miller hey good to see
you so glad everybody's here
um so excited that you guys are here
right now
um so yeah what the healing tools that i
have in that episode are really powerful
so the medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie is critical because what
people don't know and this is an
important one is that
mold has metals in it really important
right there
so mold has metals in it's part of how
everybody gets sick or
you know because of that very thing
they're getting triggered
the metals bring down the immune system
you breathe in the mold
you get it and you get you eat it the
whole bit
so you guys want to check out the
episode
uh chrissy says moldy home triggered
lyme and symptoms to come out
dormant chrissy did you check out
cleanse the heel there's
uh lyme disease information in there too
um
and i talk about that in the episode i
talk about that in this episode of
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
that
what happens is you can be triggered
into lyme now you're at a lyme doctor's
office you can be triggered
into ms now you're at an ms doctor's
into anything fibromyalgia all of it
sunday
sunday's there i love the episode thank
you so much for doing this
as i have requested several times i know
i know i remember you requested it
i do um i have not so much
and you have helped me calm down and
know the truth behind all this thank you
anthony um sunday i'm so glad
i want to be helpful i wanted to make
sure i had this episode go out
i remember you requested it and i just
want you to have this information
so it's really important it is um
so jenny fisher says could my family
still be affected by the mold we were
exposed to for 10 years
well what happens is your your immune
system can get affected 10 years ago
when you're exposed to 10 years ago
or i'm not sure if the question was
you're exposed for it for 10 years
i mean through 10 years or it was 10
years ago but that what happens is your
immune system gets triggered
because it gets weakened and then other
things come out of
us like bacteria that we have in our
bodies and viruses we have in our bodies
and we just get sick so
it so the whole point of the episode too
is to say hey we could take control over
this whether we were affected by mold or
not and we could get better
we actually could get better and heal so
that's important too
got to check out the medical medium
directory for all the tools
because in the episode there's all these
tools so the whole bit
eliza says please tell us the best place
to purchase all the items in the
detox smoothie yes medicalmedium.com
the the supplement directory at
medicalmedium.com there's a directory
there
i'm not sponsored by the companies i'm
not the owner
of the companies it's there as a
resource for you guys
and then the stuff that i trust the most
like you know the stuff i trust the most
like the vimergy b12 right here
see if you can see it and that's the one
i trust there and that's you know that's
what i take
you know i forgot to tell everybody that
i know the b12 episode came out i know
that i
already did some lives about it but now
that you guys brought up b12 earlier it
just
duh i should actually show you um mandy
driver your podcasts are incredible i
listen when i am in the bath
you're truly our incredible healer i
hope you're doing the meditations did
you do the moon meditation
the brain meditation did you do the
freezing bird meditation
i'm sure you did right because they're
really they're really
healing all of it so um
so you guys the whole thing with mold is
like this it's there are some people
they don't get affected by it at all
like they could eat the stuff
they could breathe it in they could live
it they could just
it's all it just doesn't bother them
it's amazing how it works
and then there's someone that's all they
have to do is just live in it for a
little while
breathe it for a little while um be a
part of it for a little while and then
when they are
whoa it hits them hard chemical
sensitivities
all of that they just get totally
whacked by it totally hit hard by it
and that's a big deal you know apple
podcast yep apple podcast is where
medical medium podcast as
is you can listen to the mold crazy
maker episode there
and you know like look i subtitled it
the crazy maker
because what happens is that first of
all you're not crazy
that's the whole point what people don't
get all these years i've watched is
people get sick from old all these years
and then other people including the
doctors of the past
they just would be like no no no you're
you're crazy uh it's not the mold under
your kitchen
sink it's not the mold in your basement
that's not why you're sick
and but really it's caused a lot
of hardship mold a tremendous amount of
hardship
and people who who have experienced it
are not crazy
it's the opposite they're actually
totally sane they've been through hell
and back
no one understands them what they've
been through it's just so hard
it's just so hard so this is a great
episode and you guys gotta check it out
sylvia said she loves the meditations
amazing um share them
share them share them if you can anna
said thank you after listening to the
podcast now i understand many
symptoms neurological podcast
that's one right there that you guys
might want to listen to
by the way these are not coffee talk
throw away
just you know podcast episodes they are
docuseries informative
high production podcast episodes
for you guys and i just want you to know
that i did i didn't just turn on a mic
and just have a guest come on real quick
and just
shoot the crap and then hope you guys
listen
and then here today gone tomorrow and
just gets tossed out
that's not what this is this is powerful
medical medium healing information and
tools
in a docu-serious style high quality
you know production and a lot of work
involved all that to make sure that you
guys
get the best information and
and that's what it's about it's it's
about not i didn't want you guys having
get the coffee talk versions you know
what's your it's great there's a lot of
people out there that's what they do
you get a guest on you ask a couple
questions everybody banters back and
forth it's great
but that's not this i want you to know
that i didn't want to do that i wanted
to make sure you had this
it's important um candy says i've
struggled with mold for so many years
and i'm not sure what to do about it ah
what happens is
if you're struggling with symptoms and
conditions
like when you diagnose with fibro where
you diagnose with some needs you have
the fatigue
um was a hair thinning or you're just
not well
and heart palpitations and dizziness and
blurriness and
all of it and you know sleep problems
whatever it is all of it
that there's other things causing that
it's just mold
triggers it so mold is the trigger it's
one of those big
triggers um you can learn you know god
you can learn about this stuff for sure
just list the episode
denise says can you share the protocol
thank you so the healing
tools that are in the episode
so let me answer the question the
healing tools that you'll see a couple
of different herbs in there
you'll see that um you'll see some b12
in there like the dimmer gb12 you'll see
that
and other thing but you'll see the
healing tools in there the healing broth
medical medium healing broth
that one right there really important
and then i talk about the leafy green
and leafy green herbs in there so the
cilantro
i talk about the spinach i talk about
those the leafy greens the lettuces and
how good they are with mold as far as
helping to get it out of the body
okay i talk about winter squash have you
guys had any winter squash because right
now
um in different parts of the world you
can get it it's a great pleat it's great
to get winter squash is helpful when
you're dealing with mold issues
so that's important too um sage yep
keeley says you mentioned adding sage as
a treatment
yes i did you listen to the podcast
episode incredible um
and what about burning sage
i have a friend who burns sage to clean
house once a year
well um i would i would do a sage
essential oil and a diffuser that's what
i would do personally
like i wouldn't burn i personally
wouldn't burn sage
you know and um and be careful too if
you're doing that make sure
it doesn't get away from you you know
and um
inside the house but i would i would do
the essential oil
uh sage infuser but one of the tools i
talk about
in this podcast episode is the rosemary
oil
in the diffuser so that's that's one
right there
um trisha marie i love you i love you
and
emphasize with your experience of your
friend who thought you were overreacting
to mold exposure you were right
some mold is more toxic and some you
know
so what happens is trisha work exactly i
mean some people are more sensitive
some is more toxic but really could be
really hard on somebody who's sensitive
it's just it's just incredible yeah
trisha big
trigger big trigger totally totally
hazel says i listened to the podcast so
much information and things made sense
as you listen so glad you listened
incredible um so yeah
so this episode i wanted to make sure
that you guys have packed information a
whole bit
if you're new and you haven't listened
to it medical media podcast at apple
podcast
that's where um you can hear it link is
in the description
so i talk about mold exposure i talk
about
the mold being the trigger i talk about
the healing tools like the rosemary it's
a big important one there too
and what you hear wait do you hear the
rest of the healing tools as well
pressing print said i used a natural 100
natural rosemary oil and diffuser every
day
whoa that's really cool that you do that
every single day
deborah says deborah schultz says mold
destroyed my life 10 years ago
oh my god it is it really
has hurt a lot of people just know that
i'm so sorry you went through that
it's just it's just awful to have to go
through that it truly is truly is awful
um so monica says orgonite is helpful
against mold yeah
because mold runs on a frequency and i
talked about that in the episode you got
to check that out too
um yeah you guys there's so much you can
hear in this episode i can't even
scratch the surface
in this episode can't even scratch the
surface so medical medium podcast at
apple podcast i can't even scratch the
surface there's so much information in
there
um the link is in the description you
really have to just
listen to this one it's called mold
crazy maker
and that's that's the one right there
and i know that a mold
episode was really really important and
really critical to get out there right
now so
so jenny says what does rosemary oil do
check out the episode
and i talk about it in there a little
bit i hope you listen to it
um so i'm really proud of you guys when
you get a chance
so give it give it a moment uh take your
time link is in the description
listen to the podcast episode there's
awesome neurological episode the b12
episode
there's also um god there's so many of
them now brain fog episode the apple
cider vinegar episode
and then the meditations move meditation
uh freeza bird meditation
all of it so so much so much information
there anyway
you guys proud of all of you i just
wanted to let you know that this
this is a big episode and i just had to
let you know
fill you in on it a little bit so glad
you're here
and i will see you next time
we'll see what else i put out there so
thanks so much take care of yourself
bye bye