live right now medical medium mono
eating cleanse
challenge is on i'm excited got my
papaya
here i got all kinds of stuff right here
i'm really excited about this because i
want to show you guys
some of the stuff some of the
information really important information
first and foremost do you have cleanse
to heal
such an important aspect of it if you
don't have cleanse of heal right now
let's just you know let's just try to
learn and do what we got to do
but you should be getting it anyway you
should be getting it for tomorrow then
three days we're doing this make sure
you have the book it's
critical the details are in here and i'm
gonna be helping us with a lot of stuff
but i can't cover every single detail i
just can't
amazon.com us 51 off right now
16 take advantage of it
so we're talking about the mono cleanse
is what we're talking about why is this
good
people with any kind of digestive
problems okay crohn's colitis ibs
celiac you name it right gastroparesis
diarrhea cramping bloating sibo acid
reflux
constipation all of it this is one of
the things that have brought
people back throughout the years when
they learn how to do this and bring it
into their life
and i've seen people save their colons
because of
mono eating because medical medium i've
seen people
save their intestinal tracts where they
didn't have to cut
out their guts they didn't have to get
their guts cut out
and it's important to know that hundreds
of
miles of intestinal tract has been saved
hundreds of miles thousands and
thousands of yards
and hundreds of miles of intestinal
tracts have been safe for so many people
that would have had to have the surgery
would had to have it cut and sniffed out
would have had to you know have all
these problems and that's one of just
one of the things the mono cleanse
here's the great thing about the other
great thing about the mono cleanse okay
is it allows you to actually cleanse
it allows you to cleanse it's anti-viral
it's anti-bacterial it's anti-pathogen
did you hear that you guys
it's anti-yeast it's anti-mold
it's anti-fungus
bad fungus not the good stuff the bad
stuff doesn't like when you're eating
these foods
these foods clean and they don't do it
in an
aggravating way so important
mv doom says yay for all this aw
i'm all in yeah all right bananas only
no
way bananas only today and feels
great explanation points it's even
taking away
ankle pain that's years old
taking away ankle pain right there
i've heard that so many times too over
the years
i see people coming on michelle miller
you're on board today are you coming on
to
tick tock we're live on tick tock
facebook youtube we're live there live
on clubhouse too
i wish you guys in clubhouse could see
this but you know what it's cool you're
even here because you can hear it and
that counts right there
incredible so you guys i got papaya
right here now listen just so so
you guys don't punish me because i know
you guys
you guys might be like hey w what are
you doing
what are you doing you might see me eat
some papaya
you might see me eat some banana well
there's a banana papaya version you can
do that right
you might see me eat some potato you
might see me eat some peas
because i gotta show you guys okay
so try not to crucify me if you see me
put some peas in some lettuce or you see
me eat a couple of bananas
try not to try not to crucify me too bad
right
it's only because i gotta show you guys
and something might slip into my mouth
and get in there
yeah that's that's not you're not
supposed to mix everything up you're not
when you're doing the mono eating
cleanse you're supposed to be doing the
mono eating cleanse so just saying if
you see a bite enter because i have to
show you guys letting you know
so i got the book right here in front of
me i'm going to read a little bit about
about different aspects of it too right
here i'm glad you guys are coming on
board anybody who's coming on board now
make sure you watch this whole thing
over again
later all right so that's that's
important to know
we're talking about the medical medium
mono cleanse challenge
is what we're doing the mono cleanse
challenge the mono cleanse is in this
book right here cleanse the heel
quick reminder it's critical to have 51
off amazon.com us make sure you take
advantage of it so you have the
information
you want to get it to the at the library
if you can run and try to get it there
you could
but just make sure you have information
so you know what you're doing so you
could do this even after
and everything else so that's important
all right
so what i did this morning is i started
out with the lemon water
how many of you guys started out with
the lemon water just want to make sure
if you guys are doing that if you guys
are on with that
you start out with the lemon water
okay because that's what i have and
i'm going to cut a lemon right here
so if you're just coming on here and
you're like what is this what's he doing
and you're just kind of you know
somewhere else or out to lunch or
whatever i've been busy and you want to
check out this live right now
you happen to be here or check out this
video after it's live right
you're like what is this medical medium
mono cleanse challenge i'm going to talk
about why it's important what it does
for us
why it's a critical healing tool medical
medium healing tool right i'm going to
give you a little demonstration about
the gut a little bit right there
with the anatomy uh dummy over there so
we're just gonna you know we're gonna
cover these things
but if you just got here and you're like
well i'm not on board i don't have my
bananas
i don't have my papaya how am i gonna do
this i don't have my peas or whatever it
is you choose to do
that's okay start tomorrow start
tomorrow nothing wrong with that i just
want to make that clear
because someone's going to be coming on
board today being like i haven't checked
out medical medium in a while let me
check them out
what's going on david scott doing mono
eating
cleanse for the past three months off
and on my stomach is flat now
like high school i've heard that so many
times from the moderating cleanse
not constantly eating all day either and
you're allowed to
by the way you guys you're allowed to
eat more and that's a
hot topic i'm covering because here's
what's going to happen
someone's going to be like all right i'm
doing the mono eating cleanse and
they're going to grab a banana be like i
ate a banana
and that's it right and that's it they
ate one banana and they're just going to
be all of a sudden starving and they're
going to hit the wall and they don't
realize they could eat a lot of bananas
you can eat bananas all day long if you
want to you know because i know some
people like alright i'm ready for the
mono eating cleanse
for three days and i'm like dude that's
one two three four five six seven eight
bananas
so that's not gonna be enough if you're
gonna do the banana one for three days
eight bananas that's not enough you're
getting any bunches of bananas so you
guys guys got to be prepared
so i just want to i'm going to make sure
i'm telling you this so no one's
confused because it's easy
to get confused about this so let's go
into it a little bit we got the lemon
water right here 16 to 32 ounces of
lemon water first thing in the morning
that's what i'm doing now i didn't
mention this yesterday but you can do
lemon water again
if you want you can do a couple of them
three of them
you can do them all right so it's okay
it doesn't have to be your only lemon
water if you don't want
you can be putting lemon in water all
day long
perfectly fine karen churchill can we
include lemon water or
lemon balm tea at night if you want to
include lemon balm tea
at night you can but you can include
lemon
water on and off all day just letting
you know okay
so there's the lemon water 16 to 32
ounces
right we got that
david lopez i'm gonna answer as many
questions as i can because that's what
we're about
can we mono eat coconut water well
that's a cleanse right that's a cleanse
too but what that is
is that's a juice fast
so if you just mono eat coconut water
you're now on a juice fast
coconut juice fast right that's what
you're doing
now that's an entirely different story
okay the problem is with those
kinds of things when you're just doing
coconut water and you're just doing a
coconut juice fast
you're going to be running on adrenaline
it's not going to be enough
calories to allow you to function so
then your adrenals are going to be
flooding
is what's going to happen all right so
let's take the adrenals out for a second
and take a look at those babies
right now which i'm doing
right here now you might be somebody
that's like
you know what i'm going to outsmart aw
i'm an outsmart aw i'm going to do
and i'm not saying that's what you're
doing you know you're trying to outsmart
me but there's a lot of people they're
going to be like i'm going to outsmart
him
i'm just going to do a cleanse i looked
up some juice fast somewhere
i know that's not what you're doing but
you know someone else might right and
then we'd be like
you know this mono-eating cleanse is
cool but i'm going to go and do i'm
going to really try to detox and what
you're going to do
is you're going to try to detox but
you're going to make yourself
toxic you're going to fill yourself up
adrenaline so what happens is the minute
you start going into this
long-term juice fast or long-term
water fast or long-term coconut water
fast
you're going to end up hitting the wall
you're not going to have enough glucose
for your brain and your brain is going
to be like i'm starving with glucose i'm
starving the glucose and your adrenals
are going to release adrenaline
and you're going to just saturate your
liver with adrenaline
that's not going to be productive at all
it's not
the mono eating cleanse you actually eat
and you cleanse but you eat and you
protect yourself
you protect your adrenals you see guys
how important that is
you protect your adrenals the minute
someone wants to be like ah
i'll just i'll just do this instead or
i'll go do this instead okay fine you're
just gonna burn your adrenals out you're
gonna fill your liver filled with
adrenaline
you're gonna starve your brain of
glucose coconut water doesn't
have enough glucose in it there's not
enough
sugar in it to feed your brain while
you're functioning
but yeah it's great but you know it's
not enough
that's why we're doing the moderating
cleanse this is really important to know
all this information digital lemon water
so
celery juice that's next
right you can do a little celery juice
and um
look you guys you don't have to do this
celery juice at
in the morning if you really didn't want
to let's cover that a little bit i know
someone had a question that said
when can i do the celery juice what if i
want to have it later
and you can have it later and that's
fine okay you can have it later and
that's all right
but i like having it in the morning it's
best
then so i'm giving you different options
and stuff but i like it in the morning
that's when it's best i'm just letting
you know
so i'm going to make some really quick
some celery juice and then we're going
to cover information while i'm just
juicing
really quick you guys just bear with me
right
so uh just get this over here
the reason why celery juice is so
important on the model eating cleanse
because you have to have the mineral
salts
russell gregory but can we have coconut
water with their mono cleanse yes you
can
you can have coconut water with your
mono cleanse
yes that's all right
[Music]
you can't what you don't want to have is
pink coconut water
or coconut water with additives check
your coconut water out
dually note this
dually know this piece of information
right
make sure your coconut water doesn't
have additives
boom make sure
your coconut water isn't pink boom
just get that note somewhere in here
write it down
whatever you got to do write it down in
here write it down in here
you can write it down in here too
but make sure you have that note
pin coconut water is rancid
red coconut water is rancid they're
lying to you
when they tell you what's good for you
you're being lied to
doesn't feel good right doris can you
add lemon
to your celery juice no
no no no it's like that song on tick
tock that went around forever
when something bad happened and all you
heard was that song
oh no oh no
oh no no no no no no
here's the deal okay
[Music]
you can't add anything to your celery
juice you ruin your celery juice the
sodium cluster salts can't be disturbed
they have to they can't be diluted with
ice cubes they can't be diluted with
water
they can't be diluted with lemon they
can't
be diluted or i'll sing that song
this is really important okay can i use
frozen peas there's a question right
there
alley ally meer you know what's in here
frozen peas you know where they're gonna
go in here in a little bit you guys
stick around for that that's gonna be
fun
i'm gonna have those babies popping yeah
you can use frozen
peas boom got that question taken care
of
i'm just excited you guys because you
know why because this is
a really gentle but powerful
cleanse powerful way to heal powerful
way to move forward
learning this and having this in your
life is critical you guys just got on
here
we're talking about the cleanse the heel
book we're talking about the motto
eating cleanse challenge we're
we're in day one of a three day
challenge right
51 off amazon.com us make sure you have
the book
so you have the cleanse do not ignore
the details that are in here critical
you guys
make the investment of the 16 it's on
sale
it's worth the investment i did not
package this up and sell it to you for
three thousand dollars and
and move it to a private platform and
have you guys
you know um have to pay
this is free right now to work with you
guys just make sure that you know i'm
doing the cleanse anyways if you guys
want to
have some fun let's have some fun
right so i'm just in a little celery
juice because you want 16 to 32 ounces
of celery juice that's next
keep that in mind celery juice is
important during this
if you're somebody and you're like i
don't have a juicer i can't do the
celery juice i don't i can't find celery
juice and you want to do this still
then you better be eating a lot of
lettuce
better be eating a lot of lettuce just
telling you right now
right here you see this i got the butter
leaf lettuce right here you better be
eating a lot of lettuce
you got to get your mineral salt
somewhere celery juice is different
though because it's you know it's really
powerful
got a question on tick tock can we eat
spinach's lettuce
all depends on how sensitive you are
right you're somebody with
really bad crohn's colitis
right real bad intestinal problems
you've had surgeries already things like
that
then you just you you don't want to eat
a lot of the spinach of something you're
not used to
something that you're not used to doing
okay
but if you're somebody that doesn't have
anything you know serious going around
like you haven't been struggling really
bad with your food you're not
hypersensitive
all those kinds of things sure you can
use some spinach if you really have to
teresa lettuce what does lettuce do for
us
it's got a chemical compound that
creates
this kind of milk right lettuce milk
just so you know not bovine milk
lettuce milk right
that lettuce milk
is really soothing and gentle on the
intestinal tract
lining okay that's what's amazing about
using the lettuce for this
right lettuce is antiviral anti-pathogen
lettuce is anti-fungus the bad fungus
anti-mold
anti-yeast okay so that's what lettuce
is
a couple of things plus it's got the
mineral salts as well different kinds
kimberly heiner what if you're allergic
to celery
look if you're somebody that you eat a
celery stick your throat closes up and
you're up at the er
then don't touch celery don't touch it
right um but do you mean can i can i
just have you be your own detective
if that's okay can you be your own
detective for a second
right do you mean you're allergic
because someone said you are
but when you eat celery you're fine
so you've had celery before you've had
it chopped up in a tuna salad you've had
it
chopped up in tuna fish sandwich you had
a crudite one time in your life but you
had no problems
or is it something where you're allergic
to celery because you had that all cat
test
you had a food sensitivity test and
there were 20 foods in there and they're
like celery
uh ragweed uh uh peppercorns uh
you know strawberry and you had this
thing where it was like
all these things they're telling you
allergic to but yeah you didn't have a
problem
first of all i don't trust a single one
of those tests if a family member went
and got any of those food sensitivities
tests i would
just i would be like i don't trust any
any one of those at all because
it's a scam all of that but if you're
somebody that
your mouth swells up because you eat a
celery stick
or you're now something happens you
can't breathe or you
because you're like getting a severe
allergic reaction don't touch it
no way don't touch it don't touch it
so okay so we got a little bit of taking
the juicer down for a second you guys
all right we got some celery juice right
here 16 to 32 ounces of celery juice
really important
like i said if you don't have celery and
you don't have some meaning you don't
have the celery juice or anything like
that
you know we can always try to work
around it but you're going to have to
eat a lot more lettuce
kathy joy can remain be used if butter
leaf is not
available yes it is but what you'll find
out and you guys
right i beg you to make sure you can you
can read the details in here
about all of that i talk just about that
when it comes down to lettuces
right apollos martin i i just got the
book yesterday
wonderful and it answered my question so
excited so grateful
so okay paula martin said the book
answered his questions
that's so important important if you
just got here
51 off amazon.com us it's an incredible
tool
the model eating cleanses in here i'm
letting you guys know it's
a must it really is we're on a three-day
mono eating cleanse challenge
you know take a look at this when you
can so let's talk about the
question about the lettuce a little bit
in a minute because that's really cool
wait hold terry's got a question
can i do a second celery juice in the
afternoon absolutely
you can do another celery juice in the
afternoon definitely
you can do another lemon water in the
afternoon you can do additional water in
the afternoon
if you're doing the banana one you do
more bananas you do more papaya if you
need to
you can do more if you're hungry
absolutely
but it's but you're still gonna heal
i'll tell you why you're still gonna
have healing happen inside your body
heal yourself says there's an option for
all
budgets from papaya to peas absolutely
100 and that's what i love about medical
medium tools
it can work it can work let's pour some
celery juice right here
yeah it's got some celery juice going on
nice nice nice nice nice
incredible i'm gonna cap mine for now
you guys don't mind boom got some celery
juice there we are
so let's crack open a papaya let's do
that all right we'll crack open a papaya
i gotta find my papaya first
so got my papaya right here it's like a
football this one this is a big papaya
you might got small papayas you might
have small ones
thank you for not charging a thousand
dollars i couldn't afford it david scott
i wouldn't do that
this easily could be three thousand
dollar a three thousand dollar cleanse
program or something
i could just i could wall it off like
i'm told all the time
but by people who actually confront me
and they're like hey look you know why
don't you use this marketing why don't
you do this i go no no no no no no no
and i don't want to do that i don't want
i i don't want to do that i don't want
to take it to a private
platform everybody buys a ticket i don't
want to do that so
what i'm about is is uh making sure that
that medical medium information is is is
free
we're you know we're not a cult here the
colts
charge the the money for everything
under the sun out there and
you know you think they're not they're
like hi i'm dr so-and-so
and here's my youtube information and
meanwhile you can press this button
and blah blah blah and buy my gut health
product
i mean it's just like cults everywhere
you know it's really sad
this is about compassion this is about
getting people what they need this is
about having people's back
this is about all of that so here's
something interesting right so
i got some papaya right here are frozen
papaya is okay i couldn't find
ripe fresh papayas yes they are i think
frozen papaya is fine
oh one thing though one thing
susan on that susan blonda
check the package and make sure that
stuff's not coated with citric acid
some frozen fruit not all of it out
there
some frozen fruit saturated with the
citric acid you got to look out there
okay my papaya is orange
oh cool that's amazing that that's why
strain the cellar just again on tick
tock
you got to get all the fiber and pulp
out you have to get all the fiber and
pulp out
it'll interfere with the sodium cluster
salts of really helping you heal
which juicer do you recommend i saw that
on tick tock
it's it's not just the brand it's the
specific juicer
so it's a mega juicers.com omega
juicers.com this is the mm-900 hds
you're going to see other juicers that
look like that they don't do the same
okay
this is what i call like a miraculous
juicer of what it does
it cuts your celery bill in half it's
cut my celery
juice bill in half it squeezes every
last drop
and there's a sale coming up like 20 off
like next week i don't know what it is
but there's one coming up so
if you're looking into yes your juice
has to be strained
keep that in mind since the mm-900 hds
your juice has to be strained okay so i
just ha i just cut this papaya
and i just scooped out the inside you
might have a small papaya you might have
a big papaya if you're somebody that's
doing the papaya one or the papaya
banana one
okay and meredith i bought this juicer
and it allowed me to juice more than the
regular omega and that juicer the mm-900
hcs
hands down the best juicer i've ever had
in my life i don't care what anybody
says
it's hands down the best one and i've
tried every one out there
and it's affordable and everything else
it's incredible so look this is what you
can do
a couple of things you can take your
spoon i just want to show you guys dr
fauna md good to see you
just want to show you guys take your
your spoon right
and you can eat your papaya like this
small papaya big papaya whatever
you can eat it like this see what i'm
doing
i'm showing you guys what i'm doing
right okay
looks like a beautiful robinson okay
looks like a beautiful pie
right i'll show you another way thing i
do
all right that's one thing i do right
another thing i can do here
just be careful if you're doing this you
can put it down take a knife
and you can do these cuts going across
like this right i do it like this
but you gotta watch that your knife
doesn't go through the papaya okay
keep that in mind right there you go you
can put it on here so you don't have
that
problem and you can do this okay and
then i scoop it out
i scoop it out so let me scoop it out in
a bowl
got a bowl right here so i want to show
you guys all these things i
do with the mono eating cleanse and now
i'm scooping
right scooping and the cut pieces are
falling in
see this is what i do the cut pieces are
falling in right
now you can scoop right down to the rind
right so i'm just i'm scooping it's all
coming coming in right
see okay
there you go now you can scoop even
farther like you can scoop all the way
to the rind you might have a papaya
that's not that great you might have a
pie that turns out to be amazing
it sometimes some aren't as tasty
sometimes some are incredible
it's just the way it is right if you're
choosing the papaya
option here it is right there you go
now i want to show you a couple of
things okay
right you guys are all ears right now
it's important so you're choosing the
papaya option i take a fork
i can eat it out of a bowl like this
right
and you can eat a whole papaya in one
meal
you can have two papayas yesterday i had
a papaya that was this big so i said
look you might be one
one and a half papayas in you know into
your day but you might be two papayas
when they're a little smaller you might
be three papayas if you wanted to keep
that in mind you got to get enough
papayas if you want to go the papaya
mono eating cleanse
right that's one meal one papaya
for me or if i put banana in there first
of all you can take a piece of lettuce
just a couple different options you can
put your papaya in the lettuce
like that and make a papaya lettuce boat
okay
showing you guys right there all right
so there you go
i gotta put my last bowl all right ready
for this
you don't have to have lettuce with your
papaya if you don't want to
you can have it for dinner maybe or
another time
i'm gonna read this
sorry get ready for this if you're doing
the papaya banana one
right
this is what i do
okay i'm cutting off little pieces and
i'm putting them right on top of my
banana papaya bowl so i'm going to show
you a couple different options of how to
do this
right
okay so you can put two three bananas
two three bananas right on your papaya
bowl check that out you guys
okay just a reminder if you came on here
you want to get this book right here
okay and 51
off amazon.com us you want to know what
the mono cleanse details are we're
having the mono cleanse challenge right
now
we're here we're doing it for three days
but you're going to want the book and
have the details so you can do it
yourself anytime you want it's important
and also have it now is important too on
tick tock the question is why are
papayas so good for you
all right so let's look at that i still
want to show you more papaya options
i want to show you a blended version as
well so i want to give you that as
there you know so our papaya is so good
for you right so here the papaya section
is okay
if someone is having problems moving
their bowels
then very helpful mono eating options
are papaya
papaya and banana or papaya papaya is
useful for
relieving constant chronic full-time
constipation
and is also good for someone who has
lost their hydrochloric
acid if you guys see this right now i
know on tick tock you might be able not
to see my anatomy guy i should move it
over but
your stomach let me pull the stomach out
of this guy
right let me pull the stomach out of
this guy
everybody's stomach glands are burnt out
burnt out not producing the hdl they
need to produce
people can't even digest their proteins
anymore
what page is that uh please uh okay let
me tell you what page it is it's 199
page 199
i'm reading i'm reading the papaya
section right now you guys have been
cleansed the heel
you might want to grab that book
whenever you can amazon's running a
killer sale on this book specifically
all right so the stomach loses its hcl
producing
ability because your stomach lands get
wasted as every year goes by in our life
that's why we can't break down our
proteins as good that's why stuff starts
to rot in our gut
and when you're doing this you're
building back your hcl
so we're talking about papaya can i add
honey to lemon water you can lisa cone
you can lisa cohen you guys i'm going to
show you the pea version
peas if you want a mono eat steamed peas
i got potatoes if you want to do the
steamed potatoes these are hot they just
were steamed
right but right now we're talking about
papaya just so we're not confusing
anything
all right all right papaya is useful
for relieving conic chronic full-time
constipation is also good for someone
who has lost their hydrochloric acid
with gastric strength virtually
non-existent you guys the reason why
everybody they just start falling apart
through their guts
things just start going wrong with the
bloating the acid reflux the sibo
you know they keep on getting diagnosed
with candida problems whatever they're
getting diagnosed ibs you've got the
celiac you've got the crohn's colitis
whatever it is gastric clamping
flattering flatulence
you've got the gastritis you're losing
your hcl
it's important enough guys should have
this book you really should
take advantage of that sale so
and okay that can look extremely
difficult for
you know this can help for difficult
digestion bloating gastric pain
inflammation cramps spasms acid reflux
hiatal hernia disruptions blockages from
scar tissue
maybe blockages from scar tissue
previous previous surgeries
or if you may land a diagnosis of in
some kind of intestinal condition you
can add banana in your
in as well with your papaya okay
whenever someone has gone through a
period of not eating whether from
fasting anorexia grave illness
food poisoning blended papaya is like
magic
for the refeeding process because it
offers ample calories soothes the nerves
so
if i'm going to give you a piece of
information right now that's critical
about papaya
it soothes the nerves keep that in mind
you guys
keep that in mind all right see you guys
on tick tock see you guys here and
meredith says i thought that with the
mono cleanse
you can only eat one of the listed
fruits vegetables
so you can have papaya and banana yeah
there's one option in here that's a
papaya and banana together and
indeed indeed
papaya is anti-viral and antibacterial
contains trace minerals and
beta-carotene and digests
so favorably very
that's how to important the heel i hope
you guys have the book i hope you're
ordering it right now i hope you guys
have it because it's critical um try to
find at the library if you don't have
the
even though it's on sale and you don't
have 16 try to find it three at the
library so let's let's go in just a
little bit so one great way of having it
every day
if you're going to join the papaya
banana and pick that option
out of the book you can have your papaya
and banana together
all right be open hearted said can we
still eat potatoes
if they are growing small roots from the
eyes okay good point
let's get a potato now
this potato you'll see has a little
cutout right here
you guys this is really important
information dr sherry green good to see
you
incredible doctor see the little cut out
here
see where i flip this there's a little
cut out here the potato is just starting
to send out a little sprout
you could see it was a white little
sprout poking out of it
you cut those little white sprouts off
if your potatoes now
blooming yeah those are too far gone
too far gone so if your potatoes are
sprouting like blooming
like flowers it looks like almost you're
too far gone
potatoes too far gone okay this was just
where you saw them they were sprouting
out a little bit little white sprout
and i just kind of like took the knife
and i just took took the little pieces
off
the best potatoes are the ones that
aren't sprouting but i'm just saying you
can if they're just starting to send out
sprouts yeah you can literally take the
little pieces off that's what i did
but if it's actually shooting out like
starting to grow and starting to look
like it's it's out of control no you
don't want to do that it's not good
so let's i'll show you how to put the
fruit in the lettuce so you can
take a piece of lettuce that's what you
can do right
and i showed you earlier but i'm going
to show you again i'm putting banana and
papaya in
the lettuce boat right that's what i'm
doing
banana papaya and the lesbo can you can
you refrigerate the potatoes yes you can
leave them in there that's what i do all
the time
in fact i use a lot of refrigerated
potatoes when i'm out here doing my
demonstrations with you guys
can we add garlic to the potato cleanse
no
keep the garlic out yeah garlic's
amazing for you i talk about that all
the time it's incredible food incredible
herb
but no you don't want that in the
monopoles there's a reason why it's the
mono cleanse
when you simplify you guys
simplify you heal faster in different
ways
in different ways it's not like the
heavy metal detox movie pulls the metals
out so you can heal that way
but this does something else medical
medium tools
all the different medical medium tools
do different things
i'm just going to repeat this is so
important spirit of compassion is making
sure
i run this by you right now okay
making sure that you simplify is a way
to heal certain aspects of the body
especially digestion
it's a great way to heal right but
medical medium tools
do different things that's important to
know they do
different things the mono cleanse does
different things and when we incorporate
when we do
different strategies to healing we can
knock out all kinds of stuff
a lot of people that heal with medical
medium they'll get rid of 30 symptoms
but yet they're stuck with a few
symptoms left but they didn't try other
medical medium tools
they didn't all of a sudden go and then
do the mono eating to get rid of those
other three symptoms because
different tools in the medical medium
warehouse
tool warehouse do different things so
somebody can make successful
accomplishment of healing all the way
and getting what they need to do get
done
all right so i got some in a lettuce
boat right here a little papaya a little
banana right there it's one way of doing
it
here's another way to do it let's get
going here now i got a food processor
right here what i'm going to do is scoop
out papaya brightness food processor and
i'm going to show you something cool
this is a great way we're still going to
do steamed peas i hope you guys stick
around don't go anywhere because this is
going to be fun
seriously i'm going to scoop out the
inside of this papaya right now
that's what i'm doing i'm just getting
rid of the seeds now yes you could eat
the seeds but i wouldn't during the mono
cleanse eat the seeds
i wouldn't okay so i'm gonna drop this
in here now i'm scooping out this papaya
right in this food processor
savannah says i already messed up and
had coffee with sugar
and almond milk how do i how do i kick
this horrible habit
i'm so addicted listen to the medical
mean podcast at apple podcast listen to
the
coffee matcha tea chocolate episode
because
you know it's no it's sad i don't mean
to change a topic but i want to respect
what you're talking about you know
what's sad
is the caffeine industry has every
like almost every woman on this planet
addicted to their drug to the
psychoactive drug it's an
evil prank played on women and almost
every man
and i talk about this it's horrible the
caffeine industry just
robs and steals people's chances to heal
it just robs their adrenals
ages them fast and no one's held
accountable for it this caffeine is so
bad one reason why the mono cleanse is
so healing
it gets us off of these things i love
the chemtrail podcast i see on tick tock
so you love the chemtrail podcast
oh god i love that episode i listen to
it every so often
medical mean podcast up about kathy
joyce says
what about the recommended supplements
during mono cleanse
right well here's the whole thing right
if you want to keep some of the
supplements you can just maybe lower
them down a little bit maybe do half
but it depends someone might be on the
worst supplements out there
you want to read the chapter in the
supplements chapter of cleanse to feel
you want to read that for sure
so i just put papaya in there and i'm
putting a little bit more that came off
of this one here too
okay because you can just take the
papaya right down to the skin if you
want if
your papaya is ripe enough and i'm doing
that i'm taking it down to the skin
i don't know if you guys can see this
but i'm scooping it out
this is really a great time today
to do this this is really fun so let's
just get some of that guy out there we
go okay
all right i'm just gonna move this
butternut squash over because we'll talk
about that too
got to watch out with supplements
they'll have alcohol in it they'll have
additives they'll have msg you won't
even know it there's so many junky
supplements coming out left and right
every single day
i notice supplements are coming out a
lot now
and they're putting medical medium
recommended stuff
in there they're doing the blends where
they're putting the zinc in that medical
medium talking about all these years
doing all the stuff but yet it's all
junk
so keep in mind that that can happen so
i'm gonna
get my food processor over here real
quick
bear with me right let's get this over
here so what i'm going to do is i'm
going to blend
this
papaya okay
guys with me i'm gonna blend this papaya
is what i'm gonna do
i'm giving it a blend in the food
processor
[Music]
you guys just arrived we're doing the
medical media mono meeting plans we're
on
clubhouse youtube tick tock
facebook
nice nice
i'm excited renata aw can i have coconut
water with spirulina
barley grass cheese powder during the
mono eating cleanse i mean i would
i would hold off on that during the mono
eating cleanse that's what i would do
and you're doing
are you doing a three day model eating
cleanse after the mono-eating cleanse
you just
pick it up then i mean you can do what
you want and do what your doctor tells
you to you might have a doctor that
loves medical medium information do what
you want to do
but what i would do i'll tell you what i
would do is i would hold off
uh you know most supplements or maybe
all of them just for three days
you can do that if you're planning on
doing the mono cleanse long
term read the book and it tells you that
then yeah you can bring if you're doing
the mono cleanse long term you can bring
in the
spirulina you can bring in the barley
grass juice powder you can bring in
supplements
you can bring in the heavy metal detox
smoothie if you're doing the mono
cleanse long term you can bring in these
other healing tools
we're just doing a quick mono eating
cleanse it's good to kind of just
you know take a break on everything for
a little bit but of course
here's the other thing we're not at it
just keep this in mind okay and this is
for everybody that's listening right now
you might be somebody that wants to
curtail it your own way and you want to
use one
one medical medium tool like your heavy
metal detox smoothie and you still want
to mono eat a little bit we'll just join
them together than if you need to and
curtail it customize it the way you want
and that's okay too
keep that in mind right that it's okay
if you want to customize the medical
medium tools and kind of mix them a
little bit if you really
you really want your metal heavy metal
detox smoothie for the next three days
but you want to do mono eating then do
you do your smoothie and you do your
model eating later on and you kind of do
try to balance it out
and that's okay if that's what you want
to do but it's geared for you know
also doing a certain type of cleansing
and it's different too on tick-tock
jimmy's got a question
i'm not sure what is it uh
let's see i'm truly grateful for all
this information
i was skeptical at first and feel great
only two weeks wow jimmy i get it if
you're skeptical at first
i get it totally get it i think what
happens is that
i'm really glad you got past the whole
thing out there where people do the
spiritual discrimination against me you
know because the information work comes
from but
the irony is medical medium information
is like
science research is stealing it left and
right right now podcast doctors are
stealing it left and right trying to
call it their own
and science is actually trying to even
prove
using medical media information certain
things about diseases medical medium
information is the most forefront most
advanced
in in anything with chronic illness we
have to date in the world right now so
you're
you you know you might see me joke
around you might see me grab the sheep
you might see me honk a horn or
something over here and answer a pink
phone
but these are medical textbooks that are
around the world
millions of people are reading them
countless doctors are reading them
science research is
taking information and stealing
information thefting it from these books
it's the most advanced medical
information in the world right now to
date
hands down and that's a fact it's a fact
so
really important to know so i'm glad
you're not a skeptic anymore and i'm
honored you are
here honored on keep that in mind jimmy
i'm truly honored really
and anyway fifty-one percent off
constant heal it's got the mono cleanse
in there if you guys just came on
make sure you have the book
so cat bernard see the chapter in the
book which talks about transitioning out
of the monoqueens yeah i might read that
a little bit too that's so cool
okay anyway let's let's go a little bit
this
is blended papaya which i love
and i'll tell you why i love it i'll
show you what i do with it okay
we're still gonna get to the peas and
the potatoes and everything else and
we'll still get to that you guys the
bananas we're kind of getting to the
bananas too because
let's just move this out of the way bear
with me a little bit
i am at your service
okay i just blended papaya right
you guys thumbs up the video if you get
a chance or you know like the video if
you get a chance and thumbs it up
later or whatever um
okay i'm showing the blend papaya now
let's show you something else let's take
a banana
take a banana love this okay
i'm gonna take two bananas
got blended papaya as we speak i got two
bananas right here
okay right
so what i'm gonna do is pop these banana
pieces right on top of blended papaya
so many people that had so many so many
disastrous health problems over the
years that i helped in 35 years
people on you know just bedridden sick
with
so many conditions neurological lyme
multiple sclerosis
total mysterious problems all of it
still is mysterious to research and
science not to medical medium
information
but so many people i got their lives
back from
this mono eating strategy that spirit of
compassion has offered
i just i just totally when i think about
it how incredible it is and how special
it
is it just blows me away you know it
blows me away
get another fork out so what we have
here all right
we have slices of banana on top of
blended papaya what i love about it is
you take a piece of banana right there
and you cover it with a little papaya
like this
[Music]
is that better than some uh
terrible cereal
so good
you could do this all day long if you
want if you got an appetite and you're
hitting the wall a little bit and you
want to do more don't be afraid of it
you do two bananas and then do another
two bananas later with more papaya then
another two
bananas later so let's go a little
little lettuce option right
you got your lettuce a little lettuce
boat look at that cute little butter
leaf lettuce and i want to answer the
question on the red leaf lettuce i think
you said or
or romaine lettuce yes you can use
romaine lettuce
the gentlest lettuce those red leaf
lettuce or
butter leaf gentle if you have like
other issues california poppy good to
see you
i haven't seen you comment lately and
it's good to see it it's awesome
mm-hmm and that's with the lettuce right
now you can just have these just like
this right on the fork with a banana
so good
insane in the membrane
all right you guys let's move on a
little bit i'm trying to move stuff
around i got a lot going on
if you're craving eat more if you're
craving and you're that hungry eat more
it's okay don't do that thing where you
chop up a banana and you have a little
bit of papaya and that's all you ate the
whole day
don't do that lorraine l is that funny i
see an
l-o-l it's not my dark shirt though
lorraine the real dark one
that you like i'm new
what is that oh dear lord
oh dear lord oh my god
oh my god
oh you're gonna have to re-watch this
whole thing i can't go into it
i'll try to go with you real quick quick
quick quick quick monday in class
medical medium get the book 51 percent
off they do that
whoa whoa banana banana papaya papaya
put it in there like this you gotta do
that you can do peas
celery juice
okay re-watch it on youtube if you can
give it a thumbs up if you want all
right let's get some peas going
my god this food is giving me extra
energy
i don't even know what to say darlene
that was funny right i don't know i
thought it was funny because it made me
laugh
mono eating cleanse is what we're
talking about we're on a three-day model
model eating cleanse
challenge and guess what it's free and
you don't have to pay three thousand
dollars i'm not taking it to a private
platform
selling tickets and everybody kind of
joins and you know and boom
and you know you make you know millions
of dollars that's not what we do we're
all about
the healing community all about chronic
illness getting people better and i want
to recap the options
you start out with your lemon water
right there boom 16 to 32 ounces squeeze
your lemon right in there
and you've got your lemon water so good
flush
that liver right off the running and
guess what
because you're not eating any junk
you're not eating any crap
because you're not having burgers and
fries and you're not having grilled
cheese and you're not having eggs and
you're not having any of that
because you're not having your eggs all
that fat you're not having your pork fat
you're not having your grilled cheese
and your cookies and your bread
and because you're not having your
burgers fries or your bean burgers or
your vegan burgers or whatever it is
vegan pizzas
because you're not doing all that your
liver is going to be able to flush
it's going to flush then when you hit it
with that when you hit it with that
lemon
boom you're able to flush it keep that
in mind
keep that in mind all right i got this
on right here let's throw some peas in
here let's get those peas simmering
i want to recap though let's keep that
organized i want to recap
16 ounces then 16 to 32 ounces of celery
juice
you can do celery juice again that day
if you want you can even do cucumber
juice at the end of the day too
you can do that as well if you really
wanted to and that's okay on the medical
medium mono eating cleanse challenge
then we just ran across the whole papaya
thing so if you're new here and you just
popped on hey guys i'm late for class
hey guys i'm late for class what are you
guys all doing
i've been busy i just found you on
facebook just now
what are you guys up to what's going on
here what why does he have a papaya in
his hand
if he came late for class
papaya banana in there cutting up a
whole bunch of pieces
put it inside lettuce right all of that
i blended papaya i put banana pieces
in there too this is the medical me
monolithic cleanse if you're late for
class
and you don't even have the cleanse the
heel book you just came late
without your school book you did you're
one of those kids in class
that came that came to school and you
don't have your book
your textbook all right anyway 51
off amazon.com us make sure you know
what you're doing the details are in
that
make sure you have that book let's get
some peas in here
i got some frozen peas a question that
was asked earlier
i'm popping some frozen peas right in
that pan
okay now let's cover some of the other
things i got lettuce right here i was
putting optional
lettuce banana in the lettuce papaya in
the lettuce okay
this is the lettuce you want is butter
leaf you could always have red leaf if
you want it too okay
you can do steamed peas and put in
lettuce i'm going to show you how to do
that in a little while you can do
steamed winter squash and have an option
of some green beans or brussels sprouts
or asparagus with that
if you want to choose more of a couple
of different things if you really want
variety you can have that for the mono
eating cleanse
but you can do banana less papaya and
lettuce you could do banana papaya and
lettuce whatever a little bit
i got some other stuff here okay
you got the option of drinking cucumber
juice in the afternoon like i mentioned
earlier
keep the salt out keep the seasonings
out
keep the salt keep the seasonings out
very important to know
all right we've got some peas in the pan
drink approximately one liter of water
throughout the entire day
you can also have some coconut water as
an option too
don't do the pink coconut water you just
got scammed
pink and red coconut water stay away
from it it's rancid
and the trick of the trade was to tell
you it was better for you and that
you're lucky if you got a pink coconut
water no you just got screwed if you got
a pin coconut water
essie says i am 100 agree with anthony
because majority of the doctors are in
into celery juice now the same doctors
were the ones
demonizing him one once upon a time
the story goes like this medical medium
comes out with advanced information
for 35 years in the health field and
then medical medium
just gets spit on and totally you know
messed with
and you know poo-pooed and demoralized
demonized right when it's all
life-saving information
medical medium information has saved
more lives around the world of chronic
illness than anybody
in history any doctor any diet belief
system whatever
and now yeah they're forced to use
celery juice because they know they've
got to get results and you know what the
sad part is
can we use iceberg lettuce yes you can
if that's all you got absolutely you can
you know what the sad part is that was
on tick tock that question
is here's what's going to happen they
bro they let celery juice in the gate
right but they still don't like medical
mediums some of these doctors right
a lot of them do like medical mediums
some don't right they let celery juice
in the gate
check this out you guys and then they
give those patients all their crappy
garbage and the patients are actually
hanging in there
or getting a little bit of a benefit
because celery juice is
cleaning up the mess that the doctor's
giving them all the other crap and
garbage that doesn't get them better
the celery juice is keeping them afloat
i almost
just want to be like you know do it
right if you're going to do it at all
but
at least it's helping to some degree
all right we're doing peas right here
we're just cooking them up
see those are those are in the pan let
me pop
this on right here okay
question on tick tock tips on sugar
cravings
absolutely if you're getting a sugar
craving and you're doing the model
eating cleanse
sip some coconut water make sure you're
getting enough of the foods that are on
the motto eating cleanse
are you doing one tiny potato
are you doing just one potato and that's
all you're doing so you're going to be
on that
50 calories for the whole day and that's
what you're on
then again you're going to have a sugar
craving you're going to have all kinds
of crazy cravings
big time you're going to be a craver
you're going to be gone craving okay so
you want to make sure
that you've got some good potato serving
steamed potato servings
you want to get some fuel that you're
still healing and cleansing
question on tick tock do you have
anything in the pan
with the peas water no you know why
these are frozen
peas they already have the kind of like
that moisture around them
and i'm just letting them just cook up
real quick no water in the pan
no i don't need it no need it they're
almost almost done
i think drinking celery killed my
saw something i think drinking celery
killed killed something
killed your craving that's what it was
killed your craving
yep 32 ounces of celery juice can kill
the cravings it can
mineral salts and i'll tell you why
there's two things that kill cravings
okay trace mineral salts which
is the most abundant source on the plant
into celery juice
they go to the brain these trace mineral
assaults keep that in mind
i'm gonna take the brain out of my dummy
real quick are you guys okay with that
okay i got the brain out of my dummy
right
two things the brain runs on keep this
in mind and
one of them is not protein two things
the brain runs on
trace mineral salts
and what's the other you guys i forgot i
don't even remember what's the other
guys
you know i'm messing with you you guys
remember glucose
sugar your brain runs on sugar or trace
mineral salts
both it runs on both right it doesn't
run on protein
but look out for the protein zombies
right
protein protein protein protein
protein where's my protein where's my
protein can't live without protein
protein protein protein protein protein
robot
self-destruct self-destruct
self-destruct protein robots
self-destruct
i'm from brainwashed frozen robot
breaking robot protein rubber and i'm
simple
cheaper where's my protein sheeple
getting lying all the sheep yep we're
here where's the protein shoot sheep
sheeps protein protein birthday protein
we need a protein more sheep more sheep
we need a protein
all right sure a few or a few of you are
like
not gonna get his book now
but you know what you just get cheated
out of healing if you don't
mr robot on tick-tock
thank you very much mr roboto thank you
very much chris
all right get these peas done
anthony can you talk about salts
so can you talk about salt and celery
juice i've been doing it for a while
but my husband i guess we do some
research and told
me yesterday that salts can be an issue
but i trust you road salt's the issue
so road salt right
added salt is the issue you want to add
salt that's the issue
sodium cluster salts in celery juice are
a complete electrolyte
it's not salt and that's where science
is just totally messed up
if you believe in science says
everything science says everything
science is 100 right about anything then
then if someone believes that way and i
know you guys don't but if someone
believes that way
they get they get in trouble because
once you get sick and you're sick
science is just not there anymore they
don't catch you you fall backwards you
think science is gonna catch you
you fall backwards i'm gonna okay
science
science you'll catch me don't worry
science and research you'll catch me
right
because i got neurological lyme right
now and i i got sick for the first time
in my life
science will you catch me i'm gonna fall
now i know you're gonna catch me right
ah
boom that's what science does everybody
totally just that's what it does to
everybody just so you know
you get sick with chronic illness that's
it
um thank you for the laugh laurie said
i'm honored can i do potato banana
lettuce
octop says can i do uh banana potato
no don't don't do potato and banana
together no
no definitely don't do that make sure
you got your copy coming
so you don't make a mistake like that
make sure you got your copy coming so
you read the
model eating cleanse section so you
don't make a mistake like that okay
all right all right you guys i'm not
trying to fool around too much today you
guys because this is serious we're doing
the mono eating cleanse challenge
i know i like to joke around a little
bit i get sarcastic too i'm not trying
to do that to you guys today
lorraine l mora leafy greens has helped
me so much with
savory cravings and cj amazing
lorraine i'm proud of you just you just
know that
right these are just cooking up nice i
think they're pretty much done i was
just trying to get them some good heat
that's all a little bit more heat we're
good
yes need the leafy greens the lettuces
cover that when you're doing like the
model eating cleanse the celery juice
covers that
celery juice is an herb lettuces
are herbs too believe it or not
to some degree
this is for another minute and we're
almost there you guys i just want to
show you
something else here this is important
with the peas so i'm going to move
some of these entrees now
i'm like these appetizers can i move
some of these appetizers out
rebecca can you pair potatoes and peas
you can
when you're not doing the mono eating
cleanse you're doing the mono eating
cleanse
no don't don't pair them don't pair them
all right
let me move my celery juice over you
guys okay for that move my lemon water
over to the side you guys okay
all right let's get my spoon out of the
way
unless you want to customize it your way
right you're using medical medium tools
if you want to customize it but
but it's it's you got to be careful you
customize because you might all be like
okay i'll throw some chocolate in here
next
it's like no don't all right these are
done
these babies are done nice you guys see
the steam popping up popping up right
there
wow right
let's get this
out of here
okay we're gonna get any damage control
going on
all right all right move these over
damage control damage control
lorraine what is it disaster relief is
that what it is
when uh aw's got too much going on and
he's live
the funny thing is you guys i like doing
it live i don't like doing the
pre-recorded stuff where you just cookie
cut everything i think that's ridiculous
just eat enough you got to eat enough if
you're active
if you're active man you got to eat
enough i'm going to get i'm going to
tell you that right now
that's important to know if you're
active you definitely got to eat enough
okay
let's get the food processor out here
let's get this going
you guys hit the wall and you're active
you don't eat enough that's not good
you that's the whole point you can do
the mono-eating cleanse and live your
life
that's that and heal while you're living
your life what better
like what better thing to do than that
seriously what better thing to do than
that okay
so i'm i'm sending the ps in the
processor right now i'm making a p
hummus i just lost the p i saw it bounce
off there's one on the floor now i'm
sure i'm gonna step on it
it's life in the fast lane man
let's make a quick hummus right here no
water
no water added in okay so there's no
water added in
let's get a pea hummus going you can do
smashed peas
you can smash them that's fine too you
can blend them
a little bit more you can blend them
less
right i don't want to over blend them
because you don't have to over blend
them
right
this is becoming a show
like seriously
yeah this is out of control you guys
this is that this train this train has
left it not only left the station man
this train has lost its brakes
going down a mountain right now
medical medium mountain
let's get this p hummus out of this food
processor
let's get that going right let's move
this food processor so i can show you
guys what's up
what is going on
now i got this beautiful pea hummus
right here
i eat too much sugar anthony from your
cleanse and my candida is out of control
emma well you know what happens is that
it's it's like this okay
no one taught you about the candida
thing anyway so that's one thing
so you mean you ate bananas because
bananas kill
anything that's bad in our systems you
mean you ate papaya
is that what you mean because what
feeds candida meaning bad stuff because
candida is not even the bad thing
so just a couple of things i got to run
by anybody who who doesn't understand
candida anybody that says any kind of
practitioner doctor says you got candida
doesn't know anything about
anything in my opinion because first of
all candida is the beneficial fungus
that you're not supposed to kill
so if you kill candida then the bad
fungus takes over
so you we only thrive
because of candida candida is how
transference
of some nutrients get into your body
because there's the candida is the
beneficial fungus
that actually converts and transfers
nutrients when you kill all your candida
off
you can get so sick you can die so when
all these fancy doctors and
practitioners and people are like trying
to kill off your candida what real
people don't realize is they're trying
to kill you
without them knowing because you don't
want to get rid of your candida you get
rid of your candida you're on a fast
track the worst deficiencies on the
planet and the worst efficiencies
anybody's ever seen and i've seen that
i've seen people go through all these
candida cleanses
all these candida protocols and
literally have nothing left
that gets so many deficiencies
everything just falls apart now listen
to your doctor
if your doctor says you have candida
listen to your doctor do it your doctor
tells you if your doctor doesn't want
you to do
you know a banana then don't do it right
and the other you know so that's
important to know
the other thing is or you know make sure
you're not on your coffee make sure
you're not on your caffeine make sure
you're not doing almond milk during this
okay
make sure you're not doing nutritional
yeast make sure you're not doing acv
you know like so did you even do the
mono-eating cleanse did you put avocado
in there oil
avocados what did you put in there did
you are you eating animal protein at the
end of the day
so what happens is what people don't
realize is they'll be like okay i'm
going to do the mono-eating cleanse
and i'm going to have a banana now it's
like whoa
you still want all this other stuff i
want you to be your own detective i'm
not saying you
are but i'm saying that's possible what
supplements are you on are you taking a
bunch of gut cleansers did you actually
read the book so you're not doing all
these kind of crazy supplements that
everybody's got you on and then you're
still trying to do the mono eating
cleanse while you're doing all this
other garbage and junk
keep that in mind it's critical right
there okay all these things matter
that's the details
did you get a new medical treatment too
keep in mind was there a new medical
treatment and now the medical medium
banana you ate is causing all your
problems when really that banana is not
causing all the problems it's a new
medical treatment that you got a month
ago
like keeping i'm just i want people to
be their own detectives right here
i'm glad these questions come up it's
all important cold white spring
the sheep is leaving the show
and so you know the thing is is that
this is all important right another
thing is
if you've never got rid of the garbage
or the junk and you really
go fat free and you start doing the mono
cleanse
and you're getting rid of those fats and
you stopped your coffee and you stopped
your chocolate and you stopped your
your the junk you're on right then
you're gonna just start getting rid of
stuff and you stopped your vinegar
you're gonna start getting rid of stuff
right and then another thing too is like
i said
i watched women die over the years
because they were candida cleansed to
death because what happened was
they went all through the 80s and 1990s
when the candida scare happened
and they were literally killed off these
women were killed off
because they ran cleansers through their
intestinal tract to kill off candida and
they removed all their beneficial fungus
and then these women died
thousands of women died in the 1980s and
1990s and early 2000s from candida
cleansing
thousands of women died they lost their
lives their bodies fell apart
everything just fell apart because of a
thrush you know because
they were told they had candida thrush
and they were put on protocols
they were put on all kinds of thrush
protocols and these protocols and that
protocols and
it was to try to clear out the candida
and what happened was
they lost all their candida all right
and they died and they died
the ones that lived the the cleanses
didn't do
didn't clear out and kill all of their
candida thank god because that's how
they lived through
it okay so yeah there you go
uh someone's dealing with rush or
anything like that so it's important to
know when people have thrush they got h
pylori they got streptococcus they got e
coli in their gut
they got they got those kinds of things
happening in their gut right
they have all of that they got herpes
simplex one you know cold sore virus
they got all these different
bugs in them that are thriving when they
shouldn't be thriving and it takes time
to clear all that stuff out and learn
how to heal
um but anyway
you guys let me let me just show you
real quick right here
so i got the um steam p
option right here okay protocols are in
the book by the way they're all in the
book all protocols for how to heal so
many conditions over 200
just quick rundown you guys if you don't
have the book
i feel sad for you there's 200 symptoms
and conditions
with the causes and how to heal and what
supplements protocols and what to do
it's here the mono eating cleanse is one
of the most powerful tools
to heal people and get them better
there's over thousands of combinations
in the medical mean books for for you to
heal if you don't have the book i feel
bad for you
because it's like either someone didn't
tell you or you woke up in the morning
and didn't know it even exist whatever
it was
the naturopath had me on a no sugar
diet to remove candida and it got worse
course it did
i'm telling you right now you know uh
jimmy i'm telling you right now
i've seen women die from that candida
about you know trying to knock the
candida out and i've seen
thousands of women that died in the 80s
and 90s and early 2000s from that
candida crap
it's so sad i don't even know what to
say let's see
emma i tried i tried 369 which helped
but still suffering still stuff
still suffering from thrush what happens
is this okay
if someone's got thrush take the book to
your doctor
find the doctor take the book to your
doctor right take a look at the sibo
protocol okay
that's what i would do take a look at
the sibo protocol
so if i was somebody and i had thrush
which is streptococcus
right with streptococcus and you know
what happens is the 369
is getting you better but how many times
did you do the 369 you could do 369
advanced
like if it was me i would do 369
advanced over and over again
that's one thing i would do i would also
take a look at the strep protocol
ask your doctor what's right for you and
what your doctor says
that's who you listen to do not listen
to me i'm just telling you that
what i would do for myself or my loved
ones and my family okay
that's what i would do i'd make sure all
my supplements didn't have the alcohol
in them didn't
have all the garbage in them i'd make
sure they were recommended medical
medium supplements
i would also i would also make sure that
um i was doing the strep protocol or
flip it to the sibo protocol
i'd be doing the advanced cleanse 369
i'd be doing the mono eating cleanse
probably the potato monowing cleanses
what i would be doing this is what i
you know i would do ask your doctor
what's right for you don't listen to me
ask your doctor i'm just telling you
what i would do for myself and you can
go as far as you need to go
i would go as far as i need to go until
i was better and got past that
a lot of people get past that anyway i
got the p
hummus right here i'm putting a little
bit of the p hummus right here so this
is if you're choosing a pea and lettuce
there it is look at that beautiful green
look at that right there
now like i said earlier i had the papaya
i had the banana now i'm doing the peas
you don't want to deal with that
it's not recommended right this is just
because like i said i'm trying to show
you guys
so i'm gonna be eating a little
everything just so i can give you guys a
rundown
um all right
we're doing three days of this are you
guys gonna be with me tomorrow
one o'clock pacific time u.s four
o'clock
eastern time us tomorrow we're doing
three days of this this is the first day
right here
i'm going to ig instagram probably about
15-20 minutes
i just got to clean up the mess a little
bit maybe get some fresh stuff out if i
can
all right i'm going to go on ig i'm
going to turn tick tock back on you guys
i'm going to turn clubhouse back on you
guys coming with me
because you know i get a little bit more
sillier when we go to ig which might not
be a great idea because i really gotta
focus
on the cleanse but you know what it all
depends on what questions come at me too
okay guys the mono eating cleanse helps
to break the addictions
it helps to change the taste buds too so
that you know you're tasting poison
the the medical medium mono cleanse
makes it so your taste buds can taste
poison
so when you go and you're having this
and this
okay when you go to get sushi someday
your taste buds got so refined from the
medical medium mono cleanse
that you taste that mercury you taste
that
vinegar okay you taste that coffee which
is the poison
and then you're like whoa i was poisoned
all this time
you had me poisoned i did his mono
cleanse for a year
it it helped my gut and now i eat raw
and healed my gut whoa you did the mono
cleanse for a year and healed your gut
i can't tell you how many people healed
their guts from the mono
cleanse feeling so much better with
daily celery juice incredible too on
tick-tock amazing you guys
you know the book get the book i'm
heading to ig and i'll see you guys soon
you know i love you guys very much never
forget it always got your back
spread the word if you can but you'll
get some naysayers he'll be like what
who
like no you don't understand he's he's
got answers he's got answers
what he's the medium no he's got answers
anyway i love you guys let's keep on
getting the world better like we are and
have been okay
that's why medical medium uh information
is the leading information
in health and wellness and chronic
illness six and a half years running now
all right heading over to ig