registered dietitian here
yeah you don't need a cleanse
no no one needs to cleanse now the body
cleanses itself
nutritionists here tristan is here
yep oh yeah we just had our appointment
i know i told you you don't need a
cleanse don't listen to anybody about
cleansing
no one needs a cleanse the body just it
just cleanses itself
we're meant to cleanse
yep no don't need a cleanse uh-huh
a doc doctor here doctor here uh-huh
a medical doctor here yeah functional
medicine doctor no you don't need a
cleanse
why should you ever cleanse yeah
uh-huh yeah no we don't know what's why
you're sick
that's right that's right we don't know
why you're sick
but you don't need a cleanse you don't
need a cleanse
no never need a cleanse dietician here
dietitian here registered dietitian here
rd here
i don't know what's wrong with you no i
i
i don't know why you're sick with
chronic
symptoms but you don't need a cleanse
you don't you just don't need a cleanse
there's no reason to cleanse
no no nutrition is here yep nutritionist
that's right what's wrong with you oh i
i don't know i i don't know what's
really wrong
but you don't need a cleanse no body
cleanses itself why would you ever
why would you ever cleanse no
no okay we have to get going here
we're live and we're day two of the
medical medium
morning cleanse challenge cleansing is
critical
great mistakes out there one of the big
mistakes you guys
is that right there big mistake
it's you don't need a cleanse your body
cleanses itself it's gonna cleanse
itself you don't need a cleanse your
body does it your body fixes everything
your it's your your body why would you
ever cleanse this is an
incredible mistake happening out there
just letting you know for the 4-1-1 on
that really important we're live on
facebook
we're live on youtube we're live on
tick-tock we're live on clubhouse i'm
glad we're here you guys
it's an important day to see you now
medical medium morning cleanse
we're gonna have some fun today we're
gonna be doing the lemon water we're
gonna do the celery juice of course
we're gonna do the liver rescue
smoothie liver rescue
smoothie i'm probably gonna make some
oatmeal i'm probably gonna make some
millet
and i'll probably make some other things
too so i'm excited about this
did you guys take advantage of the sale
right now
medical media morning cleanse is inside
cleanse the heel this is
by far the most powerful cleansing book
out there
by far it has the mono eating cleanses
has the 369 cleanses
incredible i mean if you guys are new to
this you should see
some of the stories out there people
doing the 369 cleanse and coming back
from death coming back from being
literally in hospice in hospice and
coming back
and doing the 369 cleanses
coming back from going through so much
it it's incredible really what's going
on here
lorena good to see you guys are coming
on everybody's coming on here
um yeah and so you guys there's so much
information packed in this book actually
kevin good to see you the whole thing
here
is that we need information
and knowledge in order to heal one of
those pieces of information and
knowledge
those pieces of knowledge is cleansing
learning how to cleanse
knowing how to clean the body up because
your liver
your liver needs help in order for you
to heal and move forward
it's a really important part of healing
in this book by the way on amazon us
okay amazon.com us 16.99 and in this
book
are close to 200 symptoms and conditions
talking about the dosages of
supplementation what to use
how to use it supplements and dosages
the cleanses are in here 75 recipes
it's a book you want to get a hold of so
you can move forward if you guys
are new to this this is the premiere
book right here
so let's talk a little bit about
everything
insulin resistance we've been talking
about lately it's something we'll cover
today a little bit too
but let's go straight into it you guys
an important critical piece of
information if you
ever get told anywhere anyhow that you
don't need to cleanse and your body
cleanses itself
you just got lied to you just got lied
to keep that in mind
and and it's not maybe you weren't lied
to on purpose
but the industry is teaching people to
lie
to you so you got to keep keep in mind
and how that works
so the industry itself they stamp out
cookies every day and
you'll be a nutritionist cookie no you
don't need a cleanse
you'll be a nutritious cookie all
stamped out you'll be a registered
dietitian cookie all stamped out
no don't need a cleanse don't need to
cleanse don't need a cleanse you'll be a
functional medicine doctor no don't need
a cleanse don't need a cleanse
you'll be a conventional md a gp no
don't need a cleanse don't need a
cleanse no
no no they'll stamp you out like cookies
i'm gonna get my degree next let me get
my degree and have a bunch of letters
after it nope you don't need to cleanse
you don't need to cleanse
and that's how it works and but what
happens is
you're gonna get in trouble when that
you're going to get in trouble because
your body needs
to clean up and everybody's
hear it out there people are worried
about the lymphatic system out there
right
they're worried about lymphatic drainage
and lymphatic system
you can't clean up the lymphatic system
until you clean up the liver really
important
you can't clean up the lymphatic system
until you clean up the liver
this body's just falling apart right
here on here on me
but that's why we're live that's the
whole point you can't clean up
your lymphatic system unless you clean
up the liver
you have to clean that up first if you
don't clean that up
there is no cleaning the lymphatic
system there's no cleaning up the
lymphatic system really important to
know
that's how it works and
another thing too by the way you can't
clean up your brain
until you clean up your liver it's
another thing too you can't clean your
brain up either
that's a whole nother point your brain
is not supposed to be
the filter you guys your brain is not
supposed to be the filter
but it becomes the filter because our
liver stays dirty
and sick so our brain becomes a filter
it's not supposed to be a filter
so everybody walks around dirty brains
dirty
gross brains filled with sludge
and pus all going through it and acid
going through it
we walk around with acid brains because
we need to cleanse
and that's how it works once your liver
gets dirty
it starts to get clogged up over the
years everything else gets dirty
and nasty that's how our bodies work
that's how our system works
important to know right there
so i don't know if you guys were ever
told or if you ever heard about
it don't cleanse one of the most
powerful and cleansing foods bring some
of the uh
con reading some of the comments to you
guys trying to catch them wherever i can
um
so someone's saying most chemicals
cannot pass through the blood-brain
barrier
uh did you just say blood
did you say blood so on tick-tock most
chemicals and toxins cannot pass through
the blood-brain barrier
uh does your does your brain need any
blood
you guys does your brain get any blood
i'm just curious about that just because
i'm scratching my head on that one
i love when you throw a comment at me
that
is so ridiculous that it's a head
scratcher um
okay so if blood gets to your brain
in it is going to be to poisons and
toxins you know that right
on tick tock you know that right i mean
you know that
your blood is filled with garbage and
junk chemical
chemical compounds that are synthesized
chemicals toxins fragrances junk toxic
heavy metals
all kinds of exposure fat acids all
kinds of things
floating around your bloodstream right
okay all the pesticides herbicides
fungicides floating around your
bloodstream right
bloodstream did you hear me bloodstream
did you know your brain gets
blood right
so when you try to throw out that whole
thing that blood brain barrier thing
okay your brain tissue
needs blood so you're pretending no
blood goes to the brain whatsoever
so you're just pretending you're just
telling me it's all spinal fluid
so not one drop of blood goes through
the brain it's just all spinal fluid
so that doesn't even make sense
basically that's just already naturally
debunked
your blood is filled with junk your
blood
goes to the brain that's how it works
is there a part of the brain that
actually has the spinal fluid
aspect of it yeah but what about the
rest of it
what about the wrestling it's critical
this is critical information
but you know what though i'm glad you're
here on tick tock and i appreciate it
because it's those kinds of comments
that are important because
someone else is going to hear that
catherine elizabeth gaspino good to see
you
um if the liver can't
clean up and stop the toxin it's gonna
go to the brain
and you're gonna get sicker and sicker
someday or
get sick that's how it works
it's important to know so
the blood brain barrier you can't
pretend
the brain doesn't get any any blood
whatsoever
you can't pretend it gets no blood
because it does
it does and that blood is dirty going to
the brain
that's how it works yeah
the liver is your filter that's your big
filter
i'm watching the comments on tick-tock
for the moment
bro the blood-brain barrier is not your
filter
so it's not your brain's filter so keep
that in mind too
catherine says we were told to cleanse
but not in the right way okay so let's
go into that part
catherine really good point okay a lot
of people are told to cleanse
and it's all the wrong way so keep that
in mind
friends for instance you can't cleanse
if there are any fats in your cleanse
if you're downing olive oil in a cleanse
because
that happens a lot have you guys ever
heard that have you ever heard of like
cleanses where you're dumping olive oil
and straight straight in you
just let you know let me know if you
drop a comment and let me know about
that one
if you've seen that before live on
clubhouse tick tock
live on facebook live on youtube have
you
heard of olive oil being in a cleanse at
all
just curious because
you can't cleanse anything if there's a
fat
inside your cleanse okay
so keep that in mind that's important
once you have fat in your bloodstream
your liver can't cleanse
it's focused on producing bile
that's how it works so you can be
you can be somebody that's eating light
you're just doing some drinks
with with olive oil in there right
i'm seeing some of you guys have
actually seen that liver flush
right crispy apple says liver flush with
the olive oil
you don't flush the liver when you're
doing the olive oil you don't
all you're doing is shutting the liver
down it can't cleanse when you put
when you put the olive oil in there this
is really important
linea says i have a friend who is
drinking olive oil to cleanse
but he never got better because you
can't cleanse
you can't cleanse with
olive oil in your cleanse drink
it's not possible you
have to stop the liver from
having to work in order to cleanse
your liver needs to take a vacation
in order for you to cleanse
bottom line that's how it works
the minute you dump in the fat and
you're dropping in the fat
and you're putting in your drink and
someone's gave you some
brilliant brainiac cleanse idea
because of some trendy bs cleanse and
you're dropping the olive oil in
and that olive oil goes in there the
minute it goes in
all bets are off game is over
there is no cleansing it's not gonna
happen it can't happen it never will and
it won't
okay what degree of cleansing you do
depends on how
easy you make life for your liver
that's what determines a cleanse
how easy it is for your liver
that's what determines a cleanse right
there
and the minute there's fat in that
cleanse the minute there's olive oil in
that cleanse
game over there is no cleanse there is
no cleanse
the minute there's coconut oil in your
cleanse game over there is no cleanse
game over no one's cleansing that day
no one's cleansing that day you got some
olive oil no one's cleansing that day
the minute avocado is in that cleanse
game over
game over you're not cleaning nothing up
you're not cleaning nothing up
you're not elizabeth says i tried
coconut oil a few times
stopped right away i knew it wasn't
right
it's hard on the pancreas hard on the
pancreas
i've known people they've done that
coconut oil because they're ready to put
you
two three tablespoons of coconut oil in
your in your smoothie
and they get pancreatitis
because your pancreas went oh my god
your pancreas just went you just tried
to kill me
yeah it's a healthy fat yeah coconut oil
is a healthy fat
but still what about fat later in the
day
does detox stop yes your teeth
your detox stops fat later in the day
your detox stops but here's the thing
that's okay that's okay because if you
do the medical medium morning cleanse in
the morning
you did some detoxing in the morning
all night long your brain
was crying for your blood to clean up
and all night long your liver was
working hard to try to save
your brain all night long your liver
was working hard to try to save your
brain
by cleaning cleaning cleaning
cleaning everything being a
filter for your bloodstream all night
long
to try to protect your brain right
morning comes and you do the medical
medium morning cleanse
and you do your lemon water
right you do your celery juice
okay you do your celery juice right
which we're gonna do a little bit
you do your medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie
you do your liver rescue smoothie which
we're about to do
you have a bowl of fruit if you want you
drink some more coconut water or drink
coconut water you have some more lemon
water
you could put honey in the lemon water
and you're
cleansing you guys because guess what
there wasn't coconut oil in your
smoothie there was an olive oil in your
smoothie but that's not all
there was an avocado
in your on your toast in your smoothie
so you actually were cleansing you were
taking
out the trash you guys if you guys don't
have cleanse to heal you guys should
take advantage of the sale and make sure
you've got this incredible information
i can only say so much within an hour
every time there's so much information
this is a medical textbook
it's 16.99 amazon.com right now it's a
sale you don't
want it you just don't want to ignore
okay
all right
what scientific evidence is there that
oils
in your diet negatively affects ability
to remove
toxins okay it's on tick tock
right 40 and tick tock
that question right there so you you
need scientific evidence
is that what it is so what scientific
evidence has an answer for why
everybody's got chronic illness
what's scientific evidence right
is there of why children have eczema
psoriasis
they're riddled with skin diseases skin
conditions
what scientific evidence right
where science doesn't even know why
anybody's sick
where's the scientific evidence there
besides science says they don't know why
everybody is sick
even science and research says they
don't know what everybody's saying
okay so you need scientific evidence
from science
that doesn't know why anybody's sick
just think about that just try to wrap
your head around that for like two
seconds
signs of research don't know why
anybody's sick why you have trigeminal
neuralgia why you have fibromyalgia
while you have
thyroid hypoglycemic hyperglycemic while
you're
your thyroiditis hashimoto's thyroiditis
hypothyroidism graves
nodules on your thyroid right
back back pain neck pain feet pain
gout science research doesn't know why
anybody's sick
but you want scientific evidence
that's what you want but what you will
find that science takes
information from medical medium after
it's been published so and here's one
thing for like if you're a
science-minded person
science and research has never proved
medical medium information wrong yet
it's only proven it right that's a fact
the info is advanced it's already healed
millions worldwide from chronic illness
and i have the street cred
see what i like is street cred
scientific data doesn't make me happy
because i've seen millions of people
screwed over out there
losing their lives losing their
livelihoods losing their careers losing
their relationships losing their
husbands and wives
losing their boyfriends and girlfriends
losing their fiances
because of sickness and chronic sickness
and illness because it's either made
them
lose it completely or made them so sick
lerna says science was not able to help
me with my bad trigeminal neuralgia mm
healed me science just drilled my
healthy
teeth until i lost several of my
beautiful teeth so
on tick-tock did you hear that
see how important it is to know how
things work so i get it i know you're
curious where's your scientific evidence
about fats
but you're when you're dealing with
medical medium information you're
dealing with medical medium information
you're dealing with advanced information
that science takes later
all the doctors are using now people are
stealing it left and right in the health
movement and not citing it back to
medical medium even though
factual it's been published first
so what you're going to find if you're
new here mm info has never been proven
wrong and it's never contradicted itself
fact but when you go listen to your
doctors on your doctor podcast or
something
and they're stealing medical medium
information
or they've contradicted themselves a
million times throughout the last 10
years of the career
think about that for a second so let's
talk about this
our livers get sluggish and stagnant
they get overworked they get pathogens
inside of them
everybody has bugs inside their liver
just letting you guys know
really important everybody has bugs
inside
their liver okay it's a buggy world
we live with bugs austin said
aw doesn't contradict himself if you
read the books
you listen to the podcasts listen to any
interview i've ever done
and you can go back to lectures a long
time even long before
okay and you'll find there's no
contradictions i've been saying the same
thing since i was four
years old saying the same thing since i
was four years old
so let's go into this a little bit on
the liver side of it very
important
you guys we're live on tick tock we're
live on facebook live on youtube okay
so here's the question can you cleanse
in the pm
not in the am nope that's a tick tock
question
can't cleanse in the pm
you have to cleanse in the am
when you wake up wait a minute if you
slept
all day because you have a night shift
yes you can cleanse in the pm if that's
when you wake up
if you wake up cindy lou good to see you
if you wake up in the afternoon
or at night because you had to sleep all
day because you had to work all night
and now that's your morning technically
even though it's late afternoon early
evening yes you can cleanse
start your lemon water when you wake up
boom get it done
get your celery juice going boom get it
done right
exactly have your heavy metal detox
movie
that we did yesterday boom get it done
okay have your liver rescue smoothie
which we're gonna do you say you wanted
your oatmeal
don't put anything in your oatmeal
don't put peanut butter in your oatmeal
don't do that don't put nuts
in your oatmeal don't put almonds
you guys on tick tock in your oatmeal
you do that you're not gonna cleanse
just so you know
when you're when you're overnight when
you're sleeping you're not eating any
fat
when you're awake you're tanking the
fats
so your liver is doing its cleansing all
night long
because you're not bombarding it with
fats
here you go you have your dinner at
night and whatever your dinner is
you just hit your liver with fats right
that's how it works
so you had to roast the chicken at night
for dinner you had your roasted chicken
at night for dinner you just slammed
your liver with fats okay
but you go to bed and the hours go by
right say you eat at seven o'clock at
night
three hours later it's ten o'clock at
four hours later it's eleven five hours
it's twelve
six hours it's one two o'clock in the
morning you're
seven hours since eating your fat
three in the morning i think we're at
three in the morning two in the morning
three in the morning
three in the morning okay
we're another couple of hours in
now we're getting to the point where we
haven't eaten
in a lot of hours keep that in mind
you're eight hours into not eating
eight hours right
so now your liver is free
it's clean it's already been working on
dealing with processing that dinner time
fat it was processing and working on it
hours ago eight hours ago
see guys how it works eight hours ago it
was already processing
by three four in the morning now
we're nine hours into it if
my math is right right there four four
four in the morning we're nine hours
into it
five in the morning we're 10 hours into
it your liver hasn't
had to deal with fat in 10 hours
six in the morning
you're 11 hours into it or whatever
now you're 9 10 11 hours into it
you wake up at seven in the morning
let's just may you wake up maybe you
wake up at six maybe you wake up at
seven
your chicken fat
isn't hurting the liver so much anymore
it's now it's detoxing it's ready to
detox it's ready to cleanse it's ready
to clean
your liver is ready to clean now you see
how it works you guys
you see how it works your liver is ready
now
okay the chicken you ate
the chicken you ate was a long time ago
right the chicken fat was a long time
ago you guys
but here's the deal you don't want to
put
fat back in your diet in the morning
because the minute you do
you can't cleanse you can't clean
up it's not going to happen
i'm letting you know
the minute you drop in that peanut
butter on your smoothie the minute you
put
that olive oil in your smoothie the
minute you have your coconut oil minute
you put olive oil on your bread
the minute you have avocado
you're not cleansing anymore done
it's over and i know that gets people
upset they're like oh he doesn't like
avocado
he must be a real stupid guy in the
health scene he must be really dumb
because every single podcast i listen to
they talk about how healthy avocado is
everybody's having avocado toast he must
not know what's going on are you kidding
me
i i still don't i still i'm still not
sure we'd be here in the avocado world
like we were if it wasn't for 35 years
of me
trying to teach people to eat avocado
because i needed them to eat avocado
instead of pork because it's a better
fat it's a healthy fat
but it doesn't it doesn't change
the fact that when you have your avocado
in the morning
your cleanse just ended
i try to get people to eat avocado
instead of actual
butter 30 years ago 35 years ago so i
love when someone comes on board
doesn't even know what's going on and
says well he's anti-avocado he must not
be a smart guy because everybody knows
everyone knows avocado is so good for
you now
let's make some lemon water
let's go remove the
peanut butter
medical medium warning cleanse let's
start out lemon water 16 to 32 ounces
let's do it let's cut the lemon in half
there you are
got the lemon cut in half you guys
this medical medium morning cleanse is
in
cleanse to heel just letting you know i
see more people coming on so i want
everybody to know
where to get the information i could be
here i could deliver it you guys we're
going to cover a lot of ground
but honestly you should be reading this
at night
you'll find so much information on how
to heal conditions symptoms
everything the different cleanses it's
16.99
okay 16 i mean it's on sale 51 off at
amazon.com
us you might want to consider it
get a free the library if you can't if
you don't have the 16
so 16 to 32 ounces of lemon water first
thing in the morning
you want to flush you want to flush you
guys
that's what you want to do
got some water right here you want to
flush
okay the whole thing about lemon water
flushing the liver flushing the body
is medical medium original information
that's where it originated from
lemon water didn't originate with
medical medium people had been putting
lemon in their water
long before i was born but it wasn't to
flush the liver or cleanse the liver it
was to make a delicious beverage
important to know your liver gathers
all these toxins all night long
and we need an acid neutralizer
acids and toxins the calcium
in citrus is unlike anything else and
you can do
lime you guys want lime
let's do lime let's do lime right here
let's do lime you guys don't like lemon
i don't like lemon
do lime i can't tell you how many times
over the years
i don't particularly like lemon anthony
so i'm not really going to do that lemon
water in the morning
miss ferguson do lime then the lime
lime lime seen this over and over again
if that's what you're gonna do anyway 16
to 32 ounces of lemon water
we got that going on let's squeeze it in
there
okay get that lemon in there you got it
right
get the lime in there you got it
right already
you're doing it you just woke up
you're doing it okay now here's the
thing just so you know
i'm gonna give you some very important
tip right here
you wake up in the morning
and you have your coffee and you say
well i'm not eating anthony
so i should be cleansing fine i just
have my coffee
and i'm drinking my coffee black aw
so i should be cleansing because there's
no
fat in my coffee i'm drinking it black
wrong wrong here's how it works
the minute you use the psychoactive drug
caffeine
the minute you use that in the morning
guess what happens
your adrenaline stops your cleanse
adrenaline produced by the psychoactive
drug caffeine in the morning
stops your cleanse your cleansing
over done and done
that's how it works just so you know
because adrenaline is so highly
corrosive and toxic
that the liver has to put up with it
immediately
it has to shut down it's cleansing
immediately your liver is done
it's done the minute you drink your
coffee in the morning
i don't care if you're someone's like i
don't really eat much in the morning i
don't need anything i just drink my cup
of coffee
so i'm not a big ham and egg person in
the morning
so i aw really you know i got it covered
what happens is the minute you drink
your coffee you have your psychoactive
drug in the morning
your adrenals start to explode release
all the epinephrine
and your liver has to suck it up and
absorb it up and it has to stop
cleansing immediately and
decaf still it's the same thing it's
caffeine green tea is still the same
thing
matcha tea is still the same thing just
letting you know
so you do your coffee in the morning
guess what
you're not cleansing it's over
no plans happening no cleanse happening
lerna says coffee is extremely toxic on
the body it destroys bones and teeth it
does
it does now if you're going to keep your
coffee in i still want you to do your
celery juice
they're still going to be helpful
abilities that everything
has i still want to do your lemon water
i'm talking i'm talking about the
medical medium morning cleanse about
cleansing
deep stuff so you cleanse every day
and you work on healing and the minute
you bring in that caffeine
cleanse stops because your adrenaline is
so toxic your liver has to absorb it
so cleanse over done
over
if you're gonna drink your coffee and i
can't stop you you drink your coffee
afternoon you drink it after the medical
medium morning day cleanse
after the process of your cleanse in the
morning
drink your coffee later have your coffee
later
that's what you do you guys have your
coffee later i'm just letting you know
that's what you do and by the way
there's caffeine information
in cleanse the heel that's critical
check it out
there's also information about
fragrances how bad they really are
protect yourself learn so you can pull
out your air fresheners out of the wall
learn how to protect yourself there's
information about all the troublemakers
you guys don't know the troublemakers
you guys don't heal lucy good to see you
okay let's move on so we got the lemon
water we did that you guys that's the
first part okay
get that going
all right and all of this is important
now it's a celery juice
let's get into the celery juice a little
bit
let's make sure we're doing it
very important part gotta have your
celery juice
second step in the morning celery juice
okay
now if you don't have your celery juice
you don't have it
just don't do your fats sure
your cleanse might not be as powerful
without the celery juice but you're
still
cleansing see guys you're still
cleansing
now keep this in mind if you're someone
that doesn't want to eat or drink
anything all morning long and you think
that will be
a cleanse because you're not doing any
fats like aw
says don't do any fats you're not going
to cleanse
the reason why you're not going to
cleanse
is because when you run on adrenaline
and you have no mineral salts or glucose
in your bloodstream
and you run on adrenaline you can't
cleanse
so you could be somebody that doesn't
eat anything till noon
you know what i got aw beat not only am
i not gonna do any fats
i'm not gonna eat anything or drink
anything i'll just drink some water
do a little workout you're not gonna
cleanse
you're gonna be on adrenaline so you
won't be cleansing
you guys see how it works see how
important this is
[Music]
you can only cleanse in the morning if
you
keep the glucose and the mineral salts
in your diet
which the medical media morning cleanse
provides and you
keep the adrenaline out of your
diet out of your morning
[Music]
see how it works you guys
each piece of this information is
powerful
each piece of piece of this information
is critical
let's see ask how quickly do we have to
eat drink or
lemon water from waking up you don't
have to do it quickly
you can wait a little while you just
want to get to it
eventually if you you can wait an hour
you can wait an hour but you don't want
to wait too long but you can wait an
hour
if you want to okay
you can do that dorsey lease is such
incredible information and it makes
sense
and it's free and it's free
and it's free you know
my friend was watching the cooking
channel right
a friend really likes cooking shows
cooking channels
all those different kinds of things
right
and
[Music]
and my friend said that
every time they go into like a
restaurant like a mom and pop restaurant
and they check out the person's recipes
and stuff they're always like no it's a
secret recipe
secret recipe it's grandma's secret
recipe
grandpa's secret recipe it's our
restaurant secret recipe
we can't give you all the ingredients
there's chicken
there's butter there's olive oil
there's nutmeg and we can't give you the
rest
[Music]
everybody protects their information
protects it
medical medium my friend told me
is stupid it's my friend
my friend said medical medium is stupid
i said why why am i stupid
you don't protect your recipes of all
your critical information
and have people pay for it and keep it
protected you give it out
you give it out you give everything out
for free
you have legendary information that
people in the health industry steal and
charge for
they create programs and steal it they
do
they do uh they sell products with the
information they steal
from you and they sell things and you
just give everything away from free you
for free you must be so stupid aw
you must be so stupid
mike thanks i really appreciate that
so next is the celery juice
celery juice is glucose in it and
mineral salts keep that in mind
glucose and mineral salts are in celery
juice
keep that in mind okay
and glucose and mineral salts are
critical so your adrenals
don't burst every day every morning they
don't
burst and release all that epinephrine
that shuts your liver down okay
that shuts your liver down keep that in
mind really important to know
right really important enough
mineral salts help stop the cravings
glucose helps stop the cravings
got your got your celery juice
lemon water 16 to 32 ounces in the
morning
upon waking or you could wait a little
bit longer like
let's see was asking celery juice 16 to
32 ounces
a little bit later now listen if you
don't have
frugal frugivore bear good to see you i
just saw your handle come up
um if you don't if you don't have celery
do the lemon water we can get by we can
do a fruit bowl we can do something
that doesn't have fat in it but has
mineral salts and glucose
your lemon still has in your lime water
still has mineral salts and glucose you
see how it works you guys
important to know see so i'm going to
move the juicer out of the way right now
we're gonna make some oatmeal in a
little while but we're gonna do some
fruit first
okay so that's an option right there
that's got a nice mango right there so
you guys got a mango in my hand
just so you know that's an option right
there you could do oranges
you can do some mangoes you can do
papayas that can be something you can do
too we're gonna do the liver rescue
smoothie
but got papaya in my hand right here
look at this
so i'm just gonna cut a couple of these
open real quick you guys just so you
know that these are real
papayas real mangoes
just guys so you guys can see this see
the inside here
let's do that
that's the papaya we have right now
right
it's a beautiful papaya don't be afraid
of fruit it's one of the obstacles that
happens
one of the obstacles which is really
messed up out there
one of the obstacles is that
is that we're afraid of fruit we got the
fruit fear right
that will get in your way of healing
because guess what
if fruit is not in your diet you're
going to rely more on what
what are you guys going to rely more on
you're going to rely
more on fatty fruits
it's a fruit but fatty fruits they're
going to rely on more on nuts and nut
butters and
almonds right peanut butter you're going
to rely more on these
things is what you're going to do
you know and that's what's going to
happen
you're going to rely more on those
things
so
a lot of times when we rely
we rely more on those things we get in
trouble because now we're relying on the
fat
is what we're relying on and
there's really no way out with that one
you're going to think well no i rely on
protein that's what you're going to
you're going to think you're going to be
like no i rely on protein
i'm not relying on fat and that's where
we get in trouble right there because we
don't realize that
our protein is filled with fat
and that's something we don't realize is
that our protein is filled with fat
you know what's fun about doing these
live
that when you mess up
everybody knows it
so so when something's going on and
you're doing damage control
everybody can figure it out all right
i'm back i'm back
where did i go green blue i forgot to
defrost the
pitaya so
i got some frozen pattaya here you guys
dragon fruit right there
i forgot to defrost it so i basically
had a bag of dragon fruit
and it was all stuck together and i was
trying to chip away at it like this
chipping away with a spoon to get it out
guys we're live on clubhouse live on
tick tock
we're live on facebook live on youtube
i'm gonna do liver rescue smoothie
let's get the blender out let's drop in
some bananas
liver rescue smoothie is legendary for
helping people to heal
so many people swear by it
but science didn't didn't say so
it doesn't matter what people say
doesn't matter about people healing
doesn't matter about people getting
their lives back doesn't matter
right because science science didn't
okay it
did you know science didn't okay you
guys healing
you're not allowed to heal you know i'm
putting a little bit of wild blueberry
juice in
in this in this smoothie because i just
i just i waited forever and i got some
it's incredible this i know you guys
have
have been um waiting for your blueberry
juice i hope you guys got it too
i just got some so i put a little bit in
here i'm putting wild blueberries in
here but i have been doing this where i
put the
wild blueberry juice in there too i put
like one ounce
in here too
some medicinal factors right
that's the weimann's by the way just so
you know what that is
i work with them on that juice by the
way i work with them
this is for the record that's the
wyman's wild blueberry juice you guys
i'm i'm obsessed with it obsessed with
it
so i just popped in some frozen wild
blueberries
right that's two cups of frozen wild
blueberries i'm making the
medical medium liver rescue smoothie
let's get the bananas next where are the
bananas
some bananas going
so science research
doesn't if they don't okay you healing
you didn't heal if your eczema went away
it's not real science research didn't
okay it
you're not allowed to heal on your own
science and research won't validate it
putting two bananas in here
so whenever you hear anybody come out
and throw signs of research crap
like where's your science about that or
where's your research about that
you've got to realize where they're
coming from they're coming from a real
ignorant place
the person who's saying where's your
science where's your research is
completely ignorant to one fact
science research doesn't want you to
heal they won't even validate if someone
actually healed on any level even if
they got partially better
science research won't validate it think
about that
how psycho is that that's actually
psycho it's evil really
it kind of goes beyond it's actually
evil
you didn't heal you didn't get better
your 50 symptoms didn't go away
besides the research didn't okay
it just they didn't go away so let's go
into this a little bit
a lot of people are hung up on the
protein factor and i think this is
important i'm making a liver rescue
smoothie but i want to just drop this on
your critical piece of information
you might be thinking i'm not doing fat
i'm doing protein in the morning so
you're thinking your
your salmon in the morning is protein
you're thinking you're tuning in the
morning's protein you're thinking your
chicken in the mornings protein you're
thinking your protein powders are
protein you're thinking
there's fat and all that you're thinking
that your nut butters in the morning are
protein you're thinking your nuts and
seeds are protein you see how it works
you're thinking your protein bar is
protein
but it's all fat your protein bars fat
so you're having fat in the morning
thinking you're doing protein in the
morning and then you stop your liver
from cleansing so just keep that in mind
that's
really important right there and here's
another thing too
don't get obsessed about protein
proteins in every single
food protein isn't what keeps your
muscles growing
proteins not what makes your muscles
grow proteins
not what what not it's not what keeps
your muscles strong
okay so it's glucose
that keeps your muscles strong okay it's
sugar
sugar has to enter every cell in the
body sugar has to enter
your muscles in order for your muscles
to work
sugar plus mineral salts keep that in
mind if you're a bodybuilder you're
saying why isn't aw
like built like a tank that's because i
don't have the time and energy
because my time and energy goes into
working 20-hour days
and if i sit there and i do a two-hour
workout every day
basically what's gonna happen i just
lost two critical three critical hours
and so i can't do that right now i have
a book deadline coming up i have a book
deadline for the next so many years
so what i do is i'll go out for a quick
run or something
or i'll go out for a quick bike ride but
i can't go into the gym
and i can't and i can't go in there for
two three hours a day
start dedicating my life to bulking up
it's just not it's just it's not
something it takes an actual commitment
of time
doesn't you know i can't i go out and i
try to do a half an hour where i can
so keep that in mind if you're
somebody's a bodybuilder what i do is i
help bodybuilders i help you pro
bodybuilders out there get their you
know get their muscles
to wherever they need to get it and i
notice that when when a body builder
gets older they lose their muscle
unless they get enough carbohydrate you
guys hear that you hear that
when uh when when when athletes and
bodybuilders get older
and now they're in their 40s they start
losing all their muscle
because they're they're getting maxed
out with fat
they're just their fats are stuck all
the fat
in their protein they're eating is
stopping their muscles from being able
to stay strong
so they start to decline so then you've
got to switch it out you've got to take
the fat
out of their diet and bring in more
carbohydrate and then when they're 40
years old you could get them built back
up again
that's how it's done medical medium
style
so we're doing a liver rescue smoothie
we've got bananas in there while
blueberries i put some wine and wild
blueberry juice
um that's at shop lyman's
lymanshot.weimans.com
and keep the protein powders out
keep the protein powders out okay very
important to know
keep the protein powders out um
i'll put the vimergy wild blueberry
powder in there too
thing is with antioxidants is i love
antioxidants right like i always have
going all the way back so i try to get
them where i can
so i'll put the vimorjiwab blueberry
powder in here
with the frozen wild blueberries with
the wyman blueberry juice right
keep protein powders out they got hidden
sugars they got hidden msg
so that's another thing to keep in mind
another important piece of information
boom keep protein powders out you want
to get healthier keep protein powders
out
protein powders don't make you healthier
they got natural flavorings
in most of them most of the protein
powders have natural
flavor in them
and those natural flavorings is msg
so in some protein powders they got
added fat in them
they got added msg in them okay
and too much protein by the way kills
your kidneys it kills your liver so
there you go you don't want to be doing
that
lissy cone says and p protein is harsh
on the stomach
right question mark totally right let's
see totally
harsh on the stomach totally
important to know let's get working on
this let's drop some pattaya in there
so i got the dragon fruit right there
see
let's get that in there you see guys
we got the pattaya
right now we're gonna put some water in
here let's go
get a little water in here
you can do a half cup of water
let's do that right
i think we're ready i think that's the
liver rescue smoothie
is what i do believe put this over here
let's get this blended up
got it blending up right now you guys
envy doom says aw can you use prickly
pear instead of
pattaya uh
no
don't use prickly pear instead of
pattaya and be mindful about prickly
pear
self-limiting extremely self-limiting
keep be mindful on that one
okay i like prickly pear i do
right but it's self-limiting it's
dehydrating
just letting you know very dehydrating
so when you have prickly pear
like it's never been a no-no i've never
said a no on it
right you've never heard me say no on it
but
it's just a little reminder try not to
tank it try not to tank that prickly
pear
take that prickly pear you're it you'll
get some dehydration going on
you might even get the runs but it's
runs
on the opposite end of the scale which
is runs
not from detox from the prickly pear but
runs from the hydration from prickly
pear
but yeah i still like
the rescue smoothie done done
we are done
bam look at the color in that
you guys look at the color on tick tock
okay if you don't want the smoothie cold
you can defrost everything keep it room
temperature
keep in the fridge look at the color
is that insane or what
right i mean is that is that incredible
or what
liver rescue smoothie
what do you think on tick tock you guys
live a rescue smoothie
what do i say about that i say boom
i say boom okay we've got
we got some more to do let's turn on the
griddle
let's get the griddle on
griddle's on let's go more to talk about
okay i'm just focused on
not knocking crap over and breaking
stuff right now
so i'm just focused on making sure i'm
not
dropping a whole bottle of juice or
something down
if you need a heavy heavier meal you
could do steamed potatoes winter squash
sweet potatoes millet oatmeal
you can do oatmeal now oatmeal is high
it's higher in fat okay
that's oatmeal right here right it is
higher in fat but you're not adding fat
to it
it's higher in fat but you're not adding
fat to it
so you can still do some cleansing with
a medical medium morning cleanse if
you're an oatmeal person and it's
something you feel like you need
in the morning if you feel like you need
that oatmeal if that's what you that's
what you want
just don't put any fat in it
know the difference when you have your
nut butter
that's your fat don't dump it in there
yeah nancy oatmeal has fat
okay so let's get a little let's get we
got the griddle on
by the way you guys if you just came on
here
if you don't have this you might want to
consider it
to have it in your personal home
personal library a whole bit
it's a medical textbook lunell good to
see you
april says no plant milk
on oatmeal just water correct no plant
milk
your nut milks that's added extra fat
you're going to stop cleansing
see if you have your nut milks
right in your oatmeal you just stopped
your cleanse
in the morning you want your nut milk
and your oatmeal in the afternoon
you do it then okay
that's the uh cleanse the heel 16.99
amazon.com us just so you know your
minds will be blown once you have that
book in your hand take advantage of the
sale
amazon does that and they only do it
here and there so um
all right let's go let's pop some water
in here's what we're doing it's 51
off or get it free at the library but
the library i keep on hearing is hard
hard to get the copies and it's bumming
me out people have to wait six months
for a copy of the library someone told
it told me that the other day and i just
i was
so upset about it all right let's go
with a little bit of oatmeal
now
i'm gonna make some oatmeal
let's do that let's get some water in
here
you're somebody that does steel steel
cut you do steel cut
that's what you do
if you want to do steel cut you do still
cut
this is a quick oat right here this is a
quick oat
got the heat cranking up
do you now here's the thing with oatmeal
right
here's what i do about water
measurements i tell people all the time
water measurements for oatmeal
okay and it depends on how creamy you
want your oatmeal
do you want a creamy put more water you
want it thicker
pastier less water that's how it works
that's exactly how it works you guys
have you just arrived
medical meeting morning cleanse day two
just giving you the 4-1-1
right it's a cleanse arrived out of the
book cleanse the heal
medical meme information critical way to
cleanse
so you can heal be open-hearted good to
see you
over there on youtube
we're live on tik-tok facebook youtube
and clubhouse just for a 4-1-1
if things seem confusing
so i got some oatmeal cooking right now
it's really easy
it's really easy take a second then i
realized
yeah gluten-free oats
oatmeal is an option if you're somebody
that can handle grains
keep that in mind you're somebody that's
that's okay with grains they can handle
grains
oatmeal is an option gluten grains
are what you want to use it's
gluten-free grains
that's what you want to use
okay if you're somebody that's not
trying to
if you're somebody that's not trying to
heal at all
it's still the best grains to use it's
millet that's your number one best grain
oatmeal is your second best grain if
you're somebody not trying to heal
and then you can put your nut milks on
there if you're somebody that's not
trying to heal or cleanse you put nut
milk you put nut butters if that's what
you want to do
but i recommend not doing it i recommend
there's plenty of fat in oatmeal
if you're somebody that wants to heal
you can still cleanse
and do oatmeal and millet
just keep the fats out keep the fats out
so you can still cleanse
okay so this is almost cooked
so some people like their oatmeal really
really creamy
they dump all this nut milk in there
they make it basically like an oatmeal
soup i don't like it that way personally
that's not my style
i like it really thick that's just the
way i like to do it
so i'm going to add some blueberries in
the oatmeal it's cooking right
right up right now i'm going to add some
wild blueberries
you can cleanse and still have this
in the morning isn't it interesting
putting a few more in here there you go
you can cleanse and still have this in
the morning
the reason why you'll cleanse
is because you don't have the almonds in
there
you don't have the peanut butter in
there you don't have that in there you
don't have the nut milks in there
now you can cleanse so you can have the
oatmeal if that's what you want
you want to get the best out of a
cleanse in the morning you do the lemon
water
or lime water you do the celery juice
you do the liver rescue smoothie or the
heavy metal detox smoothie or both
both you do your you add additional 16
ounces of water or
coconut water right you do it all before
noon
that's your best option right there
that's your best option for cleansing
but you but if you're somebody that
needs something like a steamed potato
don't put the fats on and you'll still
cleanse if you're somebody that's
needing some oatmeal or some millet i'm
cooking oatmeal right now if you guys
just got on here yesterday i did potato
waffles you saw that yesterday right
you can check that out on youtube it was
yesterday's youtube
seaweed hero good to see you
so i like my oatmeal really thick
i'm cooking oatmeal in a pan not in a
pot and i'm not making it super creamy
that's the way i like it but look you
guys have it the way you like it
here we go then i'm going to add some
um
get a bowl
so uh everybody likes their oatmeal a
certain way i guess that's just
how we are as creatures on planet earth
right what's funny is we're the only
creature on planet earth that
really likes things a certain way
okay so there we go
now your that's your oatmeal right there
and what you could do is
you can add some blueberries do it
[Music]
okay and some maple syrup extra
blueberries if you want i'm gonna put
maple syrup on this one
a little bit of maple syrup is good
pop this pan off for a second
[Music]
okay
i'm gonna quickly cook a little bit of
millet
get that water up there
[Music]
i'm going to put a little bit of extra
blueberries on top of
my oatmeal
right on top here i'm gonna show you
guys this
i don't like runny oatmeal i just don't
like wet
juicy runny oatmeal i like it thick
is the way i like it
so here we are right here just so you
know i don't know if you guys can see
this on tik tok
that's a really thick creamy oatmeal got
maple syrup on top i got some wild
blueberries on top just so you know
there it is right there
and i'm gonna cook some millet working
on that right now
all right
so why that's why that's uh heating up
the water right there
let's talk about a couple little things
how important
how important is our life to us how
important is your life to you
how important is our life right is how
important it is
to other people that love us or people
or friends or people that care about us
how important is our life
yeah and don't you want to know
the best ways you can protect yourself
the best ways you can look after
yourself
don't you guys want the best information
to protect you
now i always talk about i hear this
whole term woke all the time
it's like you know or you woke or you
woke or you woke and
i see people out there
that say they're in the health industry
say they're in the health world they're
influencers or something or whatever
they're doing youtubers or whoever they
are or maybe there's kind of podcast
doctor
meanwhile they're lighting all their
scented candles they have their friends
over and they're letting their scented
candles
and they're so woke on health and
they're just burning all that chemical
ingesting all that chemical
they're drinking apple cider vinegar
which basically just
ends up destroying their teeth as years
go by
they're doing all their caffeine they're
doing all their caffeine
but they're so woke in health you know
so many people think they got it down
like they got it all down
foods to avoid in the morning okay don't
put it on your oatmeal
let's cover that real quick avoid
walnuts
okay avoid walnuts walnuts are great
it's a healthy fat have it later on
in the day if you want a couple of
walnuts right and if you're sick maybe
you want to do a medical
medium mono eating cleanse with no fats
maybe you want to do the 369 cleanse
right 369 cleanse if you're sick so you
can learn how to heal and get better and
recover
and keep your walnuts out almonds right
i've had those almonds forever right
there peanut butter
keep your peanut butter out in the
morning don't do any of that keep your
chocolate out keep your chocolate powder
keep your cacao nibs out that's cacao
nibs right there
keep those out keep those cacao nibs out
in the morning keep that out
that's caffeine keep caffeine out don't
have that
so no caffeine
you want no caffeine and no fats
cacao is caffeine and fat it's a double
whammy
right there if you have cacao in the
morning cacao powder chocolate powder
you're having caffeine and fat you're
having the double whammy in the morning
that you are definitely not gonna
cleanse it's not gonna happen
you seem fine to me chris says
contributing to the chemical warfare
without knowing it
i can't tell you how many times chris
out there
people that they think they're totally
on to it with health they think they
mastered everything
you know and they think they got it down
they've been into health for a few years
they're on their influence or
platform or there's some podcast person
whatever it is
and they just think they got it all down
their avocado toast and everything else
and their kombucha tea
right meanwhile they're burning yep
they're adding to chemical warfare
they're burning all those fragrances
they're doing all that stuff and they're
just polluting the planet with it
they're they're feeding the chemical
companies
i can't tell you how many influencers
use scented candles
who are into all natural all health
being
being awake being woke and everything
and they're just
literally giving money to the chemical
companies
okay and they're poisoning themselves
they're poisoning their friends
poisoning their kids poisoning their
pets poisoning family members and that's
what they're doing
that's just a prime example right there
anyway some of the
some of the foods the troublemaker foods
you don't want to bring in in the
morning you don't want to do eggs
you don't want to do that keep the eggs
out that's important right there
don't have the eggs in the morning don't
have the bacon in the morning
don't have the oiled hash browns in the
morning don't have the buttered toast in
the morning
keep that out that's critical if you
want a cleanse
keep the eggs out if you guys wanna
cleanse you know
if you wanna cleanse keep the eggs out
really important
you want the eggs out
if you wanna cleanse keep those babies
out right there
keep them out
if you want to cleanse
i just put some millet in here so i got
millet
now might run this right into ig
you want to keep these eggs out
of the diet completely if you want to
heal a condition or disease
or a symptom but you certainly want to
keep eggs out in the morning
don't have them in the morning whatever
you do
because you're not going to cleanse if
you have those in the morning it's not
going to happen
this is just the way it works
if you have a bagel and cream cheese or
a bagel
in butter in the morning you're not
going to cleanse
instead you're just going to get insulin
resistance it's another thing that
happens when everybody puts fat
in their diet in the morning they just
continue with their insulin resistance
worsen it and worsen and worsen over
time that's what they do
all these things are important
one of the reasons why the medical
meeting morning cleanse has to be done
is you'll save your bones you'll save
your teeth
because you'll cleanse acids out of your
bloodstream every single morning
as the night goes on your bloodstream is
filled with acid
it's filled with all kinds of acid it's
filled with
all kinds of toxins and poisons but real
acidy
toxins and poisons okay dr faun md good
to see you
so what happens is is that when you do
your when you wake up in the morning and
you don't cleanse
or give your body a chance to clean out
and cleanse
you end up losing a little bit of a part
of yourself
every day you lose your own bones they
all slowly dissolve
that's why when we get older we get the
osteopenia osteoporosis we lose our
teeth our skull fracture is easy our
hips break and fracture easy
when you get older everything just
starts breaking because
we had years of never cleansing no one
ever cleanses
so acids cause calcium to leach
if you don't cleanse the acid out every
single morning
the calcium will leech out of your bones
you see how it works you guys
see how critical this is
very important to know how it works okay
so every single day all night long
your skeleton
your skeletal system is begging to get
rid of those acids
every single day begging to get rid of
those acids
and so cleansing in the morning
doing your lemon water your celery juice
making sure there's no fats in your
oatmeal i'm making um
millet porridge right now
sun moon love that's me right now no
teeth and bones
are brittle hips and lower back
osteoporosis
osteopenia and osteoporosis sure wish i
would have known about mmm years ago
you know what i heard going back all the
way 30 plus years
opened up an office people coming to me
every day
traveling around the world people that
were sick for 20 years you know what
they all say
they would say i wish i knew about you
20 years ago well i'd be like well i was
only just
i was i was really little then i was a
real little guy
so and and but anyway
but that's what i heard every single day
people filing into the office
wish i knew about you wish i knew about
you
wish i knew about you yeah people that
get the books now wish i knew about him
10 years ago 20 years ago
okay and i believe in meditation
meditation is powerful there's medical
media meditations all in the books
but meditation and deep breathing
doesn't
fix chronic illness it doesn't
i wish it did but it doesn't fix chronic
illness because it won't get the poisons
out of your liver it won't get the
viruses out
it won't get the epstein bar out of your
system you can deep breathe all you want
you can deep breathe all you want and i
love deep breath
deep breathing you can deep breathe all
you want you can meditate all you want
that's that heals your soul
so what i love about meditation is you
heal your soul you heal your
metaphysical you
heal your subconsciousness you repair
you repair the emotional center of your
brain
that's why meditation is so critical
but if you got like multiple sclerosis
and you got trigeminal neuralgia and you
got chronic fibromyalgia and you got
severe neurological fatigue and you got
lupus and you got neurological lyme
and you got hashimoto's thyronitis you
can deep breath all you want
it's different i get it some people be
like oh i healed from all that deep
breathing and all that meditation and
all that rewiring i healed from it
you know from my so i'm going to teach
out there because i healed from it
because of my car accident what you got
from your car accident you had surgeons
work on you you had
you had orthopedic doctors work on you
you had massage
five times a week
because i've seen this out there i've
seen some people who are on the scene
and they're like lecturing and lecturing
and they're talking about how
their meditation healed them from a car
accident i'm like you know what i'm
sorry but
actually from what i recollect you had
massage
five times a week coming to your house
and you had orthopedic surgeons and you
had doctors and you were you were
you had nuts and bolts put into you and
you were put you were glued together
after your car accident you're trying to
tell me that your meditation did that
yeah the way
here's how it works with meditation
which i love it's really a powerful tool
meditation heals the soul
and her soul can be fractured your soul
you can get the betrayal and you can get
all that
but meditation is not going to remove
the acid out of your bloodstream you
have to cleanse that so i just
the reason why i go into this topic
because someone's going to say i don't
need to cleanse
i don't need a cleanse aw
i can just i can just do some deep
breathing and meditation and i can fix
my problems
i don't need a cleanse i don't need to
do the medical medium morning cleanse i
don't need to do a heavy metal detox
cleanse
you can't get the toxic heavy metals out
with meditation
you can't you can't get
mercury out of your brain so you get rid
of your condition you can't get copper
out of your liver to get rid of your
eczema psoriasis by doing meditation
it's just
the lay of the land medical medium
information has a street cred where
millions worldwide have healed
physically because you have to take some
steps
and the medical media morning cleanse is
one step
taking care of your skeletons another by
getting the acids out
so your teeth don't crumble and fall out
and your bones don't get brittle and
weak cooking some millet right now you
guys
knowing the true cause of why you're
sick is how you get better and knowing
what to do
and how to heal is how you get better
that's how you get better
okay information is critical in the book
you guys 16.99
on sale 51 off amazon.com us
check it out when you can okay your mind
will be blown
chris you seem fine to me real life
chris is it my imagination chris
or am i getting this read wrong
but didn't didn't you try all that
though like you you went down that route
where
you're physically sick and you're like
well it's got to be my
my thought process maybe my thought
process isn't right
maybe i got to do like all those
different other like you tried all that
right
and then and then you realized i mean
you tell me if i'm wrong chris
and then you realize you actually had to
find answers
anna says i am 99 cured from
mm information i was on mattress island
for eight months
oh god it's brutal to be on mattress
island
god bless you you're you're a strong
soul strong individual incredible
and that's why the meditations are in
the books they're in the book so we can
keep our soul strong and our spirit
strong
so we can then have fortitude and
willpower
to then do the information so we can
heal
but i hate when people package it up
like just rewire your mind and you'll
just you'll he'll heal i mean i hate i
hate that because
it's sad i've seen so many people with
neurological lyme thinking that it was
all in their head and they just needed
they just needed to just do you know a
meditation course
and and then they just you know and
meanwhile no one's no one's telling them
look you've got
epstein-barr said a megalith virus
simplex one you got shingles and you got
toxic heavy metals and these things need
to be cleaned up and you need to get
your
you need to get your nervous system
restored and we've got to get the right
b12 in you and got to get the vitamin c
in you
and we got to get like the vimergy b12
in you which is critical that type of
b12 right there
thevimorgy.com visavictoriamergy.com i'm
not sponsored but it's like
you need the right stuff it's like you
want to heal from neurological lyme
you've got to actually
learn what's what really is going on and
how to heal
and yeah you've got to do your
meditations to keep your soul strong
turn right go to medical mean podcast
apple podcast check out the meditations
okay because they recover and strengthen
the soul
okay meditations don't get toxic heavy
metals out of the body
i just medical meme information is about
being real
straight up it's truth it's why people
heal around the world
and if i was going to tell you that you
can meditate your mercury out of your
brain
not only would that be such a disservice
it'd be dastardly
miss herbs it would just be terrible
you got to do the heavy metal detox
movie get the metals out of your brain
and if you want to say a meditation
fixed you after you did the heavy metal
detox movie and it got the metals out
and you got better but you want to say
it was a meditation fine
but just you've got to make sure you get
the metals out
and you should credit what's getting it
out too it's just like
heavy metal detox smoothie because if
you don't credit what's getting you
better you end up hurting a bunch of
people i've seen people out there
and i've seen people out there and
people have told me this too where
they do medical medium they do the
celery juice 16 to 32 ounces every
single day
they do the heavy metal detox movie
right they learn how to heal and what
foods to stay away from
they heal and then they say it was a
meditation somebody somebody's
meditation that did it
so then that other person says it was so
then they go do that somebody else's
meditation
and then they don't know about the heavy
metal detox smoothie they don't know
about the celery juice and they just go
now they're sick for another year now
they're trying something else now
they're going someplace else now they're
going wherever
bonnie says 60 years with reynalds
shogrens and this dirty blood
you have taught me how to heal
i want it to be a poster granny for you
it's going to happen so proud of you
bonnie and i'm honored you're here
totally honored you're here incredible
really it's an honor to have you here
so i'm making millet right now you guys
just for the record
so guys we're gonna head off to ig
okay we'll be on there in just a couple
of minutes
it won't take long i'm probably going to
still have this millet cooking
because millet takes about 20 minutes to
cook 25 minutes to cook sometimes a half
an hour depending where you are
altitudes and everything else
on tick tock it says why no apple cider
vinegar can i just ask a favor
on tick-tock to the person who just said
why no apple cider vinegar please ask a
favor
can you check out my apple cider vinegar
episode at medical mean podcast at apple
podcast
and check it out and and just give it a
listen to
if you can
that would be awesome we're day two the
medical medium warning cleanse
we're going to go on ig we're going to
turn tick tock back on so you guys on
tick tock please stay around
meaning like just hang around and then
we're going to be live again
clubhouse we're going to be live again i
love you guys
okay you know you're in my heart i'm
going to be cooking the millet right
when i go on ig
we're going to make celery juice again
we're going to make something else
and you guys we're gonna rock
we're gonna rock love ya