okay the medical media morning cleanse
challenge
and hope you guys are hanging in there
keeping the fats out in the morning at
least right
so you can cleanse because you can't
cleanse you can't get rid of it you
can't get rid of the poisons you can't
get rid of toxins
you can't get rid of anything unless you
keep the fats out in the morning and
then when you bring in the powerful
healing tools
like the celery juice and the lemon
water then you're really getting the
stuff
out and then you're de-aging your
anti-aging for
real not some bogus anti-aging
theoretical supplement from some scammer
and some you know whatever
infomercial out there mlm companies
saying here's an anti-aging
supplement and everybody's eating their
bacon in the morning
and taking their anti-aging supplement
it's not like that this is the real deal
that's what this stuff is
good to see you guys are live on tick
tock live on youtube live on facebook
lava clubhouse
excited that we're here i'm making the
potato skillet
because you can do a fat free potato
skillet it's like hash browns
with no insulin resistance going
on you guys gonna talk about salicylates
have you heard about salicylate some
people say
i'm really sick you know and it's
because it salicylates
salicylates in food so i'm trying to
stay away from
all these different foods because the
salicylates it's like that's how people
get
tricked out there by trends that
actually don't make any sense whatsoever
and don't exist
the reason why someone's got chronic
sinusitis
and they got phlegm in their lungs and
they don't feel good and there's there
they got utis and stomach problems and
digestive problems and bloat and all
this other stuff
is not because of salicylates not
because of oxalates not because of
lectins and that's the trick it's like
come out with the next bs thing so we
can infomercial the crap out of people
and mlm the crap out of people
and make sure they buy our lectin
supplements make sure they buy our
salicylates
salicylate supplements make sure they
buy oxalate supplements
make sure they buy all this garbage and
stay sick
it's the greatest scam and that's the
true snake oil
in the industry out there collagen
that's another snake oil in this
industry so there's tons of that real
snake oil out there like real snake oil
salicylate supplements lectin
supplements collagen supplements right
and so that's what you guys have
probably already been around or you know
been around the merry-go-round with
right you guys good to see you guys
zabo good to see you too man hey what's
up good ashleygiving
good good to see you so upon waking 16
to 32 ounces of lemon water we're doing
the medical meeting morning cleanse day
three
we're on the challenge right here so we
got the lemon water let's get going on
that we're going to be doing the
skillet let me get the pan hot too
because
i know that some of you guys are like
what am i going to eat the heavy metal
detox smoothie
for sure you know and that's what people
should be doing yeah they should be
doing a live rescue smoothie
they should be doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie but you know they're used
to eating eggs every morning you know
so it's like everybody's used to
cracking open those eggs it's like okay
you want them scrambled you want them
fried you want the poached eggs
wants a french toast right you want
uh you want an omelette right so
everybody wakes up in the morning it's
like you know what old habit let's get
the omelets going
let's crack you know what maybe i should
maybe i should crack an egg open and get
it in the pan but that's a comfort food
and it's comfort food that keeps us sick
we don't realize that when we stay sick
we stay sick with it so we're going to
do instead the potato skillet without
the insulin resistance
because everybody gets the insulin
resistance chris good to see you came on
great great courtney good to see you
glad you guys are coming on tick tock
how are you guys doing you guys coming
on in tik tok too
great great good to see you guys we'll
have some fun today how about that all
right we'll make some food we'll have
some fun
seaweed hero good to see you let's just
get some lemon water going i'm excited
about this
let's get some lemon water going right
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water first
thing in the morning are you guys doing
your lemon water how many of you guys
did your lemon
water i'm just curious did you guys try
it
anybody new here that tried the lemon
water too and it's the first time you're
doing that heavy duty lemon water 16 to
32 ounces terry appleman good to see you
um beautiful person some amazing people
amazing people here today incredible
incredible incredible
alex lange good to see alex amazing guy
so here we are we're um
we're here so let me let me get the
lemon water
talk going for a moment why are you
drinking lemon water let's cover that
it's one thing to do the lemon water
it's another to understand what's
happening and what it's doing for you
so lemon water is flushing out the
toxins and the poisons
that's what it's doing your liver is
working all night long
you can do the lemon water room
temperature i like it room temperature
personally you can do it cold you can do
it cold
don't do it hot
don't do the lemon water
hot i gotta say it in that way because i
needed to get in the consciousness
i needed to get in there just gotta like
register
it's gotta register and sink in it's
gotta sink in
don't do the lemon water
hot so important or
it won't work it's not gonna work tick
tock the handle not the app
good to see you don't elena good to see
you don't do the lemon water
i have to say it like 10 times the
reason why is because i swear
i see people doing it all the time
deanna thanks for coming on
i see people doing all the time lorena
good to see you you guys are all coming
on
we're live on tick tock live on facebook
live on youtube you guys we're gonna
have some fun today i'm making the
potato skillet if you just came
on we're talking about salicylates
oxalates
lectins talk about collagen a little bit
too
the scams in the system out there the
scams
yeah make make the investors you guys
know how it works by the way you guys
know how it works
you got to have all this money right you
gotta have all this money
and then you get a bunch of investors
that have all this money you buy into
something like some kind of collagen
product
okay and then you put it out there
and hopes that you know you market it
and advertise it in hopes that everybody
buys into it same thing with like the
lectins you said all everybody buys into
it and then you run
ads 24 7 on your lectin supplement
on your collagen supplement 24 so you
run these ads everywhere and everybody
and then it just becomes everything it's
in every podcast everybody's using it's
on every tv commercial right
it's in every show it's everywhere it's
like college and college and collagen
that's how it works yeah why not do the
lemon water hot
okay you can do lemon water hot
but it's not gonna flush it has to be
alive
it has to be alive when it comes down to
lemon water doing what it needs to do
the cleansing action that it needs to do
it has to be alive
it can't be dead it can't
die that's what happens this lemon right
now that came off of a tree
is still alive it has living water
inside of it
the minerals the trace minerals are
alive
it's activated right
when it enters you it's activated
it creates that flushing power
now you can have herbal tea and squeeze
lemon in honorable tea
lemon the lemon will still do something
else for you but i'm talking about
flushing the liver you can put your you
can squeeze lemon in your dishes
and still get healing powers from the
lemon you guys
you can still you can still have lemon
in
tea in herbal tea right
squeeze it in there with some honey and
lemon it's still going to have
power healing powers
still going to have vitamin c it's still
going to have the calcium
it's just that when it comes down to
liver flushing you want it alive
so it flushes out the body that's how
it's done
all right a little dramatic today
a little dramatic today
[Music]
anyway good to see you guys so glad
you're coming on
awesome just got some lemon water there
you can do a whole lemon you can do a
half a lemon just giving you some tips
right now you guys
whole lemon you can you can have half a
lemon and
that's okay and worst case scenario if
you do a quarter lemon you can have a
quarter lemon
the morning cleanse has no fats in it
do you know how we get the diabetes we
get the type 2 diabetes because our
liver
gets blown out it gets weaker and weaker
and weaker and weaker
our liver gets blown out
it gets weaker and weaker and weaker
that's our liver right there
okay there it is that's our gallbladder
that's a liver
and we weaken our liver it gets
intoxicated it gets sludgy it gets
burdened by fats all that eggs that you
had all those years for breakfast
burdens it and burns it and then all the
fats you do every day because
everybody's on milk cheese eggs butter
bacon ham bologna
talked to a friend the other day and my
friend was like you know i've eaten so
much baloney over my lifetime
like i get it i mean people eat a lot of
baloney
they do right you know and so
but what it does to the liver is just
terrible it weakens it beats it down
slows it down makes it sluggish over
time
stagnant sluggish once it starts
happening the pancreas starts weakening
too
another thing too when you dump fats in
you all day long because that's what
everybody's doing they're dumping fats
in them all day long the pancreas
weakens
the pancreas weakens it does i just saw
on tic toc bologna
right and when the pancreas weakens it's
another reason why we're getting the
boobs getting set up for type 2.
so type 2 works in this way your liver
starts getting beaten down
your liver can't produce the bile it
needs so your bile can't break down the
fats as much
more fats are in your bloodstream
because your your liver is weakening
because of the fats and more fats are in
your bloodstream now and guess what
guess what happens you guys your
pancreas has to release more insulin
because there's more fat in your
bloodstream
so your pancreas has to release more
insulin more insulin
eventually your credit card gets used
up your pancreas and i've been saying
this for years if you heard some of my
early radio shows and even before that
early lectures
the pancreas is your credit card that's
your credit card you can use that baby
up man
you can use it up and then boom a1c is
higher boom a1c is higher next thing you
know hey you're type 2 diabetes hey
you're pre-diabetes hey you got a
diabetes disposition hey you're a
diabetic
michelle l good to see you on tick-tock
and
that's what happens right there so boom
you're heading
to diabetes now medical media morning
cleanse is a chance for you guys to be
insulin resistance
you're eligible to be insulin resistance
for your mornings
what a great thing to do because you
guys are gonna eat fat anyway many of
you and i know that you're gonna eat a
lot of it i can't stop you i can't stop
you from eating it
right i can't stop you from having the
fats you're gonna have fats i know that
you're gonna have your salmon anyway you
know you're gonna have your
chicken anyway you're gonna have your
eggs anyway many of you guys are gonna
have them i get it
i'm not shaming you that's not what this
all
is this isn't all about shaming that's
not it at all it's not judging either
you guys think i don't know how hard
life is you guys don't think i don't
know how
you know many of you you only can get
eggs i know somebody that's like look
right now i'm
i'm broke and a friend get drops off
eggs every day i'm like then eat them
eat them you know eat them until we can
find another option until we get more
foods to you
like i get it life's not easy but if you
have the ability to switch things up
and switch things up let's work on doing
it i know it's hard either way we get
into habits we get into patterns we get
into comfort foods we get into emotional
emotional patterns is where we get into
two
but it gives you a chance to kind of you
know lower the grass-fed beef or
lower the beef whatever kind of beef
you're eating you know lower the eggs or
hopefully get rid of the eggs lower the
chicken right that's one thing there too
and it helps and the same thing with
butter right
you're not gonna see me put butter in
this pan i'm gonna cook right now
you're not going to see me put butter in
the pan just letting you know
you're not i'm not going to put butter
in the pan
i don't want a heart attack i don't want
a future heart attack
okay anybody in the health scene that's
promoting butter is just
somebody who's oblivious to the
heart-stopping power of butter
you know i heard one time someone says
nah
butter has healing power i'm like that's
a head scratcher to me because butter
has got heart stopping power
that's heart stopping power
that butter builds up in your heart
builds up in your arteries you guys
that's what it does it builds up in your
arteries it folds up in your heart
the butter builds up in here look
right in there inside your heart the
butter builds up
in the valves over time that's what the
butter does
it's got to keep you butter free
courtney mma butterfree right
radical fats we get in trouble maybe
you're not doing butter maybe you're hip
are you a hipster are you hip
are you doing the coconut oil you found
like the new way
coconut oil still is gonna it's still
gonna build up
in the arteries and veins over time
if too much fat's in your diet it's
still going to build up in your heart
and arteries and veins over time
keep that in mind even the healthy fats
you use them sparingly
you use them carefully you respect them
people have no respect for fats laura
says why doesn't it melt
in our bodies and flush out
well laura really good question
so fat has to be dispersed it has to
break down inside her body so it has to
be dispersed
and it gets dispersed right here so this
is how it goes
okay put the i'm going gonna put the
liver back
inside this this guy right here for some
reason this guy's stomach is acting
weird over here
so
when you eat the fats your liver has to
produce something
that's really really astringent
right and that's your bile that bile
has to break down the butter that's its
role that's its
job it has to break it down okay
so when you're having that butter on
your grilled cheese sandwiches you just
cooked your grilled cheese
right and you got you you put butter in
the pan right
you did all that that butter has to
break down that cheese has to break down
too so how is it going to break down
the heat of your body isn't enough
so the heat of your body is not enough
to break those fats down
you need more than that you need a
dissolver
so your bile is a fat dissolver
right you got another fat dissolver
it's your adrenaline
adrenaline is a is a fat thinner it's a
blood thinner so
these are your adrenals right here the
more fat you put in your body
the more adrenaline you're going to have
to use then your hormones start
to go out of whack as the years go on
because you've been burning out your
adrenals by using it for fats
so you're using your adrenals for fats
all these years
and then they start to break down and
guess what your adrenals re
your adrenals produce reproductive
hormones
they also produce feel good hormones
adrenals are a hormone producer
your liver is a hormone producer
so our hormone systems break down
because we fat them to death
we fatter adrenals to death because they
have to actually create something so
corrosive that it dissolves fat in the
bloodstream and then
and then we have to push the liver
beyond its limits to to create enough
bile to break down and dissolve fat
too so we're doing all this and we're
wearing ourselves down we're wearing
ourselves down
there's just a couple of things right
here i mean we can go into this
all day on how fat works but i gotta
make some food for you guys too
lemons don't ruin teeth
they don't ruin teeth
if they did i don't think i'd have a
tooth left i don't think i would have
one left
because you got to understand something
i've eaten
lemons for years and decades suck on
them
i actually do the lemon water every
single day
like lemon is in my life every day all
day long one way or another
and i don't have the whole veneers thing
i don't have implants i don't my teeth
aren't all drilled i don't have all
these problems i don't have
abscesses i don't have gum disease i
don't have cavities i don't have
i don't have um bridges i don't have
dentures i don't need to get the veneers
i don't need to get off
so all implants don't like i said no
root canals right
and one reason right is making sure
mineralized leafy greens you're doing
all that stuff another reason is lemons
keep your teeth
they keep your teeth i don't do vinegar
i don't do
vinegars i don't do and i'm not 25 30
years old i know 25 30 year old people
that just you know
25 30 year old uh you know and they're
and they're just their teeth are just
all falling apart
falling out right i'm not spraying
chicken
and the reason why i've kept my teeth in
check
is no vinegar keeping the vinegar
vinegar's the teeth destroyer
caffeine is the teeth destroyer right
caffeine industry they're if if they
actually did not exist you wouldn't
believe the dental industry would be
like
they would be lost they would be lost
you know the dental industry is like it
is because of all the caffeine
you know and the vinegar too i mean the
vinegar is the ultimate teeth destroyer
caffeine's the ultimate teeth breaker
downer and destroyer
as time goes on that's what it does you
lose your calcium in your teeth and you
bring your calcium back with the lemon
water
so we're in the medical medium morning
cleanse challenge if you guys just came
on here
the book is still on sale amazon.com us
it's 16.99
take advantage of the sale it's a
medical textbook
take advantage of it if you can there's
cleanses in here there's the mono eating
cleanses the 369
original and advanced there's the heavy
metal detox cleanse
there's nearly 200 symptoms and
conditions dosages of supplements right
all of it insomnia talks about what
supplements to take
hpv talks about what supplements to take
i know so many people worried about that
hormone problems hot flashes night
sweats running hot
body temperatures heart palpitations
headaches migraines
simplex how many of you guys got simplex
one the cold sore and the fever blister
mary fox then why did lemon water have a
wearing effect on my teeth when i drank
it for several months
i did use to drink cacao drinks and eat
things with vinegar
is sauerkraut good for you okay so
here's how it works
teeth are a time capsule okay
if you do vinegar there's going to be
this moment where
everything finally gets pushed over the
edge and your teeth just fall apart
that's just how it works you can do this
someone can be 25 years old do vinegar
their teeth aren't going to fall apart
in two months not it
they're going to be 32 years old and
it's just going to start falling apart
and if they could have rolled up they
could have rode in a hot air balloon
the day the dentist said your teeth are
falling apart
and it would have been the hot air
balloon they floated in with friends
that caused the problem you see how it
works
they could have taken a boat ride on a
lake
and then it was around the time their
teeth just crumbled and you can just say
what was the boat ride i haven't been in
a lake i haven't
been i haven't been in a boat ride for a
long time
it's easy to blend you can start coconut
oil for the first time in your life
where i'm doing oil pulling now and your
teeth just
fall apart in one month it's not because
coconut oil coconut pulling
you know oil pulling did it
even though it causes gum disease oil
pulling does cause cause
long term it does cause gum disease the
point is is
it's like but you're gonna think it was
the oil pulling that did it in that
month you just started the oil pulling
meanwhile it's all the vinegar you did
in caffeine you did in cacao and
chocolate
by the way the oil pulling it coats
bacteria
so bacteria can thrive so when you do
your
coconut oil pulling there
right you're just gonna you're you're
gonna set yourself up for gum disease
down the road
you're gonna coat your gums and coat
your teeth you're gonna keep the
bacteria sealed in there
underneath the oil is what you're gonna
do
to buffer acidity your body leeches the
calcium over time out of the teeth until
the teeth become
weak to a point where they just start
falling apart or the cavities start
happening fast
and you could have been you know at a
fair
somewhere you could have been like
in a hot air balloon that day and you'll
think it's a hot air balloon you'll
think it's whatever
you could have eaten fish for the first
time in years
and think maybe it's because i've been
eating fish for two weeks and my teeth
just started falling apart
but no it's other things it's this
demineralized situation it's the acids
in our body
situation and then it's the calcium
leaching from all the
vinegar and all that stuff
citrus is bio-available calcium you're
doing you're sick we're in the morning
cleanse challenge you're doing your 16
to 32 ounces of lemon water every single
morning
upon waking preferably
because you're getting the bioavailable
calcium inside of you monica says but i
thought you said to wash your teeth with
coconut oil
did i imagine that yes
monica you imagined it
yep yep yep i don't think i ever said
that
i definitely don't think they ever said
that and and if i did i must have been
like i must have been
losing it for the moment or something i
don't know when i don't think i said
that
i don't think so philip k laugh out loud
philip k
fibromyalgia gallbladder infections even
if you don't know that's what you have
eye floaters energy issues fatigue
there's supplements and dosages of how
to heal it's in this book right here
cleanse the heal you guys if you don't
have one grab one
okay grab one if you don't have one
all right corneal disease type 1
diabetes type 2 diabetes
conjunct congenital eye defects
conjunctivitis
mystery hunger how many guys got mystery
hunger where you can't calm that mystery
hunger down
right cold and flu
for children supplements and dosages you
guys
cirrhosis of the liver cataracts canker
sores
children's liver problems brittle ridged
nails
with supplements and dosages in here
brittle ridge
nails in here right there's all that in
here too
i mean it's it's and then the medical
medium shock therapies as well
breast density okay
breast density bloating that's another
one brain fog
so you can have answers in what to do
and it's in here and
brain fog's one right there anxiety and
anxiousness so you see
supplements and dosages this is the
medical medium cleanse the heel book
it's a medical textbook it's on sale
16.99 amazon.com us the reason why i'm
trying to let you guys know about the
book
because the medical media morning
cleanse is in here and once the
challenge is over i need you guys to
know what to do
i need you guys to know how to heal and
a lot of you guys got all kinds of
different health issues big time
big time audio mean autoimmune disorders
and diseases you can learn about
how to heal that alzheimer's disease
dementia
memory issues adrenal problems
addiction acne abscesses
everyday liver health and maintenance
right parkinson's disease
chemical and food sensitivities okay
i mean this thing is packed gout
heart palpitations herpes simplex the
fever blister remember i mentioned that
so many people want to get rid of the
fever blister problem
people don't realize it herpes simplex
one
the fever blister eventually it causes
all the trigeminal neuralgia too like
shingles does it gets in here it causes
cranial nerves to be inflamed people
have all kinds of problems they're at
the dentist office all the time
high blood pressure infertility
ibs irritable bowel kidney disease loss
of libido if somebody's worried about
that lyme disease big time
lyme disease in this book right
information big time
menopause symptoms methylation problems
so you know about that mood swings mood
struggles
multiple sclerosis nail fungus cfs
mecfs optic neuropathy
bladder problems ocd pandas parkinson's
like i said
pid pds ptsd
pcos scar tissue shingles
sensitivity the hot and cold renauld
syndrome thyroid conditions tinnitus
utis tumor cysts weight gain vertigo
meniere's
varicose veins spider veins
you know basically you guys there's a
lot of answers in the book
and if your answer it doesn't seem like
it's in here go to autoimmune
is all you need to do is go to
autoimmune
and you can you can then find you know
you can find out what you need to do
so it's any on sales 16.99 amazon.com us
you guys should check it out it's an
invaluable resource
51 off and you can't go wrong with that
right there
so anyway we do the lemon water let's
keep on moving let me get the skillet
going
you guys are okay with this the the
potato skillet and we've got more to
talk about
more to talk about let's do it i got
some red bell peppers right here
by the way i don't control pricing on
amazon it's on sale amazon does that
nothing i can do and you can get it free
at the library if you if you
you've got some patience because i'm
hearing that the people are waiting a
long time right there for that
so i'm cutting up some red bell pepper
it's going in the pan
okay taking out the center right there
what's the name of the book it's called
cleanse the heel tell a friend
the information in here is priceless
seriously it's priceless
packaged it up so the publisher can put
it out there the manuscript out there
that's saving lives
16.99 it costs more to print the book
i don't want to i don't want to turn it
into programs and charge three thousand
dollars for a program i don't want it
not accessible i don't wanna you know
put people under that
i want people to have it for free
basically
so they can heal i mean there's people
that have gotten their lives back
recovered from debilitating disease for
16.99
it's like okay i just want people to get
a chance you know
it's called cleanse the heal go to
amazon.com us or
barnes noble or something if you're if
you can't get it there or
somewhere you know let's get some
peppers on the pan
once we get this cooking a little bit
we're going to juice a little celery
juice really quick
all right so let's get the pepper in
here
doing a potato skillet is what we're
doing it's not a potato bowl it's more
of a skillet it's going to go
in a dish let's get an onion
happening here let's hope we don't get
the
the onion tears
look if you get enough mineral salts and
glucose
you won't be hungry you got to get the
mineral salts and the glucose the celery
juice is the mineral salts the lemon
water
is the mineral salts and they're both
glucose in the morning to start with
then you can follow that up with the
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie
you guys should look into that check out
um
and make sure it's the right spirulina
make sure it's the right
barley grass juice powder if you can it
all counts all the details matter
celery juice is not high in glucose but
it has glucose in it
it stops your adrenals from flooding
it's enough glucose to keep it so you
don't
lose your adrenals and people who
intermittent fast lose their adrenals
it's very important to know that keep in
mind what do i mean by lose your
adrenals
abusing them you abuse them
and someday your adrenals won't be kind
to you because they'll be maxed out
they'll be maxed out that's how it works
so making
potato skillet these onions here
we do adrenal burnout and then all this
stuff happens we age really quick our
skin
wrinkles really fast we just start
falling apart we get the fatigue too
okay i don't use oil in cooking
i use water in cooking
if you use oil everywhere you go and
what you do if you use your olive oil
and that's what you're using if you're
doing
oil everything with what you're cooking
all you're going to do is going to get
an insulin resistance
and you're going to always have these
moments of being too hungry
and then you're going to want
carbohydrates and the bad carbohydrates
and
it's going to be uncontrollable
you got to learn how to do it without
all that
all right let's get some celery juice
going you guys we're in the
round three third day medical medium
morning plunge challenge it's to keep
fats away from you
in the morning till noon keep you fat
free very very important
that's how we can get you better
if you could only do the medical meeting
morning cleanse once in a while then
look god bless you you did it you did a
little bit of it it counts
every little bit counts you guys every
little bit counts let's get some celery
going
is everything cool with that get some
celery go
corey leon says do we even need
fat at all no we don't because it's in
every food
there's fat in every single food there's
fat and onion there's fat
the red bell pepper there's fat in every
single fruit and vegetable
[Music]
there's traces of omegas in every single
fruit and vegetable
lettuce potatoes got fat in them bananas
got fat in them
all right i got to stop this for a
second i got to stop this for a second
all right hey niza good to see you i'm
so glad you're on there
omegas are not the same as cooking oils
they are very different
spot on you know the reason why i got to
stop the juicer for a second okay
because here here's what's interesting
all right
you know what you can't live free from
live without you can't live without
glucose you know why you die
really quick you die really fast
that's why and
if you don't get glucose to the brain in
under 10 seconds your brain tissue
starts to die
in under five seconds it starts to die
when diabetics get low blood sugar they
hit the floor
i can't say how many stories i heard
from doctors and other people
all through the years including myself
by saving somebody's life with a little
orange juice i happen to have on hand
okay a type 1 diabetic on the floor
about to go into a diabetic coma
i had to actually take my orange juice
and get it into the mouth of the diet of
the diabetic
while they were still coherent and still
able to swallow
glucose we can't live without
fat you can take all the fat away you
can still live to be whatever age you're
gonna be
you take the fat out it's okay
look if it's too much keep the fats in
just do do other steps medical medium
steps
you don't have to be fat free to do some
healing and learn how to heal and learn
supplements and protocols like and
cleanse the heal
you don't have to be fat free
but it's good at times to do cleanses
keep the fats down learn what fats you
should eat or not you know if you're
gonna
but just it's it's important all these
things are important
bless your heart too uh lorena you guys
are live on tiktok facebook youtube
clubhouse
thanks for being here everybody
so let's keep on juicing a little bit
your brain has to get glucose before it
starts to die isn't it interesting
then interesting
the more fat your brain gets in your
bloodstream
the more oxygen your brain loses
the more fat in your bloodstream every
day the less oxygen
inside your brain
that's how it works notice they measure
blood sugar have you noticed that
why are they measuring blood sugar
how come they're not measuring blood fat
get
nurse get the patient in here we gotta
check our blood fat
[Music]
you don't hear that right
nurse what's the status on the patient
the patient's blood fat
need the status
you don't hear that
how come how come if it was so
important how come michelle good to see
you
i just want to know i'm scratching my
head on that one are you guys scratching
your head on that one
no right you know what's funny about
medical meme information
it's always sensible it makes sense
it makes sense know what's funny about
the other information out there in
health realm
doesn't make any sense but everybody
buys into it
[Music]
because people are suckers
they should check the blood fat levels
and see how dangerous they are
and see why someone's probably gonna
have a heart attack
but they don't and all that fat builds
up
in your bloodstream patrice spent it
good to see it
it showed a good sea cheeple
pumped sheeple
pumped people
that's your great does you agree with
that one
don't you agree with that one
nurse nurse
nurse check the patients
check the patient's blood fat
oh we can't how come oh it's
medical research and science doesn't
know about the blood fat
so what do we do check the blood sugar
okay let's check the blood sugar
[Music]
[Applause]
here's how it works you guys
i forgot to bring my sheep up here
pumped i forgot to bring my sheep up
here
i forgot to bring my phone up here
[Music]
[Applause]
nice coming along good let's get this
juice done and we can get this going
[Music]
seaweed here stop making sense
mm critics
they're supposed to be checking for
blood fat you guys
[Music]
but they don't they check for blood
sugar because yes blood sugar is
critical
they're also supposed to be checking
blood fat that's really what they're
supposed to be checking because when you
check the blood fat then you can find
out the insulin resistance for real
then you can find out that there's a
pandemic of insulin resistance
it's the high fats not letting the sugar
into your cells how many times
times have i mentioned that so high fats
not letting sugar
into the cells that's how it works
that's what creates high blood sugar
talked about that all the time you guys
[Music]
so i got um it looks like a little stir
fry going but i'm doing
potatoes the potato skillet i'm just
bringing these peppers down i'll let
this pepper down a little bit the onion
down a little bit
so what i'm doing just bringing it down
there's no oil in the pan
don't need it i'm eating oil in the pan
why do i want an oil slick
just because i've been taught my whole
life to do an oil slick
because we're taught to do oil and
everything
by the way i still can't help it but dry
pulp
the mm-900 hds dry pulp
really incredible road
let's get the celery just going celery
juice
don't add anything please please
don't add anything don't add water don't
add ice
don't add lemon you gotta love
influencers out there it's usually
really funny you gotta love influencers
you gotta love the youtube influencers
that mess everything up you just gotta
love them
you can't judge them you just have to
love them it's like okay
it's celery juice is supposed to be by
itself
it's the only way medical medium
information is taught it
but leave it up to an influence or to
squeeze lemon in it
and then take the celery juice to her
yoga class
and then tell everybody else at the yoga
class you got to put lemon in it
so that nobody at the yoga class gets
one benefit from their celery juice
because lemon was squeezed in it you
gotta you gotta just you gotta love the
influencers you guys gotta love them
they screw everything up
it's not their fault
it's an herbal extraction which you guys
just witnessed is an herbal extraction
okay it's it's what it is
it's what it is it's an herbal
extraction
how about beans beans are fat free soy
beans though boy they're high in fat
the soybeans beans beans have a higher
level of fat in them but still it's not
an overt
fat you can do you can do a hummus
out of chickpeas if you want you can do
a hummus
out of garbanzo beans don't add the
tahini
all right now i'm going to throw some
potatoes in here in a little bit i'm
just bringing these onions down a little
bit and these
these peppers
15 to 30 minutes after you have your
lemon water you can have your celery
juice 15 to 30 minutes later give it a
little time that's all just give it a
little time
if you're in a rush you can dump it in
just but you know try to have a little
time between
you can consume some fruits okay i'm
gonna put i'm gonna get this rest of
this cooking real quick you guys
i'm gonna squeeze lemon in here i like
to do that i do like to squeeze a lemon
in this
i just saw a lemon seed go in there
okay and i'm gonna get some potatoes
going in here i have some steamed
potatoes over here you guys so
let me get these out
got some steamed potatoes
i'm going to cut them in these nice
little wedges here
potato skillet look you can have
something really
really really really um
you can have something really really
hardy here too
so keep that in mind you can have
something really hearty okay
keep that in mind this is a very hearty
dish right here
you can have a hearty dish right here
you can definitely have a hearty dish
and that's what this is
this is a nice hearty dish for best
results though
stick to fruit in the morning okay for
best results
stick the fruits in the morning that's
what i would do
for best results just so you know
let's get these in the pan get them
cooking
put a little bit more lemon in here and
then we're going to make a fruit bowl
and we're going to talk about some other
nitty-gritty
some health truth so you can heal so you
can get what you need
heavy metal detox movie is ideal you
guys everybody's loaded with metals
everybody's loaded with metals keep that
in mind like everybody's loaded with
metals okay
everybody's loaded with metals that's
something to keep in mind right there
so many people are loaded with metals
it's ridiculous
so that's definitely something to keep
in mind heavy metal detox smoothie in
the morning
liver rescue smoothie is a great one too
that's a great one as well
let's get this cooking i'm gonna add a
little touch of water in the pan
this pan is hot a little moisture
a little moisture so let that kind of
steam up
i'm going to add some spices in a little
bit too thank you guys for having
patience while i'm doing some cooking
here
really appreciate it
all right so what's the goal
what's the end game with the medical
medium warning cleanse
hold out till noon before you're tanking
the cacao the almonds right
the walnuts okay for your tank and the
walnuts before you're taking the coconut
oil
before you're tanking the cheese before
you're taking whatever you're thinking
you know you got your cacao right there
the end game
is to not do the fats in the morning
right
that's what it is that's the end game
right there keep that in mind you guys
give me a quick second and
when you do these things live you always
have some kind of like
little tech problem that comes up
that's just life in the fast lane
if you're somebody that's going to eat
eggs and i can't stop you from eating
eggs there's nothing i can do
and you're going to eat eggs and that's
just going to happen
have your eggs after noon have them
then have them for dinner i don't
recommend it
i don't recommend it at all but have
your eggs then
okay you can have your eggs then
all right let's make a fruit bowl
you want to give your body a chance to
cleanse and i'm going to reiterate this
if you guys are okay with this
i know i burn your ears out some of you
but i'm just gonna let you know
you can't cleanse the body ever unless
you're fat free
at least in the morning you won't be
able to cleanse even partial
toxins out it's not gonna happen it's
not gonna happen
going to keep your toxins you're going
to own them you know that whole phrase
you guys we're about to talk about
fructose intolerance um
salicylic salicylic acid uh
you know intolerance histamine hives
we'll talk about that
salicylates talk about salicylates
because you can easily be tricked you
don't know why you're sick you're
walking around you don't know why you're
sick you're going to doctor to doctor
you don't know why you're sick
nobody knows why you're sick and
someone's often says salicylates
salicylates
what's that salicylate or maybe you're
maybe
you're the lucky one that stumbled
across somebody saying
oxalates oxalates is that my problem
whoa
i didn't know it it's oxalates all this
time or you know
that those paid for campaigns like
collecting campaigns
so you can sell electing supplements
like wait a minute i'm sick because of
lectins
first of all countless people are
healing on medical medium information
and they don't even think about the word
lectin
because lectins have nothing to do with
healing or not but once you get down
that road you're stuck you're stuck in
that road man
that road of misinformation the reason
why we get the bloating the hives the
histamines raise up and the fructose
intolerance
and um we get these we get these issues
because the liver gets stagnant and
sluggish it gets
funky it gets gross it gets
yucky inside that liver the liver gets
yucky and bad inside of there that's
what happens yucky and bad
no one's getting fructose intolerant you
can't be fructose intolerant that's just
a fancy name for insulin resistance
right you guys that's just a fancy name
for insulin resistance
you can't become fructose intolerant
it's not possible on any level
you can't be fructose intolerant
but not cane sugar intolerant see
you can't be you can't be
carbohydrate intolerant
with it just being a fructose you can't
just be
fructose intolerant it means you're
all carbohydrate sugars and all
intolerant
but no one's intolerant of the basic
needs your brain needs or you die
okay so the the foundation of your
existence is blood
sugar you die without it you die without
blood without your blood having sugar in
it so you mean to tell me people are
fructose intolerant
first of all that's telling them they're
sugar intolerant
if you're sugar intolerant it's
impossible
your body is born and bred for thousands
of years
millions of years humans humans existed
you existed in this
if you want to believe they existed in
this universe
for millions of years okay
say you just believe humans existed for
ten thousand years
on earth say you're somebody that just
believes it's ten thousand years humans
only existed on earth
say you're somebody that believes humans
existed for a million years
for 10 million years whatever you
believe
the human body needs glucose
in order to run to function to thrive
no one's fructose intolerant
that's a scam that test isn't even real
it means you're all sugar intolerant no
one's sugar intolerant because you need
glucose
but what they're not saying is you got
insulin resistance
it's a it's like a back-handed backwoods
way
of saying you're insulin resistant
salicylate intolerance
is really also something that's kind of
made up
no one's salicylate intolerant no one's
no one's glucose intolerant no one's
salicylate
intolerant there's foods where
salicylates are in
foods those foods are healing foods it's
how you get better
so your symptoms go away it's like
taking
like real symptoms right real symptoms
and conditions right
you look and cleanse the heel and you go
back here and you look at these simple
just look at the back of cleanse the
heel right you guys don't have the book
edit it's on sale 51
off um right
acne adrenal problems right all that
glaucoma
fibromyalgia fatigue autoimmune ibs
inflammation lyme disease right all the
stuff that's in here
okay if you blame that on
salicylates are you kidding me you're
blaming that in salicylates like who's
going to do that
i don't know anything i don't know
anything crazier
i just don't
what else are we gonna come up
with so your utis are because of
salicylates
your styes are because of salicylates
your hives are because of salicylates
are you kidding
your fatigue's because of salicylates
your bloating's because of salicylates
are you kidding me like i'm scratching
my head on that one
your histamine levels go up your
histamine levels go up because your
liver's
all messed up it's all swollen in there
and you know pus is in there people
don't realize they got yellow pus
inside their body they don't get it they
don't get it
i talked to surgeons you're like
surgeons will tell me
i noticed one surgeon who says you
wouldn't believe the yellow puss that's
inside everybody like i know
i know spirit of compassion always told
me that well he said well spirit
compassion is right
because you wouldn't believe when we cut
open people there's yellow pus inside
people
their liver gets stagnant and sluggish
it gets stagnant
and sluggish is what it gets so i'm
gonna put some cumin in here
okay a little cumin in here
you seem fine to me chris healed my
histamine issues with medical medium
information incredible
i mean can you imagine going down the
path of oxalates or salicylates or
something
like i can you imagine going down that
path oxalates and salicylates
or lectins i mean what a scam
cayenne pepper paprika cumin
i got in there you guys let's put a
clove of garlic in there let's chop up a
clove of garlic in there
what there's pussiness why jessica
caldwell
there's pus in us fill the pus
because we never cleanse and it builds
up year after
year and we're dehydrated we're living
off of fats and we're dehydrated
we have we have several levels of toxins
inside of us
we got dairy products going inside of us
all the time
we got all kinds of garbage inside of us
our liver becomes
a pus filled ball
gets in our lymphatic system
there's some garlic in here
we're doing a potato skillet it's now
actually browning up
it's really nice i just lost the potato
damage control
we got shrek inside of us okay
what happens when somebody has a really
bad case of acne
is there any pus involved
well that pus is inside people's livers
and lymphatic systems
and if you think you're doing all this
great stuff for your lymphatic system
you got to do it for your liver and then
the lymphatic system gets that goody
gets the goody attention the tlc it
needs but you got to give it to your
liver
that's where it's all at you don't clean
up your liver your lymphatic system is
going to stay pus filled
everybody's got pus in a lymphatic
system you can go there and play around
with put
with your pus filled lymphatic system
all you want but if you're not cleaning
up your liver
and keeping the fats down and at least
doing like medical medium morning
cleanse
you're not cleaning up your lymphatic
system i don't care what
lymphatic massage you had at some spa
somewhere
i don't care the lymph system is your
second filter your liver is the first
filter
let's just clean the second filter
let's just clean the second filter don't
clean the first filter
let's clean the second filter let's keep
on cleaning the second filter
let's keep on doing it i got a phone
call coming because i got a lymphatic
massage scheduled
i had an emphatic massage schedule
hello huh
why is the phone still ringing i don't
know hey
yeah i had you have a lymphatic massage
scheduled
uh-huh yep after that i'm
after that i'm going to see this new
special practitioner and they're going
to focus on my lymphatic system yep
i'm going to buy a thousand dollars of
lymphatic drainage supplements
does the practitioner know why i'm sick
no
they're just saying your lymphatic
system needs to be
uh-huh yeah what did i eat this morning
i had an olive oil shot and then i had
avocado toast
and then i had two hard-boiled eggs
uh-huh is that gonna help my lymphatic
system i don't know my practitioner says
it's a good breakfast for my lymphatic
system
yeah what am i doing after i'm going to
focus on an exercise that helps my
lymphatic system later on in the day
uh-huh yeah it's an exercise they say
it's good for your lymphatic system
yeah i'm going to focus on that okay
all right what what lymphatic system
is your second filter what's your first
filter
what do you mean filter your liver is
your first filter
really what does that mean
so if you don't clean your liver your
lymphatic system perpetually stays dirty
well how come my doctor doesn't know
this
because my doctor doesn't even know why
i'm sick to begin with
i think it's starting to make some sense
okay i gotta go
massage helps move stuff around yeah
it starts to move fluid around but if
you don't fix the problem you're not
gonna you're
you're not gonna get okay just yeah
you're gonna have to do the sauna every
day you're gonna have to do the massage
every single day you're gonna have to
exercise
two hours a day just to try to clean up
your lymphatic system but it's a
never-ending vicious cycle and you can't
clean it because it's dirty all the time
because you can't fix your liver no
one's fixing the liver and cleaning up
their diet
so let's just exercise all two hours a
day
let me just do the massage and let's hop
in the sauna
let's get all hot sweaty let's try to
clean up let's hop into a cold tub
let's try to clean up the lymphatic
system let's get it moving keep the
lymphatic system moving meanwhile your
liver is still sick and dirty
no one gets it let's take a whole bunch
of lymphatic supplements
let's just do i mean no one gets it it's
unbelievable
what planet are we on here how come
everything's so
ass backwards how is it possible
everything in the health movement is so
ass backwards like how
how
it's insane let's make a banana papaya
bowl
oh but we're afraid of fruit
because the ass backwards health
movement tells you don't eat fruit
kristen i am a massage therapist
amazing i i'm telling people all the
time that they should get their books
good get your books and clean up the
diet they really want to feel better
you're incredible just so you know i got
tremendous
respect for massage out of all
alternative therapies just you know
you're going to hear it right from my
mouth i've been saying it for 35 years
you won't find contradictions in medical
medium information okay
and i've been saying it since the
beginning out of all
the alternative therapies out there that
exist massage is still the best one
colleen can't make money on healthy
patients no
can't
and then you know you're told not to eat
fruit let's get fruit fear you're told
not to eat fruit
from our ass backwards health movement
what does ass backwards even mean
well i can tell you this
i think it means our health movement out
there
let's make a papaya bowl real quick i'm
gonna scoop out these seeds just give me
a second so i can dump these seeds at
you guys
look i'm not i'm not judging anyone
i get it science and research doesn't
know why anybody's sick
i get it this is for mono eating this is
like
this is a mono eating kind of thing too
you guys
keep that in mind it's from motto eating
you can you can do it anyway for
anything really you can
you can do it for anything you really
can
with fruit
we got a little bit of a snag just hold
on you guys
just grabbing something over here and
then we're gonna be back in action
here's what you do for like when you're
cutting papaya what i like to do is i
take a knife like this and i do this
right here
i'll just do like little cuts in here
just don't cut your hand or anything
i just i just do that really quick let's
get a bowl
right here boom
look i get it it's nobody's fault well
some people at the top of the medical
industry including on the top of the
alternative metal
medical industry too they're not they're
not
they're not angels amber gardner
mm papaya medical medium by banana
monoglands is healing my
lifelong struggle with debilitating
digestive issues amber
incredible incredible
see what i love about this skillet i
know i'm throwing this off track for a
quick second is i love when it browns up
like hash browns a little bit in there i
use steamed potato to begin with just so
you know
the mono eating cleanses and cleanse the
heel if you want to know
okay on sale amazon us 16.99 it's where
the
medical media morning cleanse isn't
mono eating cleanse all that so i'm just
dropping some papaya in here
just like this this is how i do it make
a papaya bowl i do it this way
so what i do is just scrape out the
papaya
joan death by a thousand cuts
exactly how the system's rigged right
i just got pie in there just like that
okay
got some papaya there
let's get some banana in here too you
guys
can do two bananas here's one banana
a little papaya banana bowl you can make
it look prettier than this but you know
i'm kind of just cruising
cruising for a papaya banana bowl
bruising
because it doesn't look as pretty as it
probably should but there it is i don't
know how
you guys might think maybe you guys like
that
do that in the morning if you don't have
the medical mean heavy metal detox movie
or the liverescue smoothie or you don't
have something else but this is a great
great food right here sorry about all
the noise
super gentle on the intestinal tract
really gentle on the intestinal tract
be cautious about the fruit fear being
created by
the practitioners out there that have
misinformation
because it started out as a as a total
attack on fruit
originally by the upper echelon of the
medical industry
and then they put plants out there to
spread it
long ago you want the banana ripe but
you don't want it over ripe because you
don't want it fermented but you don't
want it under ripe you want you don't
want the banana under ripe
you don't want the banana over ripe keep
that in mind
really good tips right there you don't
want the banana overripe you don't want
the banana under ripe
under ripe then it's fermented you just
you know fermented food i don't like
fermented food
don't like it at all for a lot of
reasons
overripe gets you in trouble when it's
over over ripe you don't want the banana
so
over ripe you don't want the skin so
brown and the bananas mushy
you don't want to do that because then
it's just it's just it's starting to
ferment
you don't want to do that i get hungry
after eating potatoes make sure you're
doing leafy greens in your diet
i saw that come up through make sure
some leafy greens coming up in your diet
too
keep that in mind right yeah
now i'm hungry maria so i got the banana
bowl right there
i'm gonna plate this you guys bear with
me i'm going to do a little plating
right here
this is like hash browns basically
there's some spices in here it's
delicious
notice that i didn't put salt in there
if you really can't live without some
salt and you want a little in there
as long as you're fat free that's a
major plus
okay that's an that's a major plus
being fat free
look maybe you can save this meal here
maybe you can do like a fruit bowl after
you had your celery juice and lemon
water right
and you can then save this for lunch and
then have a fat free lunch and go a
little bit longer fat free how amazing
is that
there's thousands of combinations
thousands of combinations to heal and
medical medium books
and information just so you know it's
all here there's no one medical medium
protocol
just try to be you know try to keep that
in mind you may say you're doing medical
medium
but you're not doing medical medium to
its fullest extent or you're not doing
medical medium properly or you're not
doing medical medium you're not doing
the right supplementation medical medium
is talking about
you're not using the right b12 you're
not using the right information it's all
here
it's all here
what happens is when people say they've
been doing medical medium for a year we
don't know if they've been doing medical
medium because every time we look into
it or we
talk to somebody or whatever we find out
they haven't been doing medical medium
they got all these things that that are
from all the other health places in
in the world you know health health
gurus and stuff like that
they're doing charcoal they're doing
they're doing
butter they're doing grass-fed butter
that's not a medical medium
and they're doing like they're doing
like all kinds of different things it's
just endless
doing eggs yeah they're doing eggs
got a phone call coming in i think the
phone's ringing
[Music]
what you doing she says she's on a
medical medium
let's go see now i see apple cider
vinegar in the refrigerator
yep well that's right you know i see
hold on a new medical treatment yeah i
see a receipt for a new medical
treatment
yep yep it's sitting over there there's
a certificate
for the new medical treatment
it says she's not getting better not
getting better at medical medium
chocolate i see the chocolate
yeah i see the chocolate this is
six ounces of celery juice
it's not 32 ounces nope it's six ounces
there's lemon squeezed in it this is fly
on the wall
find the wall what else i'm looking
is coconut oil this is almond butter i
see nutritional yeast
i see nutritional yeast it's under kale
chips
it's under kale chips
what else flying wall here
she says it she's doing medical medium
and not getting better
let me fly by the supplements this is
fine by the supplements
flying by your supplements there's
alcohol in one of the supplements
it's a cat's claw she got cat's claw
cause the medical medium but it's the
wrong one it's got alcohol
it's a different brand it's got citric
acid
yep yep what else is she doing
this is on corella yeah
i see it uh-huh yup flying the wall
uh how many fats is she doing lots of
fats
she's not really going that far with
medical medium just dabbling
uh-huh i don't know what that's i don't
know what to tell her
yep well she's making comments that
she's doing medical medium
and putting doubt and fear in
everybody's minds
there's no leafy greens this is cilantro
no she didn't do a lot of cilantro not
doing a lot of leafy greens at all
she's afraid of fruit still this is
afraid of fruit
this is just medical medium but afraid
of fruits
okay okay all right that's i
gotta go
so that's a potato skillet right there
be your own detective i'm just letting
you guys know
be your own detective be your own
detective to others
okay but wait a minute how many fats are
in the diet
do you have eggs in the diet is there
milk cheese butter in the diet
these are kefir in the diet how many
people say they're doing mmm and they
got kefir in the refrigerator
how much caffeine are they doing when
did they do chocolate last did they do
nutritional yeast a month ago
you do nutrition at least a month ago
takes two weeks to recover from that
stuff
this rips the lining apart the msg goes
to the brain messes people up gets them
depressed
it's just you know like how how far are
they really going is it 32 ounces of
celery juice are they skipping celery
juice days have they done the heavy
metal detox movie are
they using corella which doesn't work
have they done the 369 advanced cleanse
at least one time have they
keep the fats lower are they repeating
the three six nine
what's i mean you can just just be your
own detective like how far are they
going what supplementation are they
using are they using supplements with
alcohol in it
are they using supplements of citric
acid in it are they using other stuff
like what's
be your own detective be a detective for
others too you know why because it helps
them heal because you can be like hey
okay what are you doing when's the last
time you had vinegar
because vinegar will stop somebody from
healing
vinegar will stop some body from healing
i'm telling you right now that's the
dish right there
the vinegar goes down goes in the body
boom
you stopped from healing you're not
healing anymore you're not healing
your blood turns to acid you have
kombucha tea goes inside the body
boom you're not healing anymore your
blood turns acid
that's what happens your blood turns
acid
your healing slows down your healing
stops
for a lot of people with that right
there okay
and i'm keeping people from getting a
lot of lot worse and
and when you're when you're a detective
for people you help them from getting a
lot worse you're actually helping them
you're saving their butt you're at least
helping to slow it down
for them you know when you when people
are doing
you're doing stuff they're doing
nutritional yeast they're doing the
vinegar
doing the kombucha tea they're doing
their chocolate boom you stop peeling
you can't heal tank and chocolate you
can't
you can't heal all the way tanking that
chocolate it's not gonna happen
it's not gonna happen you have to keep
these things out if you wanna go all the
way i'm not
shaming anybody i'm not judging anybody
that's not
at all what it is is if you want to go
the mile you actually want to heal all
the way if you're really tired of being
sick we got to go a little bit further
because moderation doesn't fix
us it doesn't fix us at all
it doesn't fix us moderation gets us in
trouble
then we can't heal and then we're stuck
right
the problem is if you're not so sick you
can dabble with all the out
there you can dabble with all the trends
you can dabble
you can dabble if you're not so sick you
can dabble with it all if you're not so
sick you can dabble with it all
you can just play around oh i got all my
stuff here i'm not so sick
i can do lots of cacao i could do cacao
nibs every day i could do all my walnuts
every day
i could have coconut oil every single
day i could eat almonds all day long
i can have fish i could have chicken i
could have lots of
lots of stuff because i'm not i'm not
sick yet
i'm not really sick that's how it works
i could do my nutritional yeast what
else do i have
i can do my eggs i'm not so sick let me
do my eggs let me do my nutritional
yeast
because you're you're not you're you
know
not so sick that's how it works
i could play around my blood type diet i
could screw around with that
because i'm not so sick i could play
around with a keto diet because i'm not
so sick
i could play around with another no
processed food diet
because you're not so sick you can mess
around mess around mess around until one
day
you fall off the cliff and now your head
is so screwed up from all the
misinformation out there you ain't got a
chance in hell to get better
until you buckle down until you buckle
down
you don't have a chance in hell to get
better when you go
too far and get too sick because the
trends get in the way
and then the pathogens and toxins if you
don't know about the pathogens and
toxins
if you don't know about those if you
don't know how to get them out of the
body if you don't know how to get the
metals out of the body if you don't know
what to do what to avoid
what kind of foods to avoid if you don't
know about the troublemakers
if you don't know about all this it's
gonna be hard to get better
when you're not so sick you could play
around in it i'll go do this i'll go
take this kombucha tea i'll go to yoga
class i have my apple cider vinegar
i'll go try this non-sibo diet for a
while i'll keep my fruits away fruit
fear
i'll just play around play around play
around cut powders i'll do this i'll do
that
and then all of a sudden you step in a
bigger pile of crap
and now you're like whoa whoa i'm
actually sick
i'm actually sick now and then you can't
find your way back to medical medium
because you don't even you're so lost
here in this practitioner's state try
this ayurvedic treatment
this acupuncturist say try this
treatment this naturopath say that
try that dysfunctional medicine doctor
try this
this nutritionist dietitian try this try
this i'm not saying they're
we need you know we need good
nutritionists and dietitians and
naturopaths and functional medicine
doctors and acupuncture whoever is out
there and chinese medicine people we
need everybody working together
but nobody knows why we're sick and
everybody's throwing out all the stuff
do some oil pulling take this stuff drop
some you know neem oil in your stomach
you pay later for all the harmful stuff
you're doing
try the corella death by a thousand cuts
have been telling you guys
and then we pay later no one's teaching
you how to cleanse nobody's teaching you
how to clean things up
no one's teaching how to protect
yourself and protect you
and then we pay later we pay down the
road
and then we're in the game of try this
new thing try that new thing and then
you know
and then someone goes you know some
hater goes uh don't drink celery juice
it's not good for you
it's like not good for you you kidding
anyway
we're going to instagram i might have a
little bit of this for a second
but we're heading off to instagram
this is where we're going um this is the
potato skillet
it's really good
i'm turning tik tok back on that's got a
lot of cayenne in it
i'm going to turn tick-tock back on in
about five minutes i'm turning clubhouse
back on about five minutes
you guys coming to ig with me we're
gonna be doing it
love you guys see you guys soon