live right now live on facebook youtube
tick tock clubhouse medical medium
morning cleanse challenge
to get ourselves healthy get ourselves
better
this is a special moment because we're
talking about a powerful way
to get our lives back one that's
attainable
one that's possible one that's in your
hands one that's
tangible it's there and that's the thing
it's been helping so many people
you guys if you got a story to tell tag
at medical medium about the benefits of
the morning cleanse that have you know
worked for you
what kind of benefits what kind of uh
symptoms may have gone away what's your
story
would love just love to uh see you guys
put in the comments section too
and also you can tag at medicalmedium
and instagram whatever later and
i'll post the story too good to see you
guys coming on exciting some medical
medium morning cleanse
it's a cleanse it comes out of the
medical medium right here book
cleanse to heal if you guys have this
lucky you it's it's changing lives
around the world it has already saved
countless lives around the world with
all kinds of debilitating illnesses
diseases
symptoms conditions this is 51 off at
amazon.com
us 16.99
uh what incredible book over 200
symptoms and conditions
supplements dosages what to do i mean
the tools in here are just
incredible medical medium warning
cleanse is one of the cleanses inside
this book so
make sure you get a copy when you can
good to see you guys coming on i'm
excited about this
i'm gonna be making the heavy metal
detox movie gonna be making some celery
juice
some lemon water too going to be making
waffles actually you know the potato
waffles because i know some people
they like something heartier between now
and lunch time between morning and lunch
time they like something
that's you know heartier too so the
medical media warning cleanse is inside
cleanse the heel
if you take a look right here and i'm
going to it right now so
we're getting there so it's page 174
that's the morning cleanse
just so you know so there's a lot of
information in there for you guys to
learn how to heal
so the morning cleanse is so important
because upon waking
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water so that's
right there just upon waking you want to
use that to flush out the liver to flush
it out you need that chance because what
we do
is we don't do a liver flushing routine
everybody thinks their liver is fine
they think their liver may not be
needing a flush or a cleaning
and the medical medium warning cleanse
helps to clean our liver every single
day every single morning and it's so
important to get us better to get us to
keep us from getting sick
that right there keep our immune system
strong flush out those toxins and
poisons that age us
fast and nobody nobody wants to talk
about aging until they start aging
that's the other thing too and so they
start showing all the signs that they're
aging
and the skin's wrinkling up a lot more
and you get the sun spots and you get
all these problems and the medical mean
morning cleanse is a great way
to really slow that down clean those
things up good to see you guys
you guys are coming on now i'd love to
see how the medical mean morning cleanse
has helped you guys along the way too
and let's cover a little bit 16 to 32
ounces of lemon water i'm going to show
you that in a minute
right 16 to 32 ounces of celery juice a
little later
you can pick a smoothie you could do a
liver rescue smoothie for medical medium
you can do the heavy metal detox movie
but i'm going to be doing the medical
meme heavy metal detox smoothie right
and then there's a lot of recipes in
here that are fat free the
the goal the goal
is to not do any fats before
noon really important let's cover that
for a second
love to cover that right got some peanut
butter right here
that's the peanut butter right you guys
know you love your peanut butter so many
of you
okay peanut butter is a healthy fat it's
a healthy fat
it is and but when you're doing this
before noon
you never cleanse you just can't
cleanse nothing will cleanse out of you
you won't be able to detox
everything toxic inside of us will stay
inside of us
so when you do your peanut butter before
noon
nothing leaves your system you don't
cleanse if you guys just came on we're
doing the medical medium
uh morning cleanse challenge it's
starting it's gonna go three days today
is the first day i'm really excited
about it right
so how many people are doing their
coconut oil
in the morning how many guys doing
coconut oil in the morning so
or even peanut butter i didn't even ask
you if you guys are doing your peanut
butter
in the morning right and how many people
are doing their coconut oil in the
morning
so coconut butter so that's something
right there because i know a lot of you
guys use this this is a big one
you guys use it every single day you put
it in your smoothies
and that's not recommended by medical
medium because once you do that in the
morning you don't cleanse
right imelda says the morning cleanse
and fat-free diet helped me heal
my gallbladder incredible amazing
it's really important to actually heal
the gallbladder
to heal your digestive system by being
fat free or keeping the fats low i know
a lot of you guys can't keep the fats
out
you can't keep the coconut oil out right
you can't keep it all out
how many guys are doing like the almonds
right here right
how many of you guys are doing the
almonds you're doing those before noon
you're doing those in the morning
it's almond butter that's a big one
right you guys are doing the almond
butter
and when you do almond butter in the
morning and i'm not saying
that almonds are bad i'm not saying
walnuts are bad i'm not saying peanut
butter is bad i'm not saying anything
like that
what i'm saying is you're not gonna
cleanse
if you have your almond butter in the
morning
it's not gonna happen it's just not
really important to know
this is great information here's some
olive oil right here too
some olive oil right healthy fat olive
oil
right there it really is so you know
that's the one thing because people will
say medical medium he just you know he
thinks avocado's unhealthy he thinks
olive oil is unhealthy
he thinks peanut butter is unhealthy
almond butter is unhealthy
that's not what i think it's just that
everybody's fatting themselves to death
and they can't cleanse and
what happens is you might be somebody
like yeah but i started getting my
symptoms better
by eating clean getting rid of processed
foods
you know eating healthier doing
healthier oils
healthier fats and i started i started
getting better
but what happens is you'll get sick
later you will get sick
later because all that stuff will build
up and build up in your system good to
see you guys coming on
how many of you guys are doing your
cacao nibs in the morning
how many guys doing that they're cacao
nibs right
doing your cacao nibs there's the fat
again so you're putting that in your
smoothies you're putting that you know
in on top of your oatmeal you're mixing
this in your food
right and what about your cacao powder
too i got some cacao powder right here
right so we're taught that we need to
have this in the morning have your cacao
powder in the smoothie and you're not
going to see that here
lexi says my liver was so sluggish and i
had a bad skin
condition with following your info it's
gone it's gone incredible
so important you guys are live on
facebook live on youtube
live on tick tock live on clubhouse
right now
that's amazing that's fantastic so happy
to hear so happy to hear
so people are doing their chocolate in
the morning cacao nibs they're doing
their cacao powder they're doing in
smoothies
and these are what everybody's being
told they're healthy fats right
you got your almonds and here's your
walnuts too
so we got our walnuts right there
another healthy fat
look at that right now when it comes
down to the chocolate the cacao
and the cacao powder it's not a healthy
fat really
because basically that caffeine just
annihilates any real health benefit you
can get from chocolate because caffeine
really just
ages as quickly but there's no caffeine
in walnuts
so you got that so the walnut butter
handful of walnuts right i mean that's
not a bad thing at all
but if you're doing it in the morning
you won't
cleanse you just won't and the medical
media morning cleanse is something you
can do and
live your life doing so you can get
back on track but here's the thing and
everybody's doing other things too
they're doing their bacon in the morning
so they're doing their bacon right
they're doing that so say someone's like
well hey look i don't do any carbs i
don't have the pancakes
i'm on the bacon every single morning
i'm on the eggs every single morning
that's healthy
people think that's healthy and you're
just not going to cleanse
you're just not so you can't cleanse the
liver
you can't get the toxins out of your
body and i know people are worried about
the lymphatic system
where you're not going to be able to
purge your lymphatic system if you're
having
fat in the morning so if you do your
coconut oil and your almond butter
and your peanut butter in the morning
between before noon especially before
noon and you're doing you're doing your
cacao in the morning before noon
you're not cleaning up your lymphatic
system it can't clean up
and you're not cleaning up the liver
it's really important to know
joseph says celery juice completely got
rid
of my see pitting
derma in my legs feet and ankles
and nothing else could get rid over
three years
of trying everything to do since
being diagnosed with heart disease whoa
diagnose the heart disease
cardiomyopathy whoa
unbelievable there and you're actually
getting you got everything better
also the rust looking spots in my legs
that started appearing
wow that's so good so good so important
so look if you do your bacon in the
morning you do your sausage you do your
eggs in the morning we get in trouble
that's right there say you're somebody
that's that's trying to do something
else like
say you got your gluten-free bagel right
you got your gluten-free bagel in the
morning you got your
organic cream cheese in the morning
you're not gonna cleanse
it's just not going to happen why do we
have to cleanse you guys we have to get
rid of poisons and toxins we got to get
them out of her body every day
they just build up and they wreak havoc
so that when you get
sick someday you don't get better no
one's teaching you how to get better
the reason why intermittent fasting
gives
people some relief
is because intermittent fasting is
getting rid of the fats in the morning
that's why so when people intermittent
fast
that's everybody's being forced
intermittent fast that's what's
happening right now
the younger generations are being forced
to intermittent fast because they can't
keep their weight off
they can't keep their weight off their
livers are all stagnant
and sluggish and that's what's happening
right there okay
and so an intermittent fasting is not an
answer
it's not an answer because what happens
is you blow out your adrenals when you
do your intermittent fasting
you blow your adrenals out that's what
happens along the way keep that in mind
so it's all cute it's all fun it's all
games at first with the intermittent
fasting
wow i'm feeling a little better let me
get on my let me get on my caffeine let
me do that i'm intermittent fasting let
me make sure i'm drinking my coffee
let me do that intermittent fasting is
working for me so good
i'm high on coffee all day high in
coffee all morning let me do my
intermittent fasting
i'm losing weight i'm feeling some
energy back and the reason why
is because you stopped doing
the fats in the morning you stopped
eating your eggs in the morning
you stopped eating your bacon in the
morning and that's what happened with
the intermittent fasting it's like wait
a minute
intermittent fasting is like the holy
grail or something but really what they
don't understand
is they stop eating the fats and they
stop killing their liver in the morning
that's what happened they stopped
killing their livers
and so people are being forced
intermittent fast and that's not the
answer
this is this isn't a pro intermittent
fasting deal here
claudia says i was close to dying on an
almost
total fat diet so sick
a lot of people get there with that that
fat diet
i almost healed i'm almost healed
from about 80 long-term conditions
thank you aw for saving my life
incredible no problem
i got a lot of lights in my eyes right
now you guys from
lighting in front of me the lights are
so bright for some reason today
so it's it's like the comments get
kind of like whited out write it out but
uh
thanks for leaving the comments
incredible intermittent fasting hurt me
i just saw that
so intermittent fasting what it does is
it burns out the adrenals
and it does hurt us over time when
you're younger you can pull it off it's
like just do the caffeine
stay high all day long and then take
that big
fatty meal at the end of the day right
and you'll notice
you'll start to slim down a little bit
your belly goes in a little bit
you start to you start to lose some
weight so intermittent fasting seems to
be
the greatest thing but it's really a
mistake
a bad mistake so what you do when you
intermittent fast you burn out your
adrenals you trash them
along the way and so there's something
better we can do
because you can't just live on
adrenaline you can't be doing this
intermittent fasting and just living on
adrenaline and living on adrenaline your
adrenals right there
right just running on adrenaline so it's
like hey i'm intermittent fasting let me
do a coffee coffee coffee
not eating not eating not eating and
matcha tea much tea not eating and just
blowing out your adrenals
and that's not the way to do things
that's not the correct way to do things
the right way to do things
really important to know hi anthony
please tell us
what's a non-radical fat
first of all steve radical fats
are anything that's cranking up the fat
you've got your cacao that's a radical
fat
you got your walnuts that's a radical
fat you got your peanut butter that's a
radical fat
right you got your coconut oil radical
fat you got your olive oil radical fat
right there
okay radical fat radical fat that's what
all those are whoa
what's this what's this
avocados now what you're gonna find
here is i'm not saying avocado is not
good for you
that's a healthy fat i like it if you
guys eat avocados
it because your guys are gonna eat fat
anyway i'd rather have you eat avocados
instead of an animal protein eggs milk
cheese
butter yogurt those are all radical fats
by the way
butter radical fat so if you're going to
have a butter
use avocado right but you know you've
heard that before you're just you're
just you've heard that before
use avocado as butter okay 35 years ago
i couldn't get anybody to use avocado as
butter
i mean i got laughed off of lecture
stages for saying avocado was good for
you
30 plus years ago people would be like
avocados poisonous
you'll get a heart attack eating avocado
that's what everybody thought
doctors thought avocado was toxic just
so you know
i said no you can use it as butter
replace your butter
replace your butter with avocado people
that was so that was so bizarre to
everybody
so bizarre they couldn't handle that
truth right
but avocado in the morning
is not going to get you strong it's not
going to get you healthy it's not going
to get you better it's not going to
de-age you
it's not going to help you got to keep
the avocados
for another time you got to keep them
after lunch that's when you have to keep
your avocados and avocado i want you
guys to
see that right there right so when
you're doing your avocado toast in the
morning you're not going to cleanse
and if you're sick if you're dealing
with ra if you're dealing with fibro
hashimoto's
thyroiditis hyperthyroidism graves
thyroid nodules
back pain neck pain right if you're
dealing with migraines
exercises vitiligo any kind of condition
and you keep on doing all your fats in
the morning
you're eventually gonna get in trouble
you're not gonna be able to heal it
all the way you're not gonna be able to
go to that finish
line that finished line
oat milk that's another radical fat nut
milks radical fats
right there so these are other radical
fats
bone broth radical fat radical fat
right salmon fish radical fat
eggs radical fat right there
concentrated oat milk the fats
concentrated in there it's in there
it's a radical fat chicken radical fat
burgers radical fat
red meat radical fat right eggs salmon
tuna whatever it is
radical fat right so
what happens is everybody's
fatten themselves to death we're taught
that way
we can't live without it because we've
never been taught otherwise on any level
medical media morning cleanse is about
getting our lives back you guys just
came on if you don't have this book you
might want it in your
personal library at home okay the
information is
is incredible in here and what it's done
for people you guys know who do have the
book cleanse the heel but it's
it's imperative this book is in people's
hands who are sick
if you're dealing with any kind of
symptoms if you're living with some kind
of condition if the quality of your life
is not where you think it is this is the
book for you
this the legendary book already after a
year
it's a really heavy textbook and
it's a book that has answers for chronic
illness symptoms conditions
75 recipes in here but that's just some
of the things that it has has the
cleanse it has a medical me morning
cleanse and it's on sale right now
16.99 and the thing is with medical
medium information
is i go against the grain so
i've been called a rebel because i won't
package the information up
and sell it for three thousand dollar
programs or twenty five hundred dollar
programs
four thousand dollar programs i won't do
it i want it to be sixteen dollars
in ninety nine cents this book helped me
do
a life-changing banana mono cleanse
thank you so much mmm dan cozy
incredible
that's amazing you did that there's mono
eating cleanses in here
and that's the thing i want this
accessible that's what it's been about
with spirit of compassion i want it
accessible so people can get their lives
back
and that's how you know where do you get
the book amazon.com us
or book depository if you're somewhere
else in the world
right target that's a place right there
there's other places too the books are
at barnes and noble that's one right
there but it's on sale at amazon.com us
for 16.99
and it's a powerful book to have it's
already getting people's lives
back and it tells you about what's the
cause of
of a condition so let's just let and and
what to do everything about so let's
just get moving a little bit we got the
lemon water right here so i got some
water
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water first
thing in the morning
right cutting the lemon right now
so there's our lemon you guys you're
somebody that's
worried about lemon because you heard
misinformation like
hurts your teeth wears off the enamel
it's not true
some misinformation works lemon is how
we restore
teeth and gums bioavailable calcium
not to mention lemon is a cleanser
of the gut it's a cleanser of the mouth
lemon helps to destroy bacteria that's
in your mouth
that's eaten away at your gums
so when you hear a dentist say hey lemon
is bad lemon water is bad they're
wrong they're just wrong and that's the
sad thing
so you get your lemon water going 16 to
32 ounces upon
waking upon waking you guys we're live
on tick tock
facebook youtube we're live on clubhouse
glad to have you guys on we're doing
medical media morning cleanse i'm
excited
so that's the first thing you do i'm
gonna turn on
my little waffle machine you guys
probably can't see it too easy over
there because i'm gonna make some
waffles
what waffles is just i'm picking waffles
as a recipe because it's a fun one but
i'm picking that one
it's fat free this recipe and it's for
somebody who feels like
they need something really heavy they're
used to the bacon and eggs in the
morning and they're like well how am i
gonna survive if i can't have my eggs in
the morning
so we're gonna do a little potato waffle
in a little bit let's keep on going with
the cleanse
you got your lemon water right there 16
to 32 ounces of lemon water
now we're gonna do some celery juice
gonna run some celery real quick through
here you guys
here's the deal you've been taught to do
fats since you were a child that's how
it's done
we're taught to crank the fats up
lots of overt fats i call them radical
fats
and we feel like we can't live without
the fat we feel like we can't live
without it so i'm going to answer a
couple questions that are common
one is if i can't have my fats in the
morning
my peanut butter my oils
right my walnuts my eggs
my bacon my avocado if i can't have my
fats
in the morning how am i gonna keep my
blood sugar stable
you're having blood sugar issues the
answer's in your hands already
it's because of the fats it's
because of the fats elizabeth could see
it
[Music]
it's because of the fats that's why
your blood sugar is unstable to begin
with because your diet is so loaded in
fat what that means is your
pancreas is weakening
that's what that means your pancreas
is weakening that means your adrenals
are weakening
if you got blood sugar problems
that's because you've had insulin
resistance
for years you guys
so if you're someone that's scared to
death
of going fat free in the morning or fat
free during a day because you think
you're gonna have blood sugar
instability
then you're someone that already has a
weak
pancreas from fats
see what i mean you're already getting
injured
from your high fat diet and that's
how it rolls
if you're dealing with that if you're at
the doctor's office the doctor's like
well you got hypoglycemia you've got
blood sugar instability here
you've got a little insulin resistance
you got your a1c is is moving around
you're not stable you're already injured
from living off of fats you're already
hurting from all the fats yeah healthy
fats too
the avocados right the bacon the eggs
which aren't healthy fats
the nuts and nut butters cat beard
says that is true explanation points
when i started eating fruit and veggies
and cut out the fats i felt so much
better and quickly i stopped having what
i thought
were hypoglycemic episodes it means the
fats you've been consuming all these
years
are starting to beat down the pancreas
starting to take out the pancreas that's
what it means
regina says i've been doing that morning
cleanse for almost three years
and cannot live without it i used to
suffer from
hypoglycemia and it's all normal now
thanks to you and spirit
that's how it rolls so look you guys
what i've noticed is
once people learn this information once
they actually learn the information
it's endless what they can do and that's
what they can do get their lives back
medical medium information is about
results
like the real results not the smoke and
mirror ones
that are out there in the health
movement
suzanne says i used to have gluten-free
toast
with cheese and a poached egg every day
on the on the brain fog whoa oh the
brain fog
wow now lwcj
heavy metal detox movie and zero brain
fog now so you're doing the cj you're
doing the heavy metal detox smoothie
incredible incredible brain fog
gone amazing that's incredible it really
is
so when people don't realize you guys is
they're living with insulin resistance
every single day
every single day for living with insulin
resistance
that's what they're up against insulin
resistance is
the big one right there their pancreas
is maxed out
every single day their pancreas is
hurting every single day
this is a we're in like part of the
medical meeting morning puns right now
i'm doing a little celery juice
i didn't do celery juice yet today
anyway
so this is great i'm excited
i was like you know what i'll do it
later on i'll have some celery juice
later on
so insulin resistance
means your pancreas and your adrenals
are getting weak it also means your
liver is stagnant sluggish and getting
weak
and i don't know why anybody would want
that maybe they just don't know they
have it right maybe they just don't know
they have the problem
but they do they do have it so we're
going to do some celery juice constraint
you have to strain the celery juice
it's critical you got to get all the
pulp out you got to get all the fiber
out right
i still get blown away at this at this
machine
you know the pulp is dry it's in my
hands right here it's a little bit of
pulp it's nice and dry
i just love that what that means if you
guys have the mm-900 hds it's only this
machine
just so you know this specific machine
but boy it's just so great
saving money every time i juice celery
it's i like doing the medical medium
morning cleanse knowing i'm saving money
that's a whole other thing too knowing
my juicer is paying for itself
incredible doing some celery juice it's
part of the medical medium morning
cleanse
look you guys if you can't do the
cleanse perfectly if you can't
juice if you can't do the lemon water
then we have to find creative ways to be
fat-free in the morning
we can do a fruit bowl we can do a fruit
smoothie
we can do a medical medium fat-free
recipe we can still be creative
we can do water without the lemon if we
have to
okay lime is another thing you can do
you can do limes you don't have to just
do lemon water here's some limes right
now i'm going to throw a couple over
here
so we can do that right it's fun
it's fun so i got some celery juice 16
to 32 ounces of celery juice
right there nice big one okay
i'm excited you can consume
fruits let me get a papaya that's an
option right there
okay so we can do a papaya this is a big
papaya right here
so let me do is move this over
for the moment okay
um if you can't do the heavy metal detox
smoothie which i'm about to do in a
minute if you can't do that
you can just have some fruit in the
morning look at this okay nice papaya
right here you can do mangoes in the
morning
that's an option right there okay
we got a beautiful papaya right there
look at this
right you can do that in the morning do
a papaya bowl
chop up some bananas throw some bananas
on there i can make a little one of that
in a little bit i can make that that's
great right
that's a wonderful thing to have let's
make the heavy metal detox smoothie what
i like to do
me personally is i like to do the lemon
water in the morning
i like to do the celery juice after that
and i like to do the heavy metal detox
movie
we got to get the metals out of our
bodies
we do elizabeth says i can do watermelon
all morning you can
incredible you can do watermelon all
morning you're doing watermelon all the
more
all morning you're fat free you can do
that if you want
that's great that's great it's a great
option that's a great option
let me get the heavy metal detox movie
going
depression anxiety
depersonalization crippling anxiety
nervousness that's unexplainable palms
of your hands sweating all the time
right
tightness to the chest tightness of the
throat okay
different forms of anxiety people have
all the time
metals are involved depression
unexplained sadness metals
are involved something to know right
there right
eczema how many of you guys have dealt
with eczema psoriasis
metals are involved parkinson's
alzheimer's memory memory loss memory
problems anything like that too
conditions that are really serious
okay metals are involved als
metals are involved and then just you
know those are the more serious
conditions
go to less serious conditions right
still metals are involved
and we vitiligo boom metals right there
rosacea
metals right there so getting the metals
out
is critical ticks spasms adhd
metals so i love the heavy metal detox
smoothie that's a critical
critical piece of the puzzle let's get
some blueberries in there
got the frozen wild blueberries right
there okay
it's the wyman's ones is the one i use
after one year of the medical being
protocol
first time in my life a happy person
marija thanks for commenting i was so
sad all my life
and you're doing the medical media
protocol incredible incredible i'm gonna
drop some blueberries in here
okay so
two cups of water blueberries frozen
wild blueberries
got those in there let me get some
bananas going
two bananas got him right here
good to see you guys so let me bring it
on over
can you see that on tick tock right
two bananas just the heavy metal detox
smoothie
the only heavy metal
alternative therapy i've ever seen work
in all the decades still to today is
that medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie
you don't get the metals out with all
the tricks
and the tips that are being talked about
out there
it's hard to think of it's hard for one
thing okay
how are you to get metals out from
people who don't even know
metals even caused a condition isn't it
interesting so
nobody knew metals caused anxiety or
eczema psoriasis until medical medium
information
so let's not listen to medical medium
about how to get the metals out
let's listen to someone who says try
some charcoal when they didn't even know
metals caused any condition whatsoever
it's kind of interesting when you think
about it right someone can be all of a
sudden
a heavy metal expert when they didn't
even know a condition is caused by
metals
that's a tough one right there on it so
the only way to get the metals out
okay is making sure you got the wild
blueberries in there which we did
i got some dolls so it's a nice bowl of
dolls right there doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie
right cilantro okay
cilantro is critical that's atlantic
dolce gotta have your cilantro in there
put a little bit of that right and
i'm gonna put a little extra wild
blueberry powder
it's one cup of cilantro by the way so
i'm gonna put a little bit of the
the um a little bit of wild blueberry
powder
so what i'm gonna do now
let's do that
so
let's get that in there i like to put a
little extra
doing that barley grass juice powder
that's another great way of getting the
metals out you have to have the five
ingredients and if you don't have the
full
five ingredients and you have three out
of the five you can get some
metals out i like having five out of the
five
that's the way to really accelerate it
quicker right now i have the capsules i
just ran out of the powder
this is the vimergy brand b is in victor
i
am as in
so i'm putting in a couple of capsules
in here i'm putting in about
a teaspoon of barley grass juice powder
so we got that going in there right
and i'm gonna pop in some spirulina
right there spirulina's critical
for getting the metals out
and you can find these supplements at
the mm directory medical meme directory
medicalmedium.com but it's the vimergy
products that's the best
there is out there by far hands down
quality is unmatched so we have the
spirulina we have the barley grass juice
powder we got the cilantro we've got the
wild blueberries now bananas in there
because it
gives you more glucose because you need
glucose to get the metals out too
that's really important all it's all on
its own we got the dulce in there
atlantic dolls right
so there we go i'm gonna put the lid on
this you can add a little bit of water
you can add a little bit of coconut
water to it too
right and i think i got everything in
there you guys
we can do a little blending is what
we'll do
you can blend it sometimes without oh
yeah i got to have the orange in there
that's the part that is
good old orange right there that's the
part
a lot of moving parts today a lot of
stuff on my plate
so i'm gonna squeeze some orange in here
you got your vitamin c you can use a
little bit of coconut water if you
really like
you have that option as well you guys
just got on here we're in the medical
media morning cleanse challenge
karen i used my new juicer this morning
and it was incredible
incredible how much juice i got from one
bunch of celery
i think you know i'm trying to get that
message across it's the mm 900 hds right
here okay
that's the that's the juicer we're
talking about and the incredible amount
of
juice that comes from it's unmatched
there's no juicer that matches it in my
opinion
lily says can you put a cup of orange
juice in there yes you can
definitely can lily you can i squeezed
an orange in there
so i think we're ready to do a blend
get this going right here
so
that could meaning heavy metal detox
smoothie has helped so many people
it's really incredible when it's done
a lot of people got their lives back you
guys probably know some people that have
some of you guys maybe some of the
people that have
but really what it's done for people has
been just incredible
we got the smoothie right there
let's get a glass for it which is
totally cool we could do that right
there we are
it's the medical meme heavy metal detox
smoothie right there
incredible
love it so you can just do
the lemon water we're about to cook
something to you guys if he just came on
right here
piper haggett says after the nine day
heavy metal detox cleanse
i had a nasal infection clear up
had for nine months so you had a nasal
infection for nine months
and it cleared up in nine days
love it and my dry ear canals cleared up
too
i become a vegan and follow the protocol
every day
i have lost 12 pounds amazing the heavy
metal detox smoothie
have it every day no more dips in energy
and cravings are gone amazing
quit taking expensive multivitamins they
rip you off the multivitamins really bad
out there
this is not only for vegans i'm really
glad you went vegan that's incredible
i'm glad
uh people go plant-based absolutely
supported a million percent
and you can also do this when you're not
a vegan and you're not
you're you're when when you're animal
protein too so if you're somebody that
still
likes your animal protein and that's
your big thing and you can now you feel
like you can never
part ways with animal protein you can
still do these same
tools and heal that's what's incredible
so we just made the heavy metal detox
lily so we got the lemon water 16 to 32
ounces
boom celery juice 16 to 32 ounces
boom we got heavy metal detox smoothie
16 to 32 ounces boom
we got it you can do fruit too let's
make a quick papaya bowl
actually let me get the waffle started
and then i'm gonna make a quick fruit
bowl
pumped i'm pumped i'm pumped i gotta
tell you guys
i'm excited getting better
is exciting getting better
is a great thing so i'm popping some of
the skins off of this right here okay
so what i'm doing is i'm taking some of
these potato skins off you don't have to
take them off if you don't want to for
your waffles
potatoes become a problem
when you mix oil fat nut butter in there
grease when you stick eggs in there when
you stick
when you stick um any kind of oil in
there
butter cheese on a potato then
potato is a problem but it's not
necessarily a problem it's the butter
that's a problem it's the cheese that's
the problem and that's where the problem
really lies
i'm gonna make potato waffles it's a
great one
i really like potato waffles um i think
it's
what happens is it it's shocking for a
lot of people to do
say a morning cleanse where they're
doing celery juice and they're doing
lemon water
and they're doing the heavy metal detox
smoothie it might be hard for somebody
to imagine
that that's going to get them by so many
people i know that if they're just
starting out too they're going to be
like i need something more hearty i need
something more satiating because i'm
used to three four eggs in the morning
aw so what are you gonna do for me then
cause i'm used to a whole bunch of eggs
i'm used to like toast i'm saying well
why don't we do some waffles and what
you're going to find with the waffles
these ones right here is you're going to
find they're fat
free that's the key to avoiding
insulin resistance that's the key to not
getting your blood sugar unstable if
your blood sugar is unstable
and your hypoglycemia happening or
you're hypoglycemic or you're
hyperglycemic
then you've got a pancreas problem and
you're on the edge of diabetes
because your pancreas is basically
saying you know what i'm done
you fat at me to death i'm giving up
soon
so that's how it works okay so doing
this can save pancreases i can't tell
you how many pancreases have been saved
through medical medium protocols so i
think a pancreas is worth saving what do
you guys think on clubhouse you think a
pancreas is worth saving
what do you guys think on tick tock
here's what happens when you get insulin
resistance this is important information
while i'm peeling these potatoes right
here these beautiful potatoes these are
steamed potatoes they're already cooked
they're steamed
what happens is that glucose is how you
get your nutrients
into your cells if that's in the way
you can't get glucose into your cells
easy and you can't get all your
nutrients into your cells
you can be taking all your your your
supplements from your practitioners you
can take all your
all your different supplements all your
different stuff and what happens is
you can you're spending all this money
on all your supplementation
and it's not getting to where it needs
to go you have to have
sugar take in a nutrient into a cell
you can't have a nutrient enter your
cells
unless sugar's driving it in and then if
you're tanking the fats
you got the eggs you got the bacon you
got the nut butters in the morning you
got the avocado toast in the morning
you're not gonna
you can if you're in the morning you
keep on taking your supplements in the
morning right let me take all my
multivitamins my gut health products
supplements my probiotics let me take
everything
i'm taking let me take all my my calcium
let me take let me get all it in the
morning right
when you do that and you're still having
your avocado toast let me kind of have
my avocado toast with it too
if you do that what's going to happen is
only a fraction a tiny fraction of the
supplements are ever going to get
anywhere
only a tiny fraction of those
supplements
are going to get anywhere into your
cells because
the fat from the avocado toast even
though avocados are healthy fat
even though it's a healthy fat the fat
from the avocado toast
won't allow the sugar to drive in all
those nutrients into your cells
do you see how it works and this is
important to know
so i'm just mashing up these potatoes
right here okay
that's what i'm doing here's an option
you can do oatmeal in the morning
you can do that if you're somebody
that's like whoa i can't exist on the
heavy metal detox smoothie i can't exist
on a celery juice
in the morning i can't do this medical
medium morning cleanse
i need something denser because you've
been trained
in such a way to have something much
more denser right
and your oatmeal usually has butter in
it it usually has peanut butter in it it
has nut butters it has nut milk in it
right
so then you feel satiated you feel like
you're keeping your blood sugar balanced
but it's smoking mirrors your pancreas
is
it's throwing out that insulin it's
killing itself to throw out that insulin
when you have all that fat with your
oatmeal so what you can do you guys
you can have fat free oatmeal oatmeal
itself has fat inside of it
every single fruit and vegetable has fat
inside of it everything does
fat is in everything but added fat overt
fat
radical fat adding it is another story
you can have your oatmeal without adding
avocado without adding nut butters
without adding nut milks
you can have your
oatmeal without adding anything right
i'm making a lot of waffle mix right now
this is way more than i know that waffle
maker can take
so i'm just mashing up a lot right here
so this information okay
is priceless just that tip alone
is worth the price of admission to this
free
medical medium morning cleanse challenge
there are no tickets there is no price
for admission here
the bottom line is when you're fat free
in the morning if you do some oatmeal
you can do some millet that's an option
right there
now here's here's a trick to learn don't
do the dried
fruit in the morning
don't do the dried fruit it takes a lot
for the body to extract the sugar and
break it down
out of dried fruit it's not living water
you can't flush the liver easy
with dried fruit in the morning yes you
can have it if it's all you got
if all you got is some raisins it's all
you have
yep you can have it in the morning but i
recommend not
i recommend keeping your dried fruit out
of your morning
you know i mean that's what i recommend
so just mashing some potatoes right now
because we're going to make some waffles
and we've got some maple syrup here too
maple syrup is beneficial
when there's no fat and butter there's
no butter involved
so maple syrup has a problem when
there's butter involved so here's how it
works right
so i got some pancakes right there okay
you see maple syrup on top of the
pancake
but you also see a pat of butter on top
of the pancake
it's the butter and the maple syrup
together
that become the problem right there
maple syrup's great
may we need maple syrup to get into our
cells we need honey to get into our
cells
right we need fruit to get into our
cells but what happens is the butter
stops it from working and then our
pancreas is spilling out all this
insulin
and the butter gets in the way keep it
fat free in the morning
guys this information is so important
all right so
we've got a little waffle mix which is
some mashed potatoes
there we go looking good doing a quicker
mash right here
get this moving along
for years and years and years everybody
said
when are you going to write a book when
are you going to write a book
decades when are you going to write the
book anthony when are you going to write
it
because your waiting list is way too
long and you can't take care of
everybody
so when are you going to write the books
cleanse the heel
it's a legendary book already already
saving lives around the world
and it's here for you guys kenneth says
this is the most educational cooking
show ever
honored honored you're here truly i'm
gonna open up this little
waffle uh maker right here
and i'm gonna pop in
right now let's get this out of the way
all right so i'm gonna put in some
waffle mix which is the potato okay
so you just press it down in here like
that
i'm gonna make some waffles and i'm
gonna flip it around you guys let me
make some room
things are getting kind of crazy in here
actually
gotta juggle it all lorraine i gotta
juggle it all
i know you said in the comments section
one time i think a while back like
he's got a lot to juggle i think someone
said something i think somebody said
i think somebody said i don't know i
forgot what it was actually but
i think they were being tough on me or
something you know
i think you said he's got a lot to
juggle
i gotta hear spirit of compassion
talking in my ear
i got to make sure i'm delivering
pertinent powerful information i want
you guys getting better
and i know a lot of you guys are
struggling too i could feel it
i could feel it i know a lot of you guys
are struggling
i'm just kind of pressing this waffle
mix into the into here
like that i'm going to drop this cover
boom
let's see what happens sometimes it's a
crab shoot when you're doing waffles
everything just kind of sticks together
and falls apart but it hasn't happened
to me lately it's been going really
smooth
but you know those retrogrades
don't make a lot of things easy all
right so we've got that going
make a little fruit bowl in a minute too
so i'm excited you guys
if you just came on that's cleanse the
heel i mean it's an amazing sale right
now on amazon
i'm not in control of the pricing it's
16.99
the information in here is life-changing
i was asked
write a book write a book for years this
is one of the legendary medical medium
book series books right
here it's called cleanse a heel book
take a look when you get a chance
try to find it free at the library if
you don't have the 16
the last thing i want to do is break
your pockets that's why i don't do
the subscription charges and holding
withhold information from you guys
that's why i don't package up programs
for you guys i want you guys to have
access to it all and i know everybody
tells me
you know what no one appreciates it
that's what people will say out there
marketing people
trying to contact me be like how come
you need to know you need to charge
charge
charge and then they buy it and they
they they actually appreciate it because
they spent lots of money i said don't
insult my people
i said don't insult them so i said to
actually a marketing person that reached
out to me marketing person i said don't
assault my people
they appreciate it having it for free
are you kidding
they do the information it's life-saving
they appreciate the books being on sale
they appreciate all that you don't need
to charge them 500 for some program or a
thousand dollars or something for them
to appreciate it don't insult my people
man
they told that's not how they work um
so being
vegan or plant-based is not an answer
it's not an answer
being healthy keto clean animal protein
carb free is not an answer it's not an
answer being carnivore not an answer
it's not being pescetarian
is not an answer it's not being
vegetarian
is not an answer it's not
there's still bugs in everybody's system
no one knows how to clean them out
they're still toxic heavy metals in
everybody's system their livers can
still be stagnant and sluggish
in everybody's system you can be
plant-based
and your liver be still stagnant and
sluggish and stuck
fill the toxins everybody's eating too
much fat
on top of it the plant-based people
they're fat and
they're fatting themselves to death they
are it's all fat in the plant-based
movement
let me have my peanut butter let me have
my cacao let me have my
walnuts let me have my walnuts let me
have my cacao powder
let me just you know let me have my
peanut butter right let me have my oil
let me have my coconut oil right there
right there's the olive oil right there
let me have my coconut oil
okay let me have my nut milks i'm vegan
i'm vegan
i'm vegan it's i'm vegan a plant-based
i'm vegan all's gonna be good all's
gonna be fine i got the secret i finally
got it got the holy grail i'm vegan i'm
plant-based
by the way if you're vegan or
plant-based stay vegan stay plant-based
but learn how to do it right learn how
to do it right
can i have dates in the morning i prefer
not to in medical media morning cleanse
but of course you can
at least they're fat free so if you
wanted dates in the morning
i would throw dates in a smoothie if
you're going to have dates in the
morning
get them blended up so you're not
gobbling them down
all you know all thick and pasty right
and concentrated
throw the dates in the smoothie and
blend them up that's what i recommend
yeah you can have dates if you do it
that way
so i'm vegan i got it all down i got it
all down
i got a beeper here start it back up
so it's not the answer
i'm keto i'm keto can't tell you how
many times i hear that i'm cheeto i got
the holy grail i'm tito i'm keto
i'm keto animal protein i got the holy
grail i'm unstoppable i'm gonna get
better i'm losing weight i'm keto on
keto
you don't got the holy grail dude you
don't got it
i'm keto vegan i'm keto vegan
i got the holy grail no you don't you
got a plastic cup
a plastic cup you'll end up pissing in
at the doctor's office is what you have
that's what you got that's what you have
i call them keto i'm keto animal protein
i got it down i got it down
i got the holy grail no you don't got
the holy grail you got a plastic cup
you're going to be pissing in at the
doctor's office just like everybody else
down the road
and you're going to be sick because
everybody gets sick
they all get sick you can be plant-based
and boom you get sick you can be animal
protein keto and get sick
and now you're at the doctor's office
you're peeing in a cup
and you're getting your blood drained
from you all the time you're getting all
your blood drained from you
right cooking some waffles right now
let's make some make a little fruit
salad too
let's do that get a little bowl out
that's what we're doing make a little
fruit salad i got a bowl here
your liver needs a chance to cleanse you
guys your liver needs a chance to
cleanse
it does desperately needs a chance to
cleanse keep that in mind
it doesn't want to be bombarded by fats
every single morning your liver does not
want to be
slammed by the fats every morning
it doesn't even want to be slammed by
the fats at all
but we're taught to do the high fat diet
we can't run
from it we're stuck with it we're stuck
we can't get out of the fat free diet
we're stuck
that's how it works out there there's a
way to get out
you know i mean the high fat diet we
can't free ourselves of the high fat
diet
that's what it is
we can't free ourselves if we're stuck
in the high fat diet
that's what it is our liver does not
want to be bombarded all the time it
wants to get a break our pancreas
doesn't want to be bombarded
i love this whole lymphatic system talk
oh my god if i hear it one more time out
there
lymphatic system lymphatic massage
lymphatic drain it's all your lymphatic
system do these supplements for your
lymphatic system your lymphatic system
can't drain
can't clean can't unclog can't cleanse
if you're doing fats you gotta be fat
free you gotta at least be doing
fat-free mornings if you want lymphatic
systems to cleanse at all
and that's what's happening out there
it's everybody lymphatic lymphatic
lymphatic
and i even hear somebody every now and
then somebody will peep up and be like
medical medium doesn't even he doesn't
know nothing about lymphatic system
i don't uh uh
okay uh science research is only
stealing all medical mediums information
about why people have chronic illness
uh okay uh you know after it's been
published by medical medium
it's just one out of a million examples
uh no i don't know anything about the
lymphatic system well let me just
give you a little bit of insight if
you're not working on your liver
your lymphatic system is just that's
just a non-issue
either way you can't just work on your
lymphatic system you got to work on your
liver
if you don't clean up your liver your
lymphatic system is going to perpetually
stay dirty
perpetually dirty okay go ahead go get
your lymphatic massage every single day
go ahead do your saunas every
single day okay go ahead keep on working
on your lymphatic system keep on working
on it but guess what
your dirty liver is going to stop your
lymphatic system from ever cleaning
you're just you're going to be in a
phantom world of thinking you're
cleaning up your lymphatic system when
your liver is still clogged and dirty
and someone's not going to teach you how
to clean up that liver so you're never
going to get your lymphatic system
better and that's how it's going to roll
the liver dumps all its junk into the
lymphatic system just you guys know
the 4-1-1 okay the 4-1-1
right there so i got some papaya
basically i just chopped up some papaya
right there
you can do a lot of things you can do
papaya you can cut an orange i got some
bananas right here
when your liver is stagnant and sluggish
there's no doing anything for your
lymphatic system
i don't care who you are where you are
what you're doing
there's no there's no happening anything
happening to you
that's positive with your lymphatic
system your lymphatic system is the dump
for your liver you don't clean up your
liver you you keep a
dirty lymphatic system
chopped up a banana right here i got
some bananas on top here this banana
papaya bowl
you can do this in the morning how about
that don't put
nut milks in there don't put avocado on
there
you can have avocado have it at the end
of the day have it another time
have your avocado at another time do it
then do it later put it on a salad have
some leafy greens
take your cilantro make a big batch of
cilantro right here
right and chop up avocado and put it on
top of a cilantro salad later on for
dinner
put some tomatoes in there i'm not
saying you can't have avocado
keep that in mind you guys hearing a lot
about your lymphatic system out there
it's making you feel left out like
wait a minute someone's got the answer
for my lymphatic system that means
everything
what where what if you don't clean up
the liver
you're never going to clean up the
lymphatic system your lymphatic system
is perpetually going to stay dirty
it's going to constantly stay dirty and
there's nothing you can do you can buy
all your lymphatic system supplements
you can buy all your lymphatic system
whatever you can do all your things you
want to do
but unless you clean up your liver i'm
going to let that cook longer unless you
clean up your liver
are you ever going to have a clean
lymphatic system
the 4-1-1 right there right there
really important to know we're critical
to know actually
all right so that's a fruit bowl i just
made i'm doing some waffles right now
we're covering a lot of important
information heavy metal detox smoothie
right here
it's of emergency spirulina femirji.com
that's the one that's the best i'm not
sponsored by those guys
the lymphatic system is not your gut
it's not your inside of your gut dr fong
good to see you
dr fong will you come on someday i i'll
have you come on
we'll do a split live someday or
something looking forward to that
uh great md incredible md so
what happens is that people have to
understand is that your lymphatic system
is not
your gut gut okay yeah it wraps around
your gut
all your torso it goes down into your
thighs it goes into your armpits your
lymphatic system travels everywhere
and the majority of your lymphatic
system is the center
of your body so everybody says oh well
the gut's where all your immune system
is but first of all
that that's completely wrong how that
works your immune system is all in your
bloodstream the second place your immune
system is
is your spleen the third place your
immune system is
right is your lymphatic system your
bones that's a place for your immune
system too
so it's all these other options but the
bloodstream is where the majority of
your immune system is at
it's in your bloodstream okay and
the what they confuse everybody with
everybody thinks i'm going to take a
probiotic because the immune system's
all in my gut but what they don't
understand it's not in the lining of
your intestinal tract so your immune
system
is not in the lining of your intestinal
tract you got to know that your immune
system is not
inside your colon so i'm going to remove
a part of this colon right here
let me remove this okay see if it can
come out
stomach came out the liver just came out
hey we got a liver in our hands that's
good i'm going to need that for a second
talk about that most of your immune
system is in your bloodstream
this alone kind of makes everything just
fall apart out there
you wonder why years of alternative
medicine
and nobody getting better that's what
happened out there
i watched it for decades years of
alternative medicine people saying you
got candida women
being carried into doctor's offices
because their fatigue was so bad they
couldn't even speak
or sit up and they'd be like you got
candida that's why you're that sick
years of women suffering right and then
here we go the greatest alternative
medicine we have now
out there the greatest altar in medicine
so-called experts out there your immune
system is all in your gut let's just
brainscrew everybody
and confuse everybody inside here
right inside your colon is not your
immune cells
that's not your immune cells so that's
where they're just messing everybody up
so you can buy all their gut health
products make sure you do that
by all their gut health products all
that
because you think you're building your
immune system up all your probiotics all
your
your gut flora products that's what
they're teaching you
right they say because your immune
system's all in your gut
they don't tell you because
maybe they don't even know that that's
not where your immune system is
not inside your intestinal tract it's
not inside your stomach it's not inside
your colon it's not inside your duodenum
it's not inside there your immune system
yeah you have an immune system inside
your lymphatic system
and that wraps around your torso wraps
around your organs and your torso yeah
the majority of your immune system is in
your bloodstream and that enters every
single organ every single blood vessel
there is in the body to make sure you
don't get sepsis and die
that's the immune system yeah there's a
lot of immune system in your lymphatic
system but let's be straight out and
i'll call it the lymphatic system let's
not make everybody think you can swallow
a probiotic and for some reason you're
going to have an immune system develop
inside your colon
it doesn't work okay it doesn't work
like that
so
the misinformation is so great out there
that there's nowhere to see like there's
no way to escape it
there's so much misinformation just the
simple simplicity of this one
the chickenpox virus is the shingles
virus no it's not they're two separate
viruses
so if we have a medical system that
can't get one thing right
alternative and conventional how is
anybody gonna see straight
where's the sensibility going to be
where's where's any of it going to be
we're on the mo we're in the morning
cleanse right here give me a recap i'm
cooking some fat-free waffles right now
here you guys
which is really cool radical fat-free i
talked about the radical fats a
different kind of radical fats milk
cheese butter eggs
fish meat chicken bone broth
those are all radical fats nuts seeds
nut butters peanut butter olive oil all
radical fats coconut oil all radical
fats i talked about that
we're keeping all of that out
important now lemon water 16 to 32
ounces you can do some coconut water
in the morning that's cooking the water
in here right there
you could do some coconut water in the
morning if you want to but let's do the
traditional medical medium morning
cleanse right upon waking
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water upon
waking
wait at least 15 to 30 minutes then
work on that celery juice 16 to 32
ounces of straight
celery juice because you want those
mineral salts the sodium cluster salts
to bind onto the toxins to get into the
liver
and do what they need to do
you want that you can consume fruits
after 15 to 30 minutes after your celery
juice you can consume fruits
which you can which is an example right
here here's a fruit bowl papaya banana
right in my hands
crack open some oranges do that if you
need to
okay crack open some oranges you can do
that
heavy metal detox movie is really a
great
way of doing it so what i would do is a
16 to 32 ounces of
of lemon water first thing upon waking
i'd wait 15 to 30 minutes hit the celery
juice
16 to 30 000 celery's wait a little
while and i would go into the heavy
metal detox smoothie that's what i would
do
right and if you need to do a bowl of
fruit like i said you can do a bowl of
fruit that's fine
if you need something heavier i'm making
it right here it's a fat free option
that i'm making right now i got it
inside the waffle
maker it's a potato waffle you can do
millet as an option
you can do um oatmeal as an option but
keep the nut milks off
keep the avocado away if you want to do
a piece of gluten-free toast and that's
what you want to do
do a gluten-free piece of toast if
that's what you want to do
keep the avocado butter off of it
in the morning keep away from eggs
keep away from eggs too i'm going to see
if this is done
so i'm giving you all the different
options you can do additional water you
can do 16 ounces of water and you can do
16 ounces of coconut water some people
aren't going to have the coconut water
so you can do more water which is fine
but drink another 16 ounces of coconut
water if you can
or minimum 16 ounces of water keep away
the dried fruit
it's okay if some is in there if that's
what you want to do you're still ahead
of the game because there's no fats
going on but try to stay away from it
and don't consume radical fats before
noon if you keep up this practice you
move ahead you move ahead
you really do you move ahead
and that's what we want i want you guys
to heal i want you guys to move ahead i
want you guys to get your life back
i got two really hot waffles in my hands
right here look at that these are the
potato waffles
and wow those are hot those are really
hot let me get a plate
patricia says wow i thought almond milk
was healthy
almond milk isn't how it it is a healthy
option
avocado is a healthy option
nut butter is a healthy option
i know this is hard for a lot of people
it is okay
walnuts are a healthy option almonds are
a healthy option
okay coconut water by the way i'm going
to talk about that in a second don't do
the pink coconut water right
peanut butter is a healthy option if
it's the
really good stuff right not the not the
junk
right but those are healthy options
but when you do them in the morning or
late morning you won't cleanse and you
won't go through that you won't go to
the finish line to heal
that's the problem have your avocado or
your almond milk
at the end of the day have it in you
know have it
in some oatmeal after maybe maybe
afternoon
okay have it in oatmeal for dinner have
avocado toast for dinner
have a salad if you're into fish and
that's what you like to do
and that's what you love to do then have
your salmon
at night for dinner
have it dead but you don't have it
during the morning try to go as far as
you can i try to go
like further like further without having
the avocado i try to do it at night
i'll try to do it at the end of the day
if i'm going to have avocado
okay so i know it's it's i get it
the minute here's what happens
here's what happens i say stay away from
avocados stay away from nut
milk stay with nut butter stay away from
everything and then
instantly and i i get this everybody
feels this way not everybody but most
everybody says wait a minute
thought avocado was good for me he's he
must be wrong because everybody's saying
how avocado's so good he's must be out
of touch he's not advanced at his info
i got some waffles i'm going to put some
syrup on there right now these waffles
are insane gianna oat milk
has a more concentrated amount of fat
versus just
eating oatmeal yes gianna it does
spot on so i got these waffles right
here now i'm going to put a little maple
syrup on here this is
say someone wants something heavier just
like say oatmeal in the morning keep the
radical fats off what you won't see here
is butter
you won't see avocado on these waffles
you're not going to see that i'm
dropping some
some maple syrup on i'm putting a lot of
it on
because it's perfectly fine you're not
going to get insulin resistance
if you don't put on the milk cheese
butter whatever it is the avocado you
don't do that
you got your waffles right there
the key is to learn how to live your
life
and gaining energy from healing and not
from caffeine
not from caffeine abusing your adrenals
that's a big key right there you don't
want energy from caffeine
abusing your adrenals you don't want to
be doing the caffeine and living on that
all your life
and then the the caffeine causing your
adrenals to go into fight or flight
and then we just kill our adrenals over
time as the years go on
you want to get energy from having a
clean liver you want it from having the
medical medium warning cleanse
you want your energy from having your
organs working right
you want your energy from having the
toxins out of your body you want the
heavy metals out of your body
you want your energy from your body
healing working and getting to the place
it needs to be
okay guys you know tag medical medium
medical medium
put your story out there if you want and
how maybe the medical media morning
cleanses helped you like so many
on here i'll post it going ig
bringing tic toc back on bringing
clubhouse back on
we're going to be on instagram in a
little bit tag
medical medium at medical medium if you
guys got things to say so i could repost
sometime i'm heading over to ig i'm
turning tick tock back on i'm turning
clubhouse back on
and if you think you saw the show here
and you don't need to go to instagram
or turn tick tock back on you're
mistaken
for some reason as the day goes on
things start getting a little crazy so
i'll be
i'll be seeing you guys on instagram
love you guys
take care god bless you