[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now
and in this episode today you're really
going to see that when it's coming down
the thyroid cuz that's what we're
talking about today today's a really
exciting show seriously this is um
another thyroid show we did one a long
time ago but we need it to refresh
because I need it to make sure I
dedicate as much time as I can in an
episode to really deliver all of the
information so that's what we're doing
today and as I've always said 10 20 30
years people are waiting for answers out
there they're waiting they're waiting
one year for answers two years for
answers they're just they are waiting
out there you guys know have any of you
waited for real answers and you know it
just it takes time and we're delivering
them and that's what we're doing here on
this show it's so important to know that
when I say hey you heard this here this
is where you heard it you're going to
hear this information here when I see
that I'm saying that so it's important
to know
you know when it comes down to your
healing process you want the right
information you want to know what's
going on so that you're not accidentally
somewhere else hearing something else
like that broccoli is bad for your
thyroid which is not true or that kale
is bad for your thyroid which is not
true and you can get lost in that and
not heal so when I say hey you heard
that here at the medical Medium show
this is where it started or this piece
of information started here you just
know I'm doing that so you get the right
information so that you don't get
strayed or you know you don't stray and
get lost somewhere cuz I'm going to tell
you guys something you know if you
Google or if you got hop the internet
and you look for you know what's the
tallest bridge you know what's the
tallest bridge out there what's the um
what's the deepest ocean out there
you're going to get an answer and it's
going to be a real answer it's going to
be real okay it's going to be accurate
most likely it will be accurate you know
um you can type in anything be like the
tallest mountain and it'll be accurate
what causes Hashimoto
thyroiditis and the only information
that's really out there now on the scene
just coming is because I released the
information that Epstein bar is the
cause of Hashimoto's thyroiditis okay so
what I'm saying is this is where it's
out here for your healing and for your
loved ones healing because the
information is not out there you also
hop on the internet you do a search on
um you do a search on what's good what's
bad for your thyroid and they'll tell
you broccoli cruciferous is bad for you
know the family Cru is bad cruciferous
family is bad for your thyroid the kale
the broccoli the cauliflower
misinformation and so I just want you to
know that it's here for a reason Spirit
offers us information we're going to get
you moving forward this is serious stuff
and we're really going to go into it so
let's talk about it and let's get get
started with the healing now Today's
Show is about mysteries of thyroid
fasten your seat belts get the seat belt
ready okay and do you have do you have
something to drink are you drinking any
you know any green juice or a cup of tea
or some water or some coconut water you
drinking anything you know relax and
then have a little something maybe to
eat maybe have a a date in your hand
maybe have you know a gluten-free
cracker if that's something you like
whatever so I'm totally there with you
so the whole point is today's about the
thyroid millions of people deal with
mysterious weight gain hair loss fatigue
brain fog hot flashes are you guys
dealing with any of that do are you
dealing with any of that dry skin
restless leg syndrome oh restless leg
syndrome you know when people tell me
about that I just feel bad for him
because you know that's rough but what I
what I'm happy about for him is we know
how to fix restless leg syndrome so um
so there is a happiness about it okay
restless leg syndrome dizziness anxiety
insomnia impaired memory depression
menopause
symptoms and it keeps on going and going
and going all those symptoms are blamed
on a thyroid condition and and not you
know you may have a thyroid condition so
I'm going to reveal the truth about
thyroid disorders in this episode so
we're totally on it this this is what's
happening here um I'm going to be in Los
Angeles uh November 5th for the event
we're going to do the light blast and
spirit sends light down and everybody
body head on the crown of everybody's
head it runs through their body it un it
unblocks stagnant energy helps lift
organs in a better place like if you
have a stagnant liver it helps move
people forward ignites the healing
process um helps detoxify their
bloodstream helps change you know the
State of the State of what people you
know are in if they're really highly
stressed out all these things and more
and and it's been doing that since I've
been a the in young age before and after
when I asked Spirit later on when I
started getting a little bit older I
asked Spirit can we do something else
because I I'm seeing everybody in this
in suffering I see they have all these
illnesses so when I was a child I was
telling Spirit what else can we do it
was really overwhelming and spirit said
well we can do the light so um I did the
light in different various times when I
was younger for people and growing up
and so forth and did the light wherever
I could now I'm saving everything I got
my reserves you name it to have spirit
and I do the light ask the events and
make sure we ignite people's healing
process it helps conditions recover it
helps people recover in many ways and
shapes and forms we've had miraculous
miraculous stories of the last couple of
events with the light blast and just you
know hundreds of of testimonials so um
you know look into that
medicalmedium.com and then of course
lifechanging Foods is coming soon it is
coming I am beyond excited I said this
before
I am so excited about it because when
you guys open this up when you open this
book up you it's not the same it's not
the same as books out there right now
it's not a throwaway recipe book it's
not anything like this this is serious
and it has hundreds over 700 conditions
and
symptoms listed in here and what food
specifically helps if it's eaten
properly and it's brought in into the
diet the book is spirit's Masterpiece
I'm not saying mine I'm saying spirit's
Masterpiece not my masterpiece it's
spirit I can't take the credit
whatsoever but it's information head of
the time head of science head of medical
research about what food can do for us
um and also uh there's a infertility
fertility chapter in there and there's a
angel chapter of spirits of spirit you
know giving me information about angels
never been released ever in any Angel
Community anywhere and I'm just so I
can't wait for you to see this and it's
also about how to protect your family
how to protect your loved ones what is
causing problems right now the
unforgiving for Spirit calls it these
are four things you have to look out for
in your life that cause harm in your
health and your loved one's health and I
list them in there first time ever in
history it's listed in a book like this
so I'm just excited I'm sorry about the
the passion I'm sorry about the
excitement make sure you lock a copy
down whenever you can I don't even think
they're going to be in stock when they
come out some of you might want to put
your name on a pre-order um I know you
know I know I'm making my family and
whoever else and friends do that cuz I
want to make sure they don't have to
wait for it um anyway so let's move on
to thyroid thank you for your patience
of even you know dealing with the fact
that I'm excited like this cuz I know
you guys want the information and and
sometimes I just get too happy about um
about all these different things so okay
right on to thyroid let's do it let's go
into it now um here's the deal with
thyroid here's the deal the most
important thing to understand is the
great mistake the great mistake okay
this is the great mistake and and I'm
going to sound like sound funny with
this one again but it's the great
mistake that's buried a knife brought to
the attention of the medical world
communities and everyone else right now
this mistake you're only going to hear
over here and I've I've you know
uncovered this mistake so you can heal
and thankfully from Spirit and the
mistake is autoimmune it's the great
mistake is autoimmune understanding
autoimmune now we're told our body
attacks itself and I talked about this
in other shows but you got to hear it
when it comes down Hashimoto thyroiditis
when it comes down to thyroid conditions
and we're told our body attacks itself
so if we have Hashi if we were diagnosed
with Hashimoto thyroiditis and keep in
mind Hashim Modas is just the name of
some guy a long time ago that actually
woke up one morning went to work okay as
a doctor went to work a patient came in
and he felt their thyroid and he said by
golly I think your thyroids inflamed and
that's all we know today all these years
all these decades it's all we know about
Hashim moous thyroiditis until the
release of the medical medium book okay
till the release of the medical medium
book where thank God I've been able to
um and thank Spirit of course been able
to get the information out there so what
happened was a doctor woke up and one
morning went to work and said well my
patient's thyroids inflamed so
thyroiditis was the name for
inflammation ashim modus was the name of
the doctor and that's it and so we live
by this rule where we go to the doctor I
see people all the time they go to the
doctor and they they get their first
diagnosis and they walk out of the
doctor's office
baffled first of all they're accepting
the fact that they're accepting the fact
that the medical research and medical
science thinks they know what they're
doing or talking about that's not the
doctor's fault it's about research and
Science and they accept it like okay
what does this mean and they walk out
confused baffled totally just don't
understand what's going on and
rightfully so rightfully so I would and
second if I was just someone who didn't
know much about medical stuff but I know
everybody's an expert in their own
fields and they know information about
other things but they may not know a lot
about the medical field they walk in
they get a
diagnosis um and they walk out and they
just got told that their body's
attacking itself that their body is
destroying their thyroid okay first of
all that's not accurate and for the
first time in history we're changing
that or bringing that information and
that's why you guys got to stay you know
you got to stay holding on to the these
these shows because I need you to have
this information cuz you're spreading
the word I hear it happening now the
word's spreading I mean this is a
blessing because we're helping people
and I'm helping you you're helping
others and and that's that's like my
prayers have been answered and they've
been answered with that because when
you're a young woman and you get told
you got Hashimoto thyroiditis and your
body's attacking itself you instantly
plant a seed a seed is planted a
poisonous poisonous
um um seed venomous seed is planted in
the body in the brain that your body has
betrayed you it is cutting your legs
from out from under you basically it's
backstabbing you it's breaking
trust and you go home you tell your
husband you tell your fiance you tell
your boyfriend or you just go home and
tell your best friend your soulmate that
my body's turned against me because
that's what happens I'm watching it
every day and finally I said you know
what something has to be done about this
something has to be done first of all
there's an auto an antibody an auto
antibody that's discovered by research
and science through blood work that auto
antibody is not attacking the thyroid
gland like medical research thinks
instead it's produced by your immune
system to attack the virus called
abstein bar that's attacking your
thyroid the inflammation in your thyroid
is caused by Epstein bar creating the
inflammation the vipin bar is creating
inflammation in the thyroid gland as it
Burrows itself in your body has no
responsibility in attacking itself and
is not by any means never would never
was and it doesn't in any autoimmune
disease or diagnosis that's out there
nowe please take in that information
please because it is
lifesaving lifesaving I repeat okay
because it's the truth and it's life
saving and so those Auto antibodies
they're going in they're going in to get
the Epstein bar they're not causing
inflammation the inflammation already
occurred it's already happening and it
continues to happen with Epstein bar
doing its thing and this is how it's
done
this is what's happening okay it all
starts out with mononucleosis now you
don't even have to remember having mono
because not everybody gets diagnosed
with mono when they're sick in fact not
a lot of people really do it's just
those more bad cases of mononucleosis
where you're just so sick that you go to
the doctor's office and you get your
first mon mononucleosis
diagnosis um relatively most people have
a sore throat for a week and never even
go to a doctor sore throat goes away and
they had a mild kiss Amano and it goes
away and that's it
it goes away get leaves the bloodstream
it hides itself in the liver and sits in
there for a long time until stress
deficiencies immune system uh weaknesses
um anything losses that we go through uh
anything happens emotionally um you know
meaning stress meaning things that break
us down all of that and then with that
you know bad food that we eat and
everything else around bad foods and
then it comes out it comes out and heads
to the thyroid causing
hypothyroidism that's what Epstein bar
does so this is stage three of Epstein
bar it heads to the thyroid and it's not
going to be diagnosable as Epstein bar
because that's only when it's in its
mononucleosis phase all this information
you can only hear here you can hear it
you can just read it in the medical
medium book and in the future books I'm
putting out but this is how it works now
science and research is going to get
there down the road um and they are
going to find out and figure it out and
they are going to work on it and then
maybe this will be remedied some of this
stuff but we're not there yet and it may
take another 20 years so we got to do
something about our health and our
children's health and our family's
health and all our loved ones and we
have to do something and we have to
fight for this a little bit have to
fight what's for what's right and we got
to get ourselves better and we got to
protect ourselves because here's the
deal Medical Research Medical Science
doesn't have answers for something you
have to take the blame then you have to
take the blame I'm just telling you how
the system works okay there's a lot of
issues in the medical system that we
know about that are evident that there's
other people talking about this one here
no one's talking about and it's the most
important it's the most important out of
them all it's the greatest mistake of
all time in medical history it's it's a
greater mistake than even when they you
know when they were blood letting even
when they were blood letting even when
they you know when poor George
Washington first president of the United
States was blood leted to death over a
sore throat okay I mean that was a
horrific mistake without a doubt but
this mistake here is affecting millions
of people millions of people so what
happens is Epstein bar enters into
thyroid slowly over time and some people
it happens faster depending on their
immune system deficiencies and how much
heavy metals they have in the body and
what kind of foods they're eating and
what kind of stress they're under it
Burrows into the thyroid causing
hypothyroidism okay so that's what it
does and it can do a few other things in
some people's body bodies um the the
immune system okay tries to take calcium
and protect you and wall off the virus
and you might get a nodule that's from
calcium being make these little calcium
prisons being built around the Epstein
bar to stop it and that doesn't hurt us
at all
and it's there to stop the Epstein bar
when your Epstein bar gets better and
your thyroid is getting better and you
do things to do to take care of yourself
like I've seen hundreds do and get rid
of their Hashimoto and their and their
hypothyroidism and their nodules those
nodules go down and clear up and um
sometimes they Le leave a little bit of
a little Scar Tissue behind or something
like that but they can clear up there's
no question now since research and
science doesn't know what's wrong with
you the best way the best out is to say
you have H otus thyroiditis and your
body's attacking itself that's the best
out because you have they have to put
the blame on you not the doctor the
doctor's not putting blame on you
doctors are you know all doctors are
good good people they go into the
industry to help people I know some
amazing doctors in fact without them we
wouldn't even have Epstein bar on the
radar Epstein bar it was named after two
doctors that discovered it now if they
didn't Discover It Spirit would have
just you know would call it a different
name of a virus is what's Spirit would
have done if it was discovered just like
some of the viruses that Spirit does see
now that we don't have names or tags for
that when we do scan spirit and I do a
scan we see different viruses in people
that have no names they're not even
discovered by research and science but
Epstein bar was and by two brilliant
Physicians they were
underfunded so the whole point is is
that it was discovered and that virus is
responsible for Hashimoto thyroiditis
and the best way to get kind of past all
that for the industry is is to blame it
on you it's autoimmune your body's
destroying itself so this is just so
important for you to know it really is
now let's talk about some things let's
talk about symptoms mysterious weight
gain hair loss fatigue brain fog hot
flashes dry skin restless leg syndrome
insomnia impaired memory depression
menopause symptoms anxiety dizziness
those are Epstein bar symptoms not
thyroid problem symptoms they get
classified as thyroid condition symptoms
by practitioners that have no clue It's
Perfectly Normal rightfully so that
Epstein bar is causing those symptoms so
that's another mistake we have on the
Block the only real symptoms you can get
from a thyroid problem are just very
mild fatigue at best and temperature
fluctuations temperature
fluctuations that's at best with a
thyroid symptom the symptoms people
experience that are being blamed on
thyroid right now by the best functional
doctors and everything else those are
Epstein bar the fatigue is Epstein bar
the heavy fatigue the brain fog is
Epstein bar the hot flash is Epstein bar
heart palpitation Epstein bar and I and
I in different shows I've explained what
these symptoms and how it goes um tentis
ringing in the ears Epstein bar in The
Labyrinth of the inner ear restless leg
syndrome abstein bars uh affecting the
central nervous system insomnia in the
central nervous system once again being
affected by Epstein bar impaired memory
neurotoxins once again affecting um
neurotransmitters depression neurotoxins
from epine bar once again creating
depression affecting
neurotransmitters um menopause symptoms
like heart palpitations and and hot
flashes and weight gain all Epstein bar
Epstein bar sitting inside the liver
Epstein bar causing trouble these are
all stage three and stage four Epstein
bar
symptoms you guys might want to listen
to this show again you got to go to the
archives and hear this one again because
I'm going a little faster on you so you
might not even be able to take notes
because I want to make sure we get what
we got to get in the show so just bear
with me you got your seat bels on let's
go let's go um we're putting the pedal
to the metal here all right these
symptoms are all Epstein bar related
symptoms blamed on the
thyroid yes there's thyroid problems and
we see it in thyroid testing even though
thyroid testing is
Antiquated it's antique it's Antiquity
there's no doubt someone told me you
know where I got the antique thing
someone told me like a while back they
said I'm totally the ant into
Antiquities that's what they said to me
right and you know and and I think
that's really cool cuz things from the
past is really cool so I was like hey
that sounds great you know um I like all
that and you're like you know um do you
know anything about antiques that's what
this person said to me and and I said I
you know I mean Spirit knows all my
information in life comes from Spirit so
it all all comes from Spirit there's
really nothing I've kind of been able to
learn on my own I've just had to learn
everything from Spirit in my own life
and like oh I do know something about
antiques from what Spirit has taught me
about all kinds of different things but
I'm not a you know expert and uh and
person said well do you you know what do
you know that's about antique and I said
well how about whoa and it hit me how
about the uh outdated information that
gets put out fresh every day how about
the the information on Hashimoto
thyroiditis that's in the top thyroid
books literally is is ancient history if
if they don't realize the body doesn't
attack itself and EP bar is causing the
thyroid and you know literally ancient
history anything coming out brand new
about autoimmune ancient history that's
an antique already coming off fresh off
the press okay I just for warning you
guys is is what I'm doing by the way so
you don't so you don't get fooled that
your body's attacking itself the last
thing I ever want you to do is think
that cuz it's disastrous so those are
the Antiques that I'm seeing and that's
why I talk about that a little bit more
because it really really triggered that
into that area so let's talk about how
the thyroid Works a little bit thyroid
produces some hormones it produces you
know thyroxin and and and that's what it
does it produces hormones it gets
signals by T TSH from the pituitary um
pretty straightforward research and
science actually has that down and
that's what's great about research and
science because they do have pieces to
the puzzle thank God and when it comes
to you know heart surgery and it comes
to those kinds of things and when you
break a leg there I mean you need them
car accidents you need them when it
comes to chronic illness they fall short
it's simple as that it's that's that's
that's where we're at right now and
human history with with science and
research in medical in the medical world
so okay so you know we know how that
works with the thyroid that part okay so
that does work like that but testing for
thyroids is still outdated and
Antiquated when you go to the doctor's
office and you get some blood drawn and
you know your numbers are there they
show your numbers um and you know
thyroid profile and the doctor says well
you have this or that or you have no
problem it's really not easy to to know
because the minute you go to the
doctor's office your adrenaline is
running a little bit even if the
doctor's office is the most favorite
place on in your life to go like you
know say it's even like meditation some
people say I just love my doctor visits
because I love my doctor and um so even
if you're in that state but the minute
you get a blood test the minute the
needle goes into your
arm okay the minute it goes
in Adrenaline fires off the adrenals
pump they pump ferociously even if even
if it's for 10 minutes or five minutes
they pump ferociously and that
adrenaline confuses and cancels out TSH
readings thyroxin readings you T3 T4 you
name it all the testing that we have
today gets boner totally boner from that
alone Disturbed from that alone now you
would have to get a blood test once a
day for 30 days and then the average
number be taken from all 30 days to give
you an
idea of a closer
number number one and even that's not
going to secure us because the
adrenaline ran all 30 days when you got
the blood test let see how it works and
and this is this is one of the problems
we have with blood test it's one of the
reasons why a so many people have a
hypothyroid problem or or they have
hypothyroidism and it doesn't come up on
the tests but they have Epstein bar and
all the Epstein bar symptoms and they
have all the thyroid related Epstein bar
symptoms and it doesn't come up on the
test they got the temperature
fluctuations they got the basic thyroid
symptoms and then they have all the
Epstein bar symptoms I was talking about
and it doesn't come up and they're told
it's all in their head or you know go go
somewhere or head to a lime doctor and
get a fake diagn get a false diagnosis
of Lyme disease so because those blood
blood blood tests don't work either
those are really insufficient too from
the best Labs I talked about that in the
lime La the lime show about lime labs
and blood works so I talked about that
you should you should listen to that
show again someday if you guys ever you
know if you've missed it maybe this is
the first time hearing any of my my
shows and so you got to check that one
out so what happens is there's an
inconsistency with blood testing all on
its own all on its own and this is a big
problem with blood tests and how it
works um so let's go into a couple of
things things that are really
important and um one is thyroid
medication so I'm sure you guys are
curious in this department thyroid
medication now thyroid
medication um isn't prescribed to fix
the problem so it's not prescribed to
fix the problem
because no one knows the thyroid is
inflamed from Epstein bar originally
they just go by the numbers you know
thyroxin is not being produced um is
being under produced TSH is being
overproduced so then thyroid medication
is prescribed so your TSH comes
down and um and so that's the game but
really it has nothing to do with fixing
you or your thyroid technically your
thyroid still hypo or hashimotos
thyroiditis it's still hypo or has
thyroiditis that can't change unless
someone wakes up someday and says wait a
minute you got a viral condition to your
thyroid we have to address it we have to
kill off the viral condition we have to
clean it out of the thyroid we have to
recover the thyroid we have to restore
the thyroid and until that happens which
is not happening anywhere else it's not
happening in other books I've seen it's
not happening in anything else going on
until that
happens then we're going to fix our
Hashimoto then we're going to fix our
thyroiditis then we're going to fix her
hypothyroidism and then we're going to
fix her hyp hyperthyroidism which I'm
going to talk about in a little while
too this is why I'm speedy speedy today
because um there's so much to talk about
so you're given you're given a
medication the medication you think you
you're fixing your thyroid you walk out
of the doctor's office and your thyroid
continues to worsen over the years cuz
no one ever got the Epstein bar
out and a lot of people get worse when
they take a thyroid medication because
it's a steroid and when it's a steroid
some people react to it so they can't
take a thyroid medication steroids tend
to make viral conditions worse so they
end up getting more heart palpitations
more symptoms and then there's a small
crew people that can handle a steroid an
additional steroid in fact it actually
helps suppress symptoms too it
suppresses some symptoms in people with
Epstein bar related symptoms because
it's a
steroid and you know and they're not
they're it's suppressing symptoms even
though the epscene bar could be getting
worse but the symptoms are being
suppressed because they're not as
sensitive of people there's some people
hyp sensitive that can't handle that
kind of steroid and they instantly start
reacting now so thyroid medication I'm
not saying you you don't you don't have
to take it or whatever it's a Band-Aid
the the deal is where you want to go
with it all is you want to work on the
problem itself even when you're taking
your thyroid medication so that someday
you can talk to your doctor and ask your
doctor to help wean you off and see
where your numbers are again even though
it's difficulty to even get the right
number when your adrenaline's pumping
you know it's like white coat fever you
go to the doctor and your high blood
pressure goes I mean your blood pressure
goes up and start to go high I know
hundreds of people who go to the doctor
and they and they all of a sudden look
like they have hypertension they go home
and it's gone it's White Coat Syndrome
every and that happens when you get the
needle in your arm it's like kind of
White Coat Syndrome the needle goes in
and the adrenaline pumps and it cancels
out the blood test so we don't get
accurac full accuracy blood tests but we
have to go by whatever blood we can and
whatever blood test we can regard this
is some kind of background because we
got no other choice the bottom line is
you go to the doctor and you talk about
weaning
off weaning off and and um the
medications with your doctor's
permission and him you know him being
supportive and her being
supportive if you're working on
recovering your thyroid if you're
working on recovering your thyroid and
so when you're doing you know taking
action and that's what we're talking
about today so that's an option for you
you can also keep your thyroid
medication going and still recover your
thyroid and work on your your thyroid
and still do that that's something too
but talking to your doctor is always a
great thing no matter what when it comes
down to that now here's the
deal um
hyperthyroidism let's talk about that
for a little bit hyperthyroidism is
Epstein bar there's over 60 varieties of
Epstein bar I talk about that in the
medical medium book you guys probably
have read it and seen it um but 60
varieties of of of Epstein bar some of
them are a little bit more aggressive to
the thyroid
and they get into the thyroid and they
because they're a little bit more
aggressive the thyroid produces cells
not to attack itself in fact far from it
it
produces tissue thyroid tissue and
cells because the the Epstein bar is
being so aggressive see so it's the
Epstein bar attacking the thyroid not
the body and this what this does it
sends the opposite direction going on
and it sends you into the hyperthyroid
thyroidism play place that piece of
information doesn't exist anywhere else
but here um once again I've been saying
that like I said so that you don't fall
in you know for something else that's
not going to get you better so for
hyperthyroidism it's still Epstein bar
related now um it's one thing to
understand and you can heal
hyperthyroidism and then there's some
people who have um two varieties of
Epstein bar three varieties of Epstein
bar you can pick them up along the way
you can get them when you're a child you
can get them from your mom and dad you
can have them in your system you can get
them from your first boyfriend first
girlfriend you can get them in college
you can get them you know down the line
and that we can collect a few you can
get them in a restaurant when you know a
chef Cuts their finger because it
happens all the time and you just you
just get them and when you have more
than one when you have an you some
people have two and they'll be both in
the thyroid and one will be creating
hypothyroid one will be creating hyper
that's just how it works um now let's
talk about something that's interesting
if you had thyroid
cancer that's a variety of Epstein bar
that specifically causes thyroid cancer
Epstein bar creates breast cancer uh
causes breast cancer I'm the first one
ever to bring that information into the
world and it's finally being researched
um and talked about a little bit and
then you know as far as the thyroid goes
thyroid cancer that's caused by Epstein
as well um you know we have an epidemic
of Epstein bar and I call it an epic
demic because it's really that epic at
this point in a bad way but the bottom
line is if you had thyroid cancer and
you had your thyroid removed um there's
it there's still a lot of positives with
that a lot of positives um I'm bringing
to light for the first time about how
positive it is if you did you know lose
your thyroid it's not a negative thing
because you can't get rid of all your
thyroid the best surgeon can't remove
your whole thyroid I was even talking to
Dr Christian northr about this when um
when you know I was talking to her
recently and both of us were talking
about that because she you know she's a
an amazing doctor one of the best
actually out there that I've ever met
ever and um and she said no you you
can't get all of that thyroid
removed um it's not possible and so so
lot of tissue gets left behind could be
even 1% could be 2% could be 3% that
tissue produces thyroxin and it also
tells the body you still have a thyroid
regardless see so anyone who has had
their thyroid removed understand that
you your body believes you have a
thyroid it does you should kind of go
along with that and tell your body hey I
do have a thyroid it's not missing you
believe I don't meaning to your body
your body doesn't believe you know
that's missing so so you you know that
the body thinks you have a thyroid you
have to go along with that it's
important because why because your
body's picking up traces of thyroxin
traces of thyroxin that's what the
body's picking up and and it it knows it
knows something so and same thing if you
if you had radioactive iodine and just
you know the radioactive the radioactive
iodine treatment that kills off your
thyroid wears off after a while and you
start getting your thyroid back always
remember that and it never kills off the
thyroid completely it's another thing
another thing that's so critical you
guys critical to know and you can bring
back your thyroid after you know having
it killed off from Radioactive radio
iDine treatments so you can you can
actually have your thyroid come back now
iodine let's talk about that iodine
kills
off viruses it's an antiseptic
antibacterial and anti antiviral when
you were being told not to use iodine
when you have hashimotos thyroiditis
another incredible mistake okay now you
don't want to be iodine deficient with
Hashimoto because it can end up into a
thyroid cancer case down the road for
some people who have the variety that
causes it and you just don't want an
iodine
deficiency because that allows Epstein
bar to thrive in the body now you don't
want to have to take a lot of I you
don't have to at all if you think you've
been iodine deficient you can talk to
your practitioner and take a little bit
of iodine but I I like also having like
just a little bit of seaweed a little
bit of kelp in your diet once in a while
some spirulina Hawaiian spirulina um
dols is the best one so DOL uh Atlantic
Sea Atlantic Sea vegetables and they
sell dos and you get a little dos in
your diet if you want you can get a high
quality inent iodine and take one or two
tiny drops or three drops or you you
know you can take even more if you don't
feel like you're reacting at all you can
take a little bit more if you feel like
you're reacting that's the virus
reacting because the virus doesn't like
the iodine it's why they even you they
don't here's the thing they found that
radioactive iodine kills off the thyroid
but they don't know what's happening
they just they just think it's killing
off the thyroid but what it's doing is
it's knocking down the viral
condition and research and science
doesn't know that part yet they just
know that something changes with the
thyroid when they use radioactive iodine
I don't recommend it I don't recommend
the treatment there's other ways to
actually get rid of your Epstein bar and
and head in the right direction and if
you've had it if if you had the
radioactive iodine treatment and you've
been told your thyroids been killed off
it's not killed off and much of it's
alive and functioning and it and it
recharges especially if you do all the
right things you take care of yourself
and you eat right and everything and
things start getting better and we start
knocking down the Epstein bar virus and
things start getting better and it
really helps now I want to make sure I
covered as many topics with this is a
can I covered the thyroid testing I
covered the thyroid symptoms which are
Epstein bar symptoms we talked about the
autoimmune thyroid medication we covered
that we covered the nause Cy and tumors
we covered
hyperthyroid covered the iodine we
covered the missing a thyroid okay so I
think we're getting there I really do I
think this is great cuz we got talk
about a few other things um let's talk
about supplements for the thyroid zinc
is critical it's the best anti- Epstein
bar weapon because it stops Epstein bar
from proliferating zinc zinc if there's
anything you can take away from this if
I went too fast and I was blasting out
all this information and you just you
know you don't have a chance to listen
to the show again just make sure you
know your zinc is up to par and that
protects your thyroid it helps with
hyperthyroidism immensely with
hyperthyroidism with Graves disease it
helps with goers and Graves disease and
hyperthyroidism zinc is critical good
liquid zinc the one that I I talk about
that's on like my supplements um page on
on the website and stuff if you're
looking for some links to get you to a
place and um so zinc is good B12 the one
I always talk about the B12 is critical
Ester C vitamin C and you could do the
rose hip tea when you take vitam vamin C
and the rose hip te ignites vitamin C it
lifts it up it turns it into something
more that's information out of my
life-changing Foods book that you guys
are going to have in your hands pretty
soon and so that's one thing that helps
it it's it's incredible so Ester C
larger dosages of Ester C you know see
where your sensitivities are at you can
double the dosage from the bottle if you
talk to your practitioner and ask them
practitioners tend to use a lot of
vitamin C and they do different
different things so you know you can
talk to your practitioner say I want to
take a little bit more vitamin C and let
them figure it out with you um spirulina
Hawaiian Spirit Leen a secret weapon
against Hashimoto thyroiditis
hyperthyroidism secret weapon against
thyroid disorders
hypothyroidism um thyroid cancer it's a
great weapon it just helps with the
thyroid in general so it supports the
thyroid in case you're up against
something cat's claw cat's claw talk to
your practitioner about using it you
know before you use it but cat's claw
that's a great one you know the bark and
so the inner bark you know that's a
great one there cat's Claw is incredible
for knocking down Epstein bar helps the
thyroid recharge El tyrosine that's an
amino acid El tyrosine very helpful
Eline because it knocks down Epstein Bar
El tyrosine supports your thyroid Eline
kills off the the virus that's in the
thyroid ashwagandha helpful for the
adrenals and for the thyroid ashwag
Ganda so you know aswa you know ashwa
gandha EPA and DHA non-fish oilbased
because Mercury is not helpful when it
comes down to um Epstein bar so you
don't want to be eating tuna you can
have a little salmon if your your
heart's in Salmon or some hbit or hack
if you're really into fish but to stay
away from tuna stay away from shark I
don't know who eats shark but stay away
from Shark stay away from stored fish
you know stay from that kind of thing um
but you don't want fish oils in their
package State you know in fish oil
supplements you don't want those I saw a
commercial the other day cuz you guys
know how I feel about fish oil about how
bad it is and why it's bad it's
different than eating a piece of fish I
promise you it's entirely different but
um I saw a commercial the other day on
television where you know a doctor was
recommending some kind of brand of fish
oil and it was just first of all it was
just bad fish oil and um it wasn't even
good fish oil second of all it was just
terrifying for someone who has epsteen
bar someone who has brain problems
someone who has inflammation someone who
has brain fog someone who has memory
loss someone who has Alzheimer's
dementia just horrendous for
horrendous um so just you know um hey
look if your practitioner your doctor
offers you fish oil make sure it's high
quality it'll be safer it will be
safer um it's it won't be like as
horrendous as the poor quality fish oils
that I was just complaining about but it
still will be safer but it still won't
be good with Epstein bar make sure you
do plant-based EPA
dhas you Omega-3s um lemon balb it's a
secret weapon right there licorice root
can be helpful for um also the Epstein
bar helpful for the the Hashimoto
thyroiditis and hypoy
hypothyroidism okay and then then we
have Foods so hang in there you guys
talking quick I'm talking fast losing my
breath cuz I'm like rapid fire um wild
blueberries amazing anti-ep bar food
antiviral food helps rejuvenate the
thyroid wild blueberries get the Frozen
wild blueberries celery
juice celery
juice incredible for bringing back the
thyroid and Epstein bar related problems
like a sluggish liver causing poor
digestion intestinal problems everything
celery juice is incredible for the
thyroid
asparagus incredible for the thyroid
really helps clean up the thyroid helps
support it helps rejuvenate it garlic
kills off epsteen bar in the thyroid use
a little garlic every day
radishes radishes I I have a lot of
these Foods right here that are in all
these foods are in the life-changing
Foods book but literally volumes of
information in there about how to
overcome illness with food first time
ever that's been out there to this
degree
radishes coconut oil that's another one
you can do coconut oil coconut products
are okay you know that kind of thing
meaning Co dried coconut from a really
good source could be okay if you want to
play with it but coconut oil for cooking
coconut butter is good coconut butter is
and I'm not talking about suntan
lotion or hair care products I'm talking
about like coconut butter which is the
oil but it's got some of the coconut in
there too you can find some good brands
that have some good ones
kale kale that's what I want to talk
about I want to talk about kale and um
and cruciferous and I want to talk about
Collard broccoli um cauliflower broccoli
rob you know all of those um you know
micro greens that are like kale and
broccoli Sprouts all these are critical
for your thyroid um the F fads and
transs out there which I talk about in
the books and I even mention it again in
life-changing foods but I go more deeper
into it actually um it's a bad Trend
where there was a mistake made where
these these Cogen compounds cogenic
compounds that disarm the thyroid make
it hypo this is inaccurate the same
vegetables like kale have an anti- gorog
genic compound anti- gorog genic um
compound that shuts down the gorog genic
compound that's number one you couldn't
even eat a 100 pound barrel of broccoli
and if you did it wouldn't hurt the
thyroid so instead antiseptic antiviral
foods that help knock out epine bar out
of the body and out of the thyroid that
help rejuvenate the thyroid sulfur are
in these vegetables that help restore
the thyroid and slow down the Epstein
bar kale can help bring your thyroid
back so this is an
example of what's going wrong out there
example you know and it's unbelievable
but this is this is how bad it is I mean
there's times where I'm doing like a
show somewhere or a summit somewhere or
whatever and there's a lot of different
speakers in there like you know whatever
just tons of speakers and someone else
would be talking about how it's bad for
your thyroid without knowing any
information about this that's how
rampant the trends have gone so protect
yourself protect yourself DOL incredible
for your thyroid I talked about that
sprouts and micro greens red clover
sprouts sunflower sprouts peas shoots
amazing for your thyroid hemp seeds the
omega-3 and hemp seeds butterleaf
lettuce the Omega-3s and butterleaf
lettuce and hemp
seeds help clean up the thyroid and help
rejuvenate it spinach lots of spinach
and then there's once again fads and
Trends oh spinach isad fad it's got ayc
acid in it it's it's you know oxalates
you know the whole bit and that's not
true raw spinach raw spinach like raw
spinach in a
salad actually doesn't do that it
doesn't have that in it it's when you
cook spinach then that's when it shifts
and turns into something you kind of
don't want you can cook other things you
can cook other greens if you want but
you don't want to cook spinach because
that changes the structure of the
spinach and you know and that oxyc acid
could become annoying but that's only in
cooked and then they have it flipped
everybody out there has it flipped they
have it when you you're saying you can't
eat raw that's not true the raw helps
heal the thyroid it helps bring the body
back it brings the skin back it builds
muscles it's really high in protein
spinach is one of these god-given gifts
literally one of these god-given gifts
that you can partake in every day so if
you take this list of food Foods
incorporate it into the diet and then
take out the foods that feed Epstein bar
and Quicken the disease process of of
hashimotos or any kind of thyroiditis or
any kind of thyroid problem or any kind
of thyroid disease or thyroid cancer
take out eggs eggs are the worst Food on
the planet for hashimotos thyroiditis
the worst people get sent home from the
doctor's office okay they get sent home
told their body is destroying itself
given a medication that's not fixing the
problem the core of the problem with the
root problem all right and then told to
eat
eggs and that's what's
happening or grass-fed bacon okay so you
know it's that's not good for a thyroid
fix now you can still eat some animal
proteins if you really like high quality
animal proteins but you can't touch the
eggs you can't touch the pork you can't
touch the dairy
products you can't touch the milk cheese
and butter butter I don't care where the
butter was raised it feeds the Epstein
bar you know it's not about what I like
or don't like or what I'm against or
what I'm not against I have no interest
groups that I'm I'm I'm affiliated with
okay and and same thing with all the
supplements and stuff um I have no hands
and supplements I don't it's all about
just you it's just you and what's right
for you the best companies the best
products that are there for you to fix
your problems the best foods I'm not
backing one horse back and another or
against another I'm all for everything
but here's what I'm for mainly is what's
going to fix your Hashimoto if you don't
have Hashimoto if you don't have
hyperthyroidism if you didn't have
thyroid cancer if you're not missing a
thyroid if you didn't have all these
things going on if you're not having
thyroid symptoms or abene bar related
thyroid symptoms then I would say yeah
you can have probably you know um you
know whatever every day or this than
that or an animal protein or even an egg
I probably would say you can have an egg
if your heart's content once in a while
but I still don't like eggs because they
grow PCOS cysts tumors fibroids breast
cancer uh which is epine bar and eggs
just feed and feed everything so maybe I
take that one back don't eat an egg okay
the bottom line is stay away from also
canola oil stay away from corn corn stay
away from corn and canola oil when it
comes down to Hashimoto so here it is
information out there stay here's the
information that's missing leading
that's out there I'm going to recap it
they say stay away from uh you know
foods like and this is just some of the
foods they're actually putting in the
category that are all wrong they're
saying kale collard greens cauliflower
broccoli wrong totally wrong you guys
okay here's another misleading mistake
stay away from seaweed with a thyroid
problem now that's another one that's
developing right there that alone
another mistake your body's attacking
itself when you have aimoto incredible
mistake one of the greatest of all time
in medical history I mean greatest of
all time okay and you know and there's
more okay and then you know and young
people now they think they created their
own problems all the time so when a
22-year-old woman you know gets told
they have Hashimoto Modo they they get
they they hear that they probably
manifested it that's not true either you
didn't manifest it you didn't create it
you know Millennials are being told
they're creating all their problems now
with their illnesses it doesn't work
like that I like using manifestation I
like manifesting positive things I like
manifesting the future I like attracting
good things but it can't be used against
you in a way that makes you feel like
you got a disease cuz you manifested or
you attracted it that's a great mistake
that's occurring right now in our young
people and in our older people whatever
it's happening both ways so just be
careful there you're a good person you
didn't cause the problem and so overall
just go back a little bit your body's
not attacking itself Hashimoto
thyroiditis is caused by Epstein bar if
you had your thyroid removed for some
reason like cancer or anything else um
that's okay you have tissue left that
you didn't even know producing some
thyroxin so your body believes you have
a thyroid make sure you're not iodine
deficient completely so make sure you
have a little bit of seaweed or some
spirita in there so you have some iodine
meaning you know on that level okay look
into some of these supplements all right
I I list these in places on like on my
website so people have an easy access so
they're not lost think about these Foods
stay away from cultivated blueberries
because they really don't offer much and
if you're going to pay that kind of
price for a cultivated blueberry you're
wasting your money go to the freezer
section and get the Frozen wild
blueberry it's a medicine for God's sake
it's a medicine most powerful one we
have on the planet get your celery juice
going get your asparagus in your diet
every day if you can so your thyroid
starts to improve when you go to the
doctor's office realize your
adrenaline's running a little bit when
you get a when you get a blood test so
you might want to just relax and realize
that your test may not be as accurate as
we want them to be but but just calm
down calm the adrenaline down and it can
help get a more accurate test so try to
kind of relax a little bit when you can
at the doctor's office knowing that it's
okay it's okay if you get a blood test
and we'll calm the adrenals down so
maybe we can try to get a more accurate
test all these things I want you to know
and and consider and understand and you
can heal you can reverse Hashimoto's
I've seen it done hundreds of times and
it's being done hundreds more and
hundreds more just from the information
that came from medical medium book so we
want to move forward check out my new
book make sure you grab yourself a copy
when you can I promise you you will not
be disappointed if you're disappointed
I'll probably be heartbroken because I
killed myself making sure that thing was
packed with getting information from
Spirit everything I can to get it in
there check out the medical medium.com
look look for my Live Events and know
that I stand behind you I didn't get
this gift for me it wasn't given to me
for me that's not what happened when I
was young I said to Spirit is this a
gift that's it's this is for me and and
spirit said no this gift is for everyone
else and I was heartbroken when I was
young when I was little heartbroken and
then as I got older I realized the gift
is seeing you heal and get the
information you need I believe in you I
really do care about you and your life
and your family's life with everything I
have I love you take care
blessings