I'm reading about mystery fears and
worries do you know somebody who has
mysterious fears mysterious worries
comes and goes sometimes you get a kind
of a grip on it and you got it in
control you're managing it and then
three months later it's like the fears
come back and then it's triggering some
anxiety and the worries are there too so
I'm reading in the brain saver books
this is an interesting topic so many
people are dealing with this by the way
this is just scratching the surface of
what's in the brain saver books both of
them
sometimes we know exactly why we're
afraid or worried
sometimes we do we like know why we're
afraid we know why we're scared of
something sometimes it feels like it
comes out of the blue though like why
did it happen those unexplained cases of
fear and worry are often due to a past
experience that's been triggered without
us knowing so here's the thing there's
people that know about their triggers so
something they hear something they learn
about or something they experience
they'll know it's triggering they'll
have experience with that but there's a
lot of people that get this mysterious
fear and worry that creeps up they were
triggered but they actually don't know
they were triggered that's an important
detail people don't know out there
because in times of pain our brains put
up healthy productive emotional walls to
help us cope our brains are putting up
emotional walls these emotional walls
are there so we can cope with life so we
can push through these are boundaries
that were not meant to be knocked down
so our coping boundary was never meant
to be knocked down these walls allow us
to get through our days without being
constantly reminded of what's happened
to us because if we're constantly being
reminded of the bad thing that's
happened to us
or something that wasn't good that
happened to us if we're being being
reminded every single minute we can then
be in a state of being that's not good
so there's healthy emotional walls built
inside our brain which I talk about in
brain saver and those healthy emotional
laws are there to protect you so you're
not thinking about that thing that
happened to you every second and if that
wall comes down and we're thinking about
that bad thing every single second then
we're kind of in in another form of
trouble
unresolved experiences remain recorded
in our brains so when we have an
encounter in our present
that invokes the past it can trigger
emotions we felt before even if we don't
understand why so we can get the trigger
without realizing it by receiving
something some kind of information or
running into someone and not realize
that that person's triggering them
and then it happens we have the
mysterious fear worry anxiety feeling
lost feeling sad everything else around
it much of the time those unresolved
episodes involved other people who
didn't Rectify or recognize their
wrongdoings
sometimes what happened was terrifying
extreme or Unthinkable sometimes it
didn't seem upsetting to outside
observers and yet we had our reasons for
finding it deeply hurtful isn't it
interesting
when someone new appears in Our Lives
who reminds us even subconsciously of a
person from the past
we can get in trouble so somebody brand
new
somebody we don't even know we end up
talking to or running into
subconsciously reminds us of something
or somebody hurtful in the past we can
be triggered and not realize it and then
we go down into that rabbit hole
even subconsciously this happens of a
person from the past mystery fears and
worries can Surface a Gateway in an
emotional wall opens because that new
person awakened a memory in the
emotional centers of the brain behind
the wall so here's how it works in the
emotional centers of the brain
a Gateway opens up so you run into this
new person the new person is triggering
because they're knocking down a wall we
don't realize so something we're
experiencing in that moment from that
new person is starting to bring down the
wall that's there to Shield us from what
happened a long time ago in the past
from an experience of another person and
as that wall starts to come down we
don't realize it and then we're in a
rabbit hole we're in a difficult
situation we're in mysterious fears and
worries and other things too like
anything can Surface after that point
bad memories experiences that happen in
the past you know anything that happened
with relationships with other people
whatever it was it can all surface as
that emotional wall crumbles down
triggered by somebody new who didn't
even have an experience with you in your
past someone that didn't even know you
up until that moment and they triggered
you into a bad situation
another source of pagan that can come
back to visit is the trauma of once
being sick or injured
if you've been sick
and you struggled with chronic illness
and you know what it's like to be in
that place and you're on mattress Island
for a long time and you lost friends and
you lost family and you lost things in
your life quality of life and you
struggled and you fought your way back
you got the medical meme information and
you fought your way back to healing and
moved forward
and you can still become triggered
because you can remember like oh my God
I remember how bad it was I remember
I was having a hard time and anybody
who's having a hard time now and you're
struggling it's okay because you're
going to move forward and do your
healing but when you're healed and
you're better you still may get
triggered once in a while kind of taking
you back down memory lane of wow so much
was going on back then after we heal
feeling a hint of a symptom or any sort
of twinge pain can put us back into fear
and worry and I see that all the time I
see people heal a hundred symptoms and
conditions from the medical by using the
medical medium books by the way the
brand saver books
wait you guys have these I can't even
tell you how much is in here
what happens is we heal we get rid of 50
60 symptoms even four or five symptoms
but you can get rid of a lot of symptoms
right with medical meme information and
then if you get one symptom because you
healed 99 of them you're like on top of
the world and then you push yourself so
hard
you get into a new relationship you get
into a new job you get into whatever it
is and you're pushing yourself and
you're burning the candle and all of a
sudden an old reminder of one of the
hundred symptoms start to creep up a
little because you're getting a little
deficient or you're not keeping to what
you need to do or you put aside the
information for months and months and
you start feeling that one symptom
concrete back up as a reminder hey you
got to take care of yourself from what
you learned it can trigger that
experience of being like Oh my God I
remember
or maybe you picked up a new pathogen
and that's what happens to so many
people they heal a hundred symptoms
conditions they heal 50 symptoms
conditions and then they're out on the
dating scene and then they're drinking
off somebody else's glass and then
they're doing whatever and they're in a
public bathroom but they end up getting
exposure from a sink in a public
bathroom whatever it is they pick up a
knee streptococcus a new Epstein bar a
new shingles virus and then they're
triggered into like oh my God am I sick
again of course it means just get back
on get back on the wagon and you know
start working on it do apply what you
need to do the tools but it can trigger
that feeling inside of us
finally if someone has been busy all
their life pushing through every day in
survival mode from a young age without
help or support and some of the stress
finally dissipates and circumstances
improve because of a windfall new job
new career opportunity to take time off
they're nourishing their friendships
their relationships it will take some
time the process past experiences
because that person's not running away
anymore here's the thing when life gets
better you're healing you're getting
stronger you're getting better and
you're not running from your pain and
sorrow
and you're not running from it all of a
sudden
that pain and sorrow can creep back in a
little bit because you're not running
from it anymore life got better
you came from nothing you struggled you
fought your way through or you came from
being sick or you came from some
situation and you fought your way
through and life got better and all of a
sudden you got some mysterious fear and
worry
and some emotions that come up with all
of that the serious fears the wars the
protocols in the book right here brain
saver it's in in this one right here
both books gotta have both books because
it's one massive book
one massive book that had to be turned
into two large books filled with
information
and once you have this you become an
expert come empowered you move forward
with your life
and I know that so many people struggle
with emotional suffering they struggle
so much they've been through so much
whether you've been sick and on mattress
Island for years
and you're working on your Hill you just
started working on your healing process
here's somebody that finished your
healing process and got off a mattress
Island maybe you're somebody that wasn't
sick physically with symptoms but you
were sick physically still
but you were sick emotionally physically
where emotionally you were troubled and
and struggling and gone through so much
either way there's information in the
brain saver books to support you through
the process so you actually become aware
of what's happening with your body your
brain your soul
your physical body and you can persevere
and move past it all
anyway you guys
I'll see you next time