one simplex two shingles
epstein-barr
immune system neurological symptoms
cold sores fever blisters
things that
happen because of viruses like cold
sores fever blisters epstein-barr
shingles like body pain aches and pains
nobody knows that why it's happening
fatigue brain fog where you're like what
what's going on the brain fog really bad
so we're covering all these different
symptoms also how to use protocols what
you see
are
it's supplementation in front of me
right here talking about how to use
protocols right
uh golden golden seal that's one right
there the propolis it's another one
right there so it's really important
including cold and flu
or cold flu and
thou name that should not be said on
here
okay cold flu and i'll name that
now you said
okay because when it's said i get even
more sensor right okay so let's go
we're talking about some great stuff
right here yeah the seaweed hero good to
see you by the way
all right everybody guys this is an
important live because it's about what
people go through right neurological
symptoms they're suffering they're
struggling they're walking around with
all these different symptoms burning
skin jaw pain teeth grinding clenching
jaw
pain in teeth that's really kind of like
undescribable pain in the ears ringing
in the ears popping fluttering buzzing
whooshing i don't know if you guys have
ever experienced that but a lot of
people get the wishing like
and it goes away right and then it will
cause like flashing lights in the eyes
and floaters and blurry vision when
nothing's wrong with their eyes right
all these different things that people
go through
and then fatigue and then the brain fog
and the burning skin and the neuropathy
right and then the itching where you're
not you can't scratch it like i'm itchy
but i can't scratch it it's it's too
deep how about that so julie says no
sound for you over there on facebook oh
yeah i probably you know exactly
check out look
check out twitch i'm live on twitch i'm
live on rumble right now just so you
know i'm live on telegram i'm live on
tick tock live on getter i mean i'm live
like everywhere right now so that's
really cool
so flashing lights that's something you
get tinnitus janet right okay
so these are all critical neurological
symptoms because they can drive people
just crazy people go through a lot about
this lisa box says mm school
so we're here we're live right now we're
talking about neurological symptoms
talking about supplementation michael
scoots talking about supplements about
supple supplementation on how to help
our immune system and how it works so
yesterday i was talking about propolis
and how propolis feeds the immune cells
right it feeds the immune cells
and viruses and bugs hate propolis just
absolutely hate propolis so it's talking
about the propolis you guys know
something about how incredible this
propolis is and this is the vimergy
propolis and how it's it's a
breakthrough it's actually a
breakthrough no no solvent was used no
alcohol no hidden solvent in alcohols
too all the propolises are out there
that do that this is one of its kind
right one of its kind and so are the
other of energy supplements are one of a
kind too for all the ways that they are
but we have like
incredible tools now which is amazing to
think that we have these tools so i want
to talk about canker sores to start with
canker sores
all right so i don't know if you guys
and you know any you know you know
anybody that has mouth ulcers mouth
sores canker sores you guys and maybe
even like cold sores too simplex cold
sore you know they don't know it but
that's it's herpes simplex and you get
the cold source
and
so i want to go into these things a
little bit here smoky mountain paradise
good to see you has dr nesbitt is he
around he might be around i don't know
what he's doing he's on vacation but i
can try to get him here alexandra said
good morning aw hey alexandra good to
see you on facebook i ordered four
bottles of propolis incredible
incredible
i actually placed an order and just
bought some more too
because i'm afraid it's going to be gone
and that might be selfish but i bought a
few more bottles because i'm afraid that
i'm afraid this is going to be gone and
then i'm waiting for it and if i needed
it for somebody like a friend that was
sick or a family member or something or
i wanted to send a bottle to a family
member on the other side of the world or
whatever it is and so i i ordered a few
more bottles of the propolis and
i did i tried not to water too many just
a few because i felt bad because i felt
like you know
you just ordered the propolis yesterday
kristen amazing yeah it it's such a it's
such a game changer and i'll just give
you an example of why i love it just
just to start with right
so let's pretend i had
a cold sore
right here
so let's pretend right so what i do is i
take a paper towel
all right i've never had a cold sore but
i can tell you this from all the people
i've spoken to and spirit of compassion
and spirit
compassion has told me about the cold
sores and what people go through right
a lot of people
they go through
a lot of pain and suffering with it it
isn't just the mouth hurting it could be
the mouth being on fire and hurting but
it's also you can get a little bit of a
temperature pain in your neck pain in
your body when it gets really bad
there's a lot of different cold sores
so it's not one so if you got a cold
sore
and someone else has a cold sore
they're not the same
that's how many different strains of
herpes simplex one are out there right
so say you get your cold sore right
so what you do
if your cold sore is wet
you want to dry it
so you want to dry it with the paper
towel you want it like this
so i'm going to show you this right here
you ordered it as well ronald incredible
incredible so i want to give you a run
down to how this works all right so if
you look at cleanse the heel i talk
about it right in here and i want to
give you the demonstration a little bit
okay and we're going to talk about
neurological symptoms and dizziness and
vertigo 2 and tinnitus and other things
too and what to do but i'm in cleanse
the heel right now i don't know if you
guys have this book a lot of you guys
have plans to heal but it's incredible
book medical textbook get it at amazon
um or go get it free at the library
which i don't care i go to the library
i'm totally happy if you do
and and and that's fine
so
we're in um herpes simplex right here
and i got canker sores but i'm going to
go to canker sores is what i'm going to
go to let's go to canker cankersource
that's what i want to do
let's get it together
okay
so i'm in cleanse the heel right here
and she got a little
postage note to tell me where to go
all right
i'm in clenza hill you see canker stores
right there in a close-up this is
incredible i love this camera right here
because we can actually take a look at
this take a look at that can you guys
see that does it go in focus right there
let me see
any better
so you see canker sores right incredible
you guys on tick tock we're just doing a
little camera work right here on this
so you're looking at canker sore
protocol in this book canker sore means
mouth ulcers
little holes on your tongue that burn
and hurt
a sore on your gum line
a sore
a sword that develops
when you have a wisdom tooth bothering
you we're talking about all these
different aspects right
so i'm in cleanse the heel we're looking
at we're looking at the canker sore
protocol
i'm excited about
all right so
in this part right here it'll say
true cause a virus in the herpetic
family that creates mouth and throat
ulcers throat ulcers a lot of people you
guys have sore throats and that's what i
love about the propolis right here okay
and if you just got on here and you're
like what is he holding i'm holding
a breakthrough like a game changer in
the propolis world
and and i talked about it all yesterday
like like all day yesterday it's not
incredible so the true cause of a canker
sore
all right a virus in the herpetic family
that creates mouth and throat ulcers
throat ulcers
right people get canker sores in their
throat all the time and don't know it
and think they just get a chronic sore
throat they get a sore throat all the
time and they don't realize it they got
a canker sore in their throat we're
going to talk about neurological
symptoms if you guys just came on too we
got a lot to cover
all right
so
causes it causes symptoms as mouth pain
throat pain
tingling sensations in the gums and
teeth canker sore virus can do that
and pain on the tongue right
so what i'm doing here is i have the
bottle so let's say canker sores first
we're not going to talk about simplex on
the lip over here anything but canker
sores what you do is you take a paper
towel
right
and if you want to get rid of a canker
sore
fast as lightning
fast as lightning a lot of people a lot
of kids suffer from them everything you
take it take a paper towel dry paper
towel not a wet one
and you dab the canker sore so if you
have a canker sore on your
tongue you dry the canker sore is what
you do
this is information that people can go
to 20 doctors 50 doctors with finger
sores riddle their mouth and not even
know what to do they leave the doctor's
office
they get some kind of mouth rinse
and they're just like what do i do
this is that valuable this information
so you dry off the canker sore
and then
keep your mouth open
and then you put
it right on the canker sore and you let
it sit there right on the mouth ulcer
right wherever that is now if you can't
reach your mouth ulcer
or
your canker sore
if you can't reach reach it
then you squirt a dropper full in its
vicinity so if you got a wisdom tooth
that's coming out or you or a corn chip
when a jagged corn chip went right into
your gum or gum line
and now you got a sore but you're like
what is that it hurts right between my
two back molars
you want to go to the vicinity like that
and be like okay it's on the left side
of my mouth
boom you hit it
that's what you do
and you let it sit there
you let it sit there on that area in
that area you let it sit there that
propolis
same
thing right
if you got a sore throat
and do what your doctor tells you to do
but i'm just showing you what i tell my
family members and my friends
okay
and it's something i would do if i had a
sore throat or what i was saying like a
sore somewhere
and so
now if you have sore throat
and dealing with sore throats you could
have a canker sore on your throat
people don't know this
same thing with people with tonsil
stones
they get sores because of those tonsil
stones starting to pop out right
tonsil stones really being streptococcus
bacteria producing tremendous amounts of
junk and garbage and then it then it um
calcifies
right
so what's happening is you take this and
you put it in there and you have it sit
there in your throat tamara says will it
work for lupus well i'll talk about all
that a little later like neurological
symptoms people with lupus have all the
neurological symptoms immune problems so
this is the propolis so this is the
vimergy propolis i'm talking about i'm
not sponsored
i'm just telling you guys right now
so it's vimergy views and victor i am as
in mary e rgy.com
right and i'm talking about other
supplements too and protocol so i'm in
cleanse the heel right now we're talking
about the kink i see a whole bunch of
people coming on
you might want to watch this from the
beginning i'm talking about canker sores
talking about mouth ulcers mouth sores
canker sores
throat sores
you know teeth pain gum line pain gum
sores all that stuff right so what you
want to do if you can't reach the spot
with a paper towel to dry it out so say
you got a canker sore on your lip
inside and you can't dry it off like
this
and then put the propolis directly on it
you can get rid of canker sores so quick
it's
insane overnight they start going away
when you use a real propolis like
something that's unbelievable like this
right
and you know
right on that spot right
check this out okay
then you let it sit there
and then you do it again
a minute later
you take your paper towel you hit the
canker sore or mouth sore or anything
like that and boom you dry it real quick
and then you hit it with another drop
and you let it sit on there
you do that before bed your canker sores
start to heal overnight they start to go
away overnight mouth sores canker sores
all that stuff now ask your doctor
what's right for you i'm just showing
you what i i give family and friends who
you know call me up i got a cancer store
i got a sore in my mouth
right
so yeah so that's one example now let's
talk about like
herpes simplex one cold sore fever
blisters now propose isn't just good for
the sore
it's good for the virus when the virus
you don't know it is creating all this
hell in your life
like neurological symptoms
like causing cranial nerve inflammation
causing vagus nerve inflammation causing
all these problems people don't realize
trigeminal nerve pain clenching of the
teeth all the time herpes simplex one
you don't need the cold sore virus to
have it it's in the nerves
randa says love everything you do makes
so much sense on facebook thank you
i'm honored you're here truly just so
you know
okay
so tamara says i have cold sore using
tea tree oil is that okay well ask your
doctor if that's okay but if i had
a cold sore i wouldn't be using tea tree
oil personally i'd be using propolis
that's what i would be using
but you if your doctor tells you tea
tree oil you listen to your doctor
anyway
the bottom line is i want to talk now
about the herpes source so people get a
lot of cold sores and so let's go into
the cold sore section here but first of
all we're going to go back and forth a
little bit because i want to talk about
some other supplements involved with
that
but i'm in herpes simplex section right
here so let's get a close-up see if we
can see this and and we were getting a
pretty good close-up before it was it
was amazing so there it is herpes
simplex do you guys see that right where
the post with postage note is
right
so there's a protocol in here this is
cleanse the heel you guys so this is a
book that millions of people have around
the world millions of copies have sold
it's almost in every single country on
the planet
people use it i hear it all the time use
it as the reference books
they use it as the reference guides they
use it as their bible a lot of people
say all of that right this is the
medical textbook cleanse the heel if you
guys don't have it okay amazon.com it's
51 off or free at the library so we're
in the herpes simplex part right here
so anita says which one is for the
tongue and mouth sore so the propolis
you use
on any source that are in the mouth
right
and
here's the thing on in other propolises
you will taste the difference right they
have alcohol in them and you'll know it
there's a difference with this one you
don't have the hidden alcohol or the
hidden solvents
it's the first of its kind you cannot
make a propolis without alcohol and
hidden solvents by the way it's not it
can't be done
first time ever it was done and that's
how incredible this is but the thing is
is what vimergy did
they did it and they left over 50
percent of the active quercetin
and other
incredible polyphenols right
now people say why not take a quercetin
supplement because it's dead
you can't really bottle corsetin that's
why medical medium doesn't talk about
quercetin all day long because it has to
be in its living form
quercetin is is practically useless
actually it's useless in a
supplementation form on its own so
everybody says well i'll take my course
and the reason why you don't see me ever
talk about quercetin is because it
doesn't work
but when quercetin is left in its active
state in a living form in the propolis
the resin itself that was that was
designed by the bees
from
from gathering it from tree buds the the
quercetin is actually alive and active
and real it wasn't baked and cooked and
run through the mill
so just so you know people who love
corsetin or think corseton's good
this is the first time you're going to
be getting a course attendant actually
works even though it doesn't say corsa
10 it says propolis
it's the only place to get quercetin
that's active and alive
so that's a piece of information all in
its own that's mind-blowing that's
mind-blowing
in the world of health
like you know i mean
it's just it's just crazy how it works
so we got the herpes simplex we're
talking about that right now um clearly
clearly nature cool handle right there
on youtube good to see you can you
explain why the propylene glycol glycol
is bad because propylene glycol is
alcohol it's an industrialized alcohol
that's why it's bad so what it does is
it destroys the active constituents that
are actually in proplus
so your propolis
is destroyed
with the alcohol in it propylene glycol
if that's in your
propolis your propolis isn't living
anymore
that means your quercetin isn't living
anymore in there that means it's not
even a fraction of what it can do
that's just one the other is alcohol and
tinctures burn holes in stomachs
i've said this for years so alcohol and
irritates everything irritates the
linings irritates the nerves irritates
you don't see alcoholic tinctures
recommended by medical medium
information because spirit of compassion
told me since day one they're the worst
and it's why people don't heal when they
do herbal remedies that have alcohol in
them that's why they go to their next
naturopath and people have done this
stuff for years they go to another
naturopath another functional doctor
another guy another guru another healer
and they're taking all their teachers
all this alcohol in them and just
getting sicker
sicker
each other says vimorji is so incredible
they really go above and beyond for us
because they care about the chronically
ill
so you say i'm so grateful for them they
really have taken my healing to the next
level every time i can't wait for the
propolis to get here hopefully today so
let's talk about the herpes a little bit
before we get cruz in here okay um on
rumble lee says hi
hi lee
i love rumble
all right
so we're in the herpes simplex section
here there are many strains of mutations
of herpes simplex one you guys and
almost every single person if not every
single person has one strain inside
their liver somewhere hiding out and
will come out or not come out or it all
depends on what's going on but a lot of
people gather a lot more than one strain
that's the whole thing with herpes
simplex 1.
herpes simplex 1 and herpes simplex 2
symptoms that can arise from these
viruses including fatigue you can get
fatigue from herpes simplex 1 in your
system not even having the sore jaw pain
ear pain pain in the lower neck pain in
the lower neck pain in the upper neck
pain in the back of the head pain in the
genital area bladder pain and
inflammation sore throat mild fever
mouth sores sores on the genitals
adjacent areas in many cases someone is
actually dealing with shingles and it's
misdiagnosis herpes simplex one or two
but still these are all herpetic viruses
and in here
okay you'll see a protocol right here
and i'll give you give you a close-up on
this protocol right here right so
there's the protocol you can't see it
it's probably a little blurry but i'm
trying to show you
right and
and in this protocol
okay you'll see propolis it says five
dropper folds twice a day or dab on the
herpes source so i want to show you this
right okay
so
if you have a cold sore if you don't
have a cold sore but you but the virus
is creating problems and making you sick
that's another story right
but you know and i'm going to show you
also in the shot glass so you take the
paper towel and you dry off
your herpes cold sore
and then you put the propolis right on
the herpes cold sore right here so at
least you can start killing
the sore where it lies here even though
this the virus is still in the system so
that's why it also says take five
dropper fulls of propolis twice a day
twice a day so you're taking five
dropper fulls right here
okay
you guys people traveled around the
world to enter my office just so you
know i've been doing this for 35 years
people traveled around the world coming
to my office
praying to god they can even talk to me
it was a sad situation to see that many
sick people people being carried into my
office
because they couldn't walk and
this information
okay
is really important i mean this could
change lives for so many people natalia
says aw what about propolis and water
base
doesn't work
for a lot of reasons
it goes rancid and ferments and goes
south
and that's
and okay first of all any propolis that
says it's in water-based it's just in
water-based is still an alcohol but
they're not saying it's an alcohol or
it's in solvents
that's a whole thing too unless you take
propolis yourself that you harvested
from a bee hive and then you mixed it in
water
but but but
that's another story and i don't think
that's what that is if they're selling
it is prolific and water-based it's not
purples and water-based you don't have
to disclose here's the thing you don't
have to disclose all the wrongs about
propolis in the world no one's keeping
after that that's how like
problematic it all is and that's why the
vimergy
uh people did a different thing
selena says what supplements would you
recommend for visual snow would it help
this condition i floaters i floaters are
a herpes virus that's what i floaters
are so it's one of the herpes family
members ebv can create the eye floaters
even a little bit of simplex all those
neurotoxins so we're we're talking about
that kind of thing and we're talking
about neurological symptoms so let's go
into this a little bit more so we're in
i want to go back to canker source for a
second here too okay
so we're in the canker sores
all right
canker sore viruses
and we're in here now so we're in canker
sores so i just want to show you
it says propolis for kinkosaurus three
dropper folds twice a day
so it's not just you dab it on the
kicker store you can you can dab it just
right on the canker sore if you want
you can do that but you can also do
three dropper holes twice a day you can
do the protocol now i want to give
everybody a little window in this when
you look at cleanse the heel and you're
learning about this and seeing the
protocols try not to just jump to the
protocols
try to read the section before the
protocols read the supplements section
like all the information the do's and
don'ts what to look out for the link for
this book is in the bio and the link for
this book is in the description right
there
the life-saving book it has a history
and street cred of saving lives millions
of people have it around the world
and amazon's selling it dirt cheap right
now because they
they i think they you know what i think
it's angelic intervention personally i
think at the same time maybe they're
trying to price it so low that i don't
i don't get my 10 cents for it but it
doesn't matter you can go to you can go
to the library and get it for free or
amazon 51 off us but the point is it's a
medical textbook critical information so
what about propolis mixed in honey
okay
so it's in either way if someone takes
propolis and they mix it in honey that
means there must be alcohol or solvent
in your honey
i'd rather take a propolis that doesn't
have a solvent or alcohol one that's
high grade at the highest grade possible
with active
polyphenols
and 120 milligrams per serving then
actually take a honey that someone
slapped in some alcohol and solvent
propolis and mixed it into a whole bunch
of honey
that's just something i probably
wouldn't want to do of course you do
what you want to do
right
um
lacey game says why
i can have it too much how why i it when
i have too much vitamin c it gives me
canker sores
what kind of vitamin c you have an
ascorbic acid
that's a whole other problem so let's
talk about vitamin c just for a second
because we we actually
i'm just looking here at this
okay so this is this is another reason
why vimmergy does what they do so i just
want to just run this by you guys
vimergy doesn't
package up ascorbic acid now i'm not
going to name all the brands out there
that have all ascorbic acid including
that one that has a packet they got the
packet so let me get my
uh urgent packet out let me get my
urgent
packet out
and they don't realize that urgent
packet is garbage it's straight ascorbic
acid of the cheap kind right
straight ascorbic acid you take too much
of straight ascorbic acid vitamin c and
yeah you will literally you could you
you could break out with canker swords
you could get a stomach ulcer you can
hurt your stomach right so the microc
is not ascorbic acid so it's not all
this it's not all ascorbic acid
then that's the difference right there
so the germ theory hoax layer which i am
honored you were here because you tend
to leave youtube comments like
mmm really is
stupid or mm is dumb
and them is
doesn't know what about anything and
then does it know right so i'm honored
to hear a germ theory hoax slayer
so you say herbal products were made
with alcohol for thousands of years and
they worked really were you there
because i'm i'm confused there were you
there thousands of years why they worked
or didn't work because everybody had a
lifespan of 35 years old back then
so i'm just curious how good did they
work and who even had access to them
that's what i'd like to know too right
and here's another thing too
was anybody up against the bugs we're up
against today no they weren't there
weren't any labs out there creating new
bugs left and right and releasing them
into the environment
how many strains of herpetic family
viruses were there then none
none so we got all these engineered
viruses now that are making everybody
sick and making everybody have
neurological symptoms
they didn't have that back then
that's a whole thing on its own and
try not to get confused with thousands
of years ago and that being like this
blatant statement if it means everything
worked a thousand years ago are you
kidding emperors died of mercury
poisoning
emperors
emperors in china
emperors around the world kings
in great britain
died of mercury poisoning or went insane
because of murky poison because they
used to give them all they gave all the
kings and queens and emperors
they gave all the the ruling class a
thousand years ago and more they gave
them mercury tonics you got sick you
were given a mercury tonic oh maybe they
put alcohol in there too that's great
they give you a mercury alcohol tonic
and then you went completely insane
that's actually known out there so let's
kind of not get confused by everything
so great a thousand years ago or 2 000
years ago
all right
thank you
all right let's go into this a little
bit more you guys we're talking about
cleanse the heel
right here and that leads me to the
whole copper thing too we won't go into
it too deep but copper vats in india a
thousand years ago to keep amoebas from
not filtering you know taking over the
water
actually helped for as far as killing
one amoeba but what people don't realize
you got copper poisoning again you died
at 50 years old or 40 years old copper
poisoning so it's like okay let's we
just got to kind of like we got to get a
grasp about how things work out there
got to get a grasp all right so we're in
canker source i'm looking at different
so goldenseal is an option right there
so i got the golden seal goldenseal is
another incredible
supplement
that's really important so when i when
what happens is you have to realize when
you go into like herpetic family viruses
like shingles and herpes and cold sores
and canker sores and epstein-barr
you have to have the antivirals that's a
big deal you have to have the antivirals
that's the thing
so when it comes down to that
if you don't have the antivirals because
that's what's happening with people
people they're dealing with all these
viral issues neurological problems you
think people just magically have a
neurological problem is it because of a
past life like why do they have a
neurological problem
now why do they have severe severe brain
fog and aches and pains their neck is
killing them but nothing's really wrong
with them why are they suffering with
burning skin and vertigo and dizziness
because they got these pathogens
and these pathogens are causing problems
so we have all these different pathogens
we got the herpes cold sore virus that
causes all that trigeminal neuralgia we
got the shingles virus that creates all
that trigeminal neuralgia too so these
are herpetic families they sit inside
the trigeminal nerves you guys they can
actually sit inside the brain stem
is what they do so
what we're doing right now is we're
talking about
ways to deal with that now part of my
time is teaching doctors just so you
know okay
so part of my time is teaching doctors
so i have conversations with doctors on
the phone okay
and in meetings
about
why people are sick
so they're learning now and they're
learning more and more about these
neurological conditions the brain stem
inflaming and doctors didn't know your
brain stem can get inflamed
that's actually recently as far as i'm
teaching doctors that stuff i've tried
to teach that throughout the years about
the vagus nerves brain stem right but
it's kind of brand new for everybody
when your brain stem is inflamed and
your vagus nerve is inflamed and your
vestibular nerves inflamed and facial
nerves inflamed all these are inflamed
all these cranial nerves you get all
these problems you get the ticks and
spasms and the aches and pains and the
jabbing pain and the popping in the ear
and the ringing in the ear and the
dizziness and you get the balance issues
in the tight tightened chest where you
can't breathe
you just can't breathe you don't know
what it is and you don't know if you're
having anxiety attack or not these are
inflamed nerves right
and that's what they are if you guys
just came on here talking about
neurological symptoms now we covered
canker sores please watch this from the
beginning when you get a chance covered
what to do with canker sores and cold
source and herpes simplex cold sores
so and we're talking about
supplementation what you see in front of
me is vemorgy products that i'm not
sponsored so this isn't the kind of
thing where it's just the best stuff
that's out there so if i was to hide the
best stuff that was out there and didn't
want to show it how would anybody
actually get
like that chance to actually really heal
in so many ways let's cover shingles a
little bit shingles likes to sit
in the spinal nerves it likes to sit in
the sciatic nerve it likes to sit in the
lumbar so people have a lot of shingles
viruses there's different varieties over
30 varieties of shingles viruses right
shingles will create a lot of problems
like that neuropathy issue
plantar fasciitis
neuropathy
pain down the leg piriformis issues a
lot of people out there they'll have
piriformis problems right they'd be like
i don't know what it is but i just can't
i can't do anything i can't walk right i
got this piriformis problem these are
all nerves that get inflamed by the
shingles virus right there a lot of
people have the epstein bar and shingles
and people who are sick with like
neurological lyme and ms and a lot of in
lupus and they have all these sets of
symptoms they get the vertigo one day
they get the ringing in the ears they
get the back pain they get the tingles
and numbness they get the tightness of
the chest they got more than just one
bug they'll have an epstein bar and a
shingles
it's mm school today
so they'll have epsine bar they'll have
shingles they might have a simplex so
here's what happens people walk around
and they'll have one or two simplex
viruses they'll have that are sitting
inside their trigeminal nerve they'll
have an epstein bar they'll have maybe
two epstein bars they'll have a shingles
virus and to boot they might even have a
cytomegalovirus or an hhv6 and sometimes
these viruses move up and people have
problems and sometimes these viruses
move down and they they survive
meaning like they get through their day
but but it's this ebb and flow of this
immune system thing and that's why it's
critical that for instance like that
propolis is such a breakthrough
so kelly says i have shingles now what
can i take for the paint
i'm going to move this over here
yeah
so
i talk about shingles in medical medium
book one new edition right here
kelly can take the book to your doctor
so you're on facebook right there right
so if i had shingles all right
i talk about it in here i talk about
what it does and also
in
cleanse the heel so let me give you a
protocol and cleanse the heel right here
in shingles so you have it
so we're going to find the shingle
section so i'm in a single section now i
want to get a close-up on it real quick
just to show you that it's in the book
even if it's blurry at least you know
it's here so i'm trying to get
everything on here we go got a lot going
on moving parts so there it is it's hard
to see it's blurry but there's jingles
now i'm going to move it up whoa
it's just about bringing it up higher so
do you guys see that
now in tick tock you probably don't see
it so much right
can you guys read that
so it says true cause the shingles virus
is the true cause of trigeminal
neuralgia
so think about that a little bit like
your teeth quenching your teeth grinding
all that stuff okay pain in your ear
pain in your jaw
now check this out too now you guys in
tik tok i'm just showing a close-up over
here so just give me a second if you can
frozen shoulder you see where it says
frozen shoulder you guys
frozen shoulders mysterious frozen
shoulder that so many people get that's
the shingles virus in their system but
nobody knows it ulcerative colitis
right there
many cases of neck pain jaw pain
gum and tooth pain tongue pain burning
sensations inside the mouth burning
sensations on the skin pain in the back
of the head
some migraine related pain mystery
sciatica
mystery lower back pain
neuropathy and a stagnant sluggish liver
there are shingles infections without
rashes and rashes and there are over 30
varieties of shingles all but one
undiscovered seath shingles chapter in
medical medium book i was just showing
you too now there's
a supplement protocol right there just
so you know
and i'm in there
okay so let's go over let's go over it a
little bit so it says fresh celery juice
is one thing it says right there in the
protocol
so
i got a celery juice right here there's
one right here fresh celery juice that's
in the protocol now understand you don't
have to do full protocols in here you
can customize medical medium information
isn't one size fits all it's an answer
to why we're sick but you can do what's
what you feel like you can do you can
take your healing as far as you want to
go but here's why everybody's so
different besides the fact that their
souls are different and unique
everybody's soul is unique another
reason why people are unique is someone
may have two or three viruses of a
different kind another person may have
only one another person may have a whole
bunch of streptococcus another person
may have heavy metals and that another
person may have one type of metal not
the other it goes on forever and ever
and ever
is different varieties of bugs different
varieties of metals different varieties
of toxins and then what happens is
everybody's got a mix of all this stuff
a whole hush pasha mix about with all
this stuff okay and different viruses
have different aggression too so
everybody's different with what's ailing
them so you can customize and go as far
as you need to go so in the shingles
chapter right here
it says aloe vera is something you can
take two or more inches a fresh gel
removed cat's claw is another one so
let's look for the cat's claw i was just
grabbing the wrong one right there so
i think we got the cat's claw somewhere
or it's over here
got the cat's claw right here okay so
i'll give you a close-up on the cat's
claw
cat's claw okay
is make or break for somebody with
neurological line
that's make or break
that's an important one right there
someone's really suffering okay that's
the vimorgy cat's claw though there's a
difference if you run out you go by a
cat's claw i can't say yeah okay yeah
could help a little maybe not so i'll
show you guys on tick tock right that's
a cat's claw okay
so
let's see here
so i'm backing guys
so all right i showed you the cat's claw
so back in the shingles right here says
cats call it two dropper foals twice a
day so two dropper folds twice a day and
you got your little shot glass right
here you can put your dropper holes
right in the shot glass you can probably
catch this on a close-up right here
okay we got a close-up right there
so i just did two dropper folds you add
a little bit of water
and then you got it in your shot glass
so i just showed you guys right here in
tick tock right
okay
and there it is
so
i'm giving an example now if you if you
read this chapter you'll see before for
all the protocols you'll see hey you can
start with just a couple of different
things you can start with b12
to give yourself then the nerve food i
call it like nerve food central nervous
system needs the b12 so that's something
you can start with right there where
it's b12 all on its own if you look in
the shingle section
right you'll see b12 three dropper folds
twice a day so a lot of people have that
sciatic nerve pain they have that
different the different neurological
symptoms so it's critical that the b12
gets in their system right so you can
take it slow you can literally take it
with some salt you can take celery juice
you can start with that you can work
your way up you can work your way up in
dosages you can start with a small
amount of b12 it says three dropper
falls twice a day you can start with a
small amount you can customize it and
work to where you're at and build
yourself up that's how incredible it is
what's the name of the book
it's called cleanse the heel right here
that's the name all right medical medium
cleanse the heel
it's a medical textbook get it free at
the library or amazon.com 51 off it's
only 16 there in the us
and we're doing protocols watch this
from the beginning too someone said uh
the b12 is life changing you take in
michelle l says i take a lot of b12 i
take a lot of b12 too you're on uh
you're on twitch incredible
so
i take a lot of b12 too i do i take i
take three four dropper fulls twice a
day sometimes i'll take two dropper
fulls twice a day
rennes says that cleanse the heel is
your bible
i'm honored that's
quite serious
so jackie says i love the b12 right
there too you can't wait to try the
alisa henry says can't wait to try the
propolis so you guys we're talking about
shingles we're talking about
neurological symptoms we're talking
about herpes simplex canker sores herpes
simplex one two talk about all the
different symptoms people are dealing
with so what happens is right now the
neurological symptoms are exploding and
everybody's just filing into their
doctor's offices with the tightness of
the chest they can't breathe right the
pain the dizziness the burning skin the
jaw pain the neck pain the back pain the
fatigue
and also like the brain fox all these
neurological symptoms so we're talking
about like game changers that's the
propolis
that's the new like the new game changer
it's a whole new level there's no
propolis out there like that i'm not
sponsored just talking about that it's
talking about how ascorbic acid the
vitamin c from vimergy is not ascorbic
acid how ascorbic acid can burn a hole
in people's stomach like make them feel
really sick in their stomach
or trigger something else like trigger
off a canker sore or something because
it's so acidic it just eats away the
linings right so that's why i don't like
ascorbic acid vitamin c so a lot of
people will make a mistake and they'll
take just straight ascorbic acid vitamin
c whether it's in that that you know
other other varieties too where they mix
fat lipids in it which is a bad idea all
of it either way it's not great and it's
hard on the system
so we're going i'm going through here
shingles a little bit more because
people have shingles more than they know
and they have problems more than they
know because of shingles right so i'm
going into a couple other things
licorice root that's another big one
right there licorice root is an
important one so i'll show you right
here close up
and the licorice root
now
licorice root and viruses don't get
along so what happens is licorice root
tends to get viruses sluggish and docile
and they can't handle licorice root the
phytochemical compounds
intoxicate viruses the ones that are in
licorice root so that's why it's a great
antiviral
and that's why it's really helpful for
all kinds of different things that we
deal with that are neurological symptoms
and viral symptoms neurological lyme i
see neurological line but here's the
irony
if you go to a lyme doctor which is
tingles and numbness
and a little fatigue and brain fog
you're walking out with a lime patch on
your back like a lime sticker on your
on your hand a lime bracelet a lime
diagnosis whatever you're going to be
walking out of the lyme doctor's office
with a lyme diagnosis so if you go into
a lyme doctor's office all you need is
just
fatigue
tingles and numbness if you go this is
he was really crazy too if you go into a
gynecologist's office
and you go in there with fatigue and
brain fog you'll walk out with a pcos
diagnosis even if they didn't find
fluid-filled cysts in your ovaries
you'll walk out with pcos i mean it all
depends on what they specialize in
two that's how crazy that is if you walk
into a multiple sclerosis doctor's
office then you've got tingles and
numbness and aches and pains and
dizziness and vertigo you're walking out
with an ms diagnosis
i mean that that's that's also you know
like so when i say neurological line
people walk around with all the
neurological lyme symptoms all day long
they got back pain they got leg pain
they got tingles and numbness they got
weakness in the limbs
they got confusion they got brain fog
they're walking around with neurological
lyme dye you know like all they have to
do is just bump into a lime doctor and
on the subway
you got lyme disease
really what's happening is no
you have low grade viral infections
or higher grade viral infections
chronic viral infections bacterial
infections too like streptococcus can
add to it but mostly the viral
infections the trigeminal neuralgia
viruses the back pain viruses all the
shingles all the herpes all the ebv
stuff cindy reeves says is propolis good
for tinnitus if i had tinnitus i'd be
taking propolis if i had any
neurological symptom i would be taking
propolis definitely okay
that's what i would be doing that's the
licorice right there but if i had
tinnitus yeah i would take propyl so
now if you look in cleanse of healing
you don't see propolis in a lot of the
symptoms and conditions right list one
reason is because the propolises that
have been out there they're hard on
people who are really sensitive so i
only had to use them where i had to use
them where i had to use them i recommend
them but now that there's a propolis
that i don't have to worry about
sensitivities for people now it's just
like whoa yeah anybody with the
neurological autoimmune all of it
propolis is fantastic for right
so yeah
this is all important information
so if you if you i could give you a
quick rundown on some of the
supplementation here right i talked
about the vitamin c a little bit this is
the ly scene right here okay
so high quality all i seen is great for
viruses too andy and anthony good handle
i'm frustrated with all the different
diagnoses tests appointments and all the
different medications and i don't blame
you one bit
i wish i just had one answer and one
solution
i could completely understand a lot of
people have gone to 10 or 20 doctors and
50 doctors and it's what i saw all day
every day for seven days a week in my
office back years ago for decades it's
people that went to 50 doctors again
remember people don't go and see the
medical medium
because
because for whatever reason they go
because they've actually exhausted every
other
angle and
bent have rather docked around the
planet i mean why would you see the
medical medium unless you weren't
desperate i mean people billionaires and
wealthy people around the globe flying
their private jets to try to get a
chance to talk to me because they had
the best doctors in the world to see but
they still couldn't get better and so
that's when you go and knock on the
medical mediums door
right i mean that's and it's also why i
get so much hate it's like i gotta kick
me sign on the on my back because of
that michelle l says labels aren't
answers and that's the thing if you get
a fibromyalgia diagnosis it's not really
a diagnosis
it's a label that someone else will give
you but someone else might give you a
lupus one someone else might give you an
autoimmune one someone else might give
you a lime one it's just exactly what
they but really what's happening is you
have these low-grade viral infections
sarah bear your info healed my vaginal
shingles
i've talked to a lot of women with
vaginal shingles up throughout the years
and it's one of the most
uh debilitating
uh
painful situation i'm really sorry even
gone through that head shingles head
shingles is just brutal
occipital neuralgia oh my god that's
really harsh too you get all the burning
with that and everything a bunch more
but those are the shingles ones whoa
whoa whoa whoa
feel bad for you that you've gone
through that and and
that's the whole point of why i wake up
in the morning is that just to know you
even went through that is just it's just
it's a lot
i'm sorry
um
and it's good to know you're recovering
thank god
so we're here right now we're doing a
live about neurological symptoms we're
till we're talking about kicker sores
make sure you watch this from the
beginning about the kanger sores and
cold swords and herpes swords you guys
that's really an important area to to
check into right we're talking about the
vimergy stuff i'm not sponsored but
these are the supplements i recommend
friends and family and if i didn't show
you these you guys everybody asked me
every day and they dm and say what do
you use anthony aw what do you use
medical medium what do you use so
like you know
but i'm showing them because of of
making sure people have every
opportunity to heal alexandra sophia
says hey
i had
been to doctors and specialists for 12
years chasing my tail into a medical
medium nothing worked until medical
medium to heal i'm honored you're here
bless your heart it's so great
and it's so sad when
people don't realize that out there and
they just love to do a hit job in
medical meeting because
they just don't like hearing medical
medium all the time out there in the
health world and just starts to bother
people
so let's go into the more supplement
land on how this works so i was in
shingle shingles is a big one so many
people have shingles
and so many people have like herpes
simplex one like i was saying in two
without realizing it but we're in
shingles right now so i want to cut into
it lysine is critical for shingles all
on its own so it says here right so
that's the vimergy lysine six capsules
twice a day you can be somebody you
could do one capsule twice a day
you can start with one capsule once a
day you can start with one capsule a
week
you can do what you feel is right for
you to build up and that's really
important deegan allison good to see you
exactly it's just the label
good to see you here so yeah i mean on
youtube right
so lysine's right here so that's an
option nettle leaf is a good one too so
then we got the nettle leaf right
so nettle leaf is a great
herb as well so what i love about nettle
leaf it has anti-inflammatory
phytochemical compounds
and
even though it's probably not out there
yet or maybe they finally talked about
it out there but it's anti-viral on a
mild level but i love nettle leaf
because it's incredible for the
reproductive system so i want to go into
hair loss for women for a minute if you
guys
if you guys got a second right so what
you're going to see coming up and women
have always struggled with hair loss out
there but what you're going to see
coming up is in a massive explosion of
hair loss for women and that's going to
be in this next you know five years so
it's going to be a massive problem
and and you're going to see more and
more and
junky hair skin nail supplements just
don't work they never did
they never will they're just kind of
like one of that stuff where you see
hair
skin nails and then as a woman you're
like well i don't like my hair right now
i don't like my skin right now and i
don't like my nails right now so i'm
gonna buy that hair skin nail supplement
so that's how they do it it's an
industry designed on
psychologically
trying to crack women that's what it is
so the hair skin nail supplements are
it's just it's just rigged it's rigged
to just gaslight women that's what hair
skin nail supplements have always been
it's just a total gas lighting right so
and this is what they've always done
but what's happening is if you really
understand hair loss or hair thinning
and you go in here and you go into like
this book here
so
if you understand i'm going to go into
how i'm going to go into ms msm right
here let's follow methylene i'm going to
go into that a little bit
so
let me find the hair loss section
anyway
[Applause]
and you look i mean there's
some just great conditions meaning not
great to have them but so many great
things in this book
to actually help with people
and their conditions
right hair thinning and loss
so i have a section right here so it
even shows licorice root in this section
it shows glutathione so glutathione is
great let me bring it closer now that we
found out that we can actually do that
so there it is
hair thinning and loss
if you guys can see that right there
right next to it it says gout
next to it over there
guilt and sadness is even in there too
so you'll see ashwagandha so let's talk
about ashwagandha that's a big deal for
hair thinning and hair loss
really big deal so let's get the
ashwagandha out right here okay
so
that's the ashwagandha right there
if you guys can see it clear you guys on
tick tock talking about hair thinning
for women
kelsey box says my hair my hair loss
grew back after medical medium
information
there's a couple of things to know about
hair loss and medical medium information
kelsey bach on youtube hey you made the
live sometimes you miss it remember and
then you leave a comment saying i missed
live
okay so
there's a lot of people a lot of women
that come into the medical medium
community and don't know it but they're
about to lose their hair
okay they had something happen in their
life
like they had something happen in the
last nine months like severe stress over
the plague we just went through
maybe they caught a flu
like four months ago and don't realize
it but they're gonna get the hair
thinning and hair loss later on
okay
a lot of women also have then maybe they
have
a stressful moment
betrayal a relationship breakup
relationship breakups are
infamous for hair thinning afterwards
childbirth
right a lot of women they give birth to
a child
three months later they're losing all
their hair now if they for some reason
just got into the medical medium
community and started drinking celery
juice for the first time
they'd be like oh my god is my hair
thinning because i just drank celery
juice hair thinning happens when
something in your life a year before was
involved or nine months before and if
you're coming into medical medium and
you're doing things you're slowing down
the hair loss and you're saving your
hair
that's why so many people who are in the
medical meeting community with hair loss
right women they actually get their hair
back if they stick with the protocols
and they work on it
so
right here
okay we're in hair thinning and hair
loss and you see ashwagandha three
dropper folds twice a day
and that's the vimergy ashwagandha so
that's that's the best one out there
okay it's only one i trust because
ashwagandhas are filled with toxic heavy
metals lots of heavy metals so
ashwagandha supplements are loaded with
metals
and i can't trust any of them
and metals is just one thing they're
loaded with they're loaded with
fungicides so what i've noticed by
buying all the different ashwagandhas
from the best companies out there and
trying them i tasted fungicide
isn't that interesting
fungicide that means all the
ashwagandhas out there were highly
sprayed with fungicides and then bottled
up
vimergy is the only one
that wasn't sprayed with the fungicides
like all that heavy fungicide so i don't
taste fungicide when i'm using
ashwagandha
so just letting you know so
anyway when it comes down to hair loss
ashwagandha helps the adrenals
and when it's hair thinning
a stagnant sluggish liver
right
along with adrenal problems
when you meet you're missing
critical hormones in the adrenal glands
hair starts to fall out
and so ashwagandha helps to restore the
adrenal glands in women
that missing hormonally start to lose
and when they start to lose that
they end up
losing everything else they lose their
hair they lose other things too
so
he's not sponsored someone's saying uh
affiliate affiliate marketing i'm not
sponsored so let's go back into that a
little bit i don't own the vimergy
company i'm not sponsored i'm not an
ambassador
okay so i'm just letting you know and i
buy my products
i buy them i order i just ordered a
bunch of propolis
but i ordered a few more bottles because
i try not to order too much because i'm
worried about it going out of stock and
then somebody with chronic illness
needs to buy up a propolis and all of a
sudden you know whatever so i'm and and
if you look if you're dealing with
symptoms you should stock up on it so
you have it so you're not out of it so
make sure so i got a couple of a bottle
so i hope you guys got enough of it
anyway
so when it comes down to ash ashwagandha
i want to go into that a little bit so
what ashwagandha does is it helps to
restore the balance
in the adrenals so dr
epinephrine is not your only hormone in
your adrenals
that's not your only hormone
so it's not like okay what boom we just
have adrenaline is complex right there's
a lot of different blends of adrenaline
and so hair loss once those adrenals
start to drop down and break down you
end up with a hair loss because you're
losing critical hormones
adrenals even produce some estrogen
right they produce that so you're losing
these different hormones in the adrenal
glands when we go through stress and
everything else so a relationship break
up something bad happens or do you just
been through a sickness
and you end up losing hair so
ashwagandha is critical so that's just
one right there and i'm just showing you
hair thinning and hair loss the
ashwagandha right here
hell glue
so there's a lot of there's a lot of
different things um
i'm looking at different stuff magnesium
is a great one so ms msm right so let's
go into that a little bit
sets of energy msm right there
and for hair loss it says one capsule
daily right there one capsule daily
so you'll see out there hair skin nail
supplements but they don't have things
that are critical for hair building for
bringing back hair
right so i'm going to show you three
critical things for bringing back hair
msm
right
nettle leaf let me show you three
critical things
and ashwagandha
three
critical pieces for bringing back hair
right there
these three
and
the msm that just came out from bimrg is
really incredible it's got the silica in
it the whole bit carrie says vimergy
supplements are game changing i hear it
all the time you're on facebook awesome
i hear i hear it all the time it's like
i stopped using my vimorgy i got another
brand or i got another thing and all of
a sudden things started changing
so rosalie
cac says i take organic ashwagandha
organic ashwagandha doesn't mean it
doesn't have the fungicides i've
purchased all the organic ashwagandhas
that's the whole point i purchased them
from all the different companies
from all the different places the best
companies and the best known brands
okay
and
it doesn't mean the quality is there for
other reasons and i still tasted
fungicide so i think the whole
ashwagandha world you can have it it's
great to have an organic one with
ashwagandha but it's not everything when
it comes down to ashwagandha because
of that fungicide
that i taste it that's the whole thing
too
so
anyway
when it comes down to
and another thing too what you're going
to say well here's the thing what people
say
it happens all the time i try to
amendment doesn't work for me and they
didn't even have the right stuff
they didn't have the right type of b12
they had cya cobalamin they didn't have
adenosine volume and methylcobalamin
so their meanwhile their neurological
symptoms aren't showing any prove
improvement and they're like i tried mmm
really because you didn't use adenosine
cobalamin and methylcobalamin combined
or really good one right so it's these
things that matter you know you know
it's like oh i tried propolis it didn't
work oh really well you tried one with
alcohol and solvents in it and it wasn't
active
so there's differences here that's
that's why the medical medium
information
is is different than other people out
there so
people say i tried i tried celery juice
they tried eight ounces for a week
i tried the heavy metal detox and they
had chlorella and charcoal in their
heavy metal detox
because someone's like
you need charcoal you need you know
chlorella you need whatever and they're
like i tried the heavy metal thing and
then they just what it is i'm an easy
target easy target to be picked on and i
get it because it's called
discrimination because i hear a voice
and i understand that i accepted that at
age four
then it's not my my first rodeo with
like
all of it with discrimination so it
happens when you hear a voice
and that voice tells you what's wrong
with people and what they need or what
they what's wrong what's happening
what's wrong with the industry and
everything else right and then you
provide that information and it's just
like just like
people just can't handle it
karen says ashwagandha isn't on vimorji
right now
check it out in scenes vimergy.com and
check it out i think it's there
they have one right i think they have
one on there
so you guys are incredible so we covered
a lot of stuff right now we're going to
head off to instagram that's where we're
going next we're going to turn tik tok
back on we're going to turn telegram
back on and then we're going to have
instagram back on so that's what we're
going to do now
tone man says what do you recommend for
chills and hot flashes
i got that information right here in
cleanser hill check it out you'll see
that supplements and dosages ask your
doctor what's right for you guys i'm
just showing you what i would do if i
was sick and what my friends and family
i recommend to okay there's over 200
symptoms conditions in the cleanse to
heal book you got to read it if you can
i know people aren't reading as much
anymore because they're too busy like
they're too busy like
watching stuff on social media they're
too busy you know watching videos and
stuff like that which i love videos but
i know people don't sit down and
actually read books as much anymore they
want quick answers from
you know
whatever the internet they want to hop
on be like okay what do i do for this
doesn't even mean if it's right or wrong
oh chlorella oh that's great let me just
take laurel
what do i need for this did you do oh
charcoal let me take some charcoal uh up
my stomach my stomach what do i need for
this it's just you know i get it you
just go online you think it's all good
and you just dial in something and type
in something and it's like okay let me
go do that
oh apple cider vinegar let me drink a
bottle of apple cider vinegar
on my stomach
after a while my teeth fell out all my
teeth fell out they don't know why their
teeth fell out two years later because
apple cider vinegar just dissolved their
teeth right i get it people hop on the
computer and they're just like
oh my god apple cider vinegar this
person says it's great you guys know
there's like a billion dollars in
investments behind apple cider vinegar
to make sure that there's a billion
people saying how great it is
it's just ridiculous
and then you just lose all your teeth
and whatever and
let me tell you that i should do oil
pulling then all the bacteria underneath
the oil just eats away at your gums and
teeth people just realize that they
didn't realize all that stuff that's out
there to trap traps and trends i'm
heading over to
instagram
and i'm turning tic toc back on telegram
just knowing i love you guys
and
i'll