i was just on amazon live earlier today
right so i just want to let you know
it's a brand new cooking show medical
medium cooking show
and
so what's so different about the medical
medium cooking show to where i do here
on youtube or anything else right is i'm
just focused on focusing on the cooking
tips
and the cooking and stuff like that
focusing on that tips you won't hear
anywhere else tips that i only share
with my family
and friends now i don't even know if i
should share really with my friends
it's just family i have hundreds and
hundreds of tips
no one's ever even heard and you may
hear one of those tips out of a hundred
be like i think i've heard that before
yeah
but you haven't it's all tips you
haven't heard and i was just on the
amazon live cooking show okay check out
the link in the description so check it
out you guys telegram check out the link
in description right youtube check out
the link in the description rumble check
out the link in description right tik
tok check out the link in the
description because i was on the amazon
live show meaning the medical medium
cooking show which is my new show i'm
doing once a week on there it's really
cool because i'm going to show you all
kinds of different things like things i
use and pans and pots and anything else
and different you know things products
whatever they you know that that are
that are not expensive that are on
amazon or whatever you're going to see
me do different things but the cooking
tips too which is really cool and really
fun
so
i'm not going to be talking about a lot
of health stuff like i do on youtube
where i talk about the protocols and and
dosages and diseases and symptoms
conditions but instead on the amazon
live show me talking about all those
little cooking tips man stuff to make
your life better and prove your life
better on a different level things i
don't even share outside of my own
family when i'm cooking for my family
and everything and i say hey this and
that i'll cover a couple of tips now
which is really cool you just watched
maria you said yeah i just watched i
love the mushroom tip really cool really
good what i just made
was something out of the medical medium
cleanse the heel book right here
so it's the mini pizza that's what i
made the mini pizzas just showing you
guys what i made earlier on the cooking
show which is really cool right
okay
these are the pizzas right here these
are what i made
and i'm talking about why they're so
good i'm talking about all these
different things about it like how to
how to make them and all that which is
really fun but honestly in that amazon
live cooking show episode i don't know
there was a bunch of different tips
whole bunch you love the onion tip
marissa says so cool do you guys any of
the other guys see the tips that i was
talking about on there i'm going to
share a couple couple of them with you
here
just just to kind of like let you guys
know what i was doing but i'm only going
to be sharing all these tips though in
the future on the cooking show over
there right
but i still you know but just know this
is
this is the channel that we talk about
like conditions and symptoms and
everything that channel we're talking
about cooking stuff so okay
and it's the first amazon live i did the
first medical medium cooking show amazon
live i did
which was really fun i just wanted
everybody to know this stuff you love
them maria says she love the mushroom
tip
awesome
i'll give you guys the mushroom tip
that's an important one right there
miranda says it was so awesome oh so
glad you were there that's so cool the
link of the show is in the description
just so you know so it's the amazon live
that i just did it's a medical medium
cooking show the link is in the
description so make sure you guys know
make sure you subscribe to that so you
can be there for those lives you don't
want to miss it my next says how do you
access the amazon channel please link is
in the description check it out so you
know how to sign up to my channel
because yeah it's gonna be really cool
and
i talked about out there how there's all
these chefs out there in the world
there's all these great cooks and chefs
there's all these different shows and
everything
but they don't know these tips they just
don't because these tips come from above
you guys know they come from soc so it's
really cool i'm going to give you lots
of tips about every single fruit and
vegetable and herb and spice and leafy
green and wild food right that you know
hey that you can't find anywhere else
that's gonna be fun i wanted to like
give you guys something more it's like
what can i do to give you guys something
more we talk about diseases and symptoms
conditions and how to heal and critical
information all the time what kind of
trendy traps to look out for how to
protect yourself against all the
sabotage right we talk about all of that
what causes conditions and symptoms we
you know you guys know medical medium
information right
but this is even extra this is like an
extra cool thing
is what this is you know cold white
spring is asking is it was it saved i
hope it was saved i hope the live was
saved i think it was so yeah so you can
watch it and catch a cold white spring
you got to check it out and tell me what
you think about the tips
seriously so
let's go over that a little bit now if
you guys just came on now
just a little reminder i made a recipe
up cleanse the heel right here okay i
made the mini pizzas
which are killer they're killer
they're just amazing right the mini
pizzas and cleanse the heel by the way
guys if you don't have this book if you
don't have this book yet in your life
you've got to try to get a hold of a
copy when you can and what's so cool is
amazon is 51 off which is really cool
16.99 right check out this book when you
can or get it free at the library
seriously on tick tock if you guys
you this is what i said on on on the
live too i said anybody who's new who's
never had this book i'm going to give
you a disclaimer right now the
disclaimer is your mind is going to be
blown prepare if you thought you knew a
lot about health if you thought you were
seasoned if you thought you knew
everything out there because a lot of
people think they think that read the
book and your mind will be blown and
it'll start reversing brainwashing
that's been happening to everybody all
through these years it'll start to
reverse that for people so they can heal
so check out cleansing here when you get
a chance
you guys on tick-tock i want to show you
a couple tips right now i want to show
you guys a couple tips right there
almost lost the book but that's why
we're live
so here's a tip right here about
mushrooms that you guys need to know i'd
love to give you this tip okay
so a couple of things about mushrooms
that are really important okay the
bottom of the stem if you see any green
at the bottom of the stem
you don't want that whole that whole box
of mushrooms needs to be tossed out
that's one thing right there here's a
tip that's really good if the mushroom's
pitted a little bit if it's pitted at
all like you're starting to pit
in different spots you see where it's
pit pitting a little bit and you're
getting too much color change
it's oxidizing you don't want to use
that mushroom pick another mushroom that
mushroom's oxidizing that means
that means the cells in the mushroom are
dying rapidly and creating a toxin so
with toxins being created so i'm just
giving you a little bit more on that the
pitted the whole pitted thing that's
that's that's a tip all on its own right
there that's really important two
another thing you want to know how fresh
your mushroom is you just look at the
bottom of the stem and you see how beat
up or shot at the very bottom the stem
is right that's another tip too and some
of these tips you know i have shown
people throughout the year some of them
i haven't shown it's important to know
right
so another tip too is people are just
worried about if the mushroom's wet and
slimy right what if the mushroom's wet
so that's something people know about
that don't have a slimy mushroom don't
work with the slimy mushroom okay but
keep in mind though that's not the big
issue you can wash that slime off the
big issue is if it's pitting
that is the key
it's not the mushroom being slimy on top
that you can wash off with hot water
another tip too wash your mushrooms off
with hot water that's another tip wash
them off with hot water
that's a key that's that's an important
key right there because here's here's
why
because if there's any bacteria on the
mushroom at all
cold water is not going to cover it it's
not going to take care of it
because people chop them up they throw
them in their salads they throw their
portabellas in their salads right you
guys and if you just wash your mushrooms
off with cool water
that's not going to be enough you could
easily get some bacteria that was in the
manure like some e coli
or anything that's on the mushroom so
you want to wash with hot water coming
out of the sink so you've got the hot
water coming down in the sink and you're
washing your mushrooms you wash them in
hot water that's important doesn't have
to be scolding hot lorraine elsa's great
tips doesn't have to be scolding hot
because you can get some bacteria i'm
just going to give you guys a whole
bunch of mushroom dips real quick and
maybe you know some onion tips that i
shared on amazon live you guys just got
on here and tick tock if you guys just
got on here telegram guys just got on
here i just did the new cooking show on
amazon live the link is in the
description just so you know where to
sign up because you don't want to miss
those cooking shows those cooking
episodes you don't want to miss those
then you're going to miss out because
they're stuff i'm going to share in the
food realm
in the cooking tips realm no one's ever
heard before in their lives no no
special chef no amazing chef no
professional chef no cooking show out
there is gonna have those tips i'm just
giving you guys a forewarning so
and that's important to know so we'll go
over them real quick again right the
pitted stuff
the pit it on the mushroom
means the mushroom's getting toxic
because the mushroom's oxidizing and
when mushroom oxidizes it's more toxic
than something else oxidizing
in important important tip if you're
going to wash your mushrooms
you wash them with the hot water you
guys i just did an amazon live just a
little while ago an hour ago whatever on
amazon live that's the new cooking show
it's on amazon live i'm still gonna
still gonna be doing youtube's talking
about diseases symptoms conditions i'm
still gonna be here and telegram talk
about diseases symptoms and conditions
talk about protocols and healing and
everything else
and you know making some stuff here and
there but the cooking show i started
this new cooking show and i'm trying to
fill you in on it it was on amazon live
today subscribe the link is in the
description just so you know i want you
guys to know and in that cookie show i'm
going to be sharing tips
that you don't you can't find anywhere
you can't google the tip you can't go
and find the tip
and
you know what i always say when i'm
watching somebody cooking or something
cooking show or anything i always say
hey wait a minute why don't you tell
them about that tip i know and then i
realized of course they don't know it
the best chefs in the world don't know
the tip that's why they don't tell
anybody so it's important to know this
stuff right so i just gave you a couple
mushroom tips one is wash them in hot
water that's how you can get the food
poisoning if you don't wash them in hot
water with mushrooms manure gets trapped
in there and it doesn't come out so the
hot water can really shock and kill e
coli or anything like that that's
important
the other thing is the pitted the pits
in the mushrooms means it's oxidizing
and mushrooms are more toxic when they
oxidize than other foods so that's just
the mushroom tips off the running right
there okay so we cover that boom you
guys want to know i just made the potato
mini pizzas and i want to show you right
there on tick tock
i want to show you here
yes show you on telegram rumble potato
mini pizzas
awesome
they're really good i eat two of them in
between or during the whole thing so i
want to give you some zucchini tips now
some of the medical medium
community
people right some of you guys know i've
always said this all the time
why do i have missing pieces in my
zucchini why's your missing pieces
okay
there's missing pieces
because i cut them out
the reason why i cut them out
is because it happens to almost
everybody out there
very few people escape this
there's
bacteria
in the spots people's nails have
scratched the skin on zucchini is really
thin when you're in the grocery store
everybody touches zucchini and their
nails go in there and that's it boom
their nails go in there and they usually
even take their nails take divots away
like that
you'll see it in the store all the
zucchinis have these things going in
them and the basically that's incubated
bacteria and viruses from people's hands
in the grocery store they're touching
the shopping carts their hands are
loaded with bad bacteria and viruses and
what do they do
they go and they grab the zucchinis and
their nails just go into the zucchinis
and they're pawing through them and all
the zucchinis get all eaten up like that
so what you do is you find those spots
and you cut them out
especially if you're going to eat those
raw
if you wash them really good to eat them
raw it's not going to help
you want to wash them good but it's not
going to help
because the fingernail went in through
the skin and put it underneath so you
can wash them all you want it's not
going to help you got to cut those spots
out that's a tip right there i talked
about
right there give you another tip let's
talk about the onion a little bit let's
do that
all right so we have an onion here
talk onion
a little bit of the onions
onion talk going on right
so
let's go here if you guys just came on
here i'm talking about never before
heard tips medical medium
on the medical medium cooking show
that's on amazon live i just did it an
hour ago i'm doing it once a week
somewhere around like once a week the
cooking show on amazon i'm gonna be
cooking and making food raw food cook
food all of it
but i'm gonna be sharing tips you've
never heard anywhere anyhow private tips
i haven't had even time to actually
share with anybody because i'm so busy
fighting all you know the disease the
illness and the chronic illness out
there
and and writing the books for all that
right so let's talk about the zucchini a
little bit more
so i have a zucchini in my hand right
here
okay
now
what you'll notice is the flower
you have the stem part where the
zucchini actually breaks off the plant
okay you guys
it breaks off the plant now i cut that
stem part off because it's hard
it was getting hard and i cut it off now
if you have a zucchini that's young
enough tender enough you can cook that
stem to be nice and juicy and good but
here's the thing
it's the butt you want to cut off the
butt
because that little piece right there
gets really hard
and people with teeth problems even if
they have strong teeth or think they
have strong teeth people with teeth
problems over
actually bite into that
and now they lose a filling they lose a
cap
they mess up a tooth they crack a tooth
it's kind of like the olive pit syndrome
i talk about you you know you you're
biting in olive and boom there was a pit
in there and now you're just totally
you're totally bad off right
so you want to cut that hard butt off
because that's where the flower was and
it hardens sometimes it hardens like a
stone
and people always mess up their teeth
because of that little tiny button on
the back of the zucchini right there so
that's a cool tip right there that could
actually save you a big hassle boom it
came off
that's it right there
okay took that off
so that's a zucchini tip that um but i
did a lot more tips like i can't cover
them all right now but let me let me
give you some onion
tip here
jess and to think that chefs on tv and
various other sources always say you
only need to wipe mushrooms with a damp
cloth i never paid attention i always
washed mine but i didn't know about
using hot water thank you script just
you can watch any cooking show i don't
care if it's an amateur cooking show a
totally pro pro cooking show it's on the
tv the chefs don't know these tips they
don't know any of them
and that's what's really cool right it's
not because i'm a special person it's
the same way
the alternative health movement
conventional health movement doesn't
know any of this that's killed people
millions of people worldwide medical
media book series it comes from above it
comes from soc it's not because i'm
special that's why you'll get all these
tips and you'll also get life-saving
information in the books if you guys on
tick-tock don't have the book
forewarning
i'm just going to tell you right now
okay disclaimer
if you're somebody that thinking thinks
you knew a lot about health
right and you're out there on the scene
or whatever it is when you start reading
this be
prepared to have your mind blown so
that's the disclaimer blown so just keep
that in mind
here caroline learn something from you
every time i watch you thank you i'm
honored to hear incredible let's cover
another tip
you guys we're live right now telegraph
live on youtube
lava rumble live on tick tock i'm
excited about this let's go let's talk
about the onion that's where i was
heading earlier okay
and go watch the amazon live when you
get a chance
watch the amazon live
all the tips i'm giving you now are tips
i was doing there and gonna be doing a
lot more the link is in the description
you guys i want you to catch me on all
the channels i'm doing this amazon live
cooking show once a week because i want
to give you guys even more stuff in your
life more things in your life
more tips more answers more everything
with that so it's important so let's
talk about the onion a little bit
so you got the onion right here okay
so
sweetest part of the onion
which nobody knows
is closer to the top of the onion where
the onion was growing meaning where the
onion was sprouting out that's the
sweetest spot so when you pull the onion
out of the ground right when you pull it
out by the green tops okay
right and they cut the green tops off
and then this seals right here that's
the sweet part of the onion it's closer
here so the worst part of the onion the
most bitter part of the onion
is the bottom where the roots were
the bottom where the roots were
that's the
the more astringent not so sweet not so
tasty part of the onion is
keep that in mind you can use the whole
onion without a doubt you can use the
whole onion right so here i am
i'm cutting this part off
you can use the whole onion nothing
wrong with that and here's the top of
the onion right here
that i'm cutting off
okay
so here's the next thing you know i mean
first of all i was talking about right
there now the best part of the onion to
work off of
the best heat because you you might be
making food for family friends you might
making food for people right
and the best part of the onion to work
off of in the meals is off the top side
going all the way down in right that's
the tastiest part because someone may be
like yeah okay you made me a salad but
it wasn't that tasty or it was okay or
i'm sensitive with onions i like onions
but i'm a little sensitive with onions
sometimes and what's really happening
too is you're they're getting the worst
part of the onion in their food so
that's important to know right there i'm
peeling back the onion a little bit
so the best part of the onion is that
top part another little tip too
anytime you see anything brown in the
onion
toss the whole onion
don't risk it
because the onions going bad
going bad
rotten onion
is the worst it can destroy a whole meal
and i talked about that tip all on its
own but you don't know it's wrong it
looks good it might but it has a little
brown spot or it has one ring
one ring is getting brown in there after
you cut it one ring
the other rings look good
but one ring's getting bad toss the
onion don't even save it can ruin an
entire meal or an entire meal for a
family you're making it for whatever a
couple little tips on the onion right
there
i gave some basil tips check out amazon
live for the bazel tip which is really
cool
so when you get a chance
check out the when you go to amazon live
link is in the description description
i'm not trying to send you guys to a new
platform it's that's not it i'm sending
you guys to the medical medium cooking
show which i'm doing once a week it is a
new platform but the point is it's to
it's to send you guys to the cooking
show to offer you all this information
and that's really what it is i mean it's
it's that's what that's what i'm always
saying hey go to rumble because i want
you guys to hear things i can't say on
other on at other places you know so i
want you to go to rumble i want you guys
to go to telegram so you can hear my my
my exclusive messages right i want you
to go to amazon live
right to hear my cooking show because
i'm gonna talk about tips i've never
talked about anywhere else
and i'm gonna talk about things i use in
the kitchen too it's not just the tips
like what towels do i use right what
mashers do i use right i was using a
masher over here for the mashed potatoes
right what strainer do i use whatever
but you know what what tomato paste do i
use right here right all of it
margie says i have your book cleanse the
heel
i went vegan september 6th following a
lot of your advice in this book so you
went medical medium
vegan or vegan before that i'm down 11
pounds and feel wonderful i've been
around a lot of very ill people and i'm
feeling that my immunity must be great
now thank you margie that's incredible
going vegan doesn't mean medical it
doesn't mean medical medium unless it's
information about it incredible but
following a lot of my advice in the book
it went down you lost the 11 pounds
incredible so you were vegan then you
followed advice in the book and you lost
11 pounds right i tell people if you're
plant-based or vegan there's there's are
you medical medium plant-based or vegan
and i tell people who are animal protein
are you medical medium animal protein
right so and because all the details
matter so that someone who's sick as a
vegan can get better someone who's sick
as plant-based could get better
someone's sick who's
animal base can get better incredible so
proud of you lost 11 pounds it's amazing
so you guys
do you have to pay to watch amazon live
tanya you don't
you know
you don't have to pay
to watch medical medium i'm not gonna
start doing that like i'm not gonna
start that unless something changes but
i've always kept and been consistent you
don't have to do subscription fees for
medical medium websites you don't have
to do subscription fees to get the
information you don't have to pay to
watch medical medium you don't have to
do a big program with medical medium in
order to get his information i give it
out i give it out i give it out i give
it out i give it out i don't want
nothing back
i just want you to heal
i just want you to heal i don't want
anything back i mean your support would
be amazing but i don't want anything
back i just want you to heal that's what
i want i want you to heal
so we're covering tips now listen to you
guys on the amazon live show i did
earlier
right i talked about a tip about basil
which is really cool
really cool i talked about a tip about
arugula which is critical the arugula
tip is really a good one i'm letting you
know
so i'm hoping you check that out go
watch the amazon live learn more
okay and i'm going to ig now now i'm
going instagram i'm going to turn tick
tock back on i'm going to turn telegram
back on but i'm going to instagram and
i'll let everybody on instagram know
about these tips i'm going to let them
know about the amazon live cooking show
the new cooking show i'm excited
and i can't wait i can't wait you guys
come over there or hang around i'm going
to turn tick tock telegram back on and
i'm going to be on ig hope to see you
soon