this
and what i was saying one time recently
right you guys saw the post about it
being a game changer for the chronicle
i mean it and there's a lot to be said
about propolis and how it works but the
problem with propolis
there hasn't been really great
propolises out there that's one of the
big problems so i'm talking about the
vimergy propolis right
and i just want to make it clear i'm not
sponsored
but i have to talk about it because it's
that important for the chronic allele i
mean when it comes down to like chronic
illness
pathogens are involved number one right
we don't have a lot of tools out there
a lot of tools that handle certain
pathogenic issues all right
and so propolis is a critical
piece that's missing out there now there
yeah there's propolis out there but
there's next level propolis which is an
entirely different thing now what i love
about
the vimergy propolis is because
sensitive people this is a big deal
people who are hypersensitive
their stomachs are sensitive they're
sensitive with neurological lyme they're
sensitive with lupus they're sensitive
with food allergies they're sensitive
with things
sensitivities
all these years so many people being
sensitive and then the propolis is all
being saturated in solvents and alcohol
out there
so over the years i'd be telling doctors
that person needs to be on propolis make
sure you get that patient with multiple
sclerosis neurological lyme with lupus
with all their aches and pains with
their tinnitus to vertigo all this
different stuff make sure you get that
patient on propolis but the problem has
always been this
different varieties of low-grade
horrible alcohol
right
and solvents
and then low-grade propolis from bees
that aren't being taken care of
watched
right are cared for so this is a big
deal so
so i'm here to talk about propolis for a
little bit chronic illness aches and
pains all the different symptoms right
neurological symptoms all of it i'm
talking about propolis this is the
vimergy propolis right here
in my hand
i don't usually do this i don't usually
sit here this like this
ecstatic like excited because i know
breakthroughs when a breakthrough comes
and i'm all over it right all over it so
that's how that's how serious this is so
i'm actually really excited about this
so i just want to say
people say well vimergy is expensive
well it is because it's not
in the sense we're like for instance
this propolis right here it's only a
little over eight dollars an ounce
there's four ounces other propolises you
get the one ounce bottle
and it's 11
10 for one ounce
ten eleven dollars for one ounce
this is roughly around eight dollars
right around eight dollars for one ounce
but there's four ounces in the bottle so
this is a whole another level of quality
so it's almost four ounces quality
and then what it offers so i just want
to cover talk about proposed for a
little bit so pro what is proposed what
is it propolis what is it right
okay
this phytochemical compounds are resin
created and gathered by bees from tree
buds
so medicine
from trees medicine from tree buds right
that's how incredible it is okay
what it is essentially propolis is like
a glue
that the bee uses to take up spaces and
hives right like any air air coming
through the hives any open spaces so
what bees do is they take that resin and
they use it as a glue
to protect the nests that's what the
that's what the bees do okay
but here's the thing propolis harbors
medicine that's ahead ahead of everybody
it's a head of science and research
that's it like science can
tap into propolis and tap into propolis
and it's gonna take them decade after
decade to find out how many different
phytochemical compounds antioxidants
polyphenols that are in there now the
vimergy propolis
it's done in a way to preserve that
that those phytochemical compounds so
it's done in a way to preserve
the quercetin right to preserve the
crystalline but to preserve the glandine
the preserve these different incredible
phytochemical compounds
right and so that's the whole point it
preserves them
and then it preserves everything else in
that so there's entity the other thing
is there's no alcohol
that's a big deal alcohol destroys
the medicine and i've talked about this
you guys alcoholic tinctures i've talked
about this all the time so alcohol
tinctures alcohol destroys the medicine
now you may be like well this isn't nero
how interesting is this he's talking
about propolis
it makes or break people it makes or
breaks their healing process
with cold source herpes simplex that
gets into the body so i want to talk
about stuff
so i want to bring
this guy in front of me right now okay
and
let me just get
let me get this guy's
muscle
muscles removed here right
so the critical thing to understand here
is when it comes down
when it comes down to propolis right
here we are
all right
so when people get sick what are they
sick with
what's going on well they're sick with
pathogens that's the thing they're sick
with pathogens and they got the toxins
right
pathogens and toxins you guys just came
on here we're talking about about
propolis but we're not talking about
just any propolis talking about a break
breakthrough in propolis and i've been
waiting my whole life for this
breakthrough i'm just letting you know
i'm not sponsored i'm not an ambassador
to the company
i'm not an mlm person
this is an impairment thing this isn't a
game this is about the chronically ill
this is about being sick and this is
about
about companies and this one
specifically that broke the mold they
went above and beyond so this is an
exciting time for people who are sick
so when it comes down to cranial nerves
cranial nerves get inflamed because of
pathogens that's one of the things that
inflames cranial nerves okay and that's
your trigeminal nerve right that's your
vagus nerves
right hypoglossal nerve
okay
so these are some of the vestibular
nerve these are the nerves that come out
off the brainstem people are sick
right they got the ringing in the ears
vestibular problems
they got the vertigo and dizziness right
because of because of inflamed vagus
nerves they've got pain in their jaws
pain in their mouth pain in the back of
their head because their trigeminal
nerves
because of things like herpes simplex
one they don't know or or shingles and
they don't know it okay
they've got the epstein bars creating
all these neurotoxins that their skin
burns they get the pudendum problems
pudendal nerve problems where they're
getting urgency and bladder problems and
pain in their groin they get all the
sciatic problems because of shingles in
the on the sciatic nerve so people are
walking around sick fatigued right
and so there's this medical medium is
about like tools to battle all that all
the time with all the different tools
and protocols right
and then vimergy comes out with a
product with with with a propolis
that takes everything to the new level
and why am i excited because it's more
people gonna get better it's more people
getting a chance to get better and move
forward i've been calling all my doctor
friends
and saying you got to get your patience
on this you got to get your patience on
this
this is the propolis we've been waiting
for it's that big of a deal
right
so deborah says does this help with
neurological symptoms and that's on
facebook deborah yes and that's the
whole point
it's for things like this and that's
what people are suffering from so i want
to talk about like okay let me just give
you some tips here cold sores
putting propolis on cold sores and fever
blisters and canker sores
that alone
is amazing when you have a propolis you
can actually dab onto cold sores
to kill
the bug to help the immune system to
help the immune cells right that's a big
deal
so people get the cold source and the
cold sore virus sits inside the
trigeminal nerve it sits in people and
so what i love about this
is people can do you
talk to your doctor or what you can do
but what i recommend friends and family
okay
anybody that has anything going on if
they had a cold sore that means they
still have the fever blister cold sore
the simplex in their system if they have
ebv they still have it in their system
if they have these bugs they still have
in their system this is something to be
taken every single day
there's the propolises out there are
harsh
they're harsh you guys
they got solvents in them and alcohol in
them by the way we're live on tick tock
we're live on we're live on uh
twitch
we're live on youtube facebook we're
live on rumble we're live on a whole
bunch of different blood words telegram
of course
so
people don't realize is that the
propolis is out there
they're weak there's alcohol and
solvents in there there's nothing like
this right here out there if you just
came on here this isn't an mlm thing i'm
not an ambassador to this company
and i'm not sponsored it's just that
when something comes out that that's
incredible it's about the chronic it's
about the chronic allele and it's about
moving the needle it's about and that's
what's critical about moving the needles
i'm talking about dosages here what you
could do
so
if you do get this talk to your doctor
on how you can take it but this is for
extra sensitive people people who can't
even take supplements
and people who have so much inflammation
in the nerves and everything else and
it's good for anybody and good for their
anybody's immune system
but it's gentle on the stomach which is
a whole nother thing all on its own it
doesn't have the alcohol
it's like a liquid gold is what it is
for what people what what's happening in
people's bodies right now it's really
really remarkable so i'm going to cover
a little bit more about this
so
this isn't just
a game
where people realize supplement
companies and supplements it's really
kind of a big part of it it's a game
it's really what it is you get the cheap
crap you bottle it up you mark it up and
you bank that's what's done out there
the difference between like vimergy is
they actually care about the chronic leo
i know because i've reached out to them
years ago i've become friends with them
and i told you that guys just like i try
to become friends with all the
supplement companies out there but they
don't stay with with their they don't
stay on course they always just go no
it's about the dollar sorry aw i don't
care about your chronically ill people
we're going to bottle up what we need to
bottle up because we're all about
numbers and figures i'm fine done with
you man
but
with vimorgy it's all about okay what
can we do
so this is the kind of people that that
i want a relationship with so i've been
friends with because and they're like
what what do people need
what do they need to heal and so they
put out
a probe list just like all their
incredible stuff right they put out a
probe list
it changes everything because when it
comes down to the whole pathogen thing
people have to if okay if you don't
believe you have a pathogen but you
believe you have a parasite then believe
you have a parasite fine
but i would still be taking propolis
you know that's what i would do so if i
had a friend was like well i got
parasites that's what i got well then
promopolis is what you need lumicali
says can it help with chronic sinusitis
chronic sinusitis is the streptococcus
right it's a lot of different strep
varieties a lot of people carry strep
people carry five different six
different straps in them ten different
straps in them that come up along the
way we go to a public bathroom we pick
up another one off a toilet seat it's
just life here on planet earth right
so propolis is incredible for like
streptococcus for e coli all the
different bacteria c diff each pylori
and it's easy on the stomach people have
stomach ulcers and stuff because
bacteria is eating their ulcers the
propolis is something that can battle
that so what i'm right now what i've
been doing right now between everything
else on my busy schedule is i'm like i'm
calling every doctor like i got just the
roller decks out and calling every
single doctor like hey hey how you been
yep haven't talked to you in a few
months listen
the propolis is critical right here for
people so if you guys just came on we're
talking about propolis we're talking
about neurological symptoms too we're
talking about
fibromyalgia chronic fatigue syndrome
psoriatic arthritis yeah psoriatic
arthritis r.a hashimoto's thyroiditis
hypothyroidism hyperthyroidism we're
talking about all the different symptoms
right
and then you've got the flus
right that are going around that keep on
coming around
i won't name any names of flus or
anything but the flues that keep on
coming around
so
these things really matter
when you think about it for immune
system and everything else right
so
so cindy lou actually that's not true
that's the cindy lou that's actually not
true
not without the solvents i'm just
letting you know singular by the way
good to see you because i know you leave
a lot of youtube comments i read them
all the time um yeah it it's yeah people
are misled
so what you said right there i told it
very interesting what you said
but here's how it works
there's no propolis out there that
haven't been involved with solvents
no problemosis it's the only one to this
day
and the other ones will stay alcohol
free
but they're not
solvent free
and they're hidden alcohols that's how
it's done with propolis
this is the only one
first time in our history where they
said no
we're not gonna hide anything we're not
gonna hide the solvents we're not gonna
hide the alcohol we're not gonna hide
anything and we're gonna make sure we
can do it without that and that's it
santara's healing good to see you so
excited to get this protocol thanks for
always looking out for us
yeah it and you can taste it when you
get when you do a hit of it you know
what's going on it's 120 milligrams per
serving of this propolis okay
right and it contains 50 of its active
polyphenols okay
that's a big deal
that's a really big deal no propolis
company can actually say
that they contain up to 50 percent of
active polyphenols i don't care what
propolis company it is with propolis
product they can't say it and they can't
say they did it without involving
solvents
they can't
that's the difference right here
that's the difference if you just came
on i'm not an mlm multi-level marketing
guy not involved with anything like that
of the sort
i'm not sponsored by vimergy i'm not the
owner of energy i told you that you guys
about that i'm not an ambassador
okay
and it's and i'm not into pyramid
schemes i'm into just making sure
there's good stuff out there for the
chronicle and that matters for what's
happening now neurological symptoms and
i told you guys it's it's exploding i
remember when i gave you a warning about
this
about all the neurological symptoms
ticks spasms
fatigue aches and pains blurry eyes
dizziness vertigo right burning skin
pain in the jaw neck face trigeminal
neuralgia right fibromyalgia all the
different neurological symptoms i told
you guys that in the heart palpitations
that are neurological and i told you
guys neurological symptoms are exploding
like never before so when you see like
darkness happen out there because it's
what it is like darkness and you see
everybody just getting sick with
neurological symptoms and then things
come from the light so then there's the
light that helps to battle the darkness
and that's the difference right so what
it this is it's a light tool basically
babyum says yo aw hey
i was alone in a real dark place with my
symptoms and illness then i found you
your lives i'm honored you're here
fabian truly my heart pours out to you
for what you went through because
you know
because basically what happens and
you're on youtube right there right and
uh
basically what happens fabian is people
don't know what that's like if they
haven't been into that dark they haven't
been in that dark place
and they haven't been there so just know
that you're a survivor and a monitor
here
so someone's asking on tick tock so how
can this help fibromyalgia so first of
all let's talk about fibromyalgia
fiber fibromyalgia
are inflamed nerves inflamed because of
pathogens epstein-barr is the
inflammation creator of fibromyalgia so
if you're somebody with fibro right
and you just your your shoulders are
sore you can't bump into a wall you
can't just go and bump into a wall right
here like that you can't do that
because what happens with fibromyalgia
you get the pain and you get the pain in
the elbows like it just rings in here
rings in the shoulders you can get
fibromyalgia where you just hurt
everywhere you wake up in the morning
and you're so sore and you just you're
in pain if you push it too far
everything hurts those are neurotoxins
floating around because of the
epstein-barr virus that's what
fibromyalgia is and medical medium
published it first and now science
researchers starting to say hey
epstein-barr causes everything now well
you made fun of me for saying
epstein-barr causes so many things and
now you're taking the info
but fibromyalgia is because of
epstein-barr right
this is an antiviral
okay
anti-viral
powerful tool right anti-viral
anti-bacterial but anti-viral
so
it's one of those things where
but it but it's
affordable but it's also gentle
that's the difference it's gentle
and it's the only one
that didn't get run through run through
the ringer of solvents
and the alcohols and the hidden alcohols
no natural flavors no hidden natural
flavors which is happening in all the
supplements now you guys
so this company won't do anything like
that but what happens is that other
companies they hide now all the natural
flavors because medical medium
said that natural flavors has the msg
that's what msg is right it's natural
flavors mm info for years now
and so what happens is so now supplement
companies are they're they're all
nervous oh that medical medium ruined it
for us we put natural flavors in
everything with msg
and so we better hide that now so
they're hiding it so what's happening is
supplement companies in the tincture
bottles are hiding all their stuff and
in the propolis world
they're infamous for hiding solvents and
hiding alcohol
so this is the first propolis of its
time
in this day right now in time in history
right here i'm marking this literally as
one of those freedom power empowerment
you know times in history
for the chronically ill
and so that's a big deal so let me talk
about how you can even use it you can
put it in a shot glass right there you
can put a little bit of water in here
too so i'll put a little bit of water in
the shot glass right that's one way to
do it
you guys on tick tock the link for the
propolis is in the bio
on tick tock the link in the propolis is
in the bio
i mean the link for the propolis is in
the is in the butt profile there so
anyway
yeah you can put propolis straight on
your lisa where you say she puts it
straight on your ex spots amazing you
can put it straight on
cold sores for sure canker sores that's
what i love for people i tell people
people with the worst kanger source of
cold search you know how you get the
kinky sores on the tongue so many people
get that where their tongue is hurting
all those little hot spots on their
tongue
that's a great place to put it too
so that's just one thing right there
but you can but you can here's the thing
you can take it as a daily
daily part of your regimen
to slowly knock down pathogens
so that other symptoms eventually go
away it's one of those tools that's what
it is
courtney may good to see you i saw you
leave some you're on youtube right now
live amazing you made the lives you
caught the live right now because you
always say i missed alive
so
donna short just ordered mine still
confused as to what it does and why so
important okay so so donna when it comes
down to the immune system propolis is
one of those critical key
tools for the immune system
it does different things for the immune
cells immune cells feed on phytochemical
compounds that's how it works so
propolis harbors
phytochemical compounds
certain polyphenols and other
phytochemical compounds any antioxidants
that the the immune system gobbles up
like candy so your immune cells
lymphocytes basophils monocytes
neutrophils your immune cells right your
white count
gobbles up
these phytochemical compounds
that the bees produced
strengthening
the immune system strengthening it
turning it into like one of those
superpowers so when the strep throat
comes you got the streptococcus when you
got the acne because it's all
streptococcus
you're using a tool that starts to feed
your immune system
but it does more than that
bugs don't like propolis so bugs in our
system that keep us sick don't like
propolis on any level they don't like
propolis
hampers bugs down it hampers bugs down
it knocks bugs down and that's what it
does
so that's how propolis works now you can
talk to your doctor what's right for you
but i'm recommending to all friends and
family the whole bit i'm going to take a
little propolis shot right now
amazing
and provost is incredible you can use it
straight in your mouth
you know no problem
if you want if you want
but
what i like to do
and i tell people
you can put a dropper full in the mouth
and let it stay in there if you need to
and that's one thing someone can do but
taking it with water is a great way to
do it ask your doctor what's right for
you make sure you ask your doctor if
it's okay to you know take propolis if
you do
venture into it
it's super gentle that's the whole point
too that what i love about it it's super
gentle a lot of people have
gastroparesis a lot of people have mild
gastroparesis more severe a lot of
people have different problems and
intestinal tract problems too but they
can't take a supplement so you've got to
take the ones that count or the ones
that are gentle
tracy vanderbilt smith love everything
you recommend because what you tell us
works then following your
recommendations for four years god bless
you
tracy that means that
any of the like you know the trolls and
everything else you've hung in there so
so long with all that my husband is off
the liver transplant list
incredible he had damage from a hep c
infection
he takes no drugs and the docs are
amazed unbelievable i have two i have
had two cases of chickenpox in my life
so i am loaded
with ebv can't wait to try this my fibro
and chronic fatigue is under control
because of following your guidelines god
bless you you've been hanging in there
for four years doing the medical medium
stuff i'm so proud of you thank you
tracy for being here
this is so great so you guys i'm heading
off to ig i'm pretty sure in a little
bit well i want to show you one other
thing too that i forgot about the msm
i'm so excited about the propolis i
can't even i can't even
wait can't remember the msm for the
moment i brought it here
so that's the msm with calcium and
silica so anybody who's into msm right
franks and pains and joint problems and
all that other stuff and connective
tissue problems like connective tissue
all that
right and hair skin nails
hair skin and nail supplements right
skin like skin and nail supplements
right they don't work so when when you
go out there and you want to buy hair
skin nail supplement they don't work
i'm just letting you know i've talked
about that so many times for a lot of
reasons because of the quality and
everything else
anyway there's the silica there's the
msm product right for there for anybody
that's that likes msm that uses them msm
it's the best there is out there and
vimergy put silica with it and put a
little calcium with it they balance it
out right and it's the highest quality
msm out there so that's something else
they came out with which is so great
and it helps with people's knees and all
that stuff that i've seen throughout the
years so that's that but back to the
propolis though you guys i can't tell
you how how excited i am about this for
so many reasons but you know what if you
can
i'm gonna head off to
instagram i'm gonna turn tik tok back on
right and i'm gonna turn telegram back
on
um
yeah
you guys you know you know what's crazy
is that
i noticed you're not allowed to like
you're not allowed to like try to get
information out for the chronically ill
you know people just all said oh what's
he trying to sell now well i don't own
the vimercy company and i'm not
sponsored
so
if i came out with a medical medium line
then maybe i would then maybe it would
seem like okay well he's just trying to
sell his medical medium line but
this is just
the bottom of my heart it's the best
stuff i'm excited it's here
and
it's like what do you do if there's a
tool that can help people you just be
quiet it's like okay i'm not going to
tell you guys
you know am i going to be like an
influencer where they're drinking celery
juice in the closet but they don't want
to tell everybody they are so they don't
want to spread the word
oh yeah i'm taking this propolis and
it's helping me heal but i'm gonna
actually say it's something else that's
helping me heal so i could sell
something now
this is incredible letting you guys know
ask your doctor what's right for you ask
your doctor if it's okay for you to to
use it if you ever do um you know if you
ever do partake in in in in the propolis
and so forth right
um but i'm getting friends and family on
it i'm going to instagram i'm turning
tik tok back on
i'm turning telegram back on i love you
guys and vote by the way
amazon live i'm doing today i'm making
sundays i'm making uh ice cream today
making ice cream sundaes
so on amazon live at two o'clock eastern
11 o'clock pacific i'm gonna be on
amazon live
right you guys know my amazon live show
it's the medical medium cooking show
where i have all this different stuff on
there and everything i'm making ice
cream sundaes dairy free but i'm making
ice cream sundaes the link is in the
description links in the profile you
guys at tiktok and everybody here you
guys the link is in the description
right i did it yesterday i did a show
yesterday or okay you should check the
yesterday show too right i did it about
all kinds of different cool stuff but
listen i'm gonna be on amazon live today
two o'clock eastern 11 o'clock pacific
i'm gonna be making ice cream sundaes
and
you guys it's gonna be mind-blowing i'm
not kidding because i'm gonna be making
these incredible beautiful ice cream
sundaes i'm gonna put all this
incredible stuff on it it's gonna be
like you're at a
ice cream place
it's gonna be really fun make sure
you're there at amazon live today with
me okay see you guys on tick tock i see
a bunch of you guys are coming on here
now
you guys i just wanted to let you know
that i'm going to be on amazon live the
link is in the profile okay the link is
in the bio i'm going to be on amazon
live
at two o'clock eastern 11 o'clock
pacific i want you guys to know on tick
tock and i'm going to be making ice
cream sundaes i see everybody coming on
here everybody's like what what's he
doing what's this what's in his hand
i just saw somebody say what's in his
hand what's he doing what did i miss you
guys
what's he doing
so the link's in the bio the link is the
link is in the bio so the amazon live
hey man what's he doing
he's got something in his hand
yeah hot fudge sundaes all right i'm
taking off i'm going going on ig
in a couple of minutes i'm going right
on ig a couple minutes okay and i'm
turning on tick tock and i'm going to
lose all this stuff all right i can't
wait to see you guys i'm going live
again a little bit