on youtube live on facebook it's
saturday night
you guys lots to cover making nori rolls
check this out i got my nori sheets
right the nori sheets you guys got the
nori sheets
got tomatoes i got spinach how much
spinach do you
guys eat in a week you might want to
note that down because a lot of people
don't eat any of it
green onions which is scallions got some
oranges i'm going to show you how i use
that on the nori rolls
carrots i don't usually do a lot with
carrots i almost lost the carrot here
don't usually do a lot with carrots and
for some reason the comments aren't
coming up
so oh there we are coming up great to
see you again too
sunday sunday's in good to see you all
right awesome you guys coming on and
coming on talking about the nori rolls
the whole bit
brook says hi m.m hello
enigma aaw you guys are all coming on
awesome got some red bell pepper here
making nori rolls but we're also talking
about guest get this we're talking about
vagus nerve
i posted a vagus nerve tick-tock video
by the way just letting you guys know
we're talking vagus nerve we're talking
tightness at chest vertigo
talking about epstein-barr reignition
of epstein-barr that's medical medium
information and now science is using it
and so yeah so we're talking about
epstein-barr talking about the plague
a little bit how the plague is knocking
down everybody's immune systems then all
their epstein bars are
cranking up sally arnold oh my god
unbelievable you're here tonight
you guys i don't know if you know who
sally is sally
her story is in thyroid healing
that's so cool sally thank you for being
here she's dear
dear friend of mine it's an honor saw dr
faun come up
uh ashley kevin ashley your videos are
amazing i can't
i can't say it enough your videos are
always amazing i'm a fan
i'm letting you know that i'm a fan um
anyway becky says loving the new book
the new book we're going to talk about
that a little bit in the new book so you
guys are making noise rolls i gave you
the rundown you're all coming on
spina joy rolls we can do a whole bunch
of different stuff
and if you eat animal protein i would
say don't put it in the nori roll i
would say have it on the side or
something if that's what you want to do
or if you're
plant-based or vegan or something we'll
talk about that too if you wanted
avocado
in your nori roll but these are going to
be fat-free nori rolls but they're going
to have all kinds of great stuff in
there you can do potato in there too
letting you know you guys this is the
new edition do you have it this is the
medical medium new edition revised and
expanded i'm going to be talking about
the plague a little bit
talking about how it knocks down our
immune system along with some other
stuff too
and i might bring in a little bit of the
blood draw talk because it's saving
lives right now people are talking about
it
they're talking about it they're careful
they're telling their doctors i told my
doctor half vial
and my doctor said that's perfectly fine
and it saved me and i didn't have i
didn't feel tired i didn't feel weak
anymore i didn't feel like i was sicker
and getting sicker it's
changing people's lives talk about the
blood draw thing a little bit
and um and who knows what's going to
happen so i
got lots of good props so we can talk
about different things it's been really
important
so um talking about vertigo
tingles and numbness tightness of chest
talking about epstein-barr symptoms
talking about epstein-barr it's going to
here a little bit
glad you guys are here might even talk
about eggs a little bit
because can't get enough of it there's a
lot of confusion people say well if you
cook the egg
if you cook the egg then you don't have
to worry you can eat all the eggs you
want
no that's not how it works cooked raw
the bacteria the viruses they're not in
the egg
they're not in this egg no they're not
in the eggs
they're not see they raise pathogens in
the egg they take the top off the egg
like in the video on tick-tock they take
the top off the egg
and they and they they place
the pathogen inside the egg they grow it
and so forth that's what they've been
doing for 100 years right
but when you eat the egg you feed your
epstein bar you feed people are like
reactivated epstein-barr my doctor's
looking for reactivated epstein-barr
yeah medical medium information that's
the only reason why they're looking for
it right
but what they don't know details matter
details matter when you eat the egg you
feed the epstein bar barr
epstein-barr gets re-activated we'll
talk about that a little bit
lorraine oh my god egg confusion is
alive and kicking and tick-tock land
o-m-g
man omg like for real lorraine
it really is good to see you lorraine
lorraine is hard right
it's no fun those trolls they're just
like impossible
ichoda good to see you got the new
edition of my hands
uh making noise rolls karen my daughter
healed her eczema
she's had her whole life thank you so
much
so happy here that that means the world
to me okay that you're on facebook there
it means the world to me we're live on
youtube and facebook right now
it really does because children suffer
with eczema
and all science research cares about its
matcha tea discovery that's it
that's it a matcha tea discovery that
that's all they care about it's like
it's like yeah no
i took my daughter to to the er it's the
fourth time this week
yeah her skin is is it's it's so bad
she's bleeding and we have to change the
sheets constantly
yeah no her daddy is is is that
yep he's at the emergency room now with
her
i couldn't make it tonight i'm so
exhausted yeah
um do you think science research is ever
going to care
do you think they're going to be able to
offer something for for my child
there's a matcha tea discovery so
science research
is busy with trying to find an
antioxidant and matcha tea and green tea
they are you know that's just sick
it's sick it's sick it's sick it's sick
and that's how that's what our system is
that is in a nutshell that's
fact right there what's happening fact
they don't care about our children they
pretend they do
they don't they don't they would
actually go
they would they would be doing something
about it and they're not
kathy celery juice and heavy metal detox
smoothie have changed my life
thanks from the bottom of my heart you
know
it it just matters kathy i'm glad you're
here
our bodies love us unconditionally you
guys hear that
okay new edition you get it on
amazon.com or free at the library
um it's on sale on amazon our bodies
love us
unconditionally okay they do not
judge or blame or hold on to resentment
our bodies don't
resent us samantha says i suffer so bad
with vertigo doctors said learn to live
with it samantha we're going to talk
about vertigo
we're talking about it our bodies love
us unconditionally they do not
judge or blame or hold up hold on to
resentment
day in and day out all of our body
systems are working for us
without complaint working with us
without working for us
and with us without complaint our bodies
love us the immune system is constantly
ready for battle patrolling
every part of the body looking for
invaders our immune system is looking
for that's our immune system that's your
white blood cell there it is
it's floating around in your body right
now it's in your bloodstream
right now and what is it looking for
invaders little green invader
the immune system is constantly ready
for battle patrolling every part of our
body looking for invaders
let's make it crystal clear
nobody wants to be sick
do you want to be sick do you guys want
to be sick or
do you want to be sick do you want to be
sick or do you want to be sick you want
to be sick because that's what they
think
they think we want to be sick do you
want to be sick
let's make it crystal clear nobody
wants to be sick or compromised nobody
has a fear of healing
do you have a fear of healing do you
know what they told everybody years ago
i'm talking 10 years ago i'm talking
five years ago
probably now too okay if i really looked
into it a little deeper
it's probably now it's been happening
for 20 30 years
because no one knows what's wrong with
anybody they all think everybody has a
fear of healing
oh you got a fear of healing you know
i'm a spiritual advisor
you got a fear of healing that's what it
is
let's make it crystal clear again nobody
wants to be sick or compromised nobody
has a fear of healing i believe in you
with the knowledge and power i know you
guys can heal
and that's revised addition we're going
to talk about that
making some more roles michelle l you've
been told that right that you have a
fear of healing
yeah you michelle you got a fear of
healing you're scared to heal you don't
want to get better
of course you do that's how bad things
are out there
elena nobody wants to be stuck on
mattress island
exactly well you know i'm honored to
hear it
i'm so glad dede francis no doctor can
diagnose my dizziness
derealization i've stopped going because
all they do
is give medication that are refused you
know what else they'll do too
they'll want to take all your blood and
take more and more and then you get
sicker and sicker your immune system
weakens did you listen to the
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
please listen to the blood draw episode
it's so important you guys hear that
episode i know many of you guys listened
already
i know you listened i saw you say it in
the comment section in um
youtube the link is in the description
and listen to the blood draw when you
get your blood tested listen to that
episode
it can save your life i'm not kidding
because it can sneak up on you they
sneak up on you and then boom the system
just
pulls out your immune system and you go
boom boom
and downhill downhill downhill um you
were told that too cornelia
yeah yep i totally believe that you got
a fear of healing
that's the system and you know what
you're gonna be told that you know what
else you're gonna be told
you're gonna be told that you manifested
your sickness right your illness you
mean you don't
know what else you might be told this is
a good one too
hello should i say hello when i have the
phone in my hand and not like before i
pick it up
hello yeah yeah um
why am i sick i i created it
how um a past life
really what happened in a past life
i uh i was sick in a past life and i
didn't want to let it go
so you mean okay so my life before this
lifetime
i was really sick is that what you're
saying okay
and i just didn't want to let it go
right i wanted to stay sick
so i brought it into this next lifetime
wow i was also the queen of england
in 1342 and i had my head chopped off
and that's why my neck hurts um
that whoa wait a minute i was queen
victoria
is that what it was i was queen victoria
okay and
okay i gotta hang up now thank you
have you guys ever heard that one right
have you linda blood draws show what our
bodies are
doing yeah it's great it gives the
doctor who doesn't know why you're sick
a window into hopefully guessing more to
what's going on
because that's how it works people with
chronic illness
they go they go they go they go they go
to the doctor they don't know what's
wrong
they have all the dizziness tingles
numbness chest tightness and now they're
going to a specialist another
neurologist
and they get all this blood taken right
linda totally
and yeah to try to get a window and i
believe in blood tests i want people to
go get a blood test but there's a way to
do it that can protect you and save your
life because they take
too much blood and you lose your immune
system listen to the episode linda
that's what you should do right there
it's important so
when they take your blood you lose your
cbc
cbc you were good to me now you're going
off
bye bye you know you know that's how it
works because they take your your
complete blood count right a piece of
it a piece of it you lose your white
blood cells they take
20 vials 30 vials they'll take 24 vials
they'll take 14 vials
and you just lose lose lose and the
whole 7 vials
5 full vials but complete vials right
full vials
and we lose our immune system and it
takes months to get our immune system
back but
while that's happening a little buggy is
coming up
reactivated epstein-barr that now signs
research takes
by information and they're using it now
right i published it first
but anyway reactivated epstein-barr and
what happens is
that reactivated epstein-barr comes out
because you're losing your immune system
from
all the blood draws right and then in
the end sure
the doctor might see something in your
blood draw but
also when they keep on taking blood
they keep on making you deficient so now
it's like
if now it's like this whole thing really
the last blood test i had i'm more
deficient than i was before
my my nutritional my nutritional
profiles worse
why is that huh i got to start eating
better i am eating better
what it is is they start removing
everything from you from all that
deb scott surprised to find find you
making fun of spiritual advisors
and all that airy fairy stuff you know
like when spirit told you to tell your
grandmother she had lung cancer i think
we've been duped you come a long way you
know
deb what happens with me okay just so
you know is i've had to undo
a lot of spiritually damaged
people through 35 years of work okay
so people who are chronically ill and
really sick
come pouring into my office okay
including
patients that doctors would send right
pouring into my office
and people were so mind damaged
they were told they had a fear of
healing they were told they manifested
their sickness
can you imagine you're being told that
so i created it
like i created my sickness and then they
they do that right they've also told
people it's all because you didn't
solve something in a past life right so
that's another thing too
i've had people just so head screwed so
duped
so fooled okay and we're really hurt and
bad because of it
because if yeah i'm not saying spiritual
advisors are bad
i'm just saying i've seen some damaged
people being told
some crazy stuff and they walked into my
office
and guess what spirit of compassion did
told them what was wrong
so their doctor can help them uh spirit
of compassion didn't say
that they had their they were beheaded
okay in 1645
the spirit of compassion didn't say they
manifested it spirit of compassion never
said to anyone you
created it spirit of compassion never
said you got a fear of healing
and spirit of compassion never said your
body is attacking itself like medical
science
and they never said anything else like
that he never said anything else like
that but they
always tell people that it's your body
attacking itself that's what they say
so what that's the difference right
there
and i have respect for any spiritual
advisor
even when they're making massive
mistakes like i've seen along the way
and that's just that's just how it is
you guys making nora rolls about
starting a little bit i know you guys
are coming on but thank you for the
comment i think that's what you were
saying i wasn't sure
entirely but i thought that's what i
read pam if i'm wrong please you know
please forgive me if i'm like
i mean if i'm wrong how i'm dressing the
question you know
yeah two years of no answer sherry says
two two years of no answers it's just
it's just no fun
we're talking about the plague a little
bit today we're talking about the
epstein barr
vertigo tingles and numbness tightness
of chest we're on dr
fun man i've heard that mumbo jumbo
i just saw it one that went up there
let's see if it
if i could catch that comment again
because dr faun has wisdom
man i've heard that mumbo jumbo about
past lives and how
a family member was hung by the neck so
he has
neck pain
huh yeah no my neck has been really
hurting
been hurting for a few years
really i was hung
in a past life and that's why i still
have this neck pain
oh thank god i have an answer that's a
freaking nightmare though
exactly it's a nightmare it gets into
your consciousness
and it hurts it hurts lunell
soc is more practical than most you know
the whole thing with
yeah well i mean that's interesting and
true so you
you guys stop fooling around going
around too much
seaweed hero says seaweed hero good to
see you why does facebook always say
content can't be played right now so
glad i can see you on youtube the reason
why is because they're kicking everybody
off of facebook
facebook's supposed to have probably up
to 10 000 people on there
live and they kick them all off while
you're trying to come on
um so we only have like a few people
they're only allowing a few people
tonight that's what they do
same thing on instagram um margot so
getting viruses is completely
random no no karma at all and there's no
karma involved
absolutely not absolutely not we come
into this world of viruses we come into
this world with ebv
and shingles that we get from utero we
get passed down from our parents we come
into this world like that we easily can
get
viruses here i'll talk about that too
relationships
friendships drinking off of somebody's
glass
you can just it's easy to get pathogens
you didn't ask to be sick like there's
no
karma involved that's not you're not
paying back
you're not paying back on the karmic
channel
you know so that's important too you
know bugs were
created by well they were they were
manipulated
bugs were manipulated a hundred years
ago
by some mad men okay in the industry
they were manipulated they were raised
propagated
they were proliferated they were put
into the system along the way
and that's how it works darkness and bad
people okay
darkest bad people um
your spiritual advisor so there's no bad
people in the world
what do you mean there's no bad people
in the world you mean everybody's good
so there's people aren't bad
really that's hard to believe though
because what about the six million jews
that were gassed
and murdered that there wasn't a
bad thing or something well the people
weren't bad that did it to them
um so there's no bad people out there so
what about
all the viruses that they raised in all
the
eggs and stuff and then somehow escaped
the labs
bad people weren't creating bad bugs
okay then how did it happen and that's
how it works it's really kind of
strange i'm gonna make some food can't
fool around all night
and um so
so anyway i'm going to move the eggs and
i'm also going to wash my
hands really quick okay you guys bear
with me please
um i got a sink right here i don't know
if you can see it you're probably
catching a little bit of it there
um touching eggs and i don't think it's
a smart move to touch
eggs and to be making minority rolls to
start making normal let me get the blood
off of the
counter too if that's okay maybe even
get my phone over here
terry went against medical advice
refused the meds and went with the 369
protocol
a1c from 100 from 10.5 to 6.5 in three
months thank you anthony
terry you're working hard you're working
hard okay
and you know you're you're working on it
you're doing it
okay so i thank you for doing the work
and that's really you know if you guys
get kicked off go to youtube if you guys
get kicked off facebook i i always
forget to say that go to youtube
youtube live right now um
anyway let's make some noise so what i'm
gonna do
is and i'm gonna make noise and talk
about
the vagus nerve a little bit too i just
want to thinly slice
i want to thinly slice some celery right
here
if you guys are okay with that we're
going to do a little celery slicing
right here
the thing is with the vagus nerve it's
always been a mystery
no one knew it had anything to do with
these symptoms before medical medium
put the information out there so medical
medium information was the vagus nerve
becomes inflamed and you get the tingles
and numbness and the tightness of the
chest this 35 years of work
and now the vagus nerve has seemed to
get popular because just like medical
medium information getting out there
people pick up on it
you guys can't even imagine or maybe you
can't imagine how many practitioners and
how many doctors
have read the medical medium books never
mind how many i've talked to before the
medical meeting books came out
and how medical immune information has
has renovated the medical world or the
holistic world too
renovated refurbished
because um no one knew what did what
with all these mystery symptoms
linda says so nobody's ever known what
to do with the vagus nerve until the
medical medium has
spoken okay that's a bunch of charlton
talk
that's a good one there linda
hey linda linda linda
um just so you know
medical medium book was published
six and a half years ago yeah yeah and
it was all unique and original
fact yeah and then science and research
took the information and published it
later
but you don't like that right so linda
you don't like that
okay so someone's not allowed to
actually
start something original and unique and
take any credit
okay okay so let me just bow down i
can't take any credit
ever i started all this new information
that never was out there in the world
published first by medical medium so i
guess
is it because i have a big ego linda and
the ego needs to be fed it's not because
i need people to heal so they could find
out where it originated so they have
answers
uh okay all right i will bow down
um i i didn't start anything new
okay all right i i don't want to get you
upset linda i know it's too much for you
okay i'm gonna go i gotta go you're
you're just
you're really hard to talk to you guys
have to understand this that
what linda doesn't understand and it's
really hard for her is that medical
medium information started a tremendous
amount
of original and unique information
that's in our system today yeah we knew
about the vagus nerve of course we did
we did not know that it gets inflamed we
did not know
that the epstein-barr inflames it we did
not know
that the vagus nerve causes tingles and
numbness okay
nausea we didn't know that tightness in
chest
alright anxiety we did not know of any
of this information
35 years of work just like the blood
draw information okay
medical medium is the first to put out
the information
that they're removing too much blood
removing your immune system and people
are going backwards with
their health that is unique and original
medical mean information
so why is it that i got to keep on
coming out with unique original
information that's never been heard
anywhere else
and then doctors take the information
and then it goes around and goes around
and then somebody named linda just
doesn't want to hear it
just doesn't even believe it and doesn't
want to hear it when it's
fact including other public publishing
too
linda says neurologist do you know that
why are you acting like
nobody knew that see this is arrogance
right there and it's an appropriate
neurologist
know that that's possible and noted its
medical journals really because
millions of people went to neurologists
and they didn't know their tingles and
numbness
came from their vagus nerve you are 100
wrong they didn't know the nausea that
was mysterious
came from the vagus nerve they didn't
know the vertigo
ever came from the vagus nerve guess
what they still don't
medical research and science doesn't
know any of this doctors are
using the information now for medical
media anxiety
vertigo mysterious nausea is all from
the vagus nerve that's medical medium
information i'm really sorry but you're
a hundred percent
wrong call it arrogance call it what you
want i'm a bad
person you don't like me whatever
doesn't matter
michelle l my neurologist never told me
that
no neurologist has ever told anybody
that not
one neurologist pre-medical medium books
probably don't even tell people that now
and so i'm just saying but not one
neurologist has ever told millions of
women
filing into doctor's offices the 35
years work i've done
the doctors i've talked to the over 200
like 200
000 people i've talked to over all these
decades
not one person found a neurologist that
knew the vagus nerve
did any of those symptoms including
vertigo not one not one healer
not one doctor call it arrogance call
what you want
i don't care it's just a fact you know
it's a fact
and it's a proven fact if you do your
research linda
you look in the books and you do your
research yeah it's a proven fact
um anyway michelle exactly michelle so
many thousands and thousands of women
walked into the neurologist's office
and never got told any of that exactly
um ichota i'm looking at chota too it
showed him a neurologist and i had
many and never said anything even close
to that either they told me
they told me my post-concussion vertigo
five months
sorry five months on was all in my head
so they just thought it was all in your
head they thought you were making it up
each other and that was
that was many neurologists you went to
right
um and then uh let's see
uh ud says bs we all know what the vagus
nerve does
oh you do it came from medical medium
information
so guess what you're talking bs
sorry but you're talking bs see you know
what's interesting
this is how it's done like i noticed
that
trolls they ch you know they and and
certain people
haters and naysayers they just
don't like the truth they don't they
make stuff
up monica i went to a neurologist
vanderbilt could not tell me what was
going on
yeah incredible neurologist right could
not tell anybody
a marjorie i would have never known the
reason why i was losing my voice it was
the vagus nerve
yeah exactly um
sandra so the vagus nerve is inflamed by
the ebv
yes the shingles can inflame it too and
i'm gonna cover that
gotta make some food though we're having
a good time tonight it's great
jennifer it's frozen shoulder
neurological if it's not an
injury if it's not a bad injury
my neurologist diagnosed me with it and
can't
sorry and believes it to be viral it's
medical medium information
so the shingles
is the virus this is that's medical
medium information
originates from here not one doctor
on the planet knew that frozen shoulder
was
viral this is you got to remember
millions
of this first edition went around the
world
patients brought their books into
doctors there's not a doctor
out there that a patient didn't bring in
a medical medium book to them
there's not one out there and so the
shingles
i released to the world how the shingles
is behind frozen shoulder
so yeah you guys i mean
i don't need the credit for an ego thing
just so you know
okay so i know that someone might think
that i don't need the credit for these
incredible discoveries of
medicine right that are being used right
why everybody just dumps on me you know
what i mean and says that where's my
research papers where's my studies
how come i'm not a doctor right and
again i get peed on constantly all the
time
and i don't want credit because i got
this
like it's got to feed my ego i want
people to be able to find out where they
can hear how they can heal it it's one
thing when
a neurologist picks up the medical
medium information tells a patient
hey this is what's going on it's another
for the patient to be able to actually
find information and get and get better
they they project their own darkness
michelle ell says
constant my dog constance my doctor
looked at me like i had a third eye
growing
when i mentioned my vagus nerve was
irritated and taking
and and taking lemon balm helped relax
it
exactly but uh but
constance i thought everybody knew about
what the vagus nerve does i thought
every single doctor knew what the vagus
nerve does
you know exactly luno
it's frustrating the thing is is yeah it
is lunalle says it must be so
frustrating to share the info first and
then so many plagiarizing and signs
catching up with the mm info
and still mm info gets dragged in the
mud
it's part of i guess the you know the
entire
journey exactly it's just it's
incredible road let's make some noise
rules let's get going on this
but you know what i don't lose sleep
over it
because i figure it this way that
look the information's getting out there
okay
people won't heal if they don't get the
rest of the information
right or if some of these some of these
doctors or practitioners or health gurus
take some of the information it look
like heroes themselves fine
i'm all right with that i just want
people though to be able to get back to
all the info to heal that's what gets my
goat right there
uh rachel paid 1 000 for the doctor
and they couldn't explain my heart
flutters took your microc
no flutterings heart fluttering that's
topic ectopic heart flutters that are a
topic
um uh mystery heart palpitations which
i'm going to talk about medical medium
it's the epstein-barr virus it's low
grade viral right
so um let's do like a little heart thing
really quick we got a bigger heart
you guys okay i'm taking a little food
break but i'm gonna make the food so
what happens with the valves right
there's this sticky stuff
that gets created by the epstein-barr
virus
okay advanced information the head of
science and research of course
and they're going to steal this too so
they'll steal everything from me down
the road
which i don't care but people won't be
able to find their way back
to get all the information to heal all
the way and that's what's scary to me
so the virus sits inside the liver okay
and it releases all of this byproduct
and i'm talking about information right
out of here
new addition it releases all this
byproduct
the byproduct builds up in your liver
and builds up in your liver and builds
up in your liver this is the sludge
and it builds up in your liver right and
then eventually
it puffs out of the liver and
heads up the highway highway is your
bloodstream
heading directly to the heart
that junk sticky jelly starts to build
up in the valves
becomes a mystery to the doctor it
builds up in the mitral valve
okay uh tricuspid valve it
bicuspid valve if you're somebody with a
bicuspid valve right
and um aortic valve right
so it gets in there okay and it and
and then it sticks and all of a sudden
it sticks for like like less than a
millisecond
and when it does that because the
jelly's in there you get the heart
flutters
so when you start taking care of
yourself like medical beam information
the celery juice and everything else
you're cleaning up your liver
you're cleaning up that gunk all right
and the heart palpitations go away or
topic heartbeat or flutters they go away
right
there's a heart palpitation protocol in
medical medium new addition too
just just so you know right so let's go
and
just just cover one last thing with it
but
vagus nerve can also cause the problem
electrically electrical
your vagus nerve nerve nerves nerve
signaling to the heart from toxic heavy
metals
and viruses inflaming the vagus nerve
it could go that way or the junk in the
heart it could go either or
and then you got it right advanced
medical information
linda how do you like that just
wondering
um are you gone yet so let's think about
vertigo in a second
um okay right to vertigo
natalie so what what do we do now vagus
nerve exercises i want my life back
from vertigo okay so
if i had vertigo like what what um
i was just talking about i mean for
family members
friends if i had vertigo i'd be on the
micro sea
and the microc was helping the other
person with
her vertigo because it was cleaning up
the viral junk so that epstein-barr
viral junk was getting cleaned up it was
getting cleaned up
out of the liver plus the vitamin c
it does is it supports the immune system
so your immune systems eat eating up the
vitamin c
your immune system your white blood
cells they're there those are the things
that actually fight the virus
right so when you give your white
blood cells vitamin c okay
and you can get any vitamin c you want
to get out there this is just the one i
use for my for me
my friends and family this is the
vimergy microc and i'm not sponsored
just letting you guys know which one i
use and which one i give to my family
so anyway the bottom line is your white
count
feeds off of vitamin c gets nice and
strong
then goes and kills off the epstein bar
less epstein-barr
heart flutters that are mystery
mysterious from to the doctor
start to go away that that's important
right there okay
um let's talk about vertigo a little bit
too
so okay let's go back to this so vertigo
you got your epstein-barr virus okay
the epstein-barr virus is releasing a
neurotoxin
it's feeding off of toxic heavy metals
so say you're somebody that's
into tuna you got all that mercury how
much tuna have you had in your life
right
how much tuna have you eaten in your
life so
your epstein bars feeding off of all
that mercury then it releases
a neurotoxin the neurotoxin clings
to the vagus nerve so it clings to the
vagus nerve
that's what the neurotoxin does and when
it clings to the vagus nerve it inflames
it
and game on anything
and everything can happen because that
vagus nerve can inflame
at the bottom it can inflame in the
middle it can inflame at the top
it can inflame even higher and when it
gets inflamed
you'll get the boat thing you're like
rocking on the boat you're trying to
walk
you get the spins where you're just like
this is going on and you're spinning
you lay in the bed you're laying in your
bed and you're at night and and the room
is doing this
like that you're not even spinning the
room is going one way stopping
going stopping like this and if anybody
has vertigo now i'm really sorry that i
hope i'm not creating a little bit of me
not creating but i hope i'm not like
tweaking you out
that's how sensitive people get with
vertigo where anything
moving and if they can't watch
television they can't watch a show
they can't watch it's really hard right
and protocols are in medical medium book
one so
i mean if you guys don't have this linda
take the book to your doctor
okay the the person that was hating on
me take the book to your doctor ask
your doctor what they think um
candy says listen i get it but it's a
little over the top today i think we
have to hold
respect for all points of view i believe
what he says is excellent and what
not but it's just triggered me candy
this is kind of i totally see what
you're saying like in one way
right but linda had no respect
for me okay she called me a charlatan so
is that a
point of view or is that just a hater
and if i don't stick up for myself i'm
going to be kicked down and kicked down
and kicked down
right i mean do you want me to be like
that see if i lose
that ability to stand up for myself
i might also lose that ability to stand
up for you
okay did you ever think about that
because i'm standing up for you
your life your if you get really sick
like really sick and i'm not fighting
for you
and what you need and the information
you need and i don't fight
to keep in it and and be strong and
in all that then i might not be able to
fight for you anymore i might not be
able to fight for anybody anymore
and and that that that alone um
yovanna i went to went to the
neurologist ent
cardiologist ob gyn many ear visits
you name it none could help me your
books are helping me and i'm sharing
your info
thank you yovanna you're not upset right
about me
you know talking about linda's hate a
little bit i hope you're okay
because all right i mean lorraine else
is right on linda was so disrespectful
she was
she was terribly disrespectful you
definitely need to stand up and respond
and lorraine i
i have a lot of respect for you lorraine
because you know i've read
all your comments right in youtube and
and other places and stuff
and you're a strong woman i mean
without a doubt and i notice you don't
take any crap
either i mean i've you know i've read
your comments and everything and
you you've seen everything like you you
know what's going on in the world
so i'm honored okay um
so suzanne says hi from germany anthony
you are a world
you are a world to me and my family
my four children thank you for your
selfless love and your devotion you gave
us our lives back
after running from doctor doctor gonna
get me choked up here
you get me stroked up here sandy
good to see you too um she's a hater and
please read my comment on that aw has
sacrificed his life to others
what do you guys don't get sorry but he
is a blessing sunday
zen you're the greatest doreen ew is
standing up for all of us when no one
ever has and i got to tell you guys
it was really bad back years ago like
if you got sick with anything that was
mysterious
families turned against you i've seen
families turn against people i've seen
friends turn against people
i've seen doctors turn against people
i've seen people lost
no hope for years and years now it's a
little better you can go to your
functional medicine doctor and they'll
be like hearing your symptoms now for
the for you know because you're hearing
them more and more
and then they might have some respect
but it wasn't like that
kristin jay cohen he never said vitamin
c
solves vertigo
um that's just one thing first of all
so kristen that's one thing so it
very important to know that vitamin c
feeds your immune system and gives you
a chance right so let you know um
oh yeah you're correcting someone thank
you thank you kristen thank you
exactly exactly but it's one of the
tools
anyway that's the micro seed that's the
one i give my friend and family just so
you know because there's some bad
vitamin c's out there that irritate the
stomach
that cause problems all of that's the
only one i trust
right here uh constance said lorraine
for the win
all right let's start let's start
working on this a little bit i still
want to talk about vertigo and
everything
i mean right
i'm gonna grate some carrot are you guys
okay with that it's kind of like
just do a little bit this like
kind of like great it's not really great
but i'm making like um
carrot noodles in a way right julianning
them
i think that's the right word for this
process and
all right there we go want a little bit
of this grated
carrot okay you can even do the same
thing to a celery stick by the way with
this
say if you do this i like this right
here
so you can just do this as well to
celery so you got it kind of like
shredded
which is nice i got some shredded celery
got some shredded
okay russell says the power of medical
media and info is undeniable
if you work at 100 and study the info
and the books to a t
it's miraculously russell i'm honored
truly
i am i am i am it matters
details matter details matter okay so
i'm gonna put some orange in here if you
guys don't
mind i like to i'm gonna kind of like
moisten it with some orange
so these nori rolls are versatile you
can do anything with them okay
now if you're plant-based or vegan you
can have a fat-free nori roll
not put avocado in there or tahini but
you can put tahini and avocado in this
so i'm letting you know you can
put tahini and avocado in there right so
that's an option for you
i have steamed potatoes over here i
might do a little bit of that too as
well you guys so
i got a couple of steamed potatoes right
here it was in my steamer
right i always keep those handy
but i got to tell you guys something
interesting what people don't know
is the amount of haters and the amount
of hate and attacks
that that i get and it's really gotten
out of control like
it was bad years ago but it's taken this
new
height that's just been immense
and like my family tells me like how
long are you gonna do this like how long
can you
stand it you know and it's and i'm like
well no i'm in it
i'm in it i'm not i'm not breaking from
it i gotta
fight for the people i gotta get them
what they need if i disappear
and just and and take a vacation or
whatever
and not a vacation whatever you call and
i decide to like
split the scene or whatever it's just it
just wouldn't be fair to everybody and i
always say that i'm putting some
scallion in here
so jay cohen says wow you are really
using constructive
like a whiny baby jake you know
jake first of all i'm glad you're here
okay and i wonder how much whining you
do i i would like to know how much
whining you do
yeah yeah you know i'm picking on people
on the internet
that's what i do yep my name's jake
yep oh you heard me whining
you heard me crying like a baby the
other night and whining all the time
you know i got to take it out on
everybody else though
you know i got to take all my anger and
my emotions and my
pain and everything i just gotta take it
out and i'll take it out of the medical
medium tonight that's a good idea let me
do that let me take out all my
emotional pain and upsetness and
everything i'll take it out on the
medical medium i'm gonna bother him
tonight jake
it's all right you know if i don't let
the community know
like if i don't let the community know
though some things
it's important because we're kind of all
in this together
because there are millions of people
around the world right
that would have never gotten this
information
if i wasn't standing up for myself
or delivering this important information
you know
and here's the other thing jake what you
don't understand okay is that there's
there's trolls and haters that also try
to
confuse medical medium people who are
working on their healing process so say
you're somebody brand new when you're
like
you've been sick for years you've been
to your 10th doctor
you're losing your life you're losing
everything right
and you stumble across medical medium
information
okay and then somebody like jake
maybe not you jake but somebody like
jake says no
he's a bad guy or his information
doesn't work
or ignore his stuff or he's just the
celery juice guy
and they get derailed and now they're on
this
path for another 10 years chronically
ill they can't even get the right
answers right information
so if i don't kind of like make things
well-rounded and talk about
you know everything else you know what i
mean and in the whole bit
jake said make the nori roll yeah
exactly well jake you know what
it's fun having you on here tonight i'm
going to say that for sure
for sure but yeah and i'm going to make
you a nori roll right now
you better believe it because i'm at
your service jake even a hater i'm at
your service because that's how i am
um the problem is is jake just don't
ghost go into the medical meeting
community and start hating on medical
community members medical medium
community members just don't do that
whatever you do because uh that's what
it seems like people do sometimes so i
like to let everybody know hey
this is what's happening you know what i
mean it's important that everybody
it's it's everybody has the details and
they know what's going on
but jake i feel bad for you so you know
i have
i have i've been taught by spirit of
compassion have tremendous compassion
even for you know confused
people like yourself and so and that's
what i do i do have compassion for you
i really do and i hope you're actually
living your best life and doing good and
and everything i don't wish anything bad
on you check this out right
i got the celery in here i got the
carrots in here i got the tomato
you guys can cut them like this and i'm
going to show you in a little bit so
let's just get a plate
put it right here for now one thing i
know about vertigo from all these years
is it's brutal and people people
really have suffered with it i know you
guys some of you guys suffer with it now
really really bad
um the people have just suffered so bad
from it you know
and it's really sad too i'm putting in
some i'm just gonna make a few to start
with and we're gonna talk a little bit
about tightness to chest that's where
i'm heading now
put a little bit of celery in here i
like how everything just sticks out the
sides and all that i'm going to get
another tomato
you guys see these tomatoes aren't they
insane you forgot the cukes i know gina
you're so right cucumbers in here are so
great
but tonight not a cucumber night but boy
i never do the carrots really so i was
kind of doing the carrots purposely
right
i got tomato in here i'm putting a
little dolls that's dolls right there if
you guys take a look
roya says haters are poisoning their own
bodies
that's actually really that's that's
most likely true
actually you can use some potato too if
you want i'm gonna put a little potato
in here
so i'm putting some potato these are fat
free
no tahini no avocado right
no fish got a little bit of that i got a
red bell pepper
i'm gonna pop a little red bell pepper
in here
so shirley says i've suffered with
vertigo
and nausea and wicked headaches
brutal it's brutal you know
people don't get it unless they've been
in your shoes right
you get these people that like have no
idea what's happening with
people who actually are struggling with
stuff they got no idea out there
you see them all over the internet right
they think they got it all down because
you're able to work out
they want to build their muscles they
eat keto or something i'm not saying
you know you can't eat keto or something
but the keto
and they think they got it all down like
they're experts right
they lost some pounds they're working
out every day
they get they get so big on themselves
because they're like
they're like experts they know
everything right but they really don't
and i've seen people like that get cut
down fast their legs cut down
beneath them they get vertigo they start
getting a condition they can't work out
anymore their life changes
and they just fall apart because they
can't handle it they just don't know
that world or what it's like you know
and then you got to find an inner
strength in you man
triple moon goddess i was bullied online
that's how i fell
into depression and had my epstein-barr
virus relapse
that's why i'm fighting for you that's
why that's why i'm fighting for you
that's why
i was um
kindly discussing that
that info for information to linda
i'm going to use tomato to wet this nori
sheet i'm making you guys a bunch of
quick noise right now okay
and then we're going to talk a little
bit more
and um jake seems like a bully too
and that's just how it works these
bullies are really
bad news
i got some spinach right here i'm gonna
put some dill in this one do you guys
like dill
right michelle did you
say your husband has to shop so he has
to do the shopping
totally understand totally understand i
do i do
see guys what i'm doing is i'm cutting
tomato if you want to know i'm giving
you the 4-1-1
on this so what uh
so jacqueline what else do i recommend
for vertigo i'm glad you asked
okay if i had vertigo
okay if i had vertigo and you can go to
your doctor
and ask your doctor to customize it for
you if you want
but epstein-barr is the cause of vertigo
right
and i'm gonna read about vertigo too a
little bit um
and i got that section right here
but let me go and look into this book
right here which is a new edition do you
have the new edition
god there's so much information in here
it's incredible
so ebv is is what
just for the record is what is what's
behind vertigo that's mysterious unless
your vagus nerve was
injured unless it was physically injured
but if you look in here okay you guys
you'll see
supplements all right just look there we
go supplements
for vertigo and veneers right
i guess you probably can't see it's
probably whiting out okay
and it teaches you how to use the
supplements right you'll say fresh
celery juice work up to 32 ounces daily
now i'm just going to give you
information here
you don't have to do everything all at
once like i tell family members and
friends who ask me about this
that they can start with a few things
read the book
though that's why it's so important to
read the book and to read the chapter
it's critical to to know what you can do
or not do meaning what's easiest to do
or what a great way to start
but you'll see here fresh celery juice
work up to 32 ounces if that's the only
thing you do
and that's how you start then that's how
you start right and you see how you go
now and then it says um
celery force right so it's a celery
force and that
that is a great i don't even have it
right here but celery force is an option
for a lot of people it helps
it is barley grass juice powder which um
is the vimergy stuff that i use but you
can if you want to use somebody else's
barley grass use powder you can
i'm just telling you the one i use that
i trust the best and then it says b
complex then it says cat's claw so
here's a cat's claw here that
i recommend for my family and friends
that's the one i use right
so it's cat's claw and it shows dosages
in
the book now you can ask your doctor any
of this information you can take the
book to your doctor
i'm just telling you what i do for
myself or for my family members i've
never had vertigo
but um but it doesn't mean i don't
understand it and it doesn't mean i
don't understand the pain and suffering
involved
and the hell people go through that cat
cat's claw doesn't have alcohol in it
and that's
one thing that goes wrong when people be
like all right i'll go get a cat's claw
right that's the vimergy
the uh v is victor i am as mary e r g y
and um the there's no natural flavors
there's no alcohol in here
someone will get a cat's call and
they'll just get one with alcohol and if
this matters
because someone could go out there buy a
cat's claw
anthony williams said do a cat squad and
they go buy a cat's claw
and i'm not getting better i'm getting
worse or i'm not feeling good
because the cat's got alcohol in it corn
grain
alcohol or natural flavors or citric
acid
right they had that in there so people
got to understand like
there's all these problems with
supplements too so i have a directory at
medical media.com for what i think is
the safest and best right
so cat's claws in here right there is an
option um
chaga mushroom that's a good mushroom
for vertigo
um curcumin that's one right there
that's also a good option for
don't have it right here but like i
recommend the vimergy curcumin
so and then um and then it goes on and
it talks about lysine now
that's a critical one right there
lysine is critical for vertigo
critical because you're dealing with the
epstein-barr virus right
so it's so important to know um
these are these are the details that
matter lemon balm
right then it has the lemon balm there
um there's a licorice root
has the licorice root right there so
there's a licorice root
right and so you can just start out
little at a time i talk about it in the
book where you can just start out with a
little b12
a little bit of lemon balm um some
vitamin c
but but you know you can do that but the
point is is that
these are the different these are the
different supplements and dosages
this is what i recommend for family and
friends right like the bimraji
but like i said take the book to your
doctor ask your doctor what's right for
you maybe your doctor doesn't want you
to use
anything in the book and your worker
wants to go different direction
for you you know um i know and so
the bottom line is the information is
there though for vertigo because vertigo
is caused by epsine bar
barr likes to feed off of foods we like
stepsim bar likes to feed off the eggs
that are right there which i don't want
to touch right now
um so anyway these nori sheets got
really wet
from sitting here and not rolling them
in time but i'm just gonna
so guys i just made a few nori's gonna
make one more
i'm gonna do another potato one
so thin sliced potato in here
i'm going to use a little bit of lime in
this one so you can you can like do
different things just a little lime
juice on here
doctors can't help vertigo jason
i agree they don't have any options they
don't have anything that can
i agree i know medical medium
information has reversed
so many people's vertigo conditions just
thousands
yeah i mean i totally understand i'm
going to put a little bit more spinach
in here
and i'm going to put a little bit more
of this dulce right here as a seaweed
right
i think i'll get a little red pepper
here i'm having a great time tonight
with you guys
i always do
um so let's put a little bit of red bell
pepper here
and i'm going to roll this up
sigridowski says evil people can be very
covertly hostile and are always in bad
mood
most people have a hard time to see what
is true or not
i know everything mm says is true i do
health food since 40 years oh my god 40
years in it
wow wow
you got me beat been doing this for 35
years yeah since age
four i've been giving uh people advice
with their health and spirit compassion
talking to me
so i guess you could say since age four
so it's a lot more than 35 years
but you know really hardcore
is different
so yeah okay guys i just made a few of
these let me cut them for you too
okay let me move the cat's claw out okay
did you guys get your wild blueberry
juice yet i'm so pumped up about this
stuff it's so incredible
um
so let's talk about titus in the chest
what happens is when the vagus nerve
gets inflamed okay
see how i'm cutting these right
i'm cutting them a little smaller so
they're not
huge pieces right when the vagus nerve
gets inflamed you can get the tightness
in the chest which is really in
a difficult one now the vagus nerve when
it gets it
inflamed higher like higher up
brain or down lower in the neck you can
still get tightness to the chest you can
still get tightness in the chest
when the vagus nerve is inflamed at the
bottom
but what you usually get when the vagus
nerve is inflamed at the bottom is a lot
of
nausea that's unexplainable right nausea
so i'm going to start putting some of
these here for you guys
you can make a dipping sauce
too like so many different dipping
sauces you can do
right
um
jessica i had my blood taken recently
and have been crazy hungry
since yeah that's a glucose deficiency
when they take out your blood
did you look at did you you did you
listened to the
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
okay
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
the blood draw
episode link is in description share it
with everybody you know i mean i would
beg you guys like i want to beg you guys
to share
that podcast with everybody and anybody
you know
um because i want to help people so
badly when they remove too much blood
from you
or remove blood from you they're
removing glucose
and here's how it works and i want to
give you that i want to give you a quick
rundown on that okay
when they remove your blood your glucose
from blood draws
right that glucose is what's keeping
your brain
strong so the minute that glucose
get disappears from the blood draw your
brain will know it's starving
it's starving um within five seconds of
not getting glucose your brain starts to
die
i mean it's really five seconds it just
starts it's like it needs glucose
and you still have glucose that's why
you're okay but
even some taken out like on the blood
draw even with some taken out
you can feel it and be just starving be
hungry for a long time
so that happens all the time to drop
that that happens all the time
um but anyway i'm gonna just cut these
up and then we're almost there you guys
look at how crazy these are right here
all right so um listen to the blood draw
podcast
there's no commercials there's no
advertisers that's
that's uh how i do it if you notice my
youtube channel since i'm live on
youtube
right now have you guys noticed there's
no there's no ads
have you guys noticed that you know i do
that on purpose right
james palazzo says love you man you're
changing lives i'm honored
you're here thank you for being here i'm
blown away seriously
blown away
and um trying to make not make this too
messy but
this stuff just gets messy with these
sometimes putting these in
right here
okay let's get these going
all right
so a little messy but
that's just you know we're live and i'm
kind of paying attention to the comments
and everything
so it's not going to be perfect but
that's it that's the dory rolls you can
do a lot with there's potato in this one
there's there's you know tomato there's
green onions there's carrots that are
shredded shredded celery
alicia so donating blood hurts us does
our blood donation
hurt the recipient do they get our ebv
and other
viruses they get our ebv yeah they do
they get her up they get her ebv's they
get her simplexes they get her other
viruses
they get hhv sixes but
but i mean this is life i mean it's it's
either
the the thing is with blood donation is
is
we need blood donations right because we
need to save people's lives for
surgeries
life-saving medicine car accidents um
all kinds of issues right with heart
surgeries all of it so we need
we need blood transfusions for a lot of
different conditions so we need that so
yeah
people might pick up you know somebody
else's ebv
but ebv doesn't ebv is not really in the
blood a lot so that's why it's it's okay
because
even though you could potentially
somebody could get potentially get
somebody's ebv but that's if it's more
of an infectious stage in that moment
but if it's not an infectious stage not
reactivated or anything like that
then they won't get it chances are they
won't get it because ebv tends to stay
in all the organs
and it hides in all the organs but
someone could potentially get one from
somebody's shore through that it it does
happen but that's
not my concern is this is listen to the
podcast though right the blood draw
podcast my concern is
and your number one question is does
blood draw does does
donated blood hurt us and
i talk about how it takes away our
immune system so that our ebvs can come
out of dormancy
they can get reactivated we can have
more problems with their health we can
go backwards with their symptoms
so it's not it's not i don't want you to
not donate blood but i talk about maybe
a better way of doing it like preparing
yourself taking care of yourself
beforehand
i also recommend uh more men donating
blood because
it's just women that donate blood and i
know that's a pretty
bold statement that it's just women
donating blood
because there are men donating blood yes
but there's
mostly women and mostly women that don't
feel good donate blood
women that uh there's this small
percentage of women that feel healthy
and strong and don't have any symptoms
that ever donate blood
they're just but but what's interesting
is it's like
women that are living with symptoms and
not feeling good
and dealing with issues of all kinds
they're the ones donating blood for the
most part they make up the majority of
the blood donations which is
unbelievable when you think about it
right
and those are the people that
that need their reserves and need their
immune system strong
and then they're the ones giving out all
the blood and weakening themselves more
and more
that's scary all in its own when i
really think about it but
the bottom line is you can protect
yourself before a blood donation you
protect yourself after a blood donation
so i talk about that in the medical mean
podcast
at apple podcast link is in the
description the blood draw episode right
and you can learn more about it and i
believe we need to donate blood yeah but
but there's
ways to do it especially if you have a
symptom or you have a condition that's
when i tell people you know don't do it
for now
don't donate blood now when you're sick
because then you lose your immune system
through the blood donation they take a
pint of blood they take a large part of
your immune system and then you can go
backwards and even get so sick you might
be
ending up needing a blood transfusion
down the road because sickness gets you
know
it takes over so but listen to the
podcast episode
for sure it's it's all important
information
janelle i never seen a man donating
blood at the blood bank
um no it's rare it's rare
so the system has and i'll tell you one
of the reasons why this is interesting
the system has trained women to do it
you know and now the system works like
the medical system
trains women they want to train women
like dogs
like like dogs that's what they do and
it's
higher up it's not the doctors but it's
higher up and they train women to give
out all their blood
that's what they do they train women who
are sick to give out all their blood
okay is there something wrong with that
don't you think like is there something
wrong with that or what
and and then this is like this is
unbelievable when i think about it
right um and so this is just some of
this stuff
anyway you got to hear the podcast
medically and podcasted apple podcast
and you're right
no there's there's it's ever it's rare
oh here's another thing
it's rare you're going to see women
donating blood at the blood donation
clinic
that are strong healthy with no symptoms
how's that
women that are just out there living
their life don't even know what it's
like to be sick never had a symptom yet
they're not donating blood ever they're
just like it's they're not
thinking about it i don't know i think
but for some reason
women that are not well and struggling
they're like for some reason they're
hurting them in like
cattle or something to just or sheep to
just get in to just dump all their blood
out
it's the most bizarre thing um
clearly nature what do you do for chest
tightness so chest tightness is an
eptine epstein-barr shingle so these are
viral
symptoms vagus nerve gets inflamed and
look ask your doctor what he or she
thinks okay
you take the book to your doctor right
but if it was me and i had chest
tightness that was
uh mysterious to the doctor if it was me
i'd be going through here
i'd be looking at the epstein-barr
protocol that's what i would be doing
i would discover it's the vagus nerve
being inflamed that's what i would do
if it was happening to a family member i
would look in here and i'd be like okay
well i want my uncle on the micro sea
that's what i want my uncle on i mean
you do what you need to do and you you
talk to your doctor and do what he tells
you to do but i'm just saying
that i would have my uncle on some lemon
balm
i'd be like you know that's what i would
do is
it and i'd be looking in here you know
and saying okay well my uncle needs to
beyond lysine
and i'm looking at the dosages in here
and it says dosages
and well you know let me ask my doctor
you know sure but i would just say to my
uncle here it is
gina says i had a doctor recommended i
donate to to
rid iron overload
um that's
modern day bloodletting just like blood
draws in general are they take so much
blood
they don't need to take this much blood
i mean i look i talked about this before
um so that's all the blood they need
just for an a1c you guys probably can't
even see it i got a lot of lights on me
right now you see that little dot
that's all they need for just an a1c
that's all they need for just a blood
test
but when you're talking about high in
iron and being like being high in iron
instead of science research learning how
to fix the problem learning how to work
with the liver the spleen
and and the bones and the toxic heavy
metals that are inside
a woman's body that are causing that and
the viral issues that are causing high
iron instead of
signs of research trying to discover why
someone has high iron right instead of
them doing that
they just do the bloodletting so they
just say hey dump your blood
you know let's let's you know let's take
out your blood let's draw blood from you
so they draw blood or they tell you to
donate blood right
and instead of them trying to find out
what's going on and with medical medium
books you'll find out it's it's
it's the low-grade viral issues it's the
toxic heavy metals mercury is a really
big one for
why iron goes all over the place so
these just information that's really
helpful i made some noise you guys i'm
heading off soon to
on average they draw two tubes cbc and
cmp
on average um no
it's not on average um diana
average seven tubes seven tubes for
anything
seven tubes everybody goes to get blood
work no matter what blood test the
doctor
orders seven tubes five tubes is way too
much and five tubes they do
it a lot of times five tubes go out
right yeah if they just want a complete
blood count and you lock your doctor
down on that
cbc and you hold your doctor to it
then yes they may take two tubes but
that's not how it works
99.9 of everybody goes
to their doctor their doctor orders the
blood tests and five
tubes minimum they get they take minimum
no matter what seven tubes 14 tubes 10
tubes and that's not when you
if you're getting sick so say you're
somebody and you've never had a symptom
in your life and you're at a checkup at
your doctor's office and they just want
to look at your cbc
yeah you might get that one doctor that
says just takes two tubes
but i'm sorry 99.9 percent of them will
take five
tubes and they'll be like oh we're gonna
check your vitamin d2 we're gonna check
this yeah you gotta
hold your doctor down you gotta hold
your doctor down
but yeah i mean and right now people are
going backwards fast right now because
of new medical treatment so i'm just
gonna do a whistle are you guys okay
with the whistle right now
are you ready
new medical treatment
making people go downhill fast
real fast give it six months to eight
months to a year
people are gonna be a real sick
giving everybody like a little heads up
there and
that's why this is probably the most
important book of the
century because we're heading to a very
bad
place with a lot of sick people
and um and they're gonna need to know
why the reactivated epson bar
is reactivating and they're going
downhill fast so we have to make sure
they get the information there i think
some of you guys know what that whistle
means
i have a feeling i think probably a
bunch of you are like why is he
whistling
why the heck is he whistling
christina bailey i have been getting 14
tubes of blood drawn every four months
for years
this is going to stop after um hearing
your podcast
thank you that podcast episode's
critical medically podcasted apple
podcast the blood draw episode
okay am i am i allowed to hey linda you
still there
wait is she here linda you still there
linda the hater called me a charlatan
haven't heard that one before linda you
still there
um is it okay if i promote my podcast
is it okay if i tell everybody that
about the medical media podcast or is
that too much
is that an ego or something um
is it okay if i tell everybody that my
information is original and unique
are you there is it okay if i tell
everybody i'm heading to
ig and tick tock in a minute can i tell
anybody anything
i have to be quiet i have to shut up
okay i have to be quiet and shut up i'm
not allowed to tell anybody anything
i got you linda what linda you hanging
up on me don't hang up on me
don't don't
guys i gotta go to tick-tock and ig and
hopefully
i am not a little more pumped up there
because sometimes i get pumped up there
a little bit more and there's a lot more
trolls
okay guys made some noise i'm setting
everything up
again but it's ig and tick tock
look out i might bring in some new props
okay put a quirk in it linda
all right love you guys god bless you