medium new edition this is a recipe in
the 28-day cleanse
that's healed millions worldwide this is
the famous 28-day cleanse
that actually got people's lives back it
got him out of mattress island off of
couch island
and so in the new edition the revised
and expanded new edition of medical
medium
what i did was i put these killer
recipes in here
i'm making the banana nori wraps i'm
really pumped about it
and wait do you guys try these too and
it's part of the 28 day cleanse i mean
how cool is that a recipe
for the 28 day cleanse if you guys don't
have this
it's coming out soon pre-order it now
amazon.com
us you know you can get it there you can
get it you know somewhere else overseas
you can get it
um in the uk but just you know australia
just look at check into it this is the
new edition
medical medium okay revised and expanded
and i'm making the banana
nori wraps right here and if you guys
don't like banana
i'm doing a potato nori wrap too so i
have some potatoes here
um really excited about that so i got
steamed potatoes i cut them in half
right here so this is if you want the
option of not using banana
in this banana nori wrap and you can
make a potato nori wrap
so i'm excited lots of stuff to talk
about too and
i'm gonna um and i'm good hi anthony can
you put an
orange in your celery juice no don't do
that because then the celery juice won't
work
it has to be by itself it can't be
diluted you guys lots of talk about nori
sheets so that's seaweed nori sheets you
guys know about these right here
so i got my nori sheets
so um here's an oreo sheet right here
you guys know and i'm gonna make these
wraps
here's the sheet i'm excited about it
so we're going to make the potato nori
wraps we're going to make
the banana nori wraps right here
so if you guys if there's a glitch on
facebook i'm on youtube
simultaneously right now so i'm actually
on youtube right now doing the same
thing so
i'm connecting on youtube doing this
right now with facebook too
so what happens if there's a glitch on
facebook right now like you get kicked
off or something
and you're trying to find your way back
just go to youtube you can do that so
anybody getting kicked off right now or
anything like that because there's a
glitch i'm hearing
people are having a hard time finding me
and they're getting bumped off
so head to youtube i'm on youtube right
now
so on the medical medium youtube channel
letting you guys know
you don't care for bananas i just saw
that well
that's why the potato nori wrap is the
other option
so that's what i'm making um
yeah what about baking yeast for breads
and cakes bad too so nutritional yeast
is bad baking yeast is bad too
so yeah um okay you guys let's start
working on this let's start making these
i'm excited about this if you just came
on here
just know i'm actually on youtube right
now so if you have a glitch with
facebook or you get bumped off or
something
go to youtube i'm on there now live so
simultaneously with facebook right now
that's the medical medium new edition
i'm making a recipe of the
day cleanse the banana nori wrap but i'm
gonna make a potato nori wrap too hey
michelle l
bananas are miraculous they really are
i've seen them heal so many people's
digestive issues
in so many different ways so let's get
started
you guys so what's cool about these
is you can't really mess up
it's not really possible except if you
don't roll
your norrish you know right if you don't
roll your nori sheet right that may be
one way but you can't really go
too wrong but i'm gonna give you all the
tips important tips when you're doing
this right here
so everything matters with that now you
can damp the nori sheet which is what i
like to do i like to damp
it dampen it right you can dampen it
with a little bit of water
like just like very like a little bit of
water on your fingertips if you want
i like to use orange for this recipe a
lot of other recipes i use
lemon to dampen the nori sheet just
letting you know but i'm going to use
orange right here christina massey i
started in june last year with celery
juice took me four months
no more migraines god bless you
incredible
so proud of you um that's
that's the power of celery juice but
hey you know christina there's no
scientific studies out there
so for celery juice but you kept with it
you know so you must
be pretty spiritual because that
information comes from above and
there's no scientific study that fixes
people with chronic illness or chronic
migraines or anything
and that's what people say to be like
well don't drink your celery juice
there's no
scientific study oh that's funny that's
a good one
you know i cuz because i didn't know
scientific studies actually got anybody
all these
all these years better 30 40 50 60 years
of chronic illness and there's not one
scientific study that fixed anybody with
that mysterious chronic illness
but celery juice works but hey
no one wants you on there in the science
world because it wasn't studied so they
don't want you drinking it they would
rather have your migraines christina
stay there forever and free to suffer
so hey i'm proud of you amazing um
yeah i'm a handful today for sure i got
lots of stuff to talk about you guys
you might want to hang in there for this
one if you guys have a glitch on
facebook just go to youtube i'm live
right now and i'm going to be
on tick tock live later because we got
some glitches on instagram
so i'm going to be on tick tock live
later too
um there's no shingles
test just so you know that so
uh lorraine casey hi anthony what do you
ask
our doctor to test for if you think you
have shingles they
can't test for that it's really hard to
find that shingles virus
really difficult so what happens is with
viruses like shingles and epstein-barr
is they may trigger off the a a they may
trigger off the c-reactive protein test
they may trigger off the mthfr gene
mutation test these are all
in inflammation markers right
so when your doctors just say to your
doctor hey test for any inflammation
markers then if anything comes up with
any
mysterious inflammation anywhere that
could be right there the a a and so
forth an anti-nuclear antigen test
that could lead to hey there's
epstein-barr behind the scenes there's
shingles behind the scenes but they
don't have
a grip on the over 30 varieties of
shingles that i talk about in the books
there's cleanse the heel right here they
don't have a grip on that
so um anyway and then but i got to tell
you here that's protocols in there i got
to tell you
this book right here has the shingles
chapter
that has really uncovered the whole
thing with the 30 varieties of shingles
i added information in this book this is
the new edition
holt shingles chapter in here this is
the one with the non-rashing shingles
the rashing shingles this is
mind-blowing check that out
um making nora rolls right now so look
let's start with
banana we'll do potato we'll do a banana
then we'll do potato
we'll do banana then we'll do potato
right um
so anyway let's talk about shingles for
a minute because lorraine that was
really
you know important right there shingles
causes that sciatic nerve pain people
don't know about and i talk about that
in book one
so it causes trigeminal neuralgia
that's another thing i talk about in
book one so that's another one
shingles causes a lot of different
things and
this is the book that started it all
about shingles this is what's teaching
people that shingles isn't just a rash
and that's the whole point this is the
book that actually
uncovered that so now doctors know that
shingles may not be a rash
um other health professionals health
authorities know that shingles may not
be
rash based it's not just that rash the
link is in the description
about this medical medium book and
so this is the new edition um i've
revised and expanded about shingles big
chapter in here
so what happens you guys is that if you
got this mysterious sciatic nerve pain
because there's people with the worst
back conditions their backs are chewed
up beat up
discs are bulging out and they got no
pain no pain
degenerative discs okay degenerative
discs
discs falling apart but no pain
people with all kinds of back issues i'm
cutting banana i'm going to do banana
nori wraps and then i'm going to do
potato nori wraps for the people who
don't like banana
and um keep in mind that
there's a lot of people with the worst
backs not in pain
and then there's people that don't have
a lot of big problems with their back
but they're in agony and they got that
shooting pain running down their leg
they're really in a jam you know can't
function they can't walk good
and shingles and flames the lower back
it's
viral inflammation that's what shingles
likes to do that's one thing it does
i'm gonna put a strip of banana in here
so you guys with me so far i'm making
the nori
the nori wraps right here now i got
these beautiful alfalfa sprouts
so that's one thing i'm going to put in
here a little bit of these beautiful
alfalfa sprouts
you don't have to fill these up really
high
you guys don't have to do that if you
guys get a glitch
watch me on youtube live right now if
you do um janine yep your info
on non-rashing shingles has saved my
sanity
as it's the first time the symptoms you
explain are spot
on one after the other thank you janine
thanks for being here
bless your heart so glad you're here um
you guys in this nori roll i'm gonna put
a green onion which is a scallion um
you can call them green onions uh i call
them scallions and you can cut that
scallion in half if you want to
i like to cut them i also like to leave
them whole it depends on how i'm feeling
that day i might
with the mood i'm in like what kind of
mood i'm in
so i'm kind of tearing this scallion
apart a little bit
putting it in here so i got the scallion
in there
that's the green onion i got some
sprouts i'm going to put a little bit
more of these alfalfa sprouts these are
healing foods
sprouts are a powerful healing tool
we got some of this too we got some of
this cilantro
julie i get back pain every time i get a
big
upset what happens is that
when you get upset like a big upset like
any kind of stress
or something really triggers you off
adrenaline
can actually up that inflammation
because adrenaline
could stimulate and feed a virus like
shingles
also adrenaline can lower the immune
system so if you get a big upset your
immune system lowers
low-grade viral stuff kicks up and then
boom the back has a problem that's how
it works
um this is dulce these are dulce
strips right here i like being generous
with dolls inside these nori wraps this
is the banana nori wrap you can do
banananori wrap you can do uh potato
nori wrap i got potatoes here
so now you can moisten the dull strips
i'm not going to moisten these i'm going
to kind of leave them dry
and flavor is just so packed in that
nori
that that i'm sorry dulce strip that's
what it is
and michelle l hey you're here glad
you're here today glad everybody's
coming on
susie says i don't like any vegetables
except corn i don't eat onions
the corns the only vegetable you like
well there's so many great vegetables to
try susie there's so many great
vegetables
corn is a grain so that's not even a
vegetable
so i have to we have to find a vegetable
for you
because that's a grain all right so
i'm gonna roll this up so i have the
dolls in here i got a little bit of
cilantro i'm gonna talk about the power
of cilantro in a little while
kyle wick good to see you what else can
i do i do the three
things in the morning heavy metal detox
celery juice and lemon water for my
rheumatoid arthritis room toward pain
what else is going on okay first of all
you're doing some incredible things
right there
okay so that's to start with guys i just
rolled up
anori right here this is the banananori
wrap
um this is one i'm
not going to cut it yet but i'm going to
eventually get there i'm going to roll a
couple of these
um first of all there's protocols
there's a there's a ra protocol
in cleanse the heal but in this book
here
i mean there's really infra this thing's
packed with ra information with the
protocol
and what ra is diagnosed as an
autoimmune condition
autoimmune condition means they don't
know science research
doesn't know what's causing it so it's a
mystery i
i reveal that mystery it's viral the
cause of ra
rheumatoid arthritis is epstein-barr so
if you want to heal and you're doing the
celery juice and heavy metal detox
you're doing lemon water it's a great
start
but it would be good to learn maybe what
foods you shouldn't do because those
foods will feed the epstein-barr virus
make you sicker or maybe learn a
protocol that's in here
so this is the new addition make sure
it's a new edition that's the way to go
on that
so i'm going to make another one with
you guys we're going to make a bunch of
these i'm going to cut them up in a
little while too
and you guys have been thinking about a
couple different things
you know a friend of mine i haven't
talked to in a long time
right she's pregnant and
she was asking me different things what
can she do for her health
and i found out that she's on caffeine
she was on a lot of caffeine before she
got pregnant
and she's on caffeine while she's
pregnant
now she didn't know she was on caffeine
while she's pregnant but she found out
when i spoke to her she was on a lot of
caffeine
while being pregnant and i want to talk
about
what happens there because she was
asking me well what can go wrong
what can happen am i okay is my baby
okay
what does this mean so she didn't know
she was on caffeine
but she was she was eating chocolate
every day
she was told by a health practitioner
she's told also by someone else that
chocolate's really good for you when
it's the 70
80 90 the dark chocolate the chocolate
cacao nibs all that stuff
chocolate powder so she was told it was
really good for her so she
was eating it while pregnant
something to really kind of digest there
for a second while i'm making this nori
this next nori
wrap um getting some sprouts here
think about that a little bit she was
asking me well
i didn't know chocolate was packed with
caffeine i go especially that chocolate
it's really packed with caffeine she's
like okay so i've been on caffeine every
day
with my baby i go yeah
your baby's got the caffeine running
through
it you know and
you know and right now she's she so
she's
she's so she got really spooked for a
minute she's like what do i do i said
first of all stop the caffeine
and then she said well what is it doing
to my baby
what is it doing to my baby and i said
for one
your baby is not going to be able to
rest so easy
because your baby is going to be over
stimulated
and inside the womb basically your baby
is going to be all jacked up on caffeine
and that's going to be very difficult
for the baby
and she stopped immediately immediately
just stopped
she's a very spiritual person knows a
decent amount of health information
always thought herself to be you know
yeah a health expert in many ways
just a lot of natural things and having
a natural childbirth
right and she's got it all planned and
her girlfriends are pregnant they're all
eating chocolate
and what happens is people wonder why
their baby doesn't sleep
when their baby's born
babies going through withdrawal which
all can last a long time for a baby
and it depends on the breast milk too
how much caffeine are you using
that's going into the breast milk all
this stuff
really important information so i want
to keep on going with it i just want to
get this nori rolled up in a second here
caffeine so i was telling her caffeine's
a type of poison
it's a drug and
i'm going to get some i'm actually going
to get some dull strips we're going to
go inside this nori roll here
it's delicious this is going to be so
good so she was
she was mortified because she was
wondering
because she's a mama bear you know in a
sense where she told me she goes i'm a
mama bear
i protect my friends babies i protect my
baby
and that's what she said to me and she
was she was wondering why
health professionals are saying it's
okay
like she's wondering why her doctor
thinks it's okay she's wondering why
it's on the internet and it's okay and
she's wondering why
health influencers that are pregnant are
thinking it's okay and health coaches
tell health influencers that are
pregnant and other people
that it's okay and she's realizing
it's not okay and it was like a huge
awakening
huge awakening just really was
and so when you have that much caffeine
running through your baby inside of you
it's it's it's not a good thing
if you don't know you just don't know
it's nobody's fault
not well actually it's not the mom's
fault at all
it's the fault of the system it's the
fault of the caffeine
industry it's the fault of caffeine
industry
health authorities health hackers
that think they're health experts it's
the fault of all them
and then them telling women it's okay to
do caffeine
while you're pregnant okay to do
caffeine after pregnancy and everything
else
so so um but
but the thing is is that the bottom line
is when it comes down to that
a lot of things can happen your baby can
not rest
while your baby wants to rest internally
and so that caffeine makes it so if the
baby wanted to rest
naturally if the baby was going to rest
naturally because there's a resting
there's a whole resting sequence that a
baby has inside the womb
that this shifts it and it rocks the
boat constantly
so and when that happens then you know
when the baby's born
then there's all kinds of sleep problems
in different ways i mean
baby could be up all night there's
withdrawal and then
if there's still chocolate happening
dirt that's filling up the breast milk
if you if the breast milk is getting
filled up the coffee drink caffeine
it's getting filled up with chocolate
caffeine matcha tea caffeine
and so they'll say oh matcha tea is good
for pregnant women it's great for women
get a lot of energy after a pregnancy
after giving birth
so i want to talk about that a little
bit more too so i'm cutting these right
here these two for now
so that's a banana wrap right there
i like them thinner so i do like them
thinner so that's a banana wrap
and i'll show you guys i'm going to make
a lot more i got to make the potato wrap
so women do a lot of caffeine before
they get pregnant
and they wear down their adrenals and
they wear down their adrenals and they
wear down their adrenals
okay and then they have a difficult
difficult uh birth childbirth
because their adrenals weaken so it can
lead into longer labor
a much more difficult time but no one's
teaching women about that
so it could be years of caffeine use
wasting the adrenals so by the time you
have your baby
then you have a difficult childbirth so
there's that alone all on its own
so that's an issue that happens too um
it takes tremendous amounts of
adrenaline
to give birth it takes like a lifetime
of adrenaline to give birth
that's how the birthing process happens
it's from that adrenaline surge
and it's not just one adrenaline surge
it's many adrenaline surges
it's lots of adrenaline surges through
throughout giving birth
and the adrenals have to be strong for
that and
women's adrenals already are challenged
in so many ways with just
today's world in so many ways in
different for different reasons
and so when it comes down to needing all
of that supersonic adrenaline strength
to give birth it's not there so then the
adrenals struggle and they struggle and
they struggle and they struggle
okay so that happens to women a lot
that's one thing right there i'm making
these banana wraps right here you guys
be using some alfalfa sprouts
but keep in mind though
that the caffeine industry they don't
care about any of this they just want to
make sure that
you get your high no one teaches you
different
and then after birth after birth
a mom can be more exhausted than she
should be because the adrenals aren't
recouping so then you need more caffeine
you need more chocolate you need more
matcha tea you need
more green tea you need more coffee
drinks
because you're trying to overcompensate
for that more
loss that more loss and that more loss
you know
and um so that's important to know there
that's something to consider but then
it's after with the breastfeeding that's
the thing too you got to keep in mind
with the breastfeeding
because of the breastfeeding the milk is
contaminated with
caffeine which is a poison and that's a
whole other thing on its own that we got
to be
mindful about putting some dolls in here
um guys making another one
another banana roll right here
so these are all things that kind of
keep to keep an eye on
so i'm rolling this one right here
so you guys if you just got here
i'm making these bananas nori wraps
so that's what i'm making so here they
are it's in the medical medium new
edition
i'm going to make potato wraps too so
i'm in the process
um going to make another
yeah i mean look this might not be
interesting to some people but
i think our children are are really
important i mean right
that's the whole thing everybody is so
worried
about your children and rightfully so
and
i think that when health authorities and
health experts don't teach women this
it's like i mean they know better
right don't they know better like the
health health experts
doctors should know better so um
something to be considered i'm gonna
make some potato wraps right now
actually
i'm going to move on to a potato wrap as
we speak
um so i'm cutting some potato slices
nice and thin
this is what i'm doing see guys i'll
read some questions right here what
comes after the sprouts
i'll be right there
i'm back so you guys making the potato
version right here so
i'm doing some cilantro
doing the green onion again so it's for
people that don't like bananas or
they're afraid of bananas
a lot of people are afraid of bananas
which is really sad because potassium is
a critical critical nutrient it really
is
critical mineral we need potassium for
our brain for neurotransmitters
so um i got some alfalfa sprouts i got
some cilantro in here i got some green
onion
i'm gonna put a little bit of
this dulse i'm gonna roll it up now you
can do these in different ways like with
the banana nori wrap
you can do the whole banana okay
so i'll show you that version too so i'm
going to cut these
that's the potato one
now you could use the whole banana in
here which is another way i like to do
it too i like to slice the banana
but i also like to do a whole banana so
i like to do
both versions recipe in the book has the
whole banana
so i'm going to use some orange right
here to moisten it up
so our children are supposed to be
really important but i noticed that
health experts podcast doctors
health influencers they're just pushing
pushing and pushing the whole
chocolate narrative they're pushing the
whole hey it's plant medicine they're
pushing the whole coffee drinks they're
pushing the whole matcha tea
and they're pushing down to pregnant
women but nobody's thinking
nobody's thinking about the babies when
it comes down to that
and that's where i'm kind of like that's
where i'm like wait a minute are we
losing it
like are we losing it or something
putting the whole banana in this one you
guys
because that's the way that's a great
way to do it
something to think about putting sprouts
in here
putting a little bit of cilantro in this
one too
and i think that's something we just
like missed you guys are making some
nori
some banana nori wraps right here so i'm
going to cut this one
this is the one with the whole banana
right here
but then the breast feeding we got to
think about the breast milk
being pure and clean i like the heavy
metal detox smoothie because it's
removing
nettles out of the breast milk that's
why the heavy metal detox smoothie is so
great
so there you go
that's the banana that's a whole banana
right there using this one
that's a banana nori wrap right there
see so you got the sprouts in there got
a little bit of cilantro in there you
got the banana you got the green onion
which is scallion right
so you got that um yeah it's like sushi
there you go
with a banana and i'm gonna do it with
potato too so
there we go so this is really fun just
making a bunch of these
this is probably like i don't know this
is this is a more
fun one for me i like it i'm going to
use some potato
do some potato versions squeezing a
little
orange juice on top of this nori sheet
so you want your breast milk to be
really really clean
you've got to look at what's with what
you consume and what you're eating
keep the caffeine out keep that out of
the breast milk so the baby's not
having problems because that's another
thing too babies
they'll get really really cranky
when they're going through constant
caffeine withdrawal each day
and then yeah they're addicted to
caffeine through the breast milk
and won't sleep or will cry more
be unhappy because that's the caffeine
going on and that's the caffeine
talking in the baby
and almost every mom
is drinking or eating some kind of
caffeine product
while breastfeeding no one's talking
about it
no one's talking about it no one says
anything about it there's nothing out
there
health professionals don't talk about it
no well what am i saying health
professionals should say do more
caffeine
health professionals just say tell moms
that are breastfeeding do more
of it putting some dulls in here again
make sure you do lots of chocolate
so and it's really sad because it's
going to guarantee
that your baby grows up and then we'll
be consuming caffeine more and more and
more
and then the cycle never gets broken
ever
anyway so you guys are making these talk
about
a couple bunch of things i want to read
some comments too
yeah and it's not it's not the doreen
it's not the mom's faults at all of
course not no way
it's they want to do the best there is
for their kids
100 they want to do the best they want
to make sure
the kids their their babies get the best
there is all of it
and then the whole thing with after
pregnancy you get the hair loss
so a lot of women suffer from hair
thinning hair loss after pregnancies
even if it's six months after
child birth a year after child birth two
months after childbirth
during childbirth and because so much
adrenaline
was used and caffeine was stimulating so
much adrenaline so you get the hair
thinning
and look i know i've been talking about
caffeine a lot you guys would totally
get it but there's so many different
aspects of it that's why
it's not just one thing it's just not
one just not just one aspect or one part
of
the story with caffeine so i don't mean
to caffeine you guys crazy but
there's a reason for it because it's not
just okay
caffeine withdrawal and people shouldn't
be doing it not good for them no
it ages the skin the hair thins hair
falls out for women there's that the sun
spots all happen and they gotta all get
the laser techniques the hormones get
all in balance right
so all that is coming out of the
adrenals all that's you know all that
it's because of the adrenals because of
the caffeine but then the baby
the whole baby protection protecting the
baby and making sure
your baby's safe make sure your baby has
the best food and
all of that well no one's thinking about
the caffeine part there
and and um and here's the thing
coffee's just been getting stronger
chocolate's been getting stronger
and stronger so now we're in a place
where espressos there's moms out there
breastfeeding while doing espressos and
because they're told to
do it now
they're told to do it i mean look you
guys i could just forget it
i could forget it never talk about it
again how about that
never tell anybody we just don't tell
anybody
let's keep it quiet not tell anybody not
say anything okay
and then just let women that are
pregnant make sure they're eating lots
of chocolate make sure they're doing
lots of cacao make sure they're doing
lots of coffee drinks and everything
else and matcha tea while pregnant
and then also breastfeeding we can do
that we can keep it quiet
i mean we right we don't have to go
there
but i just i just i can't do that
um there's a lot of skin hacking going
these days a lot of biohacking for skin
you guys like it's all about hacking
skin
issues it's all about hacking skin
problems
you know acne scarring you know micro
needling to try to heal
acne scarring micro needling to try to
get really good
skin okay really abrasive peels skin
peels
right really abrasive exfoliations
so there's a lot of that going on
okay and so that's a big thing right now
it's all about skin so
you know you'll see on you'll see on the
internet you'll see on youtube you'll
see
you know it's all about skin skin skin
and
social media and what can you do for
your skin like
what kind of what kind of treatment can
you do for your skin skin on your your
skin on your face
in other areas and what's going on is
that when you do like the micro needling
we think that that's a good thing we're
being taught that that's a good thing
but it's actually not
so if you guys always want to know like
what i'm thinking or what
you know my thoughts are about it all
because i know you guys have a lot of
questions and i've seen a question about
that but i never answered it before
and i haven't i didn't have a chance but
here's how this here's how it works the
micro needling
injures the skin right so it injures it
so then
your skin your body's healing process
tr amps up and it tries to heal that
injury so you're doing the micro
needling so you're doing that all on
your face and micro needling and
everything right
and you're doing that and so you're
injuring your skin you're
injuring it in hopes that it heals
and it comes out better right
it's really not the reality of it that's
not how it works
what happens is that your body is over
compensating in the moment to try to
heal what you're doing for an injury
so you're doing the micro needling and
then your body tries to overcompensate
and
oh my god i got the body your body's
like talking and like i gotta heal
this your body goes into high gear to
heal this and it takes a lot of reserves
it takes a lot of physical reserves
internally to go and try to heal the
skin after you micro needle right
and do really really harsh peels um
but the problems in our skin is really
within so it's deep inside of us that's
where the real problems
lie with skin it's not on the surface
that's not where the problem
lies it's within it's deeper that's
where the real issues are
and so we try a lot of different things
we're always trying to hack our skin
we're always trying to
you know bio hacks and we're always
hacking our skin and that's a big thing
everybody's micro needling but what
happens is with that
is you end up with
more difficult skin later on from all
the micro needling
so i thought it would kind of throw that
throw that out to you guys so
just in case i can look out for you and
protect you guys because that's what i'm
trying to do it's like
i'm not i'm not doing this for
not doing this because i enjoy it so
much
doing this because i feel i have to
protect you guys that's how it's always
been since i was four years old
getting this information it's about
protecting you guys right
and if you're somebody into
microneedling that's what you like to do
you believe in it look
just move move my thoughts aside and do
it if you want to do
but you're causing an injury that's
forcing your body to then repair it
so that's what's happening you're
creating an injury forcing your body to
repair it
okay and so your body's gonna
kill itself to overcompensate
to try to repair the injuries you're
creating in hopes that
it ends up repairing any other day it's
a great theory meaning
that it can repair any other damage it's
a great theory
but what you get is you get this really
mild
mild mild scar tissue that starts to
occur and that scar tissue
gets kind of sleek okay so it gets kind
of polished because that's what scar
tissue can do
when it's even like that so you're doing
this even
version of scar tissue it's not just one
like say acne
and you got a cystic acne and there's
just one here and there's one here now
you got a scar here and you got a scar
here the micro needling first of all
isn't that deep i know
but it's doing it evenly everywhere
but it's creating a very mild
scar like a sheet like a scar
sheet everywhere very mild one and over
time
that can get really really abrasive
later on as the years go on
now
[Music]
the goal for skin and to get skin to
heal and to get skin as good as you want
to get it and get skin
really nice is you got to heal
internally
that's how it happens you gotta fix your
liver
you have to go after the very thing that
creates cystic acne too
those are the things that's where the
eye has to be on the ball like that's it
right there
you guys are having any glitches on
facebook just watch me on youtube right
now i'm on youtube
live right here because i heard people
were having some glitches
one of the ways to kill your skin is
caffeine once again
and look it's only so many times you
want to hear it probably because you're
like no
no i can't quit oh no i heard it's good
for me he's driving me crazy with this
caffeine thing
but if you care about your skin that's
one thing right there that's a big deal
the other thing is
you know the foods you're doing like
what foods vinegar is the skin killer
not surfacely not surfacely like apple
cider vinegar on the surface is actually
okay for the skin
because it can pull away any kind of
corrosive
material on the skin any kind of dead
skin cells
apple cider vinegar tends to help remove
those any kind of toxins on your skin
surface apple cider vinegar on your skin
surface is actually helpful right
diluted not straight but diluted
all right but apple cider vinegar
internally
creates skin problems that's the other
thing you guys are making the
banana nori wraps potato nori wraps
putting a little bit of cilantro
a little bit of sprouts these are
alfalfa sprouts right here i just want
to show you i don't think i showed
anybody
exactly what they look like but there
they are you guys know these the sprouts
that's a cilantro these are potatoes
this is some dolls i'm using a lot of
dolls
i really love it in these so using a
little bit more
i got the green onions which are over
here which are scallions the green
onions right
i got that so i'm making these i'm going
to roll this one up
i think i got to put a little bit of
dolls in here
love you anthony what about botox then
look i mean a lot of people everybody's
doing it a lot not everybody but a lot
of people are doing it
um i worry about it i worry about the
whole botulism thing because you know if
it
escapes get away if it gets away if it
if it there's a lot of people that have
been injured by it because it's because
it's part of big pharma
um anybody who really talks about their
injuries about it it gets scrubbed
so it gets it gets scrubbed on the
internet
you gotta search hard to find the people
who have been injured from botox
because it just if they disappear like
they never existed on the internet
so it's like they get this horrible
reaction that happens their face blows
up
they're in the hospital for a month
because the botox
they can't use their they can't they
can't talk right
they're face troops they get the balls
bell's palsy
they get something wrong with kind of
their shoulder and their arm because it
runs down in there
they get high fevers whatever it is they
get and they're in the hospital the
minute they go on social media and they
try to sell
they try to tell their story and tell
their story they all of a sudden kind of
like
get nobody watching anymore and they all
of a sudden just disappear over time
and then they're gone they've been
scrubbed they've been scrubbed off the
internet
because any kind of stuff like adverse
stuff that happens with big pharma
and you start complaining and you start
freaking out you either have a guy with
a black suit show up at your door and
tell you never to talk about it again
or you'll just get scrubbed off the
internet is what really happens in the
old days it was like somebody with a
black suit would show up
make sure you shut the hell up and never
talk about
never talk about your your big pharma
injury
this is really terrible all right guys
i got some alfalfa sprouts right here i
got some cilantro right here
oh man so anyway as far as botox goes i
mean i wouldn't
personally i wouldn't do it but i know a
lot of people do it and they they
live by it i live by it i get it
i'm not i'm not guess i'm not here to
judge anybody
it's like i'm just here to give you look
you might be somebody
that wants to know you shouldn't be on
chocolate while pregnant you might be
somebody
okay and you might be really grateful or
thankful that
i i told you okay and then you might be
somebody else who's like
hell no i'm gonna do my chocolate you
ain't gonna stop me
baby or no baby you might be somebody
like that and that's okay i'm not
judging you it's not it's a hard world
you know a lot of people need their
chocolate get by
you know and a lot of people can't think
without their caffeine they can't even
put
a sentence together without it because
they're struggling with problems and
they're not in a place where they can
fix it so easy right now
so tell you guys something interesting
you know when you get blood work
a couple things i want to tell you about
blood work okay one is
ask your doctor okay to not
when the when you do the blood work
don't do so many vials of blood that's
one thing right there
because they'll just drain the life out
of you like i've been i've been teaching
doctors
two or three vials that's it you get
another blood test if you want to test
for other things and you do another two
or three vials don't do six vials don't
do five vials don't do seven vials don't
do 10 vials
don't do 12 vials don't do 14 don't do
26 vials
no yeah guess what some doctors they'll
pull 26 vials out of people
um you got to remember this when you're
getting blood tests and i want to talk
about this about blood a bunch of
different stuff about blood
because i really haven't covered blood
enough and i want to really cover i'm
going to cover what i can now but
there's it's going to probably take a
couple of cooking sessions
to cover all the blood stuff right so
i'm going to give you a couple of pieces
with it
i'm making potato nori wraps i'm going
to cut more potato right here
okay first of all ask your doctor to
keep it minimal
less blood drawn
if he says well i'm not going to be able
to test for this and this and this and
this and this say can you cut it in half
and test for those another day i come in
write it up do it
it's one thing because when you're sick
and you've got chronic illness and
you've got any kind of low grade viral
stuff if you're not well whatever that
is
that you're going through the more blood
taken at once
you just lost your immune system it's
gone out the door
bye gone one shot you're getting your
blood work
they're drawing your blood well there's
one vial boom okay that's okay two vials
boom
three vials boom four boom here's your
immune system your white count
neutrophils basal cells monocytes your
lymphocytes all going out that's it so
your immune system is
being removed and if you're viral with
epstein-barr you got ra hashimoto's
ms you got lupus you got whatever you
got going on it could be eczema
psoriasis
anything reproductive problems then your
body has to build up and recreate a
brand new immune system for your
bloodstream and in that
moment those bugs streptococcus
epstein-barr whatever are going to creep
up they can creep
up because your immune system was
removed so you want to do minimal
like okay can i get three vials not six
or eight
and then i'll come back and you then
test for the other things and i'll get
three more vials
that's really powerful information get
two vials
and the other thing too if you can't go
that route your doctor's like no i need
five aisles i need six vials of blood i
need seven vials of blood
ask them if you can do half vials of
blood because guess what the blood
the the just so you know um when they
test for blood when they test your blood
they throw it all away
they take this much that much out of a
vial
that much most of the time and they
throw away all your blood
it all gets thrown away okay so it's a
scam too
so ask your doctor can you go with half
vials of blood
send it to the blood testing place the
labs with half of them filled
this way if you do three half vials it's
only really what
one and a half if you do five half files
you're only what two and a half or
whatever
you guys i'm doing some i hope my math
is right
never went to college
was too busy helping people heal
couldn't do it was way too busy had too
many people knocking on my door
working on saving lives all these years
it just didn't have the time to go to
school didn't have time to go to college
but i can tell you how to protect
yourself and
and give you books that have already
saved lots of lives you guys i'm making
the banana nori wraps right here there
it is medical medium
revised and expanded new edition find it
on amazon
um another thing too with blood testing
which is interesting so i'm just talking
about that part let's get some
dolls right here so i gotta i gotta
cover some more blood information if you
guys are interested you guys get blood
work all the time
you guys get blood work so i got a
little bit more
okay the labs are lying lizzy lou the
labs say they can't run the blood work
unless the vials are full
they're lying they can they actually can
how do i know doctors tell me how do i
know paint doctors patients
that i've known through doctors have
have
insisted on half files and the labs have
run it
so you just have to fight for it a
little bit
making a pile of these wow okay so
another thing too is
you can get a blood test for something
like cortisol
get blood blood tests to check your
adrenals and cortisol right
and an hour later it's going to be
entirely different than when you had it
tested that moment
blood tests are so inconsistent that's
another thing
really interesting about blood tests
you got to take sometimes a lot of blood
tests and a lot of different tests with
the grain of salt
testing changes constantly within the
hour within a day if you go to bathroom
before you
get your blood test or go to bathroom
after you get your blood this is
entirely different
i will barber says i will ask about half
files
definitely ask about half vials because
if they're taking that much blood
it gets us sicker and sicker over time
so let me just let me just be straight
out about this this is critical to know
the more blood we get taken and the more
blood we get taken the more blood we get
taken
the sicker we get you know i call the
system the ultimate vampire
they don't do it right they don't
do it carefully they suck the life out
of us they
rob our immune systems with the blood
tests and they don't they're not careful
about it
they're not and people get sicker who
are viral and chronically ill and they
get sicker and sicker and sicker because
of it
so you want to be careful and ask about
half files if you can't get the half
vials
your doctor doesn't want to do it or
something's going on there then ask for
less vials drawn
and then go back again for other tests
so it's not
all those done at once and do another
potato roll up right here
and the body is always compensating too
all the time we've got to remember this
it's always compensating so the blood
tests are picking up the body
compensating all the time
that's something to keep in mind as well
you go through a stressful event your
body's compensating
it's always doing that your body's if
you're um
getting deficient in something your
body's compensating
it's always doing that so it's really
that's something to keep in mind all on
its own i want to go into that a little
bit more
too it's interesting
okay guys putting a little bit more dols
in here rolling up another one
[Applause]
educating myself says also explains
immune lowering
during menstruation which is medical
medium information
i put that out years ago immune system
lowers during
menstruation
publish first medical medium books
um yeah it totally explains that
exactly the amount of medical
medium information that's gotten out
there over the years with no science
behind it
none at all but it becomes law out there
it's you know and then but you'll hear
everybody where's your science where's
your signs where's your science
so here's how it works too is like your
body's over compensating constantly for
everything we do
that we shouldn't do everything we do
that we shouldn't do our bodies
overcompensating
non-stop right you drink caffeine our
bodies overcompensating
right there we challenge our body it
compensates
okay we do an ice cold plunge
our bodies freaking out goes into crisis
and tries to find homeostasis and
overcompensates
our body is constantly trying to find
that homeostasis
all the time at every moment anywhere
anyhow
and and when they take blood they
they've never accounted for that really
that our body's constantly trying to
find a balance
so when they take blood they don't
realize it's much deeper than what it
really is that you read on the results
too i'm not saying all the results are
wrong and that's not it
it's just that our bodies are in it's a
working process
every day to overcompensate everything
we're doing so if we got too much fat in
our bloodstream our body's
overcompensating by really
releasing more adrenaline to thin it out
um if we're under a lot of stress
our bodies like over compensating to
deal with the stress
and it's just it's this constant tug and
pull
tug and pull that's why blood tests are
not the same
an hour later it's why blood tests are
not the same two hours later or a day
later
they're different i'm gonna do a banana
right now
this is the next one i'm gonna do
so you got to take the average you know
that's what they really should do they
should be like i'm going to put a whole
banana in here like this
they should take the average of the test
like hormone test in the morning
come back the next day in the afternoon
get another hormone test then
you get that blood run you get that
blood run the lab and then what you have
here is
you go somewhere you'll see the numbers
are different
or you get a blood test in the morning
one day and then a week later you get a
blood test in the morning that next day
and then next a week later and you'll
see why are the numbers different
why are the numbers constantly different
because you might have had a little
stress in your life maybe you had
something happen
maybe something's going on maybe you're
eating differently maybe you had
something you shouldn't have eaten
maybe something like that the body tries
to compensate
constantly the numbers change your
body's trying to find homeostasis
and that's how it works
i made a really big one right here so
when i cut it in half you'll see i mean
they become nori wraps when you make
them bigger and that's what the recipe
calls for
it really calls for this so what i'm
gonna do i'm gonna cut this one in half
like this
so that's the nori that's the nori wrap
there's a full banana in there you got
the sprouts you got the cilantro
you got a little bit of the doll
stripped in there and you got the green
onion you see
now i'm going to cut them also small too
so i'm going to do that as well i'm
going to cut them
into little circles like i like to do
and fill the plate
fill the plate up and that's where i'm
going next
yep
um you can't test for heavy metals
through blood work
because that's not going to work because
heavy metals sit and saturate inside the
organ tissue so toxic heavy metals sit
inside the brain
they sit inside the glial cells the
brain tissue they sit
they sit deep inside the brain so what
happens is they sit deep inside the
liver they sit deep inside our organs so
hey do i have toxic metals or not i
don't know let me go get a blood test at
the doctor's office
and the doctor the doctor might be like
hey you got little traces of it but i
don't think you have it bad
those traces in your bloodstream are
from new exposure
brand new exposure toxic heavy metals
old exposure sit inside your brain
forever
but new exposure on a daily level will
show up on the blood test and it might
not even be perfect on that level too
carmen says i have too much calcium in
my blood
what can i do i mean first of all
if first of all i would i would
definitely start shifting things with
your diet if you have too much calcium
in your blood
so it starts shifting things there um
start cleaning things up
are you doing any eggs get rid of those
eggs you can ask your doctor about that
see what's right for you but i i would
if that was me and i had too much
calcium in my blood
i would be getting rid of eggs that
would be something i would do right
there
guys i'm going to take two nori's
together and cut them
in pieces i would get rid of eggs i
would get rid of dairy products
i would keep the caffeine and chocolate
out because here's what what happens
when you do coffee
it sucks the calcium out of your bones
and therefore you end up with the
calcium in your blood
so when you do caffeine of any kind it's
the
caffeine caffeine that draws the calcium
out of your bones to act as a buffer
right same thing with apple cider
vinegar apple cider vinegar
pulls it pulls calcium out of your teeth
out of your bones
same thing with any kind of vinegar it
pulls calcium out of your bones
get rid of all the vinegars gone get rid
of all your caffeine gone
get rid of the eggs the dairy products
gone and then
give it a little time and then see what
happens there i mean that's what i would
do if it was me
i'm cutting these right here cutting two
at a time like this
you can make these thick and bigger
pieces
you can make them skinny
i'll show you guys i'll plate them up
hair test for metals don't work either
keep that in mind as well
those are not great indicators either
so that's something to know there
so i'm going to plate these up here
i'm going to do a bunch of them in these
plates i like doing these little
circles like this so
so that's something also to keep in mind
there that hair testing isn't
isn't a great indicator as well
i'm noticing something is i get it
everybody wants to be spiritual
[Music]
these days but how come if
how can we want well how come scientific
studies are so
important
if we're so spiritual why do we need a
scientific study so bad
in order to drink celery juice or in
order to
do something that's healing somebody
like what we're doing here
like why do you need you know a
scientific
study where's your science on that
information anthony where is it
okay well that's funny because i thought
you were a spiritual person
everybody's acting so spiritual i've
seen people in yoga studios a friend of
mine told me
a whole bunch of people in his yoga
studio
is before the whole thing happened
recently with the plague we've been
dealing with
he said there's like they're really
spiritual people
but for some reason they need a
scientific study
on everything like anything my friend
said to them in the yoga studio
anything my friend said he's a doctor
friend he said you know medical medium
says that um you know
when you when when you have your cycle
your immune system drops eighty percent
of your immune system goes to your
reproductive system while 20 percent
is left to fend for you on everywhere
else and they go where's the scientific
study on that and these are people that
are super spiritual he said
super spiritual
and he's like this is confusing why is
everybody
so spiritual
but yet they they won't do they won't do
anything
unless science involved in some way or
they think science is involved in some
way
is it hypocritical what is that
especially since many of the people in
the yoga studio had chronic illness
like autoimmune and science and research
hasn't fixed it and no scientific study
fixed it
and there they are doing yoga and they
got
a little bit of fatigue they got some
hashimoto's and they're they're they're
at the yoga center doing yoga
and science and research studies hasn't
fixed their hashimoto's on any level
but for some reason they need a study in
order to do something when they're
supposed to be so
spiritual there's the norris
right there i cut them in little pieces
i'm gonna cut some more next
uh
another thing too is everybody thinks
they're a health expert
i don't mind if they think they're a
health expert that's fine but
stop burning all that toxic incense
that's poisoning the people around you
or your family stop burning the scented
candles
with all the chemical company toxins in
it
they're killing people and
if you want to be a health expert
and a spiritual expert i just i would
suggest
maybe kind of like i don't know getting
in touch with what you're doing a little
bit
maybe don't burn those dangerous scented
candles
poisoning yourself poisoning your lungs
breaking down your immune system
one's a no-brainer maybe those chemicals
are dangerous
and if you have children i mean you
shouldn't be burning scented candles
if you have children and you look i'm
not look not judging anybody it's just
that
i want to help people because when you
learn these things you're like okay wait
a minute
okay whoa yeah i need to be on that
same thing with perfumes and clothes
this stuff is so
toxic they're chemical soups
and they they go into the sinuses and
they stick to the sinus
cavities and they actually find their
way into the brain
through the sinus cavities scented
candles the chemicals that send to
candles find their way
into your brain through your sinus
cavities
see a lot of health gurus these days
lighting their scented candles
and burning incense that's treated with
chemicals
and they're telling everybody this is
what you need to do you need to do this
you need to do that
you need to sit in your sauna for an
hour with the highest heat
until you go into hypothermia basically
and your adrenals then spill out a
lifetime of adrenaline and then you're
high afterwards
and then years down the road you get
broken down from it and everything
starts falling apart and nobody knows it
was from doing too hot
too hot and too long saunas and then
caffeine all day make sure you do your
plant medicine chocolate
all the health gurus are like do your
plant medicine chocolate make sure you
do it make sure you get lots of it so
good for you science says
and how can you really be spiritual if
you need vices
look a lot of people need vices to
survive and get through the day
never going to judge anybody on that i
know life isn't easy
life can be really hard really difficult
but but just
you know try to realize there's a lot of
people out there
that got it real easy real easy it's a
lot of people you guys out there got it
easy everything's paid for everything's
good
maybe they came for money fine not
faulting anybody
but
whatever they've never had a difficult
challenge yet maybe they're still
young and they haven't been faced with
any difficult challenges
but what's their excuse for holding on
to all their vices
and but claiming they're spiritual at
the same time
look i don't mind if you do that
it's just that to grow sometimes we have
to let go of some things we have to be
without sometimes sometimes we have to
be without
a vice one that's hurting us
you know how spiritually connected can
we get if we're so jacked up on a drug
that the caffeine industry
wants us on for the rest of our life so
they get rich they don't care what
happens to us
spiritual growth is about being without
sometimes maybe letting go of ice
and then you wonder down the road while
your body's falling apart no one's going
to tell you no one's going to say it was
all that caffeine all these years
you guys i've been on the caffeine rant
for a long time but i have to say
it's the biggest food group
caffeine is the biggest food group it's
the food group
95 of the world is on for the rest of
their lives
if they were to do the math it's the
number one at the top of their food
chain it's at the top of their food
group the number one food group their
whole life
and when you think about how scary that
is oh my god
bananas aren't at the number one food
group there for them
bananas is that at the number one fruit
group no it's not
and but the caffeine will never get the
blame ever ever ever ever
right mp i mean isn't that true it's the
number one food group it's like okay
what's your food group
is it grains is your food group fruits
is it vegetables
what's your food group is it something
else is your food group
meat is your food group is your food
group
you know is it fish is it meat it's your
proteins
it's your grains it's your fruit your
vegetables and what's your what's your
tears
all that on that and
think about that right but guess what
the caffeine food group is the biggest
it's the biggest and the most important
and it's the one that's the biggest so
why am i talking about it so much like
how come i
can't get how come i can't get through a
day without talking about it right now
because it's the biggest food group in
the world that no one's talking about
you guys these these nori's right here
these are banana nori wraps and potato
nori wraps if you don't like the banana
you can do the potato nori wrap how
about that
right and then caffeine's like the
biggest food group there is
but then everybody's saying it's healthy
more than ever before that's what's
insane
see in the past it wasn't like that
right now
the caffeine campaign got so bad
so bad because of the billions and
trillions of trillions it's in the
trillions
have been made off of it it's a monster
evil monster industry
and they want to make sure now you think
it's so good for you that you're going
to be on it for the rest of your life
and make sure
everybody's on it by the way these nori
rules are totally insane
so good don't they look good nancy i
mean right
these nori rolls nori wraps i call them
nori wraps
um yeah is that raw
sharon it is raw except for the potato
oh and the nori sheet is toasted so the
nori sheets are toasted
and you can do raw nori if you want but
i like toasted nor you know nor
anyway you guys i'm going to tiktok next
so i'm heading to ig and tiktok but
what's going to happen is i'm going to
do them at the same time and ig's been
glitching i hear they've been some kind
of glitch going on
and people are getting kind of kicked
off so if you get bumped off go to
tick-tock but
really you should go to tick-tock anyway
guys
i'm heading to tick-tock now love you