see that what is that oh that's a lot of
oil but why and where and how come it's
in my nut Butters it's in all of your
nut Butters that's right can't wait to
give you the whole rundown on that this
is going to be a really fun time look at
that ooh whoa what's up with that
exactly you see that oil right there you
guys are drinking all that oil uh-huh
let's go into it a little bit the mm
1500 right there best sale ever on the
mm 1500 $140 off
$140 off get it for somebody for
Christmas if you wait it all year and
you don't have the mm500 you guys know I
work with the Meg and everything when it
comes down to being sick every little
bit counts every little bit counts that
means if you're going to eat a nut
butter you want to make sure you're not
totally being screwed over or taken
advantage of or ripped off or your body
being betrayed The Nut Butter companies
are betraying people bottom line see
that peanut butter that oil is not from
those peanuts see that almond butter
that oil is not from those almonds you
can't see this is it isn't clear but
it's an unopen tahini and the oil on top
of that unopen tahini is not from those
seeds I hate to give you the hard truth
but it's not this is one of the best
lessons you guys can have because the
oils that are placed in all the nut
Butters declines your health this is a
tahini right
here
take a look that is straight oil and
that's not from your sesame seeds this
is part of why people can't heal they
think they're doing something good for
themselves but they don't heal this is
why vegans don't heal and they go back
to eating eggs this is why vegetarians
and people who are really mindful about
their health this is part of why they
don't heal it's simple things like this
that they don't know that is pure
straight oil but not from those sesame
seeds in all the tahini bottles and jars
that you you guys have is added oil that
comes from someplace else it's bulk
cheap lowgrade rancid oil it's in all
your nut Butters and your tahinis the
oil you're looking at is not from those
nuts or those seeds they're putting old
rancid oil that comes from bulk nuts
from around the planet it depreciates
your health it's not good for your heart
it's not good if you have chronic
illness people are eating all the peanut
butters all the almond butters all the
tahinis all the cashew Butters all the
hazelnut Butters and don't realize it
they're drinking oil that's declining
and taking down their health and they
don't even know it this is the death by
a th000 cuts and that's why it is
absolutely critical you learn how to
make a nut butter what is the point of
companies to put oil in their nut
Butters confused why they add it because
they use less nuts which cost the nut
butter companies a lot of money they use
less nuts but bring in cheap bulk oil
that cost them pennies pennies and then
they mark up the price of your nut
butter jar stick it on the Shelf at
Whole Foods or whatever food store and
you pay for ranet old oil you can't be
sure that they're just adding plain old
oil the oil could have garbage in it
crap in it it's bulk rancid old oils in
every nut butter out
there that's what nut butter is supposed
to look like right there mm1 1500 boom
why should we even care about all that
added oil I'll tell you why diminishes
your health lowers your immune system
burdens your liver and your heart heavy
on the liver and pancreas so what I'm
doing is putting it in these little jars
and then I put a lid on it you might be
able to see this on a closeup too it
looks really cool so I'm packing it down
with my hands my hands are clean I
wasn't out at the post office or at the
store or grocery store and I was opening
up all kinds of doors out there and had
my hands on the shopping cart and
carriages and now I'm putting my hands
in here so I can put all
those little buggies that I picked up
somewhere on my hands in here but no my
hands are clean look at that can put the
lid on
it boom when you make your own nut
Butters it's a game
[Music]
changer you ready I made this Nut Butter
months ago and do you see the oil
spilling out no you see actually nut
butter in here but not oil spilling out
how do you like that check this out I
made this one too take a look take a
look take a look take a look look look
look and what you see is how come
where's all the oil where's the oil no
oil and I make nut Butters almond almond
butter peanut butter you name it and
that's the key because everybody buys
oil added in their nut Butters and they
don't realize it and it's really
sad