see that what is that oh that's a lot of
oil
but why and where and how come it's in
my nut Butters it's in all of your nut
Butters that's right can't wait to give
you the whole rundown on that this is
going to be a really fun time look at
that oh
whoa what's up with that exactly you see
that oil right there you guys are
drinking all that oil uh-huh let's go
into it a little bit so right here you
guys this is the mm-1500 100 off and you
guys know I work with the mega and
everything when it comes down to being
sick every little bit counts every
little bit counts that means if you're
going to eat a nut butter you want to
make sure you're not totally being
screwed over or taken advantage of or
ripped off or your body
being betrayed The Nut Butter companies
are betraying people bottom line see
that peanut butter that oil is not from
those peanuts see that almond butter
that oil is not from those almonds you
can't see this is it isn't clear but
it's an unopened tahini and the oil on
top of that unopened tahini is not from
those seeds I hate to give you the hard
true but it's not this is one of the
best lessons you guys can have because
the oils that are placed in all the nut
Butters declines your health this is a
tahini right here
take a look that is straight oil and
that's not from your sesame seeds this
is part of why people can't heal they
think they're doing something good for
themselves but they don't heal this is
why vegans don't heal and they go back
to eating eggs this is why vegetarians
and people who are really mindful about
their health this is part of why they
don't heal it's simple things like this
that they don't know that is pure
straight oil but not from those sesame
seeds in all the tahini bottles and jars
that you guys have is added oil that
comes from someplace else it's bulk
cheap low-grade rancid oil it's in all
your nut Butters and your tannies the
oil you're looking at is not from those
nuts or those seeds they're putting old
rancid oil that comes from bulk nuts
from around the planet it depreciates
your health it's not good for your heart
it's not good if you have chronic
illness people are eating all the peanut
butters all the almond butters all the
tahinis all the cashew Butters all the
hazelnut Butters and don't realize it
they're drinking drinking oil that's
declining and taking down their health
and they don't even know it this is the
death by a Thousand Cuts and that's why
it is absolutely critical you learn how
to make a nut butter what is the point
of companies to put oil in their nut
Butters confused while they add it
because they use less nuts which cost
the nut butter companies a lot of money
they use less nuts but bring in cheap
bulk oil that cost them pennies pennies
and then they mark up the price of your
nut butter jar stick it on the Shelf at
Whole Foods or whatever food store and
you pay for rancid old oil you can't be
sure that they're just adding plain old
oil the oil could have garbage in it
crap in it it's bulk rancid old oils in
every nut butter out there
[Music]
that's what nut butter is supposed to
look like right there mm-1500 boom why
should we even care about all that added
oil I'll tell you why diminishes your
health lowers your immune system burdens
your liver and your heart heavy on the
liver and pancreas so what I'm doing is
putting it in these little jars and then
I put a lid on it you might be able to
see this on a close-up too it looks
really cool
so I'm packing it down with my hands my
hands are clean I wasn't out at the post
office or at the store or grocery store
and I was opening up all kinds of doors
out there and had my hands on the
shopping cart and carriages and now I'm
putting my hands in here so I can put
all those
little buggies that I picked up
somewhere on my hands in here but no my
hands are clean look at that you can put
the lid on it
boom when you make your own nut Butters
it's a game changer