you hear people talk about meditation
all the time that's what they'll talk
about i meditate i'm doing my meditation
in the morning
i'm doing my meditation
why is everybody meditating because
their brains are messed up
that's why they're meditating their
brains weren't so messed up
they wouldn't be meditating
no one would be sitting there for an
hour
trying to meditate when they got a lot
of things to do people be really busy
and everything but their brains are
messed up depression anxiety
depersonalization
right and that that's just three words
that cover
thousands and thousands of endless
different symptoms in it right there
just so you know depersonalization you
could have feelings of sadness
loneliness loss of hope not knowing
where you are not worrying not knowing
where you should be wanting to be
someplace else right whatever it is
feeling disconnected not feeling
connected feeling disconnected from
loved ones feeling like you can't see
feeling like you can't hear like
depersonalization is unbelievable like
the vast amount of
symptoms right
but
people have to understand the reason why
we meditate and everybody meditates is
because they either
have something that they're not settled
with they're not happy with they're
looking for happiness they're looking to
elevate their happiness they're looking
to elevate their well-being they're
looking to spiritually achieve they're
looking to kind of rise out of whatever
it is they're stuck in whatever it is we
meditate because
something's messed up
it's not like everything's perfect
everything's incredible like you
everything nothing is wrong with
anything anyhow anywhere i'm just gonna
go meditate
right it doesn't really work like that
we start searching for meditations we
start searching for reasons to meditate
and reasons to actually achieve that
kind of extra help with our brain and
consciousness and mind spiritual mind
body however we want to look at it
because something's wrong
something's wrong that's why
and then
we don't realize that i see people all
the time they got brain fog they're
struggling and they're like i gotta
meditate because i have to meditate to
try to help me with my brain fog
but yet i'm having a difficulty
difficulty with meditating because of my
brain fog i gotta meditate because i
have adhd i got attention deficit
disorder i got ocd i better meditate i
better men whatever it is you know i'm
depressed i'm having a hard time i'm
going through a lot i better meditate
it's people are meditating because
something's wrong right one of the
things that
is interesting what do you use when you
meditate you use your brain
you actually use your brain
that's what you're using
yeah you're using your physical brain
and you're trying to make that
connection to the consciousness as well
right down to the soul right
subconsciousness and consciousness right
down to the soul that bridge the soul
right to your physical brain that's what
you're trying to do you're trying to do
that
and
but when we have toxic heavy metals by
the way you guys are making heavy metal
detox we do when we have toxic heavy
metals all
jacked up in our brains
and we've got neurotransmitter chemical
problems
and we have glial cell problems
and we have msg deposits and metals and
everything else all this gunk and
calcifications and scar tissue
and all this toxic crud inside our brain
it just makes things worse so then we're
searching for more more tactics and
things you'll you'll see it you'll just
like all through the internet you see
articles and all kinds of things out
there
right all kinds of media and everything
it's like 10 ways to get your brain on
track it's like you look at the 10 ways
you're like yeah yeah i've been there
done that been there done that been
there
five ways to boost your morning mood you
have been there done that with then it's
the same old crap uh this this this this
three ways you can give yourself a
better enjoyment for the day of life and
think better and and feel more clear
okay sure that's all they're putting out
there now and you're putting all this
kind of article crap with all that there
because everybody's brains are messed up
and they know it
you know
so you'll see that all the time things
will pop up on your phone
10 experts talking about how to improve
your mind it's like okay good luck
good luck unless you really know to the
root of what's really wrong like the
crud that's inside our brain and the
toxic heavy metals that are inside our
brain unless we know about what's really
causing that and and the stuff that's in
us that we have to get out forget it
you're just going to be treading water
all the time you're going to be treading
water in an ocean of confusion that's
what you're going to be doing
that's what you're going to be doing pk
good to see your meditation saved my
life and made it worth living again they
are so insanely powerful they're
powerful pk
because they're not my meditations
that's why they're powerful they're not
man-made meditations they're not my
meditations
i wouldn't know how to create those
meditations why would i know how to do
that why would i know how to write the
brain book why would i know how to write
the brain books why would i know how to
do any of that
i'm not skilled
the reason why i knew how to do those
meditations was i got given the
information from above you guys know my
source right soc gave me the information
so i
messaged it
so that you have that meditation
but i also use the information i get
from above you guys to message how to
get
the junk out of the physical brain so
we're gonna make a heavy metal detox
smoothie
you guys know about the wyman's juice
sale right here right just letting you
know it's incredible it's a gift that
this is happening right now there's ten
percent off with the code wild wild
check out the link in the description
the link in the profile you guys
i'm jacked up on wild blueberry juice
right now just so you know
totally i'm gonna talk about how i
actually use it before i do a small
meditation in the morning before i get
centered or anything
i'm going to talk about that in a minute
too you guys
anyway you can do the subscription too
as well they got a really cool
subscription
deal going on too wymans.com w-y-m-a-n-s
dot com okay i just want to let
everybody know because they noticed
people like what sale what wyman's what
here it is
incredible product you guys know i work
with these guys and i'm trying to get
this out here because let me tell you
when people's lives turn around because
of something like this a powerful
powerful source like this
it makes a difference it really does
so we're talking about the brain and
meditation a little bit if you guys are
okay about this
and then we're gonna make a heavy metal
detox movie too right
so you see that out there all the time
what's happening is people don't realize
it or they do realize it
the industries i think realize this that
everybody's brain
is having a problem these days
neurological symptoms of all kinds right
and then the depression is off the
charts right now
the sickness is off the charts right now
and growing
growing every single day
and so now you'll see all the time
you'll see all these kind of like media
people and influence influencers and
article writers
that sell you know they get their
articles you know to whatever platforms
and
it'll be like three ways to just three
ways to better your
your mood in the morning
yeah five way five best steps for your
brain and
your thought process whatever it is
that's crazy how it works you guys guess
what we're live right now
on medicalmedium.com
which is actually incredible we're live
on medicalmedium.com right now like i
can't even believe it when i think about
it i know you guys might not be excited
but i swear to god i'm like really
excited about it
really excited about it
at medicalmedium.com you know the
medicalmedium.com website you guys got
to check that out i got some videos
going on there we're live right now on
there which is really cool you can see a
schedule and i'm going to be live in the
future on there like this is really
really cool
maybe i'm just all too excited about it
nobody else's
dress of law says anxiety and panic
attacks were killing me until i began
the 369 incredible 369 cleanse and drink
celery juice every single day thank you
so much for your wisdom you spread
so glad you're here that means
everything
you get rid of your anxiety
and you're free
you're free because anybody who had
anxiety really bad and was struggling
with anxiety really bad really
struggling knows you're trapped like in
a
god when it's really bad
you can't even put words to it i don't
even think that's even like the right
way to say it livinglight says greetings
thank you for your help appreciate you
getting soc's info out appreciate you
being here okay truly little one is
seven today strong and healing thinks
thanks be to god and soc and you aw
she got a dr nesbitt
uh really oh my god you got i it went
the comment went up talked about dr des
but dr nesbitt he might come into the
show today all depends we'll see we'll
see if he's sober
okay
so we're doing a heavy metal detox
smoothie we're talking about meditation
we're talking about
how everybody's brains are just getting
beefed up
really bad out there you see it every
day
and a lot of people are just losing
their minds
it's not has nothing to do with
it has nothing to do with people being
crazy or not that's not it
so we have to kind of be able to
separate that understand that it's not
about being crazy
you can lose your mind when you're
suffering from anxiety you can lose your
mind when you're suffering from
depression when you're suffering from
ocd you can lose your mind when you're
just you don't know what you're
suffering with and understand you don't
even know why you're dealing with what
you're dealing with
you can you can feel like you're losing
your mind
but you're not crazy
you're not crazy
okay just because you have anxiety or
depression or depersonalization are
bipolar or schizophrenia or anything
like that or
you're just brain fogged
from here to high heaven you're just
brain fogged
and what feels like you're in hell when
you're brain fog that bad too
and and you're not crazy just because
you your brain fogged out and you're
struggling you're not crazy if you have
adhd you're not crazy if you're
struggling with something with your mind
and body
and with your brain without even
realizing it's really your brain too
people don't even know they're not
connected to that they don't know what's
really their brain they don't know what
it is
but you're not crazy either way
are there some crazy people on the
planet yeah there is
there's some crazy people on the planet
i mean duh we see it every day out there
but you're a good person
and you wake up one morning and you
realize your adhd is getting out of
control your add is getting out of
control
your brain fog's getting out of control
you're up and down emotionally you're
struggling left and right you're losing
energy you're getting fatigued with it
you're getting anxiety attached you're
getting panic attacks you're getting
tightness of the chest you're getting
tightness of the throat
and you're just struggling susan you
place the order in the wild blueberry
juice you won't be sorry i'm gonna talk
about this stuff a little a little bit
today too it's it's mind-blowing i'm
gonna make a couple of something or
another's and we'll see i even have some
i might even bring out
i might even bring this out
we'll see
i want to be helpful today
i want to
i want to be helpful purposeful i want
people
to know they can heal
because
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
have
when they know what to do
you guys if you just came on here we're
talking about the brain let's talk about
meditation for a couple of seconds too
what are you using when you're doing
meditation what are you trying to
connect what are you using
trying to use your third eye right
trying to use
that direct passageway into the soul
you're trying to use the subconscious
consciousness right into the soul
right when you're meditating and we're
trying to use our physical brain to kind
of connect that that's what we're doing
right
we're trying to get spiritually
connected
we're trying to get grounded right when
we're meditating so we're actually
trying to get grounded
okay
right
we're trying to connect to above too
when we do meditations or are we trying
to connect to a bubble that's that's
something right there meditations don't
mean you're just sitting there like
doing ohms and you're just sitting there
that doesn't mean that you can be
sitting on your back porch
looking at a bird fly by
and
contemplating that's a meditation right
there
you don't have to be in a meditation
class i mean you're welcome to you don't
have to be in a meditation class
somewhere
right
with a bunch of hippies around you and
you're in a meditation class or you
don't have to be you don't have to be in
a meditation class with a whole bunch of
wealthy people around you that are in
some resort somewhere up on some
mountain in aspen
you don't have to be in a meditations
class you can be anywhere you can be
anywhere you can be literally
in your room you wake up one morning and
you're still laying in your bed and you
can meditate right there
you can lay in your bed in your bedroom
right when you wake up in the morning
and right when you wake up
what you do
is just start thinking about what clouds
look like
and what the sky looks like and you
think about the bluest sky you've ever
seen
and you close your eyes and you envision
you're looking at that blue sky right
when you wake up that's a powerful
meditation
you don't have to be about around a
bunch of sweaty people
in some resort somewhere or you don't
have to be around somewhere else or
whatever
people don't have to be sweaty or not
depends if they just did yoga
but the point is is you don't have to do
that
there's a lot of ways to do powerful
small meditations that are really true
powerful meditations
and you can do them real quick and easy
you can be sitting literally in a chair
outside in nature and you can see a bird
fly by you can see a pigeon land
if you're in the city and you can get a
meditation right off of looking at a
pigeon
but what are you trying to do
trying to alleviate something you're
trying to heal something you're trying
to achieve something you're trying to
bridge a gap
too right
hannah t says this is an incredible live
i'm honored
it's an incredible life because you're
here
so when it comes down to meditation
meditation is hard for a lot of people
who have been through hell and back too
they've been there and done that they
tried different meditations
right they've done different things and
it just didn't feel like they got
anywhere with it too a lot of people
have a lot of panic and anxiety so
trying to meditate it's really difficult
for them if they got tightness to the
chest and they're trying to breathe and
meditate it's hard for a lot of people
have neurological problems and no one
realizes that they just think they're
wimps
they're not wimps
meditation is difficult when you're
suffering from bipolar or depression or
anxiety or depersonalization or
schizophrenia or whatever you're
suffering from mentally and emotionally
or just emotional injuries and ptsd if
you're suffering from ptsd meditation is
hell i know so many people who have ptsd
and had ptsd and meditation was just
total health for them
because as they're trying to meditate
all they see is the hell they've been
through
here appleman hey good to see you with
brain fog it can be so hard to visualize
or think about anything that's why
sitting
outside on the porch and just watching a
beautiful bird a blue jay
or anything go by
is critical for meditating that's
critical watching a bee hum around and
land on a daily line is one of the most
powerful meditations especially if
you've been through a heck and tara
especially if you got the brain fog you
know you know though terror
you know
you've been through a lot
and thank you for being here you're
amazing person
and you know
meditations don't have to be grandiose
they don't have to be
this grandiose process
meditations can be so powerful when
they're just even small meditations
while you're while you're suffering and
trying to heal from panic and anxiety
and depression and everything else
but even with all this we still have to
assist ourselves and we have to help
ourselves
seeker for compassion said yes feeling
crazy on meditation
okay we're gonna keep on moving i mean
really a lot of people go you know they
have a hard time
i'm gonna crack open a little blue juice
here right
you know what
i'm actually
i'm gonna bring this out here a little
bit
i'm gonna have the hard stuff is what
i'm gonna do
actually i'm gonna do better than that
right
now do you ever see like
sophisticated rich people
right
dear
would you like some
i liquor one right here
this is a 47 year old scotch
oh dear i spilled a drop
that's okay
i have 50 barrels of this in my basement
let's try a little bit of this
that stuff is good
it's just blueberry juice it's not
alcohol just letting everyone know
letting everybody know there's no
alcohol in here
letting everybody know
this is just wild blueberry juice i put
it in the bottle before all of a sudden
all of a sudden all the
platforms get squirrely
are you guys we're live right now we're
making heavy metal detox smoothie
um i'm having a little refreshment right
now wild blueberry juice
it's so incredible
i like doing things like this
jody manic says makes my day when you do
these imitations
just don't make me do the robot
the robot gets crazy
all right
i'm honored to be here you guys i got to
make a heavy metal detox smoothie we're
talking about the weinman sale right now
just check out the link is in the
description there link is in profile
um
the wild blueberry juice right here the
wymanswildblueberryjuicewimans.com
w-y-m-a-n-s
10 off of any order you do there which
is incredible you know i work with
wyman's because i need this stuff to
stay around
i need it to stay around
it's critical that we have options to
help our brain we have options we have
antioxidant power because the world's
becoming an acid bomb
if you want to sum it up like in a
nutshell you know what i mean you have
medical medium information extremely
comprehensive you guys know that like
the brain books
are insanely comprehensive right that
you can you can pre-order them
but you know the medical medium books
are extremely comprehensive you guys
know like
big time right
if you want to wrap it up in a nutshell
just one little nutshell we live in an
acid bomb world
and we need something to help battle it
right
just want to sum it up in one second
that's it done right if you want to go
that route
but i like to go into intricacies and i
like to go into details because details
do matter when it's talking about like
getting metals out of the brain
making sure we actually can heal making
sure we heal emotionally on all levels
anxiety and depression and everything
else that everybody's dealing with
mercury retrograde yeah mercury
retrograde is kicking my butt lately
oh boy
anyway
merc retro is not being kind to the
medical medium this time around i can
honestly say that you guys
that's why i need some more blue juice
for
power there
is that stitch
where is that i'm a year into doing the
heavy metal detox smoothie
it's twitch
i'm a year into doing the heavy metal
detox movies and i've done about seven
three six nine cleanses over the course
of that year my depression and crippling
anxiety are gone
never thought i'd see the day where that
was possible
thank you anthony and soc if i had a
feather for every time which is the most
amazing gift ever
if i had a feather for every time it
says that anybody said
right that they couldn't believe they'd
ever see the day
i'd be able to fly i wouldn't have to
hop in a car
wouldn't have to
hop on a mini bike i wouldn't have to do
anything i'd be i just would be
able to fly around everywhere because
that's what happens one thing about
medical movement information that i've
seen
in ssc's information is people say i
never thought i could heal but it i did
i never thought i'd see the day but i
did
nothing else helped me out there but
this did and i couldn't believe it
so incredible camera90 says my friends
and i go tubing down the river whoa
during summer
and they all bring alcohol and get drunk
since i don't drink anymore i'm going to
bring a bottle
of the juice instead oh my god
incredible can you imagine you're tubing
down the river and you're totally
totally cocked and totally drunk and
you're tubing down the river that's
dangerous tell your friends
they gotta like slow down
no no no who am i to say anything people
want to do whatever they want to do but
that's a brilliant idea as you bring the
wild blueberry juice incredible
incredible
all right so i'm going to make the heavy
metal detox smoothie
one of the key things
i love
right about mm info
is the heavy metal detox movie uh what
i've seen that done throughout the years
and what i've i mean it's just
incredible from children to adults to
anyone in between or whatever i mean
what i what i've seen
it do helping people come out just rise
out of the ashes ronald says thank you
for your books and healing advice for
the first time in four years my thyroid
is seeing drastic
i wish there was like i'm going to have
to get a bell to ring like is that what
i need i'm going to get a belt ring in
here
that's not a pill
i don't know what that is
thyroid healing i got thyroid healing
right here but you can you can heal your
thyroid with cleanse the heal you can
heal your thyroid with medical medium
book one revised and expanded for sure
right
incredible
get them at the library for free
i mean if you want amazon.com of course
but get them at the library for free if
you want just go to the library get the
books for free
i just want you to heal i just want you
to heal
i think you guys
figured that out some of you right
i mean
yogi says i love you anthony
i legit would have been dead if not for
your information
the enemy choked up
near him each hooked up
that's for sure
shake it off
april's half
had the heavy metal detox smoothie every
day for a year
eczema finally clearing up on my arms i
will be
able to wear short sleeves that's a big
deal on youtube
that's a really big deal
it is people don't know it until they
had it happen to them no one knows what
it's like to be in your shoes unless
they had it before no one understands it
unless they've been there no one knows
your depression unless they've been
there nobody knows your eczema if they
unless they've been there nobody knows
what it's like to be on the brink of
death
and then to come rising out of that
using this information unless they've
been there nobody knows
people don't understand what someone
else has been through unless they've
been through it themselves and if they
haven't been through it themselves they
don't understand
you become like this ghost to them like
you're meaning your problem becomes like
this ghost thing like is it real is it
not that person is just weak
well that's not what it is you're strong
as heck
dr
fun
md
problem with the bell would be that
you'd be ringing it all the time and
people would be like is that my tinnitus
or the bell it's actually really funny
another problem with the bell is i'd
probably get really stupid with it and
yeah i'd be ringing it all the time and
i would probably just yeah you're right
that's the problem i would get everybody
upset
you guys
anyway i want to tell you about the
wyman sale which is incredible
what i do with with anytime i'm doing
like meditation i tend to i tend to do
it before i drink
the juice
i tend to do it many times before i
drink the juice that's something i do
right i don't know if you guys have ever
done that
where does
that juice go when you drink it where
does it go
right
it gets absorbed
through the lining of the intestinal
tract it gets absorbed
through the lining of your stomach and
duodenum
it gets absorbed into the liver
it gets into the bloodstream really fast
like quick
like boom it's in your bloodstream
and then when it's in your bloodstream
that blueness that blue
that blue
finds its way to
here right
finds its way to here that's where the
blue goes you guys it finds its way to
here
right
what's in that blue
thousands of years
there's the blueberries right there
thousands of years of information
those blueberries have seen everything
those blueberry plants have seen
everything
they've seen
tundra come
drought come
ice age
flying saucers
they've seen
alien technology float above them
okay this is wild this isn't this isn't
just organic this is above organic this
is wild this isn't just cultivated
organic this is wild
these blueberry plants have seen
everything
they've seen indigenous cultures
come by and feed off of them
they've seen right
indigenous cultures feeding off of them
they've seen bears and deer and foxes
and coyotes and animals come through and
feed off of them right
they've seen blazing hot sun they've
seen freezing cold they've seen drought
they've seen the ice age they've seen
all of it they've seen mammoths
these wild blueberry plants have seen
mammoths walk around
with big tusks
these wild blueberries
yeah these wild bloopers have seen
aliens fly around and land
they have these wild blueberry plants
have seen aliens fly around and land
right in the middle of the field
and aliens get out of that craft
and pick those blueberries
these wild blueberry plants have seen
all that people think i'm kidding i'm
not kidding on that one ready for this
these wild blueberry plants have seen
sasquatches and bigfoots
and nookie knox
they've seen
bigfoot
lots of families of bigfoots throughout
the ages
how many bigfoots were feasting off of
these in the fields these wild blueberry
plants have seen and experienced
sasquatches and bigfoots feeding off
these wild blueberries
and then they would go and disappear in
the woods and then indigenous culture
native americans other indigenous
cultures would come in and feed off of
those wild blueberries they would come
and go and then the beer bears would
come in and the grizzlies and the black
bear would come in they'd feed off of
them bears love that and they would feed
off them and they would go
walk away the alien crash would come and
land and the aliens come out of the
alien crafts in the middle of the night
or the day and they would feed off those
wild blueberries and go back in the
craft and take off
these plants have seen a lot you guys
they've seen a lot
and so that's important to know right
there
and it's more than just that they have
survived
they have adapted
this is a wild food
this is a food that takes care of itself
when it takes care of itself it holds
something holds something powerful and
this stuff is high in manganese by the
way
extremely high in manganese making these
is that
that bridge builder trace mineral
and it's high in this juice right it's
high in the wild blueberry so
people wonder like how do these
antioxidants work well that manganese is
part of how these antioxidants work and
bridge that gap
but the anthocyanins that blue color
have to go somewhere so when you eat
these wild blueberries you drink the
juice you're getting straight i always
say this is mainlining it right here
this is direct fast into the bloodstream
right so
when it's the juice it's like right into
the bloodstream fast right through the
stomach walls right through the duodenum
walls right through the intestinal tract
and that's just going through you quick
and then it gets into your bloodstream
in that blue that blue color finds its
way to where
to the meditation center it finds its
way to the meditation center that blue
color finds its way to where the
meditation
is happening
you can meditate
fast
anytime you want you can stop
and you can see a squirrel
and then you can just
instantly believe
i am that squirrel now
and transport yourself through
your thought process using your
consciousness that you are that squirrel
chewing on that nut on the tree that's a
meditation in that moment real fast
that quick
you can shut your eyes and you can
listen to the wind blow
that's a meditation
you can also go into a meditation center
and mess around and play around with
singing bowls and
sit there and
you do whatever you want but the point
is what can help
in the meditation centers what i've
always heard from spirit of compassion
is the blue color
and i've been talking about this for
over 30 years probably 40 years
trying not to date me too much
but i've been around for a while already
on this planet
i hope to be around longer
by the way if something happens to me
guys
all right
just saying
something happens to me you know
all right
yeah
anyway
i'm just telling you i didn't kill
myself or anything like that just
letting you know
or anything else
something happens it wasn't an accident
okay
something happens to me and
we lose me and they say it was an
accident it wasn't an accident
anyway out of there for a second
the bottom line is it's what i'm trying
to tell you
okay
is that that blue anthocyanin i've been
talking about for well over three
decades spirit of compassion has always
told me it goes and it gets to the brain
and it goes into a place
in the emotional centers of the brain it
goes into a place where the third eye is
it goes into the place
that harbors that energy source
that supernatural force that we have
inside our brains because we're not just
physical brain matter and gray matter or
supernatural force and soul so we're all
that so that blue goes into that
supernatural force and it goes into
there into that area in the brain
and it connects to the consciousness and
subconsciousness to the soul into the
supernatural force and that energy field
and that electricity that's in our brain
and around our brain that anthocyanin
connects to that that's what spirit of
compassion told me when i was a kid
it connects to that
and that's power
from food
i have heard over and over again people
are like yeah i know food you could use
food as medicine yeah but what kind of
food are you talking about
you talking about wild food because if
you're not talking about wild food and
you're not talking about wild
blueberries and you're not talking about
wild food then i don't know what you're
talking about
it's a big difference
every time i talk about the wild
blueberries someone goes out and buys a
clam shell with the big cultivated
blueberries in it it's like he told me
blueberries are good for me and they
dump them in there and i feel bad
because i get it because we've also
we've also been brainwashed about our
food and our
food sources out there and we're we're
just not taught we just don't know we
don't know there's a difference between
wild and then everybody and then the
organic police come in and start
freaking out and say well why isn't
wyman's organic and they don't even
realize
that wild is above organic and they
don't even know wilde doesn't love
organic they don't know that and that's
a whole sad thing all on its own
i talked about that the other day
people think
organic is holy
holy
can't do no wrong
you know like holy and
godly
they don't realize yeah we have to eat
organic food heck yeah but they don't
realize that organic foods loaded with
copper spray and
nicotine spray to kill the pollinators
and kill the they don't know what kills
the pollinators it kills the pollinators
and
organic is it all crapped up to be
right
wild food
right doesn't need to be cared for so
what happens is that you barely spray
ever you can go years without spraying a
wild food source meanwhile organic farms
are actually they're organic farms are
conventional farms did you guys know
that
organic farms came after conventional
produce conventional farms organic farm
owners companies organic farm companies
bought conventional farmland and started
planting the stuff the soil saturated
with pesticides and chemicals
and so people don't realize they're
growing all their organic food out of
pesticide-ridden soil
meanwhile a wild food gets sprayed so
very little and the soil was never
sprayed to begin with from a
conventional farm so it's pure soil down
there they don't get this beverly says
what are we going to do with all of
these shortages going on
that's the whole point like i'm talking
about a wild food
look i got my freezer stocked with some
wild blueberries
that's one thing i got and i'm stocked
with the wild blueberry juice right
there
because i've gone without food
and just sip this along the way every
day all day for days sandra says where
do you get it wymans.com w-i-m-a-n-s
ten percent off that's the wyman's juice
i'm gonna make a smoothie here i know
we're talking about a lot of different
things you guys and i know i'm kind of
heading around in different areas
alyssa saccone says you are so
incredible my sister lawrence coney got
me addicted to your healing wisdom
you're awesome for not pooh-poohing it
you listen you're incredible for not
poo-pooing it and being like yeah don't
i'm not gonna talk i'm not gonna
listen to that medium i'm so grateful
you're beautiful
for your beautiful and gentle superfood
medicine i have celery juice awesome
celery juice you guys know how much i
love celery juice heavy metal detox
lemon water herbal teas every single
morning
i now love mornings
and my
labrynitis is lessening incredible
my anxiety mornings are no more oh my
god incredible i love these morning
rituals god bless you incredible
god bless you alyssa amazing amazing
that's just incredible all right
i am going to
put a
lid on it
a little bit i'm going to start making
heavy metal detox smoothie you guys
we're trying to cover some info and i'm
also going to do another live after oh
by the way i just want to remind you
guys just so you know
you might want to try this someday watch
my lives at medicalmedium.com
i'm live on medicalmedium.com right now
i don't know if it's just me that's just
excited about this that no one cares and
maybe fine because i've done that before
where i'm excited about something did
you ever have that where you're excited
about something but everybody else
around you there's really nothing saying
about it but you are i'm really excited
about this medicalmedium.com you know my
website you guys where i have all this
information and everything i'm live on
there right now
this is the coolest thing
ever
and guess what tomorrow morning i'm
doing a video you're going to get a
video off my newsletter tomorrow morning
if you're signed up to the medical
medium newsletter you're going to get a
video tomorrow right my free videos
every single sunday free free free free
free
and you're going to get my free video
tomorrow morning you know what it's
going to be about black tongue
you know the dark discoloration
literally black right on the tongue in
the back of the tongue that so many
people get it's a talk about why people
get the black tongue i'm not talking
about coffee stained tongues i'm talking
about when you do when it's not a coffee
stain or cigarette stain tongue i'm
talking about that
michelle l you want more of the squirrel
talk yeah squirrel squirrels are amazing
check the folders on your desktop
because guess what that that newsletter
i sent you could go into your folder and
it can go into spam
check spam check your folders check
promotions because when i send that
newsletter tomorrow morning about black
tongue it can go right into the spam
right into the folder right into right
so i'm letting you know right right into
promotions it can go in there i'm
sending it out 7am eastern time 4 a.m
pacific time about black tongue guys
should sign up to my newsletters
but anyway medicalmedia.com i'm live
right now i still can't believe it i'm
live i'm live live
tonight nice
knock on line
the robot's just starting i just got to
get some blueberry juice in me we're
really gonna go let's make the smoothie
that was a lame robot everybody
okay
um
all right let's get this going
first of all i gotta calm down
i gotta calm down
i need
a glass of wine
is what i need i need a glass of wine
you guys
i need to calm down
i gotta get a glass of wine first of all
so just bear with me
if you guys don't mind a glass of wine
will be really good
right now
that's what i need
a glass of wine
i know things have been a little crazy
lately these days you guys and
i just feel bad about everything you
know and uh
the glass of wine tends to calm me down
a little bit
sometimes
you just need that glass of wine
because if you don't have it
you know you just
glass of wine is really important once
in a while
it is
phone's ringing
phone's ring
hello
dr wiggy woggy here
yeah it's a doctor the doctor's in
i'm just having my glass of wine
yes
the practice has been pretty good
everybody's sicker than ever
yes
did you know we had so many sick people
come in the other day i thought it was
armageddon
did you know i taught the nurses to do a
little dance
we do a little dance that's cha-ching
that's another sick person to change
your chin
all the nurses come out we all go
cha-ching to chi chi chang to ching
yeah
one nurse even brought a little cash
register in
and she hits it and we all go to ching
chi chi ching the sick people are coming
and cha-ching
oh yes yes
cha-ching
oh yes
what does chi-ching mean it means
money
oh yeah
okay i need to calm myself down a bit i
need a bit of wine
are you coming over later
yes
i have a glass of wine ready for you
indeed
uh-huh
i'm going to
oh this wine smells very good
it does
it smells
nice
did you know i just invested with my
other doctor friends in a vineyard
yes
in the valley
it was it was a vineyard was only 42
million dollars
oh yes
lots of sick people paid for that oh i
know
we have sick people everywhere i love it
the medical university called me and
said they're gonna stamp out another
thousand doctors
every semester they stamp out a thousand
doctors is it semester
i don't think that's right every single
year
i love being a rich doctor
are there poor doctors yeah there's poor
doctors
yeah those are the doctors that actually
give a [__]
the poor doctors the poor doctors
actually give a [__] about their
patients
yes
these are the
real poor ones
the youtube doctors oh they don't care
yes podcast doctors they don't care
no
they're all about advertisements
you don't see any patients
regardless we're very rich here because
our clinic's getting so many people
i think i'm drooling right now over this
wine
okay
i'm gonna have it
remember that dance oh the nurses get
out
sick people come here
yes i sent her out for an mri
yes i did we sent her out for a cat scan
yes yes
okay
oh yes we gave her 20 x-rays
yes we x-rayed her brain
okay
jesus
okay i i have a call coming through
through the hospital
okay i have to go
okay bye
wait
how'd you like this wine
thank you very good what what was that
you said
what was that you said
all right
[Applause]
[Music]
i got to make this heavy metal detox
smoothie you guys
i do i do
all right so what i love about this
heavy metal detox smoothie is is that i
first of all use the wild blueberries
frozen wild blueberries right but i
don't have them i just put the juice in
boom
juice goes in you know that's what i
love to do
i'm gonna drop in some frozen brew wild
blueberries because i do have them
why is this smoothie
changing lives around the world
because it actually works
that's why
and not by chance
talking just
millions right now around the world
heidi
you're hilarious so much truth in your
humor you are a gem i'm honored you're
here
and you're on facebook incredible you're
on facebook you're not censored today
amazing
at least you're not but i'm sure a lot
of people can't get on because that's
what i hear all the time they can't get
on facebook
but i'm live right now at
medicalmedium.com i just want to tell
you if you ever wonder where i am that's
a place to figure it out too
medicalmed.com i'm live there right now
we're making the smoothie there's some
wild blueberries right there you see
that on tick tock you guys
okay
i'm gonna drop some bananas in here
let's put some bananas in here let's do
that two bananas
one banana two banana i'm gonna pop a
banana in here right let's do that
banana
vegan allison hey how you doing
that is amazing that really inspired me
to drink more blueberry juice and eat
more blueberries incredible i'm so glad
you're wild blueberries
wild blueberries i know you know that
okay
you guys 10 off right now wyman's wild
blueberry juice right here okay i drink
it before i meditate i drink it after i
meditate i still have to talk about that
in a couple of minutes a little bit
about that really quick
use the code wild
sick 10
off that's an ins that's a it's
incredible
sale 10 off a lot of blueberry juice
right now use the coat wild
i just put two bananas in there i think
i want to put a another half a banana
and there's your small bananas i want to
make a big smoothie or bigger smoothie
maria
ma and then ria
i'm making my heavy metal detox smoothie
right now awesome we're doing it
together
doing it together
what else do we have in here right
i'm gonna drop some wild blueberry juice
in here
okay
boom boom boom boom boom bam
i'm getting jacked up already i've been
hooked in the wild berry juice juicing i
got my why my
my non-alcohol no alcohol no alcohol
why in there i got that
right
i got my bimrc
barley grass juice powder best stuff
there is don't get confused
do not do
barley grass barley grass
doesn't do anything it has to be juiced
and preserved juiced and saved and and
protected like juice powder right
after it's incredible so you want that
you want that so
that's the wild that's the wild
blueberries you see in there that's the
bananas you see in there right
and i'm about to put the barley grass
juice powder in next that's what you're
gonna do
it's going in there so i'm just showing
you guys right okay there we are i'm
putting that in
put a little bit more in there for you
a little cat and mouse all right put a
little bit more of that
incredible
you got to have the barley grass juice
powder and there's no pure or better
form of it
out there than the vimergy one so you
guys know vimergy v is the victor i am
e-r-g-y dot com right i'm using the
spirulina this is the famous heavy metal
detox smoothie
i love when something's famous because
it's turned lives around right healed
people around the world
there's a spirulina there's no better
spirulina i've ever found yet and if one
comes along i will be using it but there
is no better spirulina than the vimergy
spirulina
that's the one right there that's part
you know that's what i put in my heavy
metal detox smoothie right there
so that's the vimergy thermogee.com
right
got the spirulina
got the barley grass juice powder now
i'm dropping some dulce in there too
that is
the vimergy dulce liquid right there
which is so easy and so incredible just
love it
just so medicinal incredible i'm gonna
drop two dropper folds in there right
look at that this is so cool
this is cool
okay
what else do we need in here do you guys
know what am i missing do you guys know
what i'm missing
like i'm missing something i didn't put
something in here i'm pretty sure i'm
pretty sure you guys know because you
make it every day but how come i forgot
i didn't forget
you guys it's right here you guys know
that
cilantro fresh cilantro goes in here
fresh cilantro right
what else could i have in here whoa i
got an orange i'm gonna grab this orange
right here
got the orange going in next
yep
i don't know what it is
about that wild blueberry juice but that
stuff just gets me like not just
level but grounded and then also kind of
pumped up and also kind of strong
feeling and also kind of level-headed
and also kind of crazy you crazy
i'll tell you
it gets me going i'm squeezing some
orange in here if you guys don't mind
right
you guys on tick tock we're live right
now
right
you guys
we're live we're live on youtube we're
live on facebook we're live on
twitch
right
you name it
and we're live at medicalmedium.com
medicalmedium.com we're actually live at
medicalmedium.com we're live on rumble
rumble
we're live on telegram
martha 32 said reverse appendicitis
thank you aw you're welcome you're
welcome i can't take the credit
you're welcome but i can't take the
credit it's soc that gets the credit
unfortunately i can't take the credit
never get the credit
martha's on stitch twitch oh my god if i
see
twitch
trick
i got tweets i gotta remember that you
know you're gonna have to remember like
you keep on forgetting something you
gotta remember something else with it
it's like it's like
yeah no
no they're on they're you know do it
stitch no twitch twitch stretch gotta
remember no you gotta twitch wait does
stitch twitch no stitch doesn't twitch
twitch switches twitch
[Music]
tanya gray says does it matter that the
blueberry juice isn't organic
re-watch this please re-watch this i
explained it a little while ago
a wild food is way above organic
and your organic food is not innocent
and i talk about why it's not innocent
i don't know you know what i could talk
about that probably a billion times and
i don't i don't know it's just like
you just do the best you can but thank
you for asking bless your heart for
being here
i'm gonna blend this
put a lid on there too you guys take a
look at this i'm going to bring this
right on here i want you guys to see
this on tik tok
you guys a lot of blueberry juice is on
sale 10 off for an order
sick
sick wymans.com link is in there you
need to use the code wild w-i-l-d
w-i-l-d
wild wild all right let's give this a
run they got a subscription
subscription you can do
[Music]
making the smoothie
how many times have i made a smoothie in
my life
a lot
you guys know i
my uh
one of my friends told me i have a
interesting way of entertaining myself
too when no one's around
where
i'll talk to the blender
good job blender
fantastic for getting this done
all you guys in here who are happy being
blended up
we're done
[Music]
amazing
you guys it's an honor to be here with
you guys on this saturday it's
incredible
totally honored that you guys are here
dressler says i ditched caffeine drinks
congratulations seriously weed
did you say weed you ditched that too
amazing
uh and alcohol
what
now you can let them in
you can let them in
that's fine
all right all right just get yeah come
on over when you get a chance you could
put your shoes over there that's fine
what you guys i got a friend here
um
joshua hang on a second
no yeah yeah you can
yeah well i just got to take a bath no
i'll take that why don't you talk to
everybody and i'll just take a bathroom
break yeah
that's fine
yeah no
no
you can go over there
say
yeah
ocean you can go over there
yeah don't worry just say hi to
everybody yeah
what do i do with this
hey hey
hey w
we live
drastically
i ditch caffeine drinks
weed oh man you ditched your weed
what do you mean you ditched your weed
whoa
did you where did you put it
did you like bury it
dude
dude give me the phone number to the
dude you gave your weed to
don't want to waste the weed man
dude i didn't have any weed today
what i'm just listening to myself now
what
hey aw
aw what do you do with this
dude dude
dude hw
dude
i thought you were all in the health and
[__]
dude
hey hey
hey is this okay
[Music]
hey
hey i'm going through withdrawal now too
so
this is helping
hey
great
did you call
yeah
yeah i don't know
i came over a w's place
i'm just gonna hit the couch
he lets me take a nap here
yeah
you know i don't know if i'm even coming
home tonight
depends on how much we do what
yeah
it's
it's medical
uh-huh
you know that
all right
we're gonna go
hey
you there
hey ocean can you just hit the couch
you guys
sorry about that
all right we got the heavy metal detox
smoothie
god what happened over here
got the heavy metal detox smoothie you
guys i blended it up let's pour it
let's pour it
i got a glass right here and i happen to
like this glass very much
you guys good to see you
i am pouring a smoothie right now
furniture cuz says oh my god you imitate
so perfectly like you used weed all your
life
i used wild blueberries all my life
i have eaten lots of wild blueberries
since i was young
all right i'm having the heavy metal
detox smoothie right here
looks really good laureen l it's really
good
it's really actually really good why is
it so good today
is it all the weed do you get the
munchies where something tastes really
good after that
why don't do we
you guys know i'm anti-weed i'm anti
whatever meaning like you guys do what
you want
i'm not judging you on nothing i ain't
judging anybody on nothing
but i don't touch weed i don't touch
alcohol i know i'm a dud i'm boring as
hell at a party
no one wants to see me at a party
all right
you guys talking about meditation for a
couple more minutes and then we're gonna
do another live
but
guys check out medicalmedium.com i'm
live on there right now on my website
i'm really pumped up pumped up about it
not even kidding
and
i'm talking about like
i do small meditations
i do the medical media meditations the
spirit compassion game you guys know in
my podcast but
into my books but i do small small
meditations too real small ones fast
ones that happen at any moment
it's incredible really you just go
outside in nature for two seconds and
you can get a meditation going like i
was saying before just with birds just
with a butterfly you see dragonfly
meditation with a dragonfly anything
like that it's incredible what you can
do
right
victoria rising from the ashes says no
you are the life of the party without
drugs or alcohol god bless you
truly
truly you know
you're that yeah and victoria rising
you're a powerhouse you guys are
powerhouses pam
i love you guys and joe remember sale
check it out
that's the wild blueberry juice right
there
okay
there you go
and 10 off wymans.com
w-y-m-a-n-s-com link is in the
description right the whole bit
use the code wild w-i-l-d
all right you guys i love you you know
i'm gonna go do a live pretty soon i am
going to do instagram and i am going to
do tick tock and i'm going to do
telegram
i'm going to do that all right
see you guys soon