oral health it's a big deal a lot of
people have canker sores cold sores
fever blisters mouth ulcers oh it's just
a mouth ulcer that's all it is just a
mouth ulcer you know it's like well
what's a mouth ulcer what is
that what's a mouth ulcer right and
we'll talk about all this kind of stuff
talking about immune system inside the
mouth which is a big deal so your immune
system in your mouth one of the most
important places our immune system is
when lymphocytes are freaking out every
day in our mouths because they're trying
to protect us they all this different
stuff going in our mouths lymphocytes
are always at it lymphatic glands
underneath our neck right all these
different areas here so this is really a
uh an important topic because so many
people have not just oral health issues
but immune system issues in the area of
their oral health because that's really
a big problem right there so it's the
immune
system in the area where oral health is
and they both work together okay we're
going to talk about the whole stuff
mouthwashes bad bad bad bad bad you
don't want to use all those toxic
mouthwashes out there I've been saying
that for years because this stuff is
terrible it's like putting gasoline in
your mouth it's basically like just
sucking gasoline from a gas tank out of
a hose what you see here and then
rinsing out your your mouth and then
spitting it out that's what it is
basically good to see you guys oral
health we're talking about okay so this
is a big deal this is a show that's
important worth watching worth watching
for free it's worth it so what you have
in front of me right what I have in
front of me and in front of you is
golden seal golden seal I can't even
express how important golden seal is
golden seal shock therapy how critical
that is I mean just life saving for
people in so many ways what you also see
in front of me is
propolis
propolis yeah yeah the heavens open up
light comes out of the
sky because propolis is literally
literally like so powerful so powerful
okay so propolis is in front of me right
there too oral health propolis oral
health propolis oral health propolis and
then another thing you see is good
oldfashioned
zinc good oldfashioned zinc that's fmer
G products right there you guys know I
love those guys I endorse them
wholeheartedly because they never ever
did crazy crap to their supplements
added all kinds of garbage natural
flavors alcohol citric acid that's just
the name a few that's not even like so
many other things that are in in
supplements out there you yeah magnesium
sterate soy whatever I mean just all
that garbage right they don't do that so
that's the vimergy stuff right there if
you haven't experienced the vimergy
propolis I don't know what to say I
could I
could golden ticket smack it out of my
hand golden ticket smack it out of my
hand kick it out of my hand kick me in
the face okay I'm just saying that
propolis if you don't have it and you
haven't experienced it I don't know what
more I can say I barely talk about it I
talk about it what once every 6 months
don't hold me exactly to that time
period because I really can't
remember exactly what day it was but
yeah I it's that important so what you
see right here is the zinc you see the
zinc right you see the propolis you see
the golden seal hint hint hint hint
immune system how critical that is
especially with everything going around
everything going around right right and
if you're on the dating scene if you're
on the dating scene
okay
propolis golden seal like say no more
say no more and zinc if you're smooching
with somebody you don't even really know
that much you're on the dating scene and
you're you're smooching in the car after
a dinner or whatever it
is and you propolis you get home and do
the propol
you get home and you do the zinc you get
home and you do the golden
seal you do that you fortify your immune
system in areas that are
critical that are
critical seriously important
areas
so um yeah yeah if you're swapping Spit
with
someone yeah definitely need that okay
all right all right all right I'm just
excited because we're talking about the
immune system I'm excited because we're
talking about oral health it it's a
favorite topic of mine I love talking
about it because when you get people
help when you actually get them real
help where they where they can do
something that's really beneficial not
just [ __ ] coconut oil you know oil
pulling I'm sorry I hope I just didn't
make 10 more enemies you know I mean I'm
the original enemy maker in the health
movement because I told people about the
collagen bull crap I told them about the
oil pulling I told them about the lectin
scam so I'm the original enemy maker
before people now or like shot and all
like blah blah blah blah blah blah in
the health you know in the health world
right now screaming their heads off
about every little thing right but what
happened was earlier on you know I I
don't think I made that many friends
when you're ripping apart collagen
supplements fish oil supplements and
you're ripping apart all that garbage
and all that junk you just don't make a
lot of friends
anyway the point I'm trying to say is
oil pulling does not do anything for the
mouth's immune system it doesn't it may
make your mouth feel a little slippery
your teeth feel a little slippery you
know it might feel good rubbing your
your tongue across your teeth your front
teeth and be like w oil pulling but it
can't hold a candle a candle to
something like prop especially the right
kind of propolis because there's
propolis with alcohol this propolis
doesn't have alcohol in it you can find
propolis out there it'll say alcohol
free but there's still alcohol in it
they're allowed to do that because they
keep it down a little bit right you the
Mars info I know I know it blew my mind
blew my mind asking Spirit of
compassion but what happens is the oil
pulling isn't effective the mouthwashes
aren't effective either and a lot of the
mouthwashes that the natural ones there
there's all kinds of crap in there and
they're not effective for immune system
health for your oral
needs but propolis is one of those
miracles on the planet and when it's
done
right it's done right and that's the
difference right so the pure propolis
right there is is a whole another level
it's just so incredible so that's it
right there the vimergy one but so let's
go into propus a little bit let's go
into oral health like what's going on in
people's mouth
you got the herp simplex one you got the
cold sorce you got herp Simplex
2 yeah herp simplex one herp Simplex too
in people's mouths some people got two
varieties of cold sores they'll have a
fever blister that looks a little
different does something a little
different and then they'll have like
cold sores on the outside of their
mouth then they'll have cold sores in
their
nose fever blisters in their nose it's a
herpes simplex one or two and the key is
immune system for battling that that's a
big
deal immune system so if you guys just
got on here we're doing a little oral
health talk which is so needed for
people I don't want to forget about it
time goes by a lot happens there's a lot
going on I'm releasing a book pretty
pretty soon there's there's a lot of
things going on and but I just you know
I just have to make sure I'm a
reminder about what this can do and
about what propolis can do and golden
seal and zinc and how important these
things are so we're here we're live
right now okay so let's cut into it
right here okay so gums that recede
because bacteria that's not good is
working on them and trying to break them
down and try to eat away at them so
that's one thing that happens receding
gums they get real thin they start to
break down they start to right they
start to Decay one of the reasons why
for receding gums one of the
reasons is people have a lot of metals
in their system they got mercury in
their system they got mercury in their
gums that's sitting in there they got
mercury in their
tongue people have mercury in their
tongue yeah they do like if people's
tongues were dissected if people's
tongues were when when someone dies and
if they did this thing where they remove
the tongue instead of cut instead of
cutting open the brain and and
pretending they actually are looking
inside somebody's
brain which which really they don't
terrible I mean they they slice the
brains when they do the experiments
right when someone donates their brain
to science or science buys it without
them knowing did you hear about that
lately did you hear about that because
I've heard about it for decades where
people and don't know it but their
bodies get sold off if they say it's by
accident their bodies get sold off yeah
like they'll sell a torso
of a girl for $600 they'll sell a head
yeah a head for
$300 they'll sell two legs for
like a $100 a piece $50 a piece to
science I mean I don't I don't know
anything more deranged I don't there's a
lot of reasons why that's totally
deranged but it's true and it happens
it's happening every day just just you
know
we're let's bring it back bring it back
to to oral health please yeah so what
happens is that when they slice a brain
okay they they slice it open like you
know when you put a um you go to the
deli and they
put a big slab of you know some cold
cuts right and you get cold cuts at a
deli and they're slicing it can I have
that slice thin please and they set the
cutter they set the cutter some like 0
10 or something like that and they slice
it thin well they do that with brains
and they start looking for stuff they
start taking a look at things what they
really need to to do is they need to
take tongues and they need to do that
with tongues they need to actually test
what's in tongues tongues get really
really toxic really dirty and really
toxic that's why eating tongue like beef
tongue is ridiculously stupid eating
beef tongue unless it's all you have
it's if it's all you have and you live
in some country somewhere and you're
like you're really dead poor and it's
either that or eating dirt then yeah
then I completely understand you eat a
beef tongue you eat a cow tongue I
understand I am not shaming anybody or
saying don't you know don't ever do that
or anything like that I'm just saying if
you have the ability not to do that if
you have access to some resources and
access to some food don't eat a beef
tongue a cow
tongue don't highly talk toxic highly
filled with you toxic heavy metals you
got to watch out with organ Meats organ
meats are the worst if you're an animal
protein person stick with the regular
animal protein stick with that I'm just
saying if you're an an I support you if
you're an animal protein person I
support you if you're eating all these
toxic organs too of course I support you
because I just I just want to offer
whatever I can to add to whatever you're
doing even if you're doing something
wrong yeah sorry
wrong but the organ meets are oh my God
the trend is insane talking about
getting somebody so toxic so fast in
their life if you're somebody and you're
starting out Young on organ meets like
you're starting out at 15 years old or
something or 14 years old and your
family's feeding you organ meats and
you're starting out that young oh dear
lord nobody knows nobody knows and then
10 years go by 15 years go by the
toxicity level in a child that turns
into a young adult that turns into an
older adult the toxicity level is so off
the chart compared to um if you're going
to have grass bed beef from a certain
cut you know what I mean muscle from a
certain cut right versus if you eat beef
Hearts I mean for Animals it's different
you need want to feed your dog grass fed
beef Hearts you know it's it's different
but but it for humans to be eating all
the beef hearts and beef liver oh my God
and cow liver and cow tongue and cow
heart cow what a freaking nightmare to
the body and they don't even know nobody
even knows they don't even have a clue
the organ meat thing is utterly
ridiculous I'm not trying to be a jerk
or anything that's not what I'm trying
to do I'm just trying to be the voice of
reason the voice of reason you know
Advanced information I know Trends take
people down all kinds of rabbit holes
and then they're doing it they're
getting clicks and likes and they're
getting all this play out there and
they're they're like you know moving and
grooving and then they're they're
pushing all their organs organ meat
stuff and whatever it is I get it I get
it
but never never never
never would I eat beef liver never great
way to intoxification
right it's in grass-fed beef it's in
small small mounts but it's in there
it's it's in everything it's in
everything this isn't an anti-animal
talk that's not it if your animal
protein stick with the regular animal
proteins meaning grass-fed or something
really good you know if you raise your
own cows whatever and just the point is
stick with with the regular thing and
I'm saying this
because you start eating tongues and
livers and hearts and other organs too
you spleen what whatever you start
eating these and you're going to just
intoxicate yourself at a rapid Pace at a
Mach one level so we're back to oral
health I apolog my apologies truly and
this isn't an anti-animal protein thing
at all and it's not an anti- plant-based
thing too I say a lot of things about
the plant-based eaters and the vegan the
vegan eaters and stuff like that because
they do things wrong and they they don't
know it but they're intoxicating
themselves and that's just it that's
even a word intoxic ating okay let's go
into oral health a little bit so tongues
are toxic they are and it's hard on our
immune system when we have these toxic
tongues very hard on our immune system
in our mouth in our mouth area lymphatic
vessels lymphatic system the whole bit
there's a tongue right here um they take
a look right there there's a tongue you
see it's right underneath the eyeball I
don't know if you could see that on IG
how about on Tik Tok you guys see that
on there so there's a tongue okay our
immune system is guarding our tongue we
have a lot of immune cells in our tongue
and there's a reason for that tongues
get attacked tongues get a lot of
cancers tongues get a lot of different
herpes viruses tongues get different
kinds of bacteria you know infested in
them so it's a big part of how our
immune system is always like under a
battle under a war in a war it's a big
part of it tongue gets toxic okay for
multitudes of reasons one is it's highly
absorbent things we put in our mouth can
go into a
tongue faster than they stick around in
the
bowel that's right faster than they
stick around in the bow you ready for
this too something can absorb in the
tongue that's toxic that you're eating
or something like that say you're eating
some tuna then you're doing like the
Mercury thing you're eating tuna tuna I
I got a friend that says I'm I'm eating
this wild cot tuna I said really you
like
Mercury
so what happens is say you're eating
that tuna right well your tongue will
absorb the Mercury
first uh-huh uh-huh it will it will
first before guess what your liver and
your liver is going to absorb it next it
is it's going to go down in this the
stomach and down in the dadum down the
small intestinal tract down in the guts
it is and then it's going to be absorbed
it's going to go up the hepatic portal
Highway into the liver into your liver
right your liver is just going to suck
it up and absorb it up whatever it is
and take it all in but your tongue had
first divs first
divs another thing interesting your
tongue has to have a lot of blood it has
to have a lot of blood flow lots of
blood flow you guys Lots because it has
lots of it has it has that hyper blood
flow in your tongue somebody gets their
tongue
pierced I mean there's nothing wrong
with that and someone wants to do that
it's up to whoever wants to do that but
it's a shock to the tongue because the
immune system needs the tongue just kind
of left alone and you know doing what it
needs to do you know I had another
friend who had their tongue pierced many
years ago and I told them you should
take that piercing out and just let it
heal just let it heal you know but if to
each to each their own people do what
they want to do I mean I'm not judging
anybody it is what it is but the
tongue is
inherently
vascular it just is so what that means
is it
pulls
pulls what that word is it means that
the blood pulls there does it pulls
there a lot and then it drops off a lot
of toxins our tongues get toxic our
tongues get toxic just like our livers
get toxic they just get toxic so not
only do tongues absorb when you eat
something so if you're eating like uh
tuna fish and the Mercury will go into
your tongue it'll actually enter it and
stay in
there but here's the other thing you
think the tongue is
vascular
hypervascular what about the heart
that's why I tell people you're into all
kinds of like organ meats and stuff like
that do not eat Hearts they're so toxic
so toxic because they're so
vascular and and the toxins pull there
you know this really a rough one I mean
you know people don't know but again
it's all about the trends Trends Trends
not about really people healing in the
end it's about the trends and then when
the trends don't really work or they die
out or they shift then it's on to a new
trend but it's not about people healing
it's sad it's
sad Lena what about dental fillings same
as with tuna of course if you got the
mums if you got the the silver fillings
and stuff if you had the silver fillings
yeah I mean absorbs into the tongue
absolutely our tongues get toxic it
absorbs things and then our immune
system gets compromised in our mouths
but our immune systems get compromised
in everybody's mouth it's also why the
herpes viruses are so Vigilant they're
so so hyper
catchy that some people catch them boom
they got it some people it takes two
years right you're smooching with
someone whatever and you're on the
dating scene and then everything seems
okay you don't have anything nothing's
happening whatever next thing you know
it you know two years later you break
out with your first cold sore you're at
the doctor that's a cold sore that's a
fever blister came from the date two
years ago it just happens right depends
on your immune system too sometimes and
it depends on what kind of varieties of
bugs we're talking about now if you guys
came on here we're talking about the
propolis we're talking about the zinc
we're talking about especially the
propolis too oh my God I can't talk
enough about it and the golden
seal we're talking about
those there's a lot of different
varieties of HH you know hvs1 herpy
simplex
one lots of different varieties of
Herpes Simplex 2 and people get them in
their mouth first and they get them
there
and they battle this and it comes
out some people get two or three you
know over time just because you got
fever blisters doesn't mean you're not
going to catch another fever blister
that's the other thing too just because
you caught one six years ago doesn't
mean you're not going to catch another
from somebody else and it's a different
variety so now you got two one pops up
this month one pops up that month one
pops up this month you really don't know
the difference one pops up another month
that's why like oral health is critical
oral immune system health is
critical I'm not on here right now to
have some fun I got a lot going on it's
just that I feel a
responsibility
so let's talk about oral health a little
bit more when it comes down to immune
system so lymphatic
vessels lymphatic
lands down there in the neck that's a
hot spot that is such a hot spot right
there the neck the glands lymphatic
glands all around the neck back of the
neck bottom of the you know the base of
the
head your throat all of it and then we
got our tonsils too so we got our
tonsils if you still have them if you
still have your tonsils but I get it a
lot of people still don't have their
tonsils they lost their tonsils a long
time ago
because of immune system challenges they
had chronic strep and maybe didn't even
know they had chronic strep maybe they
were diagnosed with strep throat one
time but they didn't know they had
chronic strep for so long
um tonsilitis tonsils being inflamed
tonsils being swollen all this matters
with oral health with gums and teeth
gums and
teeth and tongues a lot of people have M
mouth ulcers they have them on their
tongue they get canker swords on their
tongue and they hurt like heck and they
bite their teeth into it they're like
trying to bite them like and they're
biting them a lot of people do that
they're biting their
tongue um rightfully so so that's
another thing that people go through so
our immune system is heavily challenged
and it showcases itself through oral
health tongue health and then what about
crinkles crinkle tongue crinkle tongue
Sahara Desert tongue
right so the whole thing thing with the
tongue and and crinkling and getting the
lines in it and all of that too you know
and a lot of people are like well you
know it's you go to somebody you go to
you know Chinese medicine or you go you
know Oriental medicine or you go to um
atic you know medicine or whatever and
you're going to you know you're doing a
all that and you're going to different
practitioners NDS herbalists right
acupuncturists and they're just like oh
I'm looking at your
tongue you know you got liver heat
looking at your tongue and you got this
but here's another thing people don't
realize your
tongue it's not just coming from your
gut or your liver or anything like that
and showcasing signs of
that your tongue itself is challenged
challenged on immune system levels it's
challenged orally you're challenged on
an immune system oral
health and you could be getting healthy
kicking butt getting rid of you could be
doing medical medium stuff you're doing
medical medium stuff you're getting rid
of neurological symptoms you're moving
forward and you're kicking butt and
you're healing and you're just you're
you're you're crushing it you knocked
out 40 symptoms and you're moving
forward and you can still have a beat up
tongue for quite a while because
sometimes the tongues are the last to
heal sometimes the tongues are the last
to heal deep seated tongue issues right
the
grooves all all of
that sometimes that takes time and it
could take you it could take years
tongue could be tongues are some of the
most toxic things in our body next to
our hearts yeah our hearts really toxic
our livers really toxic and our brains
really
toxic down the road they're going to
offer programs it's going to be closer
to more closer to ending times but it's
was talking the spirit of compassion and
spirit of compassion is closer we get to
ending times down down the road there
going to be offering programs where you
know you just you not only do you are
you like an organ donor you have an
organ organ donor card but you also have
an organ feeder card so because there's
going to be all kinds of problems with
crops and the Food Supplies are going to
dim down because of toxicity and
everything else down way way way way in
the future and
um they're going to be offering people
who pass away offering organs for being
consumed because the food supply is
going to be so scarce um I think I'm
going to do something about that or talk
something about that that's really
intense
stuff but anyway tongues are going to be
on the menu is what I'm trying to say
and that's where I was going they will
be on the menu and it won't be just cow
tongue all right
um let's let's go into it
here if you're new I'm Anthony William
the medical medium if you're new and
you're on here and you haven't seen me
talk about stuff or do anything um if
you want a little window into me about
stuff most people healed on the planet
outside of any single protocol or belief
system or Diet belief system or whatever
it is you want to call it out there a
trend most people healed and the most
most people around the planet around the
globe
healing the most the most most attacked
because of it but the most and that's
special and because of s so not because
of me I'm just a messenger so let's talk
about the pro propolis and everything so
if you if you're
here let's learn about the propolis I
got a little shot glass here and um I
might do something kind of funny here I
might put a little bit of this tea water
in
there so I want to talk about how to
apply to canker sores cold soures mouth
ulcers so here's what you do even though
I got this little shot glass out there
because you can put it in there too if
you don't like the taste The Taste is
actually good in my opinion The Taste is
great in my opinion okay so you got I
got the propolis right here so applying
it you apply it right on the source
that's what I tell all people I know
that are dealing with anything right on
the sore droing a little bit right out
of the thing you put it on the soore
okay but I well here's the best way
doing it that's the lazy way lazy way of
doing it you take a paper towel or or a
wash cloth that's dry and
clean not one that's been used for all
kinds of things you take a was washcloth
or a paper towel on the inside of the
mouth you just dry that canker sore dry
it yes dry it so you just go tap tap tap
you know you take that paper towel you
go you you dab it you dry the
sore it could be a sore on your gum it
could be a canker sore on your gum on
your tongue it could be a blister from a
cold sore which is different herpes cold
sores are different than canker
sores right or that area line you know
what I'm talking about the lines
so what about the ker swur lines sharp
Jagged pain in the inside of the mouth
right the lines you know you feel them
and there's like lines on the side of
your mouth you're like the heck where'
those lines come from and the lines are
there right people have this all day
long out there and they got two or three
canker sturs just on the line and the
line hurts or if they bit their tongue
they bit their lip they bit the side of
the inside of their cheek and now a krur
is coming it's on its way it's not just
going to be a sore it's going to be a
kerur Janessa says I love propolis for
my
kerur it makes them disappear in a day
thanks aw and SSC for this tool you're
welcome I'm
messenger
and S so has the data and the info so
the thing is about the propolis which is
unbelievable is yes I've seen it take
away canker saurus in a day in a day
some people have dim siiz canker saurus
and it's going to take more than a day
some people have quarter siiz canker
saurus some people have canr saurus in
the throat like deep in the throat they
got canker saurus and some people have
canas saurus going down the
esophagus but what you do is you dry off
the area if it's on the lip dry it on
dry it off if it's outside of the lip
it's already dry pretty much but you
apply the propolis every single hour you
apply it to the blister to the dry
blister to the blister on the outside of
your mouth on your lip the Blister in
your nose the blister wherever that
blister is it could be a you know a cold
sore fever blister right in the inside
of your nose right there put a little
propolis on it put a little propolis on
it if it's if it's in your lip inside
your mouth and it feeds the immune
system in that area it feeds the immune
system in the
area yes it does so the propolis is
something that you
apply right on the
spot and oh my
God what it does but it's not just that
sure okay you might be somebody that
doesn't have a canker swur but you got
receding gums you might be somebody that
doesn't have a canker stur but you got
some other problems you got other mouth
problems happening of all different
kinds bad
bacteria you put propolis in your mouth
as your mouth wash or mouth rinse but
just swallow it because it's your
propolis what it can do for your oral
health if this what I was trying to say
oil pulling it's not that a lot of
people are even doing oil pulling
anymore oil pulling is
ridonculous
compared to using propolis now keep in
mind this is the vimergy propolis I
endorse these guys for a reason because
nothing touches that stuff it has a
living coratin in
it I mean polyphenols a whole bit has a
living cortin in it it's not like dead
coratin it's living coratin inside there
I mean that's a whole another story
about why this propolis is so incredible
so what you see it's in the middle out
of these three it's the propolis pure
okay so that's the vimer GV is in Victor
I saw somebody ask what company V is in
Victor i m is a Mary E RG
y.com vimergy.com
it's just incredible
stuff um you can take it internally for
your immune system I'm just talking
about oral health but what it does for
the immune system what I've seen it do
for people with health problems off the
chart I I have to talk about it if I
don't and someone doesn't have this tool
someone will go out and buy a
$5,000 um somebody will go out and buy a
$3,000 $5,000
program to some so-called idiot out
there that doesn't even have the right
kinds of information and they'll go do
that thinking they're hoping to God they
can find some kind of magical pillar
Panacea and I'm sitting here for free
letting you know that
OMG what propolis can do for your immune
system and for your
health and I and I apologize for using
words like idiot and stuff like that I
mean sometimes you know I'm not look I'm
human I'm human I'll say something you
know I'll swear once in a while I will
one will come out
um I don't know what to
say but doesn't matter if you like me or
hate me or think I'm cool or think I'm
you know whatever doesn't matter it's
it's about having this information
that's all that matters is having this
information when Spirit of compass
passion came to me you know and I got
the gift since I was younger so I would
say you sure you want
me you sure you want
me to be your
rep truck driver David okay so let's go
into it a little bit
more Fast Track boom cold sores herpes
sores of all different kinds okay I mean
like in different parts of the body
herur cold sores mouth ulcers big dimiz
canker sores CID canker
sores yeah gum problems all kinds of
different issues neurological stuff
inside the mouth that's immune system
related neurological stuff people are
dealing with burning tongue burning this
Burning
gums trigeminal neuralgia is something
that like eats people up I mean that's
that eats them up the pain in their jaw
and the pain in their neck brutal all
these different bugs all these different
bugs so so the bottom line
is it's immune system needs care and
love it needs help and our immune system
really really is very very productive
around our mouth in our mouth in our
neck in our
throat how many people get tonsilitis
how many people get their tonsils out
how many people have sore throats how
many people have strep throat how many
people have all kinds of problems left
and right you name it and their teeth
end up problematic down the road and
their gums end up problematic and they
end up getting sores and all kinds of
stuff in their mouth and they end up
getting other things too so oral
health there's like hands down propolis
should be in everybody's like bathroom
that's a great place for it too not just
in your supplement section wherever you
keep your supplements and everything and
you got your supplements lined up or
whatever that might be and you have that
propolis should be there and one should
be in your bathroom for cold sores and
kker sores and oral stuff and whatever
it should be in there so you can put it
in your mouth you can put it on your
tongue you can actually just you could
put a squirt of it in your mouth and let
it just mole around for 30 seconds you
can do a dropper full and let it mole
around for 30 seconds seconds or a
minute in your mouth let it just absorb
into the immune system so the immune
system can use it and Gobble it up that
incredible living coratin that's in
there what what like God's Gift really
the problem is with propolis is out
there they're polluted they're burnt
they don't have those those um
phytochemical compounds that are active
because alcohol's been put in there and
alcohol just kills every phytochemical
compound that's why the alcohol world
inting Ure world it's it's it's dying
because medical medium exposed that
medical medium exposed that tincture
should not have alcohol in them it
should not have that corn grain alcohol
in them I mean oh my God that was
happening for years and years and years
and I don't care like grape
alcohol still not good still not good oh
yeah no this is grape alcohol this isn't
corn grain alcohol like you know they
use in a lot of supplements uh I don't
care still not good bad idea bad idea
still kills everything still kills the
phytochemical compound so the vimergy
stuff they won't do that they won't play
with
that they they instead put together a
propolis that doesn't have that it's
just you can't like can't get any better
than that
so
cavities cavities okay what I love about
propolis is it's a great thing to keep
the mouth's immune system strong because
cavities can be something that's really
annoying see a lot of people have toxic
they're high and toxic heavy metals they
got a lot of viruses like Epstein bar
hhv6 out aular virus they got all kinds
of stuff HPV they just got lots of
different bugs and so those bugs end up
you know challenging the immune system
over and over again and so when that
happens bacteria that's not great
bacteria that's sitting inside the mouth
can actually produce cavities a little
bit more especially if there's Metals
around and metals in the tissue and some
of these high in metals the immune
system can't keep up with it so cavities
start getting produced even if you're
healing I know people they're healing
look I know people in medical medium
they heal all their cavities they heal
their their mouth they heal they their
teeth regrow enamel so many people
throughout the years their teeth are
regrowing
enamel like they had a hard time with
their teeth because of the deficiencies
and nutritional deficiencies they had
for 20 years and all the medications and
the drugs they've been on and all the
different stuff and the benzos and
everything else everything they tried
you know you name it down the line right
and they're beat up and their teeth all
of a sudden just crumble all the apple
cider vinegar that's another thing okay
okay if there's one thing I can give you
one thing you can take away from this
stop the Apple C of vinegar stop all
vinegars but stop the Apple C of vinegar
if Apple C of vinegar is the only
vinegar you're going to use because
you're going to use the B worst vinegars
then use the Apple Coda vinegar but stop
it if you're worried about your teeth
and your HC and your gastric glands be
careful with the apple cider vinegar
because apple cider vinegar will start
leeching all the Calum will leech out of
your teeth and over time and then years
go by and even if you're doing the right
things finally your teeth crumble even
when you're finally doing the right
things you find like answers and you're
healing you know why you're sick from EP
bar you're getting Metals out your teeth
can still have the delayed effect of of
all the vinegar for 20 years so it takes
time for that to heal too
mirio says I had receding gums and
exposed tooth and celery juice fixed
that for me celery juice does I wrote a
book the celery juice book that talks
about what it does for gums and teeth
and how it could even stop errosion and
enamel erosion and gum receding yeah I
mean it's critical you have to have the
celery juice too there's some people
that need more than the celery juice but
the ACV does damage and it does damage
that shows post post damage later on all
right so let's talk about the golden
seal
so we're talking about the propolis this
is VY stuff right here V is and Victor i
m is and Mary E RG
y.com okay themy stuff I endorse these
guys because they are the greatest the
greatest and the greatest you see people
who like you know like whatever rep
companies out there and stuff like that
you see it out there they're not saying
that you know this is the greatest and
they don't say all the good reasons and
all that right but when you know what
they're doing and how they're doing in
the process I had to stand behind this
company do you know how many companies
come to me out there you
guys a dozen a day medical medium can
you get behind my company medical medium
can you get behind my company medical
medium if you guys only knew what our
inboxes looked like you wouldn't believe
it I could rep a 100 companies out there
make hundreds and hundreds and hundreds
of millions of dollars but I don't the
point is it has to be like something
special the best thing in the world
world the best thing I think is out
there in the world and that's the
vimergy
stuff anyway the golden
seal the golden seal speaks for itself
it just does I talk about it in the
books I talk about in the medical medium
series the book
series golden seal right I love it for a
lot of reasons there's golden seal shock
therapy you should look into it
everybody should have a golden seal and
not a golden seal with alcohol in it
natural flavors not a golden seal with
citric acid in it not a golden seal with
some other crazy stuff that they're not
listing on the bottle remember I told
you there's this like there's this
there's 10% law I something like I don't
know it's a small
percentage and all these supplement
companies can put all the stuff in it
nobody even knows they don't have to
list it well vimergy doesn't do that
anyway golden seal a potent powerful
golden
seal you can't go wrong with that so
it's another thing too and then um
the good old
zinc zinc liquid zinc sulfate right
there the vimergy one the only one I
trust
um critical for the immune system and
we're in January right now heading into
February and there is a [ __ ]
storm heading over into the United
States it's a [ __ ] storm of a lot of RSV
a [ __ ] storm of a lot of flu bugs
different flu of all
kinds different Seas of all of all kinds
and all that you believe it at this
point still I say
C at this point everybody says what they
want out there right I still have to say
C because like I said you don't get
awards for getting people better A lot
of people better like thousands upon
thousands you don't get Awards and you
don't get
like um you don't get immunity for it so
yeah see anyway so there's a lot of that
going around there's a lot of that out
there so keep in mind you want your
immune system strong and protect it you
want your immune system in a good place
what you see in front of me is the zinc
you got the propolis and check out
golden seal it should be in your cabinet
it should be in your kitchen it should
be by your
nightstand I keep the golden seal by my
nightstand that's right I shoot some in
boot boom down it goes what I like to do
with golden seal is I like to actually
just let it sit in my mouth and sit in
my
throat that's one way of using golden
seal and um I like to do the same thing
with propolis and zinc so I put zinc in
propolis and some golden seal I put a
little bit in my mouth and I let it you
know sit there you can put it in a shot
glass just like this there's nothing
wrong with that can do that I'm going to
put some golden seal in here if you
don't
mind I'm going to put two dropper fulls
of golden seal in there
I'm going to put um dropper full of
uh look at
that that go that propolis is insane
just this going to pop some zinc in
there too there we
go try not to make a
mess I seem to all right if you guys
just popped on here we're talking about
immune system oral health you might want
to watch this uh video from the
beginning this live from the beginning
because there's so much
information rowanne from France my front
teeth were thinning and getting
translucent in my mid-20s whoa about to
be 39 congratulations and 5 years
medical medium and my teeth are coming
back yes they can yes they
can yeah they can sick boy over there on
YouTube thanks to your recommendation of
vitamin C for the gum
I healed chronic gum bleeding of seven
years that four different dentists could
not
fix okay Asia over there on YouTube
golden steal and propolis shock therapy
saved me from a lot of suffering I don't
take that lightly ASA I don't take that
um lightly okay if you're saying
suffering it has great meaning all right
and I know and I know because I
understand I understand best of my
ability I I understand
truly um and that's the thing you you
know the amount of teeth and gum help
people have gotten from medical medium
protocols and medical medium
information is is is really really um
special on all levels truly special
miraculous really I mean the amount of
people the level of gum and teeth repair
and oral health improvements for people
it's been just really special right
and then you get somebody you get
somebody then they you that's the thing
the the problem is too you get somebody
out there they're not really doing
Medical medum but they're saying medical
mediums that's the whole thing you
remember there's no programs I'm holding
people to did you guys sign up for
medical medium programs for $3,000 a pop
and then we actually we have coaches on
hand and we watch your every move and we
we put you to the task and you do every
little thing no there's no there's no
like rules in a way there's no no one's
being beholden into any kind of like
system it's just the medical medium book
series when someone says they did a
medical medium what did they even do
especially if they're complaining about
something like I tried medical medium it
didn't work I have a cavity it's like
really because I would love to look at
everything I want to look at your
grocery store receipts let's take a look
at them I want to look at your medical
records let's take a look at them too if
you give me permission let's look at
them we'll sit together we'll sit there
and we'll put it all on a coffee table
let's look at all your medical Rec look
all the medications let's see the side
effects on all the medications let's
look at your restaurant receipts let's
look at them how many times you're going
out to different restaurants what have
you been eating let's look in your
cupboards how much vinegar is in the
cupboard that's just one
thing let's look at everything you're
doing did you just get your house
painted are you breathing in all these
paint fumes did you just get a room
painted in your house you breathing in
all did you get your carpets cleaned
what kind of plugins do you have around
the house what kind of detergents are
you using what are you actually getting
in you right what are you eating what
kind of processed foods did you eat in
between it all that have food chemicals
and
everything what kind of exposures have
you had too what kind of alcohol
consumption I'd like to see all the
receipts and everything you're doing and
what kind of recreational drug use you
tried iasa and you're trying to blame
your your your cavity on medical medium
I don't even know what you did and you
did iasa on and off for the last 10
years the group of people in some
Retreat
somewhere so you know let's let's look
at all your records let's see your
dental records I want to see all your
dental records going back Mercury
fillings everything I want to see all
your dental records how many fluoride
treatments have you had because they're
saying I've been saying fluoride's bad
forever but now they're saying
fluoride's really bad so it's hitting
mainstream so you're going to blame me
for a cavity or you're going to blame me
for
something you're going to blame medical
meme information but you're you're not
like the people in the medical M
Community who literally have been there
done that tried everything and they're
seasoned and they're really applying
medical medium and customizing it for
themselves and they have they're humble
they're humble and their integrity is is
unbelievable the people in the medical
medium Community their integrity and
their humble nature and their
their they have respect for other people
in the community The Compassion they
have is unlike anything else out there
so you if you drift into the medical M
community and you try one thing and you
don't like me for some reason because
you don't like my hat or don't like my
glasses or something like that and
you're just pissed or you hear something
that's a lie and false information out
there about me because there's a bunch
of people spreading that constantly if
you're that and all of a sudden you're
going to complain about your cavity or
something or your gums did you really do
medical medium no and what about the
medical treatment did you get the
medical treatment and what about birth
control were you doing birth control
when you were 16 years old 17 years old
10 you know 10 years ago were you doing
it when you were you know 15 years ago
how much birth control did you do and
what about the Medical Treatments you
had too like you know what I mean like
those whatever it is there's a lot of
stuff so yeah get cracking at it I'd
like to see all the receipts and see all
the data let's bring it all out on the
table
okay yeah
exactly and if somebody's out there and
they want to take it to a whole another
level of like whatever it is saying that
harm was created because of this because
of because of you know like some
fruit and you could eat meat you can be
vegan you can do whatever you want and
still do medical medium but if you're
like you think you were harmed by
actually learning some really good
information and taking care of yourself
well then we're going to look at all
your
records
yeah yeah like if you want to take it
out there and put it out there publicly
like then we need to see all your
records I want to see all your
medications I want to see all your
medical visits I want to see all your
restaurants I want to see all the food
you buy I want to see everything I want
to see every single
receipt
yeah
so
mhm and we should do that too if someone
wants to take it to to the full extent
of I've been hurt by actually doing some
wild blueberries and and my teeth fell
out from doing medical medium really cuz
everybody's teeth are healing on medic
medium and if sometimes it's a delay
Factor people get into medical medium
they're already their teeth their their
teeth was having problems but if you're
going to go there to the full extent and
and go like hogwire public about it or
something then yeah we have to do
something like legally we need to look
at all your documents all your records
all your stuff we need to see like were
you in a case study somewhere where they
were only feeding you medical medium
stuff and they had they were watching
everything they're watching everything
you did every food you ate every no
it's an insane
world but you guys know
that living light right there shared
medical medium information with
cooworker as soon as she learned she got
life-changing foods and started medical
medium healing immediately and her A1C
has dropped from 6.5 to five that's
actually really incredible by the way
and she's lost weight doing morning
cleanse it's amazing you know know why I
don't talk about type two type diabetes
and type one two you know why I don't
talk about Len and everything else and
diabetes and stuff like that and and and
it's in the books I talk about diabetes
and pre-diabetes and pre pre pre pre
pre-diabetes in the books Liver Rescue
you guys I I I I love talking about the
reason why I don't talk about it because
you get fixed when you're doing medical
medium there's so many different
difficult neurological symptoms that we
need that I always try to help people
with and push them forward with because
those are oh man those can dog along
because nerves get damaged and you got
to repair the nerves and they take time
but man type 2 diabetes boom like boom
off insulin after a while boom yeah
because you know you lower those fats
you're getting the insulin resistance
and your oh my God the diabetes
information out there by the way the
glucose stuff out there and the glucose
people out there are talking about
glucose and making big like you know
making big waves out there because they
got they run a billion ads they got
money behind them right and they're
they're not censored they're not Shadow
banded and they're out there and they're
doing the glucose crap out there all
those people talking about that the
influencers and
stuff I don't know how anybody survives
what they
offer all they offer are insul creating
insulin resistance that's that's all
they offer out there they offer things
pretending it's going to help eat this
with this eat this with that and all it
does is create insulin resistance I
don't know how anybody's going to get
better out there with the amount of the
amount of crap that's regurgitating and
recycling back into itself it's like a
giant monster of [ __ ] people send in DMS
and comments non-stop on all the trends
people ask me are good and bad and so
forth that's why I do bring it up do you
guys want to know I'm talking about it
because I get dm'd all the time like
what about this person what about this
what about that what about this podcast
doctor what about you know they're
asking all the
time all right so what do you have in
front of me I put some zinc in here I
need an immune immune system boost right
now though I me I got to tell you guys
like I'm finishing up I'm finishing up
the spiritual
book I don't use this term but I'm
scared
because I even put like this thing on
there saying you know this is serious
content right here and just want to
forewarn you I even put that there like
here's a little forewarning because what
you're going to hear is um
it it hits home it hits
home yeah anyway so I'm doing like the M
I'm burning the midnight oil is what I'm
doing burning the midnight oil Antonio
my wife is healing her
teeth wait Antonio that's your name
Antonio over there in YouTube my wife is
healing her teeth with good results with
the medical medium teeth protocols wow
oh that's powerful on YouTube thank you
thank you
Antonio Helen medical medium helped me
to get out of a very toxic relationship
because my brain healed and I could see
clearly and actually think for myself
thank you medical medium God bless you
Helen God bless you truly
truly God bless you right here I got a
little shot glass you guys I'm going to
take it it's the propolis pure if you
don't have these get them
you won't be sorry you won't be ask your
doctor what's right for you you know um
show your doctor the video show your
doctor the information show your doctor
the medical medium books please please I
want your doctor on board you know and
having a doctor is an amazing thing it
is a beautiful beautiful privilege it's
a beautiful thing to have and ask your
doctor what's right for you using any of
the medical medium stuff please you
know it's important it's important I
always say it and ask your doctor if you
can you can have some zinc ask your
doctor if you can have the propolis and
and use
it mateline over there my teeth turned
gray
initially as I was on medical medium and
cleansing I
continued as Anthony advised just a
little bit some
reason trying to get that
one aha I you can see it now it was
halfway on the screen I continued as
Anthony advised advised and they are
white strong and the recess I had prior
to starting medical medium was improved
my recession improving tool I'm going to
tell you right now the one thing even be
just so you know before before the
medical medium book series years ago
when I was working with people oneon-one
and you guys know my history working
with people one-on-one for years and
years and years then I'm going to start
doing some podcast casts pretty soon of
people that medical medium information
healed that I worked with 20 years ago
20 years ago 25 years ago 30 years ago
okay I don't know anybody who can do
that out there who has that all the
newbies that got into Health movement
and they're trying to get somebody to
eat like carnivore or something or they
got a podcast whatever it is I don't
know anybody that has that I'm going to
bring people on the medical Me podcast
that had babies when they couldn't have
babies and the kids are now 20 years old
and the kids are now 18 years old and
you know things like that so we're going
to have some fun it's going to be really
cool that's eventually going to come too
it's just I'm trying to get whatever I
can get done and all the things I can do
vimer g v is in Victor i m is in Mary E
RG y don't miss out on having the tools
you need ask your doctor if it's okay if
it's right for you but that propolis
pure the zinc and the golden
seal seriously something you should have
in your medicine cabinet yes in your
medicine cabinet and just you should
have it and have the cleanse to heal
book there's one sitting over here
cleanse to heal book let me see if I can
grab it real quick you should have that
I'm going to move my chair over here if
you guys don't mind I'm going to bring
my chair back okay if you guys don't
mind okay brain saver protocols which is
over there too cleanse the heels a great
book to have you can get it for pennies
I declare pennies amazon.com go to a
bookstore go to the library and get it
for free you guys know the drill I don't
care if it's for free doesn't matter I
want it to be for free so please get
cleanse to heal if you haven't had this
book yet critical book you got the
morning cleanse you got the mono cleanse
I can't wait to do some monoc cleanse
stuff with you guys it's on my list it
is on my list to do some monoc cleans
stuff with you guys get on my newsletter
medical medium newsletter
join join me on my medical medium
newsletter or you'll get information
join the medical medium newsletter and
you'll get information there you go all
the time free information and you'll
know about when the spiritual book is
coming I repeat the spiritual book is
coming
um so blew my mind with the spiritual
information that came I put it in the
book
look I can I have no words if you guys
see me go quiet for a second it's called
I got no words when you hear and
read working on it
Fast Cleanse to heal should have this
too okay just want to tell you guys
anyway when it comes down to oral health
we want to build our immune system we
want it strong we want the immune system
in our neck and in our throat and in our
mouth to be strong so it kills off
things that enter our mouth so it kills
off stuff when you go to the
dentist something you know just all
kinds of different things
and here's what I recommend if you're at
the dentist office make your dentist and
the
hygienist right and the
assistant make them change over their
gloves if you're at a dentist office
where they're they're they take your
they take their gloves off and they
place it
down like on the counter they leave the
assistants leave because they're on like
this policy of like they don't want to
waste gloves and then they come back and
they put the same pair on okay I talk
about this in brain saver brain saver is
over there but what I'm trying to say is
you go to the dentist since we're
talking about oral health make them
change out gloves because the gloves are
to protect the you know protect them
right but you want you want it to
protect you too I can go into detail
about that we can do a whole show on it
but the whole glove changing thing is
really
important so it
is because they touch everything and
they're touching all the stuff and all
that and it's the glove now they're you
know I'll do a telegram on it check out
my telegram by the way um I did one on
Mars last night don't miss out on my
telegram exclusive messages I don't say
the things that I say on there on here
because it's just it's just what comes
in the moment just what
happens you know yep yep yep
t.me forward
slmed
medium forward slmed medium
t.m medical
medium that's my Telegram
exclusive messages on there okay Lynette
over there on Facebook I messed up my
diet but still drink celery juice and do
the heavy metal detox
smoothie I juice greens also started
eating junk food from being in the
office it's hard to get clean again
gained 15 pounds ug ug ug completely
understand Lynette I completely
understand okay and I totally understand
it's not easy the stress stress eating
is really difficult I'll do it stress
eating podcast episode I promise okay
I'll do a stress eating podcast episode
I'll try to be as helpful as possible I
understand okay um if you need to just
look call upon the Angels at night when
you're getting in bed and you're tucking
yourself in say to the angels listen I
need extra support I could do this I
could do this and and
and realize
something that you know you know life's
not easy you know you're up against a
lot you know you're working really hard
okay so don't beat yourself up so
Lynette don't beat yourself up about it
whatever you do you be kind to yourself
kind to yourself you're a good person
and then okay it's going to hit you
where you're going to be like okay I
think I can get stronger I think I'm
going to get back on I think I'm going
to get back doing it a lot of people are
all or nothing too and I totally
understand that I'm not saying Lynette
that's what you are but so many people
they're all or nothing where they're
like they're doing it doing it doing it
and then they're just like I can't do it
anymore I'm not going to do anything
until they do it again if you're one of
those people we can do it again we can
get back on track but Lynette I
understand stress is really difficult
you mess up your diet happens every day
please please know that and stay you
know in the community someone's going to
help you come on you know remember what
Lynette remember on one of the lives I
talked about chips crunchy chips and
stuff like that and everybody said they
were eating chips remember that like
okay let me just ask everybody now who's
eating chips I mean the healthier chips
but who's eating healthy chips they like
the crunch who's eating the chips just
curious are you guys eating chips um so
I just wanted to ask you about so many
people are eating chips they can't stay
away from chips they love the medical
medium information but that's the whole
point you can eat chips on medical
medium no one's it's like you didn't buy
some $5,000 program and we're holding
you to making sure you don't louse up we
this is this this you know you've got
the freedom and the Free Will and right
you can have the chips you can do that
me me me yeah chips chips chips oh my
God you guys you're eating chips I knew
it you're eating chips again
no no no the chips guilty ktina what no
you love the crunch everybody your kids
too they're eating the chips oh my God
here's a no there's a no no sir sir no
sir Joshua no
sir you're not eating chips
okay the chips the
chips yep when is the next Cafe
Gratitude yep the wellness reset at Cafe
Gratitude is there now it's a cleanse
it's an incredible cleanse it's Dirt
Cheap in my opinion because they make
all the food for you you have the
cleanse they'll have it ready for you go
to their website Cafe Gratitude go to
their website so you can pre-order the
cleanse okay Cafe Gratitude in La make
sure you pre-order their cleanse which
is the wellness reset that's the medical
medium cleanse that's there at Cafe
Gratitude it's incredible they got the
craving shifter in the cleanse the
craving shifter in the cleanse they got
the hmds in the cleanse they have the
celery juice in the cleanse Cafe
Gratitude has the medical medium cleanse
there they prepare it for you they make
it for you it is incredible you guys
should like pre-order it and make sure
you get it please it's so good for you
and get ready the pizza party dinners
popup dinners are coming soon get on the
medical medium newsletter so you know
when that's going to
happen indeed indeed
indeed whoa Regina the Mars the Mars
information the Mars message is
mind-blowing that's a telegram
t.me SL telegram for my Mars
message I think that's it I think think
was a
t did I get that
right God
willing
t.me slmed medium it's my
telegram oh boy
I don't like
Mercury hey anyway I get it I get the
chips thing we all got to Pat each other
on the back and we all have
to be grateful for the good things we
have and the resource and the
information and all
that the wild blueberry babe good to see
you like all that good information we
have from above and everything and yes
we're going to end up eating chips or
we're going to end up doing this and
it's going to happen but that's okay we
don't beat ourselves up be easy on
ourselves and have
compassion you guys eat better than
anybody out there in any of the whatever
genres of health and wellness and
everything
else so your chips are a joke compared
to what everybody's eating out
there Michelle life is hard I concur I
concur
greatly anyway you guys know I love you
get cleanse to heel bring it to your
doctor and remember about the immune
system remember about the zinc and the
propolis pure and the golden seal
remember ask your doctor what's right
for
you love you guys