okay we're ready
we're talking about the immune system
how it protects the brain and how the
brain relies on the immune system we're
in the brain saver books you guys
books that are mind boggling
mind-blowing like seriously and there's
so much information in the brain saver
books there's two brain saver books okay
there's so much information in these
it's line for line for line I promise
you the greatest books of all time hands
down in health these will go down as the
greatest books ever in health I can
stand behind that I can say it with
being proud I can say it with confidence
the greatest books in history in health
no one can touch them science research
can't touch them nobody can touch what's
in these books and what they're going to
do for people to move their their lives
forward with sickness and illness
nothing will compare there will never be
a book out there by any other health
author any other health you know
industry that can ever touch the
original unique incredible mind-blowing
comprehensive detailed information
that's in the brain favorite books it
will never ever happen again you're
witnessing history I can say this if
you're somebody that came on here and
you don't own medical medium or medical
medium information you're saying well
he's biased it's his books uh they're
not my books
it comes from above I'm a messenger that
got the information placed it into the
books
and yes the books are there for the
people and these the reason why I sound
a little snarky about that is because
someone was like oh yeah but they're
they're your books and the reason why
I'm snark is like okay yeah sure but the
information came from above I'm not that
smart and if you believe it didn't come
from above and you believe that I'm that
I created this information that's in the
medical meaning book series and in the
brain saver books then okay I'm a genius
I'm a genius then I don't know what to
say I must be a genius he's a genius
everybody
but I'm not a genius Valerie said you're
pretty smart aw I'm not a genius
the information in these books is so
Advanced it's a head of science and
research
real solutions real causes real truth
you can't find this anywhere else you
will never find this anywhere else I
could say this proud the information
came down
I put it in the books it's here and I'm
not a genius for sure and when you read
these books because no one could make
this up it can't even be made up
none of it can just like in the medical
medium books and it paves the way in
alternative medicine and conventional
medicine because they poach and steal
from the mm books mm publishes it first
and they poach and steal it and of
course they they you know and then they
put slander on medical me but the point
is is this is literally a time in
history that's very special the brain
saver books I'm talking about the immune
system
how the brain relies on your immune
system to protect it
the brain relies on your immune system
to protect it okay and so that's
important to know all on its own so
here I am let me move these for now
move them over
if you don't have a copy
maybe someday you will I want to talk
about cleaning your book too which is
interesting so we're going to talk about
that in a little bit but let's get
through this
our immune system
they fight our immune system fights
to defend us our brain relies on your
immune system now I'm just giving you a
forewarning here talked about how the
brain shot therapy is so powerful that
you're gonna get into that instant
relief and it's going to be an
experience that isn't explainable unless
you experience it yourself honest to God
but I'm also talking about every line in
these books both these books
every line
is jammed packed with with information
highly detailed information so let's get
into it a little bit
there's no way humankind could
physically evolve faster than any of
these forces against us just listen to
that one line just one line
out of thousands of lines in these books
there's no way
humankind could physically evolve faster
than any of these forces against us
which brings us to the immune system so
what that means is
we can't out evolve
the chemical poisons the toxins the
exposures the garbage that our bodies
are faced everybody's getting kicked off
IG today unbelievable so they really
have it censored heavy
so
the whole point here that we're talking
about is when it comes down to it we
can't beat out the speed in which the
Earth is polluting our brains
so we need to be active in doing
something we have to learn how to
protect our brains we have to take care
of ourselves we have to have the answers
because right now
I mean the amount of people sick and the
amount of people dying is unbelievable
never before in history and it's all
kept hush hush hush hush out there
but never before in history have we seen
the amount of people dying and the
amount of people being sick globally
like it is right now it's unbelievable
unprecedented right
so this brings us to the immune system
which is responsible for protecting the
brain so our immune system has a
responsibility our immune cells have a
responsibility it's to protect our brain
our immune systems were never made for
what's evolving around us and that's a
problem all on its own our immune system
was never built
to handle what we are up against what is
being evolved around us like the
onslaught of everything we're up against
our immune systems were never created to
deal with that so we have to do
something we have to support our immune
systems we have to support our body
because it was never Geared for that
they weren't designed to fight off
engineered bugs that were manufactured
they weren't designed to deal with
toxins the our immune systems weren't
made to put up with all the amount of
chemicals
so our immune systems were never put up
with the amount of chemicals were up
against it was never put up they were
never our immune systems were never
created to deal with all the different
bugs and viruses like Epstein-Barr and
shingles and hhv6 and all the all the
different viral infections people have
our immune systems were never designed
to deal with chemicals this is something
that our immune systems have been put up
against
and everything's evolving around our
immune systems and our immune system's
job is to protect the brain and the
brain is relying on that
so there's things we can do to protect
our immune systems and to protect our
brain there's things we can do to
actually help our bodies
I mean that's incredible all on its own
our immune system was never designed to
be up against EMF
evolving around us right so EMF used to
just be this radio signals in the 1920s
the 1930s and 1940s radio signals
that was the first Onslaught against our
immune systems and our brain was radio
signals
that was the EMF of the day no biggie
was radio signals you know
so think about that right now how
interesting that is but our immune
systems were never designed for the
evolving EMF we're up against now
and the cell tower signaling that we're
up against now our immune systems were
never designed for that for cell tower
signals
our immune systems were never designed
to deal with the radiation we're up
against now you guys so that's something
that's a whole other level every time
something foreign enters into our body
whether it's EMF
whether it's radiation
whether it's pathogenic
whether it's a toxic chemical
every time something foreign enters into
our body even if it's in the form of
radiation our immune cells have to
gobble it up
really important to know
so every time we are up against anything
our immune cells have to eat it
have to gobble it up to protect our
brain so our brain's relying on this so
as
times are evolving
and we have
this attack this industry attack on our
physical bodies
as that's happening our brain is like
wait a minute here I'm relying on your
immune I'm relying on our immune system
you guys our brains talking like I'm
relying on your immune system
hey I'm relying on your immune system
like our brain is like
literally
screaming
our immune system has to save us and
protect us has to protect the brain
our brain has an intelligence our brain
has a metaphysical and physical
intelligence to know it's in trouble
with what we're up against all the time
between EMF and pathogenic problems and
radiation and toxic chemicals and all of
that
our immune system is the security system
against any attackers that want to
invade our brain think about that so
your immune system is the security
system
to actually stop attackers
to stop brain crime
our immune system
has a big job in defending our brain
so our brain is desperate
relies heavily
on our immune system
now check this out this is mind-blowing
all on its own right here
how long a white blood cell lasts
against a toxic Invader depends on how
toxic the substance is and that's
something that's huge all on its own
now one thing you'll find in the brain
saver books
is your
be educated on all the different things
we have to be concerned about
which is a big deal because that's so
important we need to be aware of of
what's going on
but people don't realize a lot of the
stuff they have in their life and that
they're partaking in their life is
breaking down their immune system and
they don't realize that and that's
really sad when you think about it all
on its own they don't know their immune
system is being broke down
how long a white blood cell how long a
white blood cell
lasts
against the toxic invader
okay
depends on how toxic the substance is
so your white blood cells job is to
gobble up anything in its way anything
that's heading to the brain EMF guess
what your immune cells are trying to
gobble up EMF radiation your immune
cells are trying to gobble up radiation
pathogens like that one your immune
cells are trying to gobble up pathogens
toxic chemicals your immune system is
trying to gobble up toxic chemicals
depending on how powerful that EMF is
how strong that radiation is how toxic
that chemical is how toxic that bug is
determines the lifespan of that white
blood cell that immune cell it
determines the lifespan
that's insane
nanopoisons from perfume and cologne
have to be gobbled up by our white blood
cells what
what
so anytime you get you breathe in
perfume your whites blood cells have to
gobble up the perfume particles
whoa Nano poisons like perfume and
cologne have to be gobbled up by our
white blood cells this is why when
people are breathing in Cologne and
they're sick and they're chronically ill
that clone just weakens them more makes
them sick brings on their migraines
brings on their sinus problems brings on
their fatigue even worse and more to the
point where they're just tasting the
cologne and it's so sickening
but your immune cells if you already
have a weak immune system and generally
immune cells have to gobble up every
part of that cologne nanoparticle
and cologne's not natural
none of that stuff's natural it's
chemical created lab created
important to know
nanoparticles from air fresheners and
scented candles have to be gobbled up is
the only one talking about plug-in air
fresheners
for years and years and now you'll see
on social media like some kind of doctor
influence or something pretending that
he just figured it out yesterday or
something that air fresheners are bad
but doesn't even cite mm but yet is
listening to the podcasts and listening
to everything but doesn't cite it back
so that people can find their way and
then they and then they sell the person
something bad for them like clay to eat
or charcoal or apple cider vinegar
gummies or crap like that it's
unbelievable
it's a sick world it's really A demented
World
nanoparticles from air fresheners and
scented candles have to be gobbled up
by your immune cells and that's a
problem all on its own your immune cells
have to gobble that junk up pathogens
such as these bugs right that everyone
lives with now people live with all the
different bugs inside of them you guys
know how that's why everybody gets sick
it's a big part of it the pathogens
right
I've seen Barr virus low-grade viral
infections weaken the immune system
because your white count has to gobble
it all up
flu viruses and beep
have to be gobbled up
flu viruses and bleep have to be gobbled
up
they have to
xic heavy metals that enter your body
through all kinds of beep and other
things and ways have to be gobbled up
and here's another thing people don't
realize caffeine
caffeine lowers the immune system
because it has to be eaten up by white
blood cells nobody knows that
meanwhile a caffeine industry evolving
around us new caffeine concoctions while
the caffeine industry evolves around us
you guys I'm reading out of brain saver
books check it out
check them out right here you won't be
disappointed when you get the brain
saver books books with an S you will be
mind blown
hands down the greatest books of all
time
and I'm sure just
people are going to be pissed about them
along the way
so I'm sure there's going to be plenty
of campaigns to try to like break down
my credibility
and then this and then the information
here will be stolen over time by podcast
doctors or whoever else
so
but you can't break down street cred
millions of people healing around the
world and the most healing stories
around the world never before in our
history
and it's is what it is
so here's how it works let's go into it
a little bit and I got a couple of
things I want to do with you guys I want
to help you clean a book because
it's important because the books get
dirty
when they get shipped to you from Amazon
and I'm going to go into that in a
minute I know we're going off topic
so here's how it works as a white blood
cell gobbles up nanoparticles
whether it's toxic heavy metals air
fresheners fragrances perfumes colognes
pathogens radiation EMF when your white
count is gobbling it up
it's taking a hit for us
it's taking a hit and that hit is like a
stab to the white blood cell it means
the white blood cell won't last long so
that's how it goes the more exposure
exposure doesn't make you stronger I saw
somebody else take that from
and then in it's an influencer doctor
took that fairly recently too
and everybody's like what I never heard
that before
it doesn't make you stronger
exposures don't make you stronger your
immune system instead gets beaten down
and broken down and beaten down and
broken down and then your brain gets
exposed
vulnerable
so it's supposed to your your white
blood cells don't last long depending on
what they're up against as they're
trying to gobble up nanotechnology
the white blood cell ceases to live so
what happens is we walk around and we
get all these exposures in our white
blood cells die
and then new ones have to be created
it's interesting if you go into the
brain saver books you'll see an epic
blood draw chapter
I recommend highly recommend reading
that chapter but first of all I'll take
the book from the beginning and and get
through it because there's a lot to
digest in these books both of them
equally
but the blood draw chapter I talk a lot
about what happens when we get our blood
draw so here we are we're getting sick
from all these exposures check this out
you guys we're getting sick from all
these exposures
so we're getting our fatigue and our
diagnoses and our symptoms and our
neurological problems and our headaches
and our aches and pains and our
dizziness or whatever it is we're
dealing with burning skin trigeminal
neuralgia back pain feet pain whatever's
going on in your life
we're getting sick and then we go to the
doctors and they're drawing tons of
blood and they're taking out our immune
system at the same time the very thing
that's been eating up all these
exposures and eating them up trying to
protect your brain and then we go to the
doctor's office which I recommend the
doctor's office of course why not
she taught you bring the books to your
doctors but then they take all this
Blood Out
because that's not regulated it should
be regulated how much blood they take
out and for good reason they don't need
much to run a blood test and you should
read that in the blood draw chapter
section but then the immune system
lowers even more because we lose our
white blood count
when a white blood cell fights a
pathogen
the pathogen explodes
but the white blood cell eventually runs
out of strength and explodes itself
the white blood cell can explode with it
so check this out so we got the
pathogens inside of us that are white
counties going after the pathogen the
white count will eat the white blood
cell immune cell will eat the pathogen
until the pathogen is gone
and then explode itself
in many situations a white blood cell
dies when it's killing a pathogen whey
blood cells are not as easily replaced
as we think they are
that's for sure
they're precious
they're not easy to replace
the more white blood cells that die
quickly due to exposure the bigger the
gap before newly released ones arrive so
here's another thing the more exposures
we have the faster and more white blood
cells die and the longer duration occurs
between getting the new immune cells
from our bone marrow that duration is
longer and longer and longer and then
we're at the doctor's office because
we're sick I don't feel good I got
fatigued I got ticks and spasms I'm so
disconnect I have I feel disconnected I
have depression you're at the doctor's
office and they're drawing more blood
now and now you already have a gap
of immune cells being produced out of
your bone marrow and then as more
blood's being drawn the Gap widens even
more and we get sicker the brain saver
books are to save people's lives
the most advanced information to protect
people that no one knows or talks about
anywhere no functional doctor no medical
system no industry no doctor anywhere
the health care provider talks about
because they simply don't know this is
the most advanced information out there
I want to cover a couple little fun
things
so you guys spread this information
around about cleaning the books and I
want to talk about this for a second
when people order the books Amazon has
greasy conveyor belts so they have
conveyor belts so when you place your
order somebody working in Amazon takes
the book out of the box that's on the
shelf and they throw it on the conveyor
belt
this is what happens at Amazon and other
stores other other stores online
the conveyor belt has grease because
they're greasing the wheels on the
conveyor belt so they go along the
conveyor belt with a grease gun
Greece petrochemicals right and they
Grease the conveyor belts
they do it every day every week grease
just gets everywhere
the book goes down the conveyor belt
heading down it's getting ready to be
packaged or thrown in a box by another
guy
and then taped up
now it's important to know this because
you'll have grease or some kind of like
Grime on a brand new book now what often
happens is someone will see a little bit
of grease on their book and think they
don't have a brand new book so they'll
give medical medium a one star review
foreign
which is sad because no one gets it
but really it's a brand new book there
are no used medical medium books I mean
the Publishers prints out all these are
all brand new books
so then what you do is you put a tiny
bit of dish soap on a damp towel
and you can wipe your books really clean
and they'll just come out shiny clean I
want everybody to know this and tell
other people because you'll see people
confused once in a while there'll be
some grease on a book or something like
that and they'll be like what is that so
that's one way of doing it and you can
clean your book up real real nice brand
new book the other thing is you don't
see the grease on other books you might
have ordered in the past because medical
medium books are like this clean look to
them
so all the medical medium books have
that white behind everything and they're
really clean so when it goes down the
Amazon
conveyor belt and it gets recently you
don't see grease on all your other
products that come down Amazon's
conveyor belt
so you're gonna see that
you can use a handy wipe right so here's
a handy wipe with alcohol
that's the way I do it too so if I order
a book for a friend or something do like
a handy wipe and clean the cover like
that with the handy wipe
that's another way to get them really
nice and clean
that's great right there so
which is really which is really great
okay so another thing to just run by you
guys if you guys have a minute is the
smell of the books
so what's really incredible about the
medical medium book series
it's stored in a warehouse that has no
plug-in air fresheners
they're stored in a warehouse that has
no perfumes colognes plug-in air
fresheners
pesticides
fungicides
that all the other books are stored at
places
so what's really awesome my publisher
promises me that the warehouse is that
the medical medium books are stored in
after they're printed doesn't have any
of that chemical stuff I want people to
know this if you can tell other people
this is really an incredible thing
like really incredible
when I even think about it so I want
people to know how it works like this is
inside info on what we do to make sure
that your books
don't come saturate it in perfumes
clones scented candles now what happens
is
that my publisher is doing me a favor by
making sure the medical medium books
don't get stored in warehouses that have
all the scented candles
and detergents and other weird stuff and
all that so it's important to know but
here's the problem if you get a book
that seems like there's some smell to it
it's only because of where it went after
it was printed and stored at the
original Warehouse it has no smells and
sense that means that if it went to a
bookstore and the bookstore has a lot of
scented candles in the bookstore too and
you order the book online and the book
gets packaged up you might have a
scented candle smell on a book and then
you just give it time and just let it
air out another thing too is
the same thing with Amazon warehouses I
have no control over Amazon warehouses
and all the scented candle smells and
all the plug-in smells and everything
else same thing with all bookstore
warehouses I have no control over that
so if you do get one book that happens
to have a smell of
something perfume
then just know that over time that will
air out
and it's not the original Source like it
wasn't the medical medium books or the
medical medium books being printed this
is so important to know because some
people might get a book they order from
Amazon at a different Amazon warehouse
that happen to have plug-in air
fresheners or some kind of chemical or
they ordered it from a bookstore line or
walked into a bookstore and the
bookstore has scented candles in one
corner so everybody can have that
experience or whatever or and if there
is a smell know that it comes from way
after the fact from wherever you're
getting the book from but the original
place the book was printed and stored
was chemical free as far as no chemicals
that were in the warehouse floating
around no plugins no perfumes no clones
no anything like this and this was done
on purpose so that the medical medium
book line in the book series
really has the Purity factor to it which
leads me to another thing all on its own
the books
they're of the light you feel it you
know it when you read it you know it
when you hold it
not only are the these brain saver books
the greatest books of all time but you
feel that energy in these books you feel
the life you feel that it's not dead
material and books have dead words
they're just dead words on a page and
then these books they're not dead words
on a page books are living words and you
feel that energy and you know it's there
and when you read the material and
understand it and learn you'll be mind
blown and when you apply the
recommendations in these books you will
feel it
and that doesn't exist anywhere else and
so that's a whole thing on its own
so you guys we talked about the immune
system how the brain relies on the
immune system how important
that is for the brain
and I only just read a couple of
paragraphs that's all it was which is
really when you think about only reading
a couple of paragraphs I mean when I
think about that it blows my mind it
just does
and when I think about just a couple of
paragraphs versus how much which is in
here
um
anyway I have somebody here with me I
have a guest I have a
a world renowned doctor who's
um coming in here so I hope you guys
you know I want you to see both books if
you're interested in both books so I got
a worldwide
famous
surgeon and psychiatrist who wants to
say hi
we weren't friends for a little while we
had a falling out and I was really upset
about it
and he was too
but we had a falling out because of the
alcohol problem he has even though he's
still a great surgeon I recommend his
surgeries to anyone
um
anyway are you gonna say hi to everybody
are you shy
Dr Nesbit says he's kind of shy but he
just wants to
see how everybody is for a second here
I hope no one's canceling their book
orders because of you Dr Nesbit I hope
nobody cancels your order
he says he doesn't care that's not a
nice thing to say
s he's kidding all right that's good he
says he's just joking around so Dr
Nesbitt has been off the alcohol for two
weeks now he's sober he only had one
surgical mistake last week he removed
um he removed
someone's
he was supposed to remove their
gallbladder but he removed their liver
instead and they tried to put the liver
back in the patient and
that's what insurance is for okay
it just didn't work out
patient's alive though
they're just walking around without a
liver
really
anyway so Dr nesbitt's just saying hi to
everybody
um somebody did LMAO do you know what
LMAO stands for
in chicken language what does it stand
for it stands for laughing my
no that's LM LM
f o
LMFAO
what's what's that that's different
where's the F how's the F coming in
there second is but you're pushing over
the book
um what does it mean in chicken
it means kiss my ass and chicken
all right so that person who said
LMAO
um that was insulting to Dr Nesbit
because it means kiss my ass and chicken
um where he comes from
anyway Dr Nesbitt graduated from Harvard
the
University that stole the medical and
poached the medical information about
multiple sclerosis right
yeah even though the doctors
yeah I know I know it was published
Years Ago by medical medium and they
actually pretended they came out with it
recently unbelievable it's a wealthy
University having to do that take
medical memes information how
embarrassing
what else
you like the books he likes the books
you guys he likes the recipes
um he took the ego shot
and he said that after he took the ego
shifter you like the ego shifter
say typically ego shifter and he went
out
scratched his feet in the dirt
says he was a new man
you guys
I am gonna go and I'm gonna take Dr
Nesbitt out to lunch so we're gonna
actually go out to lunch and we're gonna
have a good time we're gonna I'm gonna
talk about the book release he's
probably going to talk about the fact
that he's sober now and we're gonna have
a good time okay
you guys
check out brain saver brain saver
protocols when you get a chance
and
what
you like the immune system talk okay
fantastic okay we're not gonna let We're
Not Gonna torture everybody with Dr
Nesbitt we're gonna let Dr Nesbit go you
guys incredible
so I just want to tell you the brain
saver challenge is still on brain saver
challenge if you guys
check it out when you get a chance so
the brain saver challenge you'll find
the link links in the profile right
brain saver challenge is this is on
today today's day three tomorrow's the
light infusion meditation out of the
brain saver books that's tomorrow just
letting you know
okay
there we go
I hope you are checking out the new
podcast episode released last night so
check out the new podcast episode that
was released last night
so that's really good apple podcast
check it out there okay guys we will be
seeing you I will try to do another live
I might even be able to do one later on
tonight so look out keep your
notifications on if that even matters
and I will talk to you guys later bless
you guys truly