facebook live on youtube live on tick
tock live on clubhouse
our vice is in your way i'm just
wondering you guys we're going to talk
about how to heal eczema psoriasis as
well so we're talking about how to heal
health problems skin conditions like
acne
rosacea we'll go into that a little bit
too trigeminal neuralgia might cover
that a little bit some
aches and pains chronic fatigue and
we're going to talk about how celery
juice helps heal those very things
because i haven't done that in a while
where i talk about how celery just
actually
reverses your acne your eczema your
psoriasis your skin problems
your sun spots your your sunspots right
your liver spots how it actually heals
this is really important information
so we're going to talk about that as
well also just a reminder
this is still on sale for another couple
of days before the sale is off and
people are totally psyched because
they're saving
82 on the mm 900 hds that's the one you
want though i'll show you about that
later
good to see you guys come on chris good
to see you come on everybody's coming on
here patrice
good to see you we're live on clubhouse
facebook youtube tick tock
i'm excited to be on right now our vice
is in the way where
you get ostracized you get
picked on you get yelled at if you want
to try to
break a vice because it makes everybody
else feel uncomfortable
so if you try to break a vice of some
kind like you're hanging out with
somebody you're hanging out with family
you're hanging out with friends
and you don't want that cheeseburger so
you're just
weird right so you're just weird that
ever happened to you the roots report
good to see you
did that ever happen to you in your life
you guys where you're the weird one
and you're you're the one made to feel
uncomfortable lucy cohen good to see you
so you're the one made to feel
uncomfortable right
and and so we're not allowed to break
our vices did you ever
ever see that we're not allowed to break
our vices
so breaking our vices is kind of like
off limits
if you start breaking your vices
whatever those vices are caffeine
coffee cheese right
cheese milk butter whatever those vices
might be
pizza something that you guys you know
you guys like so maybe some pizza i got
a pizza right here and
whatever that vice is you have to
you have to stay in line and we get
punished if we break that line if we
come out of that line right
get punished by people around us loved
ones
friends people we know and
you're just that weirdo you're that
weirdo you're worried about your health
or you're that you're that weirdo that
has health issues
and that's kind of what happens out
there and what what's going on with
people so much is that they're up
against that so it's hard
to break your vices even if you're
breaking coffee even if you
you want to break your vice you still go
up against this
michael says 11 days no coffee feeling
better than ever
incredible teresa i bought the mm-900
and love it i think my celery juice
tastes better it tastes better for me
that's what i've noticed when you have a
cold pressed juicer especially one like
this that squeezes all the juice out of
it
because it's really it's taking all that
flavor out it's like
removing that flavor the way it should
be out of that fiber and pulp and giving
you that straight herbal extract
extraction so you know vices have been
difficult for so many people
not because they're hard to break
even though that's one aspect of it
right you guys on tick tock
it's it's hard enough to break it break
a vice
right that's hard enough i get it but
it's not the whole
show it's not the whole issue
it's not the whole problem it
it's more than that it's the people
around us and i'm not
saying we should be upset about the
people around us that's not it at all
it's just that we're made to feel like
we're in the wrong doing if we're trying
not to have that donut
if we're trying not to have that you
know because
in the thing is is they got the upper
hand like
our friends our family our loved ones or
people
in at work or whatever it is right
co-workers
they got the upper edge if they're
eating all the bad stuff
or all the vice stuff they got the upper
edge
because they know like we got that
little voice inside of us that's saying
you know what i'll just do this donut
one more time
i haven't had a donut in a while let me
just do this cookie let me do this
chocolate chip cookie one more time
let me do this donut one more time and
i'll start to i'll fix it after that i
won't do any more after that todd says
what about a little
mushroom coffee um well the mushroom
thing is fine
the mushroom that's okay but
you know what what i don't like is they
take an addictive substance
and then they try to make you feel good
about that addictive substance
by adding something good for you like a
rishi mushroom or
chaga mushroom or some kind of mushroom
to the coffee
so if you like being totally jaked over
tricked then yeah have your mushroom
coffee
if you like being suckered if you want
to if you want to be a sucker
drink your mushroom coffee if you want
to be a sucker because
the industry put the mushroom coffee
together
so that you that you would stay on your
coffee buy more coffee
feel good about your coffee you think
your coffee is good for you
and when you can do your reese's
mushroom
away from coffee so you can do your
rishi mushroom
away from it yeah i know you guys like
we just got froze out
so so what people don't get is
is here we go again it's like okay let's
make your vice
more nutritious is that what that
technique is right there so that's a
different technique so mushroom coffee
is like let's make your vice
more nutritious so that you never break
your vice
so you never break your vice instead of
let's
spare you a lifetime of adrenal burnout
let's spare you a lifetime of addiction
let's get you off of that coffee
let's get you off of that caffeine let's
not sucker you
let's not total what's not snake oil
salesman
sucker dupe you pull the wool over your
eyes
and just mix coffee with mutt
mushrooms and then mlm and pyramid it
you know and that's what they do too i
mean they're all like
they got thousands and thousands of ads
going out there
they got millions of dollars in the ads
to push that mushroom coffee on you guys
and there's so much in there you guys
don't even know it's such a scam it's a
scam to get you guys scammed if you like
being scammed
great right you know and you do the
mushroom coffee
but you have to know that yeah you guys
we're just getting cut out
totally getting cut out right now so um
we're talking about lots of stuff here
we're talking about how to heal eczema
psoriasis we're talking about
how to heal rosacea we're talking about
how to heal different health conditions
all this is important using celery juice
right and then we're talking about vices
how we get trapped in these vices
because the people
the people around us god bless them the
people around us
have the upper hand because if they're
eating those donuts
and they're eating that sushi yeah
sushi's a junk food if they're eating
those burgers if they're eating the
cheese and the milk
and the bread and the pizza and they're
having the pizza they got the upper hand
they do they got the upper hand
it's important to know and that
upper hand is really difficult
on so many it really is it is
so i know i disappeared on you guys a
little bit so it's just talking about
how
the people around us that keep us on our
vices
have that edge and they have that upper
hand
and that's the hard part one of the hard
parts right there
you're going to see family you're going
to see friends you're not going to want
to turn down the donut you're not going
to want to turn down the bagel you're
not going to want to turn down the
burger or the pizza
certainly not the pizza right not going
to want to turn down the cookies
even if they're gluten-free cookies so
we're stuck
we're stuck in the vice you know and we
need family and friend many people say i
need my family and friends some people
say well
i live life alone i don't need i don't
need
you know family around me some people
i've heard this from different people
all through my life
where but you eventually run into
somebody
or someone and even if it's somebody you
haven't talked to
in so long michelle l good to see you
like sabotage
and yeah so the sabotage occurs
and we get tangled up in it we get
caught in that sabotage
that's exactly it i think that
if you're going to break a vice you have
to be aware of this stuff
you do okay no one's a bad person for
eating burgers and
for eating hot dogs and eating chicken
fingers and eating pizza
no one's a bad person for gobbling down
vegan cookies by the truckload
gobbling down all those vegan cookies
and chocolate chip cookies gluten-free
cookies
and cakes and doughnuts no one's a bad
person for eating the milk cheese and
the butter
it's not about that it's not about if
you're good or you're bad
it's not about that at all but we're
made to feel
bad we're made to feel bad
by the people around us a lot of times
if we want
to change the way we're doing things
and one of the reasons why we change the
way of doing things i mean you guys know
this you start getting sick
you start getting some symptoms in your
life lunell good to see you
and you start getting to a place in your
life where you're sick you've got
symptoms you're seeing doctors you're
seeing people and it's like whoa i gotta
get off the processed foods i gotta get
off the
fried greasy foods i have to get off of
this stuff
and we get into a place where
it's hard to do that with the people
around us and so it takes a willpower
takes a will power because we're going
to feel like we're a bad person
we better eat that donut we better have
that slice of pizza
but they got the upper hand our friends
their family
our loved ones that that are not
really that supportive of changing our
foods they got the upper hand
because man that upper hand is pretty
intense it's like
well i'm just eating a grilled cheese
sandwich right now and
how come you're not gonna have the
grilled cheese sandwich with me you know
i'm just having the french toast and the
waffles
with all the butter on it i'm just
having the cheese right now
and you know i'm just having some sushi
i know a lot of people think sushi's
really healthy
that's that always cracks me up it's
always cracked me up all the time
it's like oh i want to get i want to get
sushi i eat sushi a few times a week
and i notice something and i see it also
out there like i have friends tell me
that they
watch a youtube or they watch you know
they watch people out there and watch
people's videos it's like they're out
getting sushi
and everybody's so proud of themselves
with sushi
they're like so proud of themselves with
sushi
sushi is loaded with the bad sugar
it's it's loaded with vinegar and
on top of that if it's the tuna you got
the mercury so you just had your vinegar
mercury delight you just had your
fermented
vinegar you know which destroys your
bones and teeth
you just had your mercury which will
bring you to alzheimer's and dementia
faster in your life
so i love when everybody thinks they're
so happy about the sushi like oh i had
sushi that covers it
i went out with my friends and i had
sushi no i ate healthy that night are
you kidding me
and that's another thing out there
you'll see out there it's like sushi
is supposed to be healthy you guys mm
900 hds
is this is the mega juicer at
megajuicers.com
omega right this is the juicer right
here the mm 900
hds um on sale 82
off which is incredible omega
juicers.com 25
off but that sale is coming to an end
pretty soon so i want to let you guys
know
so in just in case um and you guys know
i'm working with omega
you guys know that right working with
omega because
this is a medical device in my opinion
it's a medical device
juicers are medical devices so they're
extractors
for medicine did you know that when
big pharma did you guys know this a big
pharma make all their drugs
when they make all their drugs out there
right
did you know that they're doing
extractions that's what they do
they're synthesizing but they're also
extracting they're synthesizing they're
extracting
they're they have machines
in big pharma that are like juicers
so and they have these machines in big
pharma that are like juicers they're
medical style juicers they're geared for
they're small too they're like small
machines they have them in their drug
factories
and they're there to extract and
and with the alchemy that they work with
so
what people what no one gives credits to
juicers like this that's a medical
device a medical tool but it's
downplayed
that's always downplayed out there when
it's the one of the most important
critical devices in your life
you don't have a juicer i recommend
someday getting a juicer
if you don't get the mm 900 hds even
though it's on sale right now then and
you get another juicer
fine i want you to be able to juice
that's the number one goal
so it doesn't matter to me in the end
like what juicer you have this one just
saves me money
i talk about that all the time people
are getting their juicers who have order
health with liz good to see you on tick
tock
good to see you too good to see you too
so what about ice cream
once per week um anthony
um strike seven seven good question i
got a friend calling in
i've got a friend calling in too and
we'll you know that's actually
gonna talk about that as well so
you guys when it comes down to this
herbal extractors what you're looking at
right now
it's extracting medicine that's why i
call it a medical tool a medical device
because it extracts medicine
hey how you been good good i'm about to
have
i'm about to have a hot dog
yeah i'm not over doing it
just once every couple of weeks i have a
hot dog
yeah it's moderation i talk about the
moderation thing all the time right
because that's what my doctor keeps on
telling me i can have what i want in
moderation
so i just leave it to a hot dog once
every couple weeks
i had one five days ago well i did okay
that's okay i'm having one five days ago
and having one now
so that's not like two every two weeks
but this is a different month and i just
i just feel like i needed that
yeah i'll just wait a little longer and
then
i'll wait it out and try to have my hot
dog a week for and a half from now
think i can do it well
the other
i've been having this chocolate fudge
ice cream
i'm doing two i'm doing this chocolate
fudge ice cream every two weeks
yeah what what's wrong with that
so if i'm doing the hot dog every two
weeks i'm doing chocolate fudge
ice cream every two weeks did i have
pizza yeah i had pizza
i have a pizza ready for
my friends are coming over later we're
going to have some pizza but i haven't
had a pizza in two weeks
my doctor said moderation works it's it
works so what i'm doing is i'm
practicing moderation
i'm having a pizza every two weeks a
chocolate fudge sundae every week and
i'm having a hot dog
every two weeks so i'm doing the
moderation thing really well
yeah i had a little cheese the other day
and i had some bread so that's like a
pizza
um yeah i gotta eat my chocolate fudge
sundae
moderation is yeah i could
look i know i'm lactose intolerant is
that even real
lactose intolerance i know i'm i'm
i shouldn't be having dairy i know
but but i'm having it once a week right
now
okay all right i gotta go
but vices are ridiculously hard to break
because of
people around us that's one reason why
they're really hard to break
it's not because anybody's bad it's not
because there's bad people around us
there's not because of any of those
reasons
it's because of the reason of it's they
got the upper hand
i mean you're starving you're hungry
it's like hey look i'm just
bringing home a pizza um no you stick to
your plant-based diet
um no you stick to your no you stick to
whatever it is your
your dairy-free diet and but we're gonna
have everybody in the family is gonna
have a pizza
so let's put the pizza on the counter
everybody dig in
let's grab it oh you can't have it yeah
why not
just have a slice don't worry just have
a slice what do you mean you can't have
pizza tonight
have a slice of pizza tonight one slice
is not gonna hurt
it's not gonna hurt um
so we run into we run into this all the
time
we run into the solar panels reading
comments as they come up
death by a thousand cuts is what it ends
up being so we're up against the death
by a thousand cuts
so we get a job here we get a job there
we get a job here we get a job there
what are you guys doing to go against
those cuts what are we doing
dairy products feeds the pathogens that
are inside of us
so milk cheese butter will feed all the
bugs inside of us
eggs will feed the bugs inside of us
so all these little bugs inside of us
they'll get fed by
milk cheese and butter so you got your
stick of butter right here
viruses love butter they do
and it takes weeks to get the dairy out
so the question by the way that was a
really good question
about should i have some ice cream once
a week is that okay
or i eat ice cream once a week is that
okay
strike seven seven thanks anthony very
much thank you for being on here
so that's a really good question but it
takes more than a week to get the dairy
out of you
so it'll take 10 14 days
sometimes longer depends on how like
stagnant and sluggish your liver is
so getting that cheese out of you or
that
ice cream out of you that milk out of
you
getting that out any kind of dairy
product doesn't just
it doesn't get out in two days like i'm
gonna go to bathroom and it's all gonna
be cleaned out it just doesn't it sits
on the sides of your intestinal tract
for days and days and days
over a week it's there feeding all the
different bugs
all the different pathogens so if you've
got eczema psoriasis
if you've got rosacea if you have acne
if you have vitiligo
if you have any condition at all any
condition it doesn't matter what it is
whether you got
chronic fatigue syndrome or hashimoto's
thyroiditis you really don't get a good
chance to heal
because you got a dairy product in you
and the dairy product in you is sitting
there and it's feeding all the different
bugs
and it's feeding them every single day
and it takes days and days to get it out
lynette says what about organic raw
cheese that's the only dairy i give my
kids
look i look at it this way i look at it
this way
are the kids perfectly fine do they have
any symptoms
i get asked this by doctors all the time
too and
are the kids dealing with any kind of
condition any kind of symptom
so that's one thing right there so
that's just we can we put that into
consideration
because it doesn't matter if your dairy
is raw or your dairy is cooked your
dairy is pasteurized
it doesn't matter if your dairy has been
heated up in the oven doesn't matter if
your dairy is just
raw dairy it's still gonna feed
any bugs or pathogens so if kids have
rashes skin conditions
eczema psoriasis whether they got some
adhd
or they got some brain fog because kids
have brain fog
we don't call it brain fog with kids we
don't call it
we'll call it like attention you know
drifting off
and you know behavioral issues or
something and
we'll call it that and so it all depends
on what kind of symptoms are your
children
exhibiting what about their teeth that's
another one too so
are your children's teeth
or your children's teeth are they having
problems are the new teeth growing in
are the baby teeth problematic were the
baby teeth
rotting where the baby teeth getting
cavities
where the baby teeth being pulled had to
be pulled
what's going on with the baby teeth and
then the
new teeth coming in what's happening
with those teeth so that's a big one
right there
so if you have you have a child that
has teeth problems or a baby that has
teeth problems where the teeth are
coming in and we've got all these teeth
issues
then raw cheese isn't going to be a good
one because
that's how we lose our calcium too so we
lose our bones that way
so we'll talk about this right it's
actually a good segue into this here
so when mommy's really really acidic and
she's eating dairy and she's eating
cheese
she's losing all of her calcium that's
the calcium
the baby uses so the baby
get the baby's calcium comes from mom
having spare calcium spear calcium like
calcium that's derived from
fruits vegetables anything else that she
eats wild foods if she ever eats that
any kind of herbs if she ever takes any
kind of herbs
throughout her life right so that
calcium disappears
if everybody's acidic if mom's really
acidic
margaret says my little one was born
with rotting teeth
she had to get four cavities at one
years old
four caps at one years old four caps
so dr fine good to see you there
basically what happens is that pregnant
women are told to eat all the wrong
stuff
and that happens every day and then the
baby's teeth are gonna be problematic
because of that
so pregnant moms are told to eat dairy
and look there's a lot of pregnant
pregnant moms out there
they got their farms and they got their
instagram page and youtube page
and they live partially off the land and
they have their own milk
and they have their own butter they make
their own butter
and they're pregnant and they're giving
it to their children and they're eating
it and
they may have had good calcium storage
bins in them
starting from their childhood from their
mom they may have good calcium storage
bins maybe they don't have a lot of
toxic heavy metals in their system
because that takes away our calcium too
it interferes
but all that cheese and that milk and
that dairy regardless of it being
not like all natural where it's on a
farm it's raw versus pasteurized either
way
it's going to require that you lose all
that calcium inside
your bones you lose that inside your
bloodstream
over time and so when you're pregnant
what happens to a lot of babies
so when mom's pregnant she's eating all
that dairy or ate all that dairy before
her pregnancy
and there's a real serious acidic
environment going on
and then the calcium is not available
for the baby
so teeth suffer when calcium's not
available teeth suffer
so in infants that's where we we end up
with the teeth problems
we end up going into that direction
right there
so let's go let's keep on talking about
some other stuff
so when we're doing our foods when we
when we're doing our foods
like our donuts our cakes or cookies our
cheese
our milk our butter
we're creating this acid environment
from all of it
and that's not the only place we have
the acid environment we have it from
other places too animal approach people
who eat animal
protein i always tell them that they
need to balance it
where's your leafy greens because if you
just do your animal protein
you're doing your animal protein and you
only do a little bit of broccoli you
only do some green beans you only do a
little lettuce here and there
you only do some cauliflower rice here
and there but you're doing your animal
proteins
you're gonna get yourself in trouble
eventually because
you need to be buffering that with
something else the leafy greens are
critical
so the leafy greens are so important
right there
and what people don't realize is that
not enough people not not
people are not eating enough leafy
greens they're not balancing that acid
environment
and then there's all the fats so then we
got all that fat in the diet so that's a
whole other problem all on its own
so whether you're plant-based and you're
vegan
everybody's tanking the fats right i
always say you guys are fatting
themselves to death they're fatting
themselves to death
and as they're doing that that's a whole
other problem all on its own because
that's
acidic so you can be like hey i'm vegan
i'm plant-based i don't do the dairy
products i'm in the pocket right here
aw is going to let me off the hook i'm
totally cool
let's let the back to the landers be
eating they're churning their own butter
and
drinking their raw milk let other people
be eating their
store-bought cheese and stop
store-bought dairy that's been
pasteurized
i'm off the hook i'm vegan i'm off the
hook i'm plant-based
i don't have any problem at all that's
not true if you're taking the almond
butter the peanut butter
if you're eating too many walnuts eating
too many seeds pumpkin seeds sunflower
seeds every single day
if you're having too much oil and that
oil gets away from us all the time
if you're eating too many avocados if
you're doing all of this
all of that is acid it's all acid
fatty acids essential
fatty acids you're doing all your olive
oil
olive oil is acidic as heck really
really acidic
and it's acidic inside the body really
important to know
that people don't realize that they're
like wait a minute that's not acid
that's not acid
so we get this acidic environment when
we're tanking the fats
so what we do is we grow up we're
usually eating all the milk cheese
butter we're doing all the comfort foods
we're doing all the vice
foods we were talking about vices
earlier
we're doing all these comfort foods and
then
even when we go healthy or we're eating
healthier
we're still doing all the fat which is
acidic so we're basically living in this
acidic environment our urine stinks when
it shouldn't stink
because that's a whole other thing is
people's pee isn't supposed to smell
rancid
and awful like people's pee is not
supposed to smell
urine is actually not supposed to have
such an intense smell at all
but that urine is all acids so it's
everybody just
peeing that acid out urine is not
supposed to be yellow
you know it's not supposed to be yellow
and it's not supposed to smell
just so you guys know it's supposed to
be a light faint smell
and it's not supposed to be yellow all
that is
acids pouring out of us our minerals in
our body pouring out of us
that's what that is and
if you start eating really healthy
you're doing like the morning cleanse
you're taking care of yourself you're
juicing your celery juice and you still
have stinky pee
and it's really yellow now you're
cleansing out old stuff
you're cleansing out old stuff that was
built inside of you for years
what helps the acidic body what helps to
heal that
well i'm not going to say fruits and
vegetables because that's not going to
do it
it's not enough you need powerful herbal
extractions
like the celery juice so whether you get
a juicer down the road whether you get
some other juicer down the road whether
you have a juicer
and you're using it whatever that one is
that is a powerful
medical tool and that's one way
of reclaiming your health back and
balancing that
stopping the assets from injuring
and taking from you like neutralizing
those assets
neutralizing those acids people who got
eczema psoriasis skin problems health
conditions you're really really acidic
asparagus produces a smell sandra
yeah because it's got a chemical
compound that does that
so asparagus has a chemical compound
inside
of it that is creating that smell
so that's what asparagus is it's not
it's not causing it's not that doesn't
mean you're acidic but asparagus is
really cleansing it's very cleansing
if you're eating enough of it you're
going to be cleansing your system
cleansing your system we have so much
stuff built inside our liver spilled
inside of us we have so much
junk and garbage we have acid stored in
places we have salt deposits
that shouldn't be inside our body stored
in places
we have deposits of pesticides
herbicides fungicides toxic heavy metals
solvents household cleaners we have
fragrances
inside of us fragrances inside of us
i recently talked to a surgeon who has a
really good sense of smell incredible
sense of smell doesn't use fragrances
never uses fragrances and even
opted in in or to change the chemicals
that they use to a chemical that didn't
smell as much
in the or so and this surgeon
told me that because the the surgeon
doesn't use the fabric softeners
doesn't use all the different fragrances
doesn't use the chemicals doesn't use
chemical cleaners
conventional cleaners doesn't use
cologne or perfume no air fresheners
doesn't burn scented candles
this surgeon said that the smell of
patients
when they're saturated in scented
candles
on their skin from their house when
they're saturated with air fresheners
from their house when they're saturated
with all this the smell of it when
the surgeon cuts the patient open the
smell
it's the first time i've had a surgeon
ever tell me that and confirm
what spirit of compassion's information
is that that
you can actually smell the inside of
their body and smell the air fresheners
and smell the scented candles from the
inside of the body
and so the surgeon said that because he
removed
everything everything in his life
whereas house doesn't smell like any
chemical cleaners
his nose got really really sharp super
super sharp you guys
so sharp every time he cuts open a
patient
he just doesn't smell all the toxins
inside the body which is what
which has got that real gas that ammonia
comes out of people when you cut people
open
on the table right for surgery
ammonia just comes right out of them all
that rotting petrified flat
uh flesh that they've eaten that's in
their guts
all the acids that are in their blood
all the fat that's in their blood that
went rancid because it's floating around
their blood every day because they're
eating nothing but fats every single day
when you cut open a patient the stink
comes out of them
it's it's it's awful right well the
surgeon now
can smell it's not just that stink but
the air fresheners come out of people
so the air freshener coming out the
scented candles coming out
and that's what the surgeon can smell
so it's really incredible when you think
about it so when people are doing all
this scented candles that's inside their
bloodstream that's inside their liver
that's circulating inside of them we're
doing the air fresheners every single
day i tell people pull those air
fresheners out
people should be complaining to every
single clothing company
that sends anything that reeks but the
problem is people don't even smell
the new clothes reeking with air
fresheners and the factories and the
warehouses
with all that smell the chemicals on the
clothes people don't complain because
they can't smell it because they already
have it inside their house
everything stinks inside their house
it's all the chemical cleaners
conventional cleaners
detergents fabric softeners
so m tribe says
but how are people living off the
typical american diet
it seems like nothing is wrong well look
there are people on the typical american
diet right but they end up sick
they just end up sick later no one gets
sick
everybody gets sick with something i
talk to people that are on the typical
american diet sav and they've had
surgeries but yeah they're fine
afterwards
they you know they've had their
gallbladder taken out now they're back
in action
they've had panics removed now they're
back back in action
they've had some other type of surgery
now they're back in action
or they get sick later with chronic
illness they end up
feeding their pathogens they end up
picking up a new pathogen they end up
picking up a new epstein bar
or or a shingles um
ore or strep or something they pick
something up
and it finally tips the scale or
whatever's been incubating inside of
them they're fc bar for 20 30 years if
they don't have an aggressive one
finally it takes over or the stress plus
the eff the fight or flight the caffeine
finally takes over
all the vinegar they've done all these
years starts to break apart their teeth
now they're in the dentist chair all the
time getting dental work it hits all at
once so many times like that with
but the think about people like hey
those people can eat what they want
they eventually get sick and go down
they eventually do
and we're in a place where that's
happening more than ever somebody says
do celery do you support
autoimmune diseases it supports it in
the right direction
it doesn't support the auto autoimmune
disease to stay there
so so what you'll see out there is all
these things out there support
autoimmune that's what they do apple
cider vinegar supports autoimmune
in keeping it there forever vinegar
supports it
caffeine supports caffeine supports your
autoimmune disease
in the opposite direction making it
worse or keeping it there forever
it doesn't support it getting you out of
autoimmune disease
caffeine doesn't pull you out of
the vices don't pull you out of
autoimmune we keep our autoimmune you
have sushi you keep your autoimmune
you have some donuts you have
gluten-free donuts you keep your
autoimmune you have vegan donuts you
keep your autoimmune
you keep it there you have your burgers
you have
you can be in a vegan restaurant and
still have one of those bean burgers or
something like that but the amount of
crap that's in there and the amount of
fat
that's in there and the msg that's
hidden in there and the canola oil and
anything else
you're still keeping your autoimmune
and so we end up keeping that autoimmune
around forever
celery juice helps take us out of that
it helps to take you out of autoimmune
eczema psoriasis that's an autoimmune
condition or listed as an autoimmune
condition
and celery juice pushes people out of
that
helps to get rid of their eczema if you
want to get rid of eczema like really
get rid of it
if you want to get rid of psoriasis
rosacea if you want to get rid of
vitiligo if you want to get rid of acne
you have to be doing celery juice you
have to learn how to do the herbal
extraction
and if you don't learn to do it now fine
you learn to do it down the road do it
down the road do it five years from now
five years from now heavy metal detox
smoothie that's a critical one right
there too i talk about that you guys
i talk about the barley grassies powder
and the spirulina that's the vimergy
i'm not sponsored by these guys this is
just the best company with all the stuff
that they have
spirulina barley grass so you guys know
vemma gv is in victor i
m e rgy.com but
incredible products the products i use
for my friends and family too
kelsey bach good to see you here kelsey
bach healed
like dozens of symptoms dozens of
symptoms
i know what kelsey is it like 43
is it 50 symptoms what was it like i
think it was 43 symptoms right
tick tock good to see you and i don't
mean the app i don't mean tick tock app
i mean
the handle tick tock uh
i think kelsey healed like 43 symptoms
she does celery juice she does a lot of
medical medium tools
so good to see you here educating myself
good to see you too
i'm going to juice some celery now you
guys so
it's important to know these things
about getting out of that acid
environment we can talk a good game we
can talk about assets and alkaline but
if we don't know really anything about
it how can we do that so if you
if you're hearing information from
so-called health experts that know about
alkalinity
and acidity body being acidic and
they're telling you to have all your
avocados
they're telling you to have you know all
your your healthy fats you're telling
you can have your peanut
butter they're telling you all these
things your olive oil
and they're pushing it they're telling
you can have your lean proteins
that it's not that you can't have any of
that but if you're sick and you're
struggling with a symptom or you got
eczema you got psoriasis
you have something that you want to get
rid of you have to bring down the fats
because
the fats are acidic it's all acid
that's what the fats are it's fatty
acids
that's what the fats are it's all acidic
so we have to learn how to bring down
those fats
but first things first what kind of
vices do you have that's not
fats like do you have fats plus
other stuff like are you doing the
cheeseburgers are you doing the pizzas a
lot are you doing all the eggs fried
eggs
are you doing the toast all the time are
you doing the bagels doing the hot dogs
you're doing the butter
is butter going on in your diet so these
vices
you have to learn to take them out and
you're not a bad person if you keep them
in
you got my support 100 i'm here giving
you guys support
and i've been doing it for 35 years
i remember doing lectures in health food
stores 35 years ago
and and being there for people and
supporting their to get them off their
vices
old friend reached out that used to be
somebody who used to come to me for help
30 years ago reached out and said
they're still doing
still doing all the good stuff and
they're in their 80s now
they're in their 80s pinas says celery
healed
eye rash the red burning itchy peeling
and it's gone
start at the third day of juicing celery
is that incredible
that's absolutely incredible really
really is
and i'm so proud of you by the way so
proud of you just moving some stuff over
you guys
let's juice a little celery now
we're coming to the end of the sale with
the mm-900 just letting you guys know
best protocol for chronic yeast
infections
this is one part of it right here what
is a chronic yeast infection
what is it is it yeast right
no it's not it's not just yeast
yeast is just present with a chronic
yeast infection
it's just present
[Applause]
a yeast infection is streptococcus
it's strep bacteria behind everything
and that's why the yeast infection stays
chronic
because there's a bacterial infection
behind there
and the reason why people get rid of
their yeast bacterial infections
with celery juice is because celery
juice kills the
streptococcus bacteria behind the yeast
that's why so it kills the strep
bacteria behind the yeast
important to know
celery juice is no joke it's an herbal
medicine so you're witnessing an herbal
medicine
eating celery sticks is not enough
it's not enough you guys and if you're
somebody who's
on your vices still you're doing your
caffeine you're doing your chocolate
you're doing your coffee
you can't stop your chocolate you're
still doing
it you have your chocolate bars pieces
of chocolate every day
you better be countering those death by
a thousand cuts
you know when you count the squares
right here it's one two three and then
one two three four
five six so you got three across
you need four across 24 squares
that's 24 cuts 24 cuts
what are you doing to counter it what
herbal medicine are you guys doing
probably gonna say oh no i take my herbs
by a great a great healer
look into those herbs look into them
what fillers are there is there alcohol
in your tinctures
that's what i love about the vimergy
stuff there's no
alcohol but it's even better than that
there's no junk no fillers hidden in
there
no msg hidden in there and so that's the
vimergy licorice root right there
that's the dimmer to cat's claw so
what tools are you guys using to counter
counter the the cuts to counter the acid
look i don't i don't expect anybody to
do at all
unless they get there and they just
they're so tired of being sick and they
need to go further because they're
really sick
i just basically i'm just in that
place of what are you doing what can we
do
you know how many people say they're on
the mm diet you know how many people say
they're on the medical medium diet
or medical median protocol but they're
doing chocolate caffeine
they're doing matcha tea they're doing
lots of fat which is acid straight acid
even if they're vegan i noticed people
throughout the years
they've gone vegan not because of
medical medium necessarily
because they're following some vegan
doctors but then they turn around and
they don't say
hey i'm doing the vegan doctor the the
vegan doctor author's diet they say
i'm doing the medical medium diet it's
not working
they're not even doing the medical
medium diet they're not doing medical
medium anything
i see that all the time all the time
how many natural flavors are people
consuming what kind of natural flavors
that's all msg
what about the nutritional yeast what
about that
nutritional yeast and then the vinegars
how many vinegars are you using if you
have sushi if you have vegan sushi it's
vinegar
i can't tell you how many people
go with their friends to get sushi and
they get the fish free
sushi meaning no tuna and it's
loaded with vinegar and they think
they think that they're all good and
it's loaded with vinegar
then they'll just say they're still
doing the mm they're doing the mm
protocol
and they're not getting better so people
will do that all the time
and they're not even on the right
supplements it's like yeah i took a zinc
well not really if you're taking a zinc
with all the citric acid in it and all
the other crap
in there and all the fillers if you're
not doing like the vimergy zinc or one
comparable which i haven't found one
comparable but you can use whatever your
doctor tells you you know do what your
doctor says
narasini good to see you but all these
things matter so how many mm tools and
where are we going with the tools like
are we really using the mm tools
the juicer is a critical medical medium
tool
and if you have your own juicer it's
different than this use it that's
a medical medium tool if you're using
some other juicer out there it's a
medical medium toll
because if you need to use it as an
herbal extractor
and you need to extract that herbal
medicine
i just juiced all the celery juice right
and that's that's all the pulp you guys
right there
that's it on tick tock check this guys
check this out you guys
it's in between two fingers look and
it's dry
it's dry that's the pulp if i squeeze it
into a little ball
this is incredible right here this is
the most i've ever seen it get to this
point
that's it right there it's a little ball
in my
fingers you guys see that
this is dry and that's a ball between my
fingers i'm actually kind of blown away
like i don't know how this even happened
to this degree this is the best i've
ever seen
my juicer ever do and it always does
great
uh i'm holding between my two fingers
this tiny little ball of dried pulp
and that is what i'm talking about right
there about the mm-900 hds
it's 82 off it's almost 100 off and i
hear people out there saying oh my god
thank god i got it because i
saved about basically 100 bucks and um
and i got the mm-900 but it's the omega
juicers.com you got to go there you guys
omega juicers.com omega
juicers.com gotta get the mm-900 hds
because it's not any
their their other juicers aren't going
to do this they got juicers that look
like this it's got to be the mm-900 hds
it's not going to do
what i'm doing this i can't even put
this down because i don't even
understand how this happened
like that's the next level is what this
is
so i'm holding a tiny ball of dried pulp
in between my fingers
and that's how much juice i have right
here
i'm actually saving that right there
be calling up my friends afterwards
i mean it's always small and it's always
dry but that was
a whole other level so i'm doing a
little straining right here straining
the juice
you have to strain your celery juice
it's not going to work as good
you have to strain it it's
critical that you strain it it's giving
everybody the 4-1-1 on that
it's critical that you strain the juice
so what medical tools are you guys
using which medical devices are you
using
and people say well medical tools i got
some crutches
in the closet i got you know something
else and i'm like okay
a friend of mine's grandmother has a
walker
and i'm like i'm not talking about that
medical that kind of medical tool
you need the walker yes but what about
something that's going to help so
grandma can start walking again without
the walker
like we need to go into that direction
like where's the medical tool
in ecmo psoriasis i'll go into that a
little bit celery juice
is incredible because of what it does
when someone has extra psoriasis
so i just want to grab something real
quick
so when it comes down to when it comes
down to someone getting
eczema someone getting psoriasis
so here's your liver right here
that's your liver a right liver
i should have wrote it back or actually
you can see it so that's your liver
if you got eczema you got psoriasis you
got some kind of skin condition
you even have acne there's bugs inside
the liver
when it comes down to eczema and
psoriasis you got
epstein-barr inside the liver rosacea
too i've seen bar inside the liver
when you have acne you've got
streptococcus inside the liver
your liver is a little bug holder it's
the bug holder
that's what your liver is it holds the
bugs
and those bugs start to feed off of
stuff
they feed off of toxic heavy metals so
they feed off of those toxic heavy
metals you're in medical medium school
right now
so you got the toxic heavy metals inside
the liver and all those bugs feed off of
that
someone has eczema psoriasis the epstein
bar feeds off of
copper so that's what the epstein bar
feeds off of
so if you have epsilon bar inside the
liver it's going to feed off of copper
and then release a dermatoxin and that
dermatoxin is released
so we'll do a little dermatoxin coming
out of here that's a dermatoxin swimming
out of the liver
it's heading up the highway it's getting
into the bloodstream
it's a derma dermatoxin right
that's your dermatoxin that dermatoxin
eventually finds its way to the skin
and you end up with eczema or celery
juice the reason why
it's reversing tens of thousands of
people's eczema for the good
like for good re reversing eczema
psoriasis
for good forever it's because the celery
juice
is killing off the epstein bar inside
the liver
sodium cluster salts kill so the sodium
remember i told you about the sodium
cluster salts you got the macro
sodium right the macro sodium inside the
celery
then you've got the subgroup sodium
which is a little solar system
that's your sodium cluster salts that's
going around the sodium
that's your medicine so when you do your
herbal extraction you guys
with your juicer even if it's not as
good as this juicer
it's not it's a crappy juicer bad juicer
you're still doing a herbal extraction
to some degree for sure
when you do your herbal extraction
you're taking
that sodium cluster salt you're drinking
it
that's your herbal medicine so you're
actually drinking consuming your herbal
medicine
and then that sodium cluster salt
when that touches when it goes inside
the liver
cause here it goes goes inside the liver
i don't know if this is actually working
out but i think it is
so the sodium cluster salt right there
goes inside the liver
right there goes inside the number it
kills off the epstein bar
so that no more dermatoxins come out
of the liver no more dermatoxins come
out
so then your skin starts to heal your
skin starts to heal your skin starts to
heal
some people have eczema syriza so bad
and they have a stubborn epstein bar
that they need to be doing some other
things like i talked about in the
medical medium books
and the new edition medical medium new
edition revised and expanded it's on
sale
amazon.com you might want to catch a
copy of that
it's a critical book to have and the
other one too cleanse the heel is a
critical book to have
as well so if you guys don't have it you
might want to get those you get it free
at the library if you don't want to go
to amazon for the discount
the amazon they control the pricing
when you start cleaning up that liver
and killing off those viruses and you
learn how to do it
some people celery juice isn't going to
be enough but you have to have a celery
juice it's a critical part of it like
the celery juice is like a critical
piece of getting rid of that excellent
psoriasis
but if you have a real stubborn epstein
bar and you're not doing other things
then now you got to bring in other tools
in the protocols and medical medium
healing tools
got to bring in the zinc the right kind
of liquid
sulfate zinc you got to bring the right
kind of supplements in too
but i've seen people they clean up their
diet enough they get rid of their vices
they're getting off the caffeine they're
getting off of the milk
cheese butter they're using their celery
juice they're annihilating their epstein
bar
or if somebody's got acne they're
annihilating their strep
inside the liver and they're cleaning
things up so they get rid of all that
acne on their skin
so you can do it the tools are there but
celery juice is a big part of it
so is this so when someone has a juicer
is it a medical tool it's a medical
device
it is and it's an herbal extractor and
it's helping you get rid
of conditions that's what it's doing
celery juice is helping reverse
conditions elizabeth says
elizabeth ann smith is there a reason
you choose that juicer over the other
omega
yeah wide mouth absolutely that's not
the celery juicer so the other one is
not the celery juicer
um and so the whole point about this
juicer it's the celery juicer and it
juices other
stuff too it juices i love it for
anything i'll juice anything in fact
i'll do
a juice someday with other stuff the
reason why i choose this juicer
one reason is because what you just
witnessed you won't get
from any other omega juicer you won't
get a little ball
of dried pulp
dried fiber that's it right there
you won't get that that that's not in
the other juicers so if you go to
omega juicers.com and you see there's
another juicer for sale
you're not going to be able to extract
that celery juice
like this there's no way so this is
their celery juicer models the mm-900
hds
what this means is you just cut your
celery in half your celery costs in half
at least by a third at least by a third
i've seen it where it's a half so it's
half the cost
the juicer paid for itself paid for
itself paid for itself over and over
again
i mean wouldn't you tell it wouldn't you
tell your friends that if
something paid for itself over and over
again i mean this is it right here
here's the pulp
that's it just lost it that's it
all it is is that much
why do i like to throw things in the air
lorraine you're gonna have to
lorraine l you're gonna have to figure
that one out for me how can i throw
stuff in the air all the time
i wonder what that is maybe
lorraine one thing i noticed about your
comments is they're really thoughtful
and they really you really understand
medical medium information of like
is as are the people off caffeine are
they off
are they off their exactly their vices
or what other what other stuff or they
have junk and other stuff
because every now and then you'll see
somebody say oh medical medium
information that's not new
that's not original there's been that
information was out there really
because you know lorraine when i read
your comments
you you've been around the health
movement for a long time
you haven't seen all the different
protocols like this the way they're put
together
systematically by spirit of compassion
that doesn't exist out there
it's here and celery juice is one of
those tools
yeah tick tick tock says juggling the
handle tick tock
not the app uh lorraine says emote this
is motivational
it's hard to break vices when
we're around family and friends we're
the bad people
we're the people that you know we're
just causing an up eve we're making
everybody feel uncomfortable
is what we're doing i think what a big
part of the whole vice breaking thing
around loved ones and others and friends
and co-workers is that
yeah it's making it it's making them
feel uncomfortable because they're not
eating healthy or healthy enough
and they're stuck on vices they're stuck
on the
you know the bad sugar the bad fat
all the time they're stuck on the milk
cheese the butter which is the bad fat
and the bad sugar because that's all
lactose
the bad sugar they're stuck on the
different things there's you know
and they don't want to be feeling
uncomfortable because you're changing
your life
you're working on healing you're working
hard to heal
they don't want to feel that they don't
want to feel that
shannon says oh my god yes my family
thinks i'm crazy for eating healthy
so you're you need to be eating some
pizza shannon i think that's what it is
right
you need to eat a donut in front of them
is that what you have to do is you have
to
you have to throw yourself on the line
for them is that what you have to do
you have to eat a pizza in front of them
right you gotta
you gotta prove yourself do you have to
prove yourself you have to prove
yourself because that's what we feel
like
we're told to feel that way we're pushed
into feeling that way that now we have
to
we have to do it for them like let's
take a hit for them
even though it's not going to make you
healthy which isn't going to be good for
friends and family
if you're not healthy but i better take
this hit for them
and it's it's unfair really when you
think about it
so so you'll end up being in put to a
place where you're being pushed into
having to eat the foods that aren't good
for you that you know and your heart and
soul aren't good for you
but they always have the upper hand tic
toc says no more
they always have the upper hand and the
upper hand is
it's hard to break these foods it's hard
we've been raised on them we have
these are comfort foods we've had these
comfort foods in our system
for in a long many many years we've
lived with them
we know what these comfort foods feel
like inside of us they store
away inside our organs deep in our
organs they store away
and people don't realize that aspect of
it too when you eat
all the comfort foods the comfort foods
are stored deep in organ tissue they
become
part of the tissue something to know
that's really important
so when you're eating all the milk
cheese butter
when you're eating when you have all the
msg when you're doing all the
msg deposits in the brain it deposits
inside the liver
these things become part of our cells
and then we walk around with all this
baggage
of the past inside of us we walk around
with all this baggage
all the baggage of the past is inside of
us
something to consider right there so
anyway talk about the
hcs breaking the eczema
breaking it breaking psoriasis
breaking conditions breaking
health issues sun spots if someone's
worried about sun spots
so i've seen celery juice reverse
wrinkles in people
give them make them look 10 years
younger 15 years
younger reversing you know skin issues
of all kinds and that's just some that's
just one part not even talking about the
lupus and the lyme disease the
neurological lyme and
in all the other different conditions
autoimmune in general you guys
a lot of people don't even get a
diagnosis anymore
they get just an autoimmune label go to
your doctor they're
running the a a they can't really put a
label on your
illness but they'll put they'll give you
the autoimmune label but they won't give
you an individual
an individual diagnosis anymore i've
seen that out there now
so a lot of doctors are sending people
out the door they're not saying they
have lupus
they're not saying they got neurological
lyme they're sending them out the door
with just
autoimmune when it's when it's mild in a
lot of people
near xenia says i'm 20 years younger so
lorraine says i love mm info anthony and
the juggling
doing a lot of juggling today trying to
get my words right
good thing spirit of compassion is here
to help so let's give you guys the quick
takeaways real quick okay
you're gonna feel pressure from the
people around you when it comes down to
the vices
breaking vices is hard because that's
one of the big reasons why it's hard
if you don't have any of that pressure
around you it's hard enough
it's hard enough even if you don't have
all the family and the friends and the
co-workers and anybody else
that's around you pushing you into
eating that acidic acidic acidic diet
the other takeaway is
acid the fats are the acid too
fatty acids all that fat in the
bloodstream makes you terribly acidic
if you're plant-based you're eating your
avocados every day
and you want to become alkaline you're
losing your chance
so you got to slow down you got to have
a little avocado here
you gotta have just you know little nut
butter here gotta have a little bit of
olive oil here but you gotta be careful
another thing is the big acid ones
apple cider vinegar the coffee the
caffeine don't get tricked by the
mushroom coffee
basically it's they're drug dealers
right now out there it's it's it's
unbelievable what's happening and
they're turning good people into drug
dealers
because there's the mlm marketing scheme
with the mushroom coffee
and if you stick coffee with anything
just people are going to be like whoa i
feel good i feel good
because they're out they're high on
caffeine it's the greatest trick
it's the greatest trick so be careful on
that right there it's another one that's
going on around there
remember you know that this is an herbal
extractor
keep that in mind sales running for a
couple of days more
and then the sale is going to be gone i
don't know the next time this this model
is going to be on sale like that
and keep in mind too that it's all about
what what are you doing to take care of
yourself start with the mm tools
one at a time if you need to heavy metal
detox smoothie
maybe a little bit of celery juice if
you need to start that way baby steps
get out the dairy get out the eggs get
some things out of there
if you've got a baby step if you need to
go deeper you go deeper into the
protocols
and you learn how to do your 32 ounces
of celery juice
and you learn how to do the right
supplementation and dosages like in the
books
critical medical books right here if you
hear somebody that says i did mm and it
didn't work
keep in mind the fly on the wall
keep in mind on the fly on the wall
because
what are they doing what supplements had
alcohol what had natural flavors what
had msg
what did they even do the right dosages
what
foods are they still bringing in where's
the nutritional yeast which is the bad
stuff
how much vinegar are they doing how much
chocolate can they break the chocolate
they're doing chocolate every couple
weeks and you need to heal and you're
seriously sick it's not going to happen
and how many fats were you on medical
medium teaches you to keep the fats low
and everything
so lunell correct i don't recommend
coffee enemas it's one of the worst
things you can do
damage is the central nervous system
actually damages it because the stomach
buffers the caffeine and you can't
buffer it when it goes up the back end
so it goes straight to the nerves and it
injures the nerves
because so keep that in mind it also
injures the adrenals when you do coffee
enemas
you're injuring the adrenals and
adrenals are precious you guys i'm
heading off
to instagram i'm gonna put tick tock
back on i'm gonna stick clubhouse back
on
so you guys tick tock stand by and bring
you guys back on
so i'm looking forward to it and i'm
gonna put clubhouse back on so you guys
stand by
and you guys facebook youtube head over
to ig
we're gonna have some fun