best sale ever in the mm1 1500 $140 off
$140 off get it for somebody for
Christmas if you wait it all year and
you don't have the MN 1500 hands down
the MN 1500 saves people money now I'm
watching out there all the time I'm just
going to say this the juicers that are
getting popular because they got money
behind them and advertising and
influencers behind them those juicers
they don't squeeze enough juice out of
the produce and so essentially you're
throwing away money and people who are
chronically sick are trying to juice
every day people in the medical mem
Community who juice a ton of stuff they
can't just be buying cases and cases of
produce juicing it and having not the
results because you're not getting
enough nutrients extracted from the
juice it's not actually doing its job to
get the juice out and they're throwing
away produce all that leftover pulp is
getting thrown away that's what I love
about the mm 1500 the 900 this is the mm
1500 right here you guys know I work
with the mega link is in the description
links in the profile but we're talking
today about eating to protect your liver
what people don't realize they have
overburdened stagnant sluggish hot
livers that are filled with fat the
livers get dysfunctional and then your
cholesterol gets out of whack everything
else gets out of whack deficiencies
start to happen because your liver is
the great converter so what happens with
people's livers is that they actually
burden them and they don't realize they
burden them so they overburden livers
every single day and that's what we're
kind of taught we're not taught how to
protect our liver how to look after our
liver how to get our liver in a better
place and then over time our liver stops
working the way it should work it
doesn't produce enough bile and when
that bile isn't produced we get in
trouble and all that fat sits around it
doesn't break down good enough it sits
around in our bloodstream then it
eventually collects in Our arteries then
it collects in our veins and over time
we get problems where we have all this
plaque jacked up all around our blood
vessels veins arteries our liver gets
sluggish another thing too you go to the
doctor doctor takes blood work the blood
work comes back you're deficient in this
you're deficient in that you're
deficient in this and all these
deficiencies over time partly happen
because your liver is the great
converter what it does is it actually
converts the nutrients and we don't have
good livers these days so we don't get
good conversion because you want good
conversion every single nutrient you eat
almost every single nutrient you eat
nutrients that come from your leafy
greens nutrients that come from your
onions your broccoli your radishes your
carrots everything your lemons your
limes your Tomatoes your avocados all
those nutrients have to be converted
they go into the liver boom they go up
the hepatic portal highway right into
the liver here and when that happens
your liver says whoa It's conversion
time so your liver has to anoint and
bless the nutrients is what it has to do
and people don't realize this they think
that if you take a whole bunch of
supplements the supplements are going to
work for you you take a whole bunch of
different things are going to work for
you and partially that partially that's
true but your liver still has to
methylate it still has to convert it
still has to anoint and turn and change
the nutrients around around a little bit
it has to bless them enzymes from the
liver attach to the nutrients carry the
nutrients along change the nutrients too
and then the liver has to store the
nutrients at the same time but if we
overburden we beat down our livers we
drink alcohol we do all kinds of stuff
we eat really greasy food fried foods we
eat too much oil in everything we get in
trouble the liver ends up weakening and
when it weakens it can't convert so we
walk around our liver's getting tired
it's getting stagnant it's getting
sluggish and then it's not doing its job
every day and then we go to bed at night
and our liver is tired it's too tired to
work hard for us all night long so what
happens when you go to bed at night your
liver starts to work that's when it
clocks in mainly clocks in in the middle
of the night that's where it starts to
bag up all the garbage all the junk all
the toxins all the poisons they get
bagged up in the middle of the night and
you got to keep that in mind right so
when we sleep our liver working while
we're resting that's how it works our
liers working while we're resting think
about a whole bunch of elves inside your
liver and they're making all kinds of
toys and they're doing all kinds of
stuff and they're using Hammers and saws
they're working all night long while
you're sleeping and resting but when our
livers get tired and they get beat up
and they get overburdened and they get
fatty and they start to get sluggish and
stagnant when they work in the middle of
the night they're not as efficient our
livers are not as working as they should
or efficient as they should so in the
middle of the night we sit there and
sometimes people toss and turntime
sometimes people have more gas sometimes
people have they're waking up in the
middle of the night sometimes times
people don't feel good when they're
trying to sleep they're tossing and
turning and a lot of that is liver
spasming out so people get liver spasms
they don't even know it a lot of people
and inside their body they got an
unhappy liver every single day that
wants to perform that wants to move
forward that wants to heal that wants to
get better but it just can't do what it
needs to do let's make some garbanzo
bean hummus so what I have right here is
a bowl of chickpeas garbanzo beans and
I'm going to make hummus I'm going to
make it without using Sesame tahini I'm
not going to use a whole bunch of tahini
in here I'm not not going to dump a
whole bunch of olive oil in here either
this is easier food on the liver that's
what this is so what you see is sesame
seeds take a look you can get the flavor
of Sesame in your hummus without
burdening the liver with too much oil
too much tahini you don't need to do
that you can make a hummus and just use
some sesame seeds in here get it ground
up all the same in there that's that's
the difference so let's go let's drop
some of these garbanzo beans in here
right here you can make hummus without
olive oil without tahini I got some
garbanzos coming through you realize
like how very little this is a handful
of sesame seeds much different than a
tablespoon of tahini in somebody's
hummus right this is a basic hummus you
don't have to go too crazy I got a lemon
squeezing the lemon right in here there
we go let me show you right here that's
hummus and there isn't a tablespoon of
oil there's not a tablespoon of olive
oil there isn't a tablespoon of tahini
in here it's easy on the liver so I'm
just mixing this up there we go back to
the crud this time it's with hummus made
from the mm 1500 I'm going to take a
radish