How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them. Whether you're dealing with
anxiety, depression, endometriosis,
acne, eczema, autoimmune, thyroid, lime,
brain fog, fatigue, or any other symptom
or condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony Williams.
We're talking about poisoning the
people. That's right. Poisoning the
people. Toxic air pockets floating in
the sky. Poisons coming out of planes.
We're talking about chemtrails and
geoengineering. This is episode three
about geoengineering and chemtrails.
Poor air quality from factories, from
smog is one thing. Then add thousands
and even hundreds of thousands and
millions of planes up in the sky all
around the globe releasing toxic
chemicals. How this combined with the
pollution on the planet takes things to
an unnecessary level. There's a strategy
to when the planes dump the toxins.
There's a strategy to when the
chemtrails happen. They're always
happening. They're always up there in
the sky and they're always dumping
chemtrails. They're always dumping toxic
chemicals. But when holidays happen or
the weather shifts and people are
outside, Fourth of July, Easter,
springtime, Sundays, weekends,
Thanksgiving, they pour it on. They pour
it right on. More planes in the sky.
More white streaks everywhere. The
strategy is to poison the people. Hang
on with this episode. Strap yourself in.
Fasten your seat belts because we're
taking another plane flight.
[Music]
So, what is coming out of these jet
planes up there in the sky? Vitamins,
nutrients, mineral water, sparkling
water, fruit juice, essential oils. Are
they dumping nice things on everyone?
Are they dumping wonderful things on
everyone? Are all these planes that are
leaving these streaks all across the
planet, is there friendly ingredients in
those streaks that are leaving the
planes, are they dumping nice things on
us, on our families, on our children, on
our friends, on the people we care
about? When we look up in the sky and we
see all those white streaks coming out
of all those jet planes, should we say
it's organic, right? What they're
dumping on us must be organic because
why on God's earth would there be evil
people controlling an entire network of
planes? A system built to release all of
this stuff, all of these chemicals, all
of those agents on top of everyone while
kids are in the schoolyards, while
people are in a picnic in a park. Why
people are living their lives out every
day, jogging, running in it. Why
everybody's looking up at the sky,
watching a sunset. Why on God's green
earth would they ever do this? So the
powers that run this planet must be
looking out for us. Surely they must
care. Whoever's behind all this must be
doing it just to help us. It must be to
protect our planet, of course. But
that's not the truth. And wouldn't it be
wonderful if that was the truth? The
geoengineering operation and the
chemtrail operation are secret
operations no one has their fingers on.
Nobody in the public arena understands
it. Nobody in the public arena really
knows what's going on. It's all a
classified mystery. Geoengineering is a
secretive endeavor that encompasses a
large umbrella and doesn't even admit to
the releasing of agents out of planes up
in the sky because there's nobody
accountable. There's nobody to admit
anything. There's no service. There's no
phone number. There's no agency that's
known. It's a complete mystery. A total
complete mystery. Sure, you might be
able to dig, dig, dig and find
something, but in the end, after you
scratch the surface, you're nowhere.
You're not going to find information on
the scheduling, what they're dumping,
are they dumping, are they spraying,
what's coming out of the planes, is it
for weather modification, or is it not?
Are they really trying to shield the
sun? Are they doing it for climate
change? Are they doing it for climate
engineering? What is climate
engineering? Who are they? What
scientists are they? Where are the
scientists meeting? Is there a public
forum? It's all a secret. And right now,
states that are interested in stopping
geoengineering or any kind of aerosol
being sprayed out of a plane over the
state or any other chemical agents
sprayed out of planes over a state.
Right now, it's still a mystery. A
public authority can't just call a
hotline and then somebody answer on the
other end. No one's allowed to talk to a
scientist working for geoengineering. A
scientist that's formulating the
chemicals, the toxic metals, all the
different toxic agents, the scientists
that are actually saying, "Well, this
will help shield the sun. This will help
stop climate change." No one's allowed
to talk to those people. No one's
allowed to talk to anyone. It is just a
campaign that's completely off limits to
anyone and everybody. A state can ban
any kind of geoengineering, spraying of
chemtrails. They could ban them, but who
are they banning? Who are they
punishing? Who are they finding? No one
even knows where the planes land.
Commercial airports aren't governing any
of these planes. Air traffic control has
nothing to do with any of the
geoengineering or chemtrail campaigns.
At least not our air traffic control.
What does that mean? The air traffic
control that handles commercial flights,
those air traffic controllers all around
the globe at commercial airports do not
have any affiliation to the
geoengineering and chemtrail programs.
There are hundreds of airports around
the world that work with geoengineering
and the chemtrail programs. privately
classified secretive airports and air
traffic controllers. So if you're a
public authority, who do you ban? Who do
you find? What judges reside over this?
The districts, who's in charge? All we
could really do is look up in the sky
and if you see a white streak, we can't
prove it. We can't prove that white
streak is still a geoengineering trail
or a chemtrail. We can't prove it's an
aerosol coming out of a jet because that
jet can't land in an airport we can
find. It doesn't land in a commercial
airport or commercial airport in that
state that bans geoengineering or
chemtrails. So if a law is passed, which
is amazing because it's helpful, it does
get the word out. It does open it up.
But if a law has passed where
geoengineering can't occur in the skies
above a state, how do you get that jet
plane finded? How do you actually find
that jet plane? How do you know who it
is? You can't just call an air traffic
control. You can't call the FAA and say,
"Uh, excuse me. There was a plane at
this certain time flying above our great
state and um we saw a white streak
coming from that plane. Do you happen to
know what plane that is or who that is?
It is very hard to find out almost
impossible and clearly may be impossible
because there's chemtrails being dropped
out of planes. People are being poisoned
every day. It could be under the guise
of the campaign of
geoengineering, weather modification,
and it can also be chemol programs in
general. And there's not just one
program up there in the sky. And there's
not just one organization in the sky.
And the organizations communicate with
each other. This is far different than a
small plane releasing something out of
it or dumping something out of it and
then landing in a local airport where
the authorities could be sitting there
waiting for them. There are secret
bases, secret airports all around the
country and all around every country and
the globe. These secret airports have
the chemtrail planes landing in them and
the geoengineering planes landing in
them. And if you don't know where one
secret airport is, one out of hundreds
and hundreds, if you don't know where
these airports are, and you don't know
who the air traffic controllers are, and
you have no way of getting the FAA to
help you and find them, then who do you
punish? Who do you ban? It's that
difficult. But yet, it's good that
states are aware of this. It's good that
states are aware of geoengineering,
weather modification, weather
manipulation, trails coming out of
planes, agents being dropped on people.
That's very important and critical. And
we need states to actually see that. And
we need laws to be passed. But it's the
beginning, the very beginning. And
that's a great place to start. The only
time a chemtrail plane or a
geoengineering chemtrail plane, weather
modification plane will ever land in a
commercial airport, is if there's a
malfunction with that plane and the
pilot has no choice but to land that
plane in a commercial airport, to land
that chemtrail plane, which never lands
in a commercial airport ever. The only
way it's going to happen is if there's
an emergency, a malfunction, a problem
with the plane, or the plane happens to
be out of fuel for some reason. Then
they can land in a commercial airport.
They can switch the radio and
communicate to an air traffic controller
at a commercial airport and do an
emergency landing and be protected too
while they do it. Where an air traffic
controller can't question them, can't
question their airplane. Does it have
passengers or not? What is it? What is
it doing? What secret mission is it on?
They won't even question it. They're
protected. There's a reason for this.
Air traffic controllers in commercial
airports know of such planes. They're
not blind to it. They're aware of secret
missions, classified planes in the
skies. They see it all the time. They're
everywhere. So much so, more so than
commercial flights and commercial
airliners. So when a chemtrail
classified chemtrail plane or
geoengineering plane is in trouble,
they're allowed to land in a commercial
airport. It's rare, only if there's an
emergency, but it happens. An air
traffic control at a commercial airliner
at a commercial airport will actually
let them land and not question them. And
their plane won't even be inspected.
Because if they did an inspection, they
would see a hollowedout plane filled
with tanks, plastic tanks. Those plastic
tanks filled with chemicals. Chemicals
that get admitted or sprayed or released
out of little pipes, little tubes that
are attached to the plane with a motor
pulling the chemical out of the tanks
and into the pipes and out of the plane,
all through a switch that's in the
cockpit. And these planes aren't allowed
to be inspected. Instead, they're
protected, secretly protected, and they
are above the law. All laws on this
planet. Geoengineering planes, chemtrail
planes, any kind of planes that are up
there in the sky, up there flying around
releasing toxins, chemicals, streaming
out all kinds of white streaks, are
above the law. And the truth is, the
people that run all of that, that run
the campaigns, that are in charge of the
chemtrail programs, that are responsible
for 60, 70 years of contamination being
dropped on everyone, are the hidden
powers behind the scenes. These are the
evildoers, the people that pull strings,
that make things happen, that are
unbelievable as far as the drive they
have to wreak havoc and cause problems
and contaminate the earth and hurt
people, poisoning the people, poisoning
nature. Think about it. Classified
airports all around the globe, hidden
away and tucked away, many in the woods.
Planes coming and going. Planes landing,
filling the tanks back up with toxic
chemicals and toxic metals. A new pilot
going into the plane. And then the plane
goes back up. And then the pilots are
given direction coordinates to where
they're going to be releasing the toxic
chemicals. And that's the white streaks
you see in the sky. If you listen to the
last episode about contrails, they are
not contrails. They are chemicals,
solvents, metals, agents, toxic waste,
fungus, pathogens, petrochemicals, and a
lot more. And remember, there's more
than one campaign going on up there.
There's geoengineering for weather
modification, which could easily be just
barerium or a mix of two or three
different metals in high concentrations.
And then there's the chemtrail campaign,
which is anything goes. Anything toxic
comes out of those planes. Any kind of
mix, any kind of brew. Some of the brews
are old. Back to World War I, World War
II. Back stoages of lots of toxic
chemicals produced in the industries.
Now, keep in mind, before the
1960s, all the chemical factories and
chemical industries all around the
planet were dumping all of the runoff,
all the byproduct into rivers, lakes,
and the ocean and into landfills. By the
1960s, late 1960s, early 1970s, and 80s,
it started changing. Chemical factories,
chemical industries weren't dumping as
much toxic chemical into the rivers,
lakes, landfills, and ocean because it
was polluting them too severely. Rivers
were dying, lakes were dying, landfills
were getting worse and overfilled,
oversaturated, and the chemicals had no
place to go because of this. And by the
1980s, more chemicals were being
produced than ever before because of the
industries and for the need of a lot of
different products because the
population was growing. But yet, even
though there was all this backup storage
of byproduct from all these different
chemical industries, it wasn't being put
in the oceans, the rivers, and the lakes
anymore. just to actively produce one
chemical, one foundational chemical for
products in the industry, it can produce
millions of gallons of runoff and
byproduct. So, think about all of the
hundreds and thousands of chemicals that
are produced in the chemical industries
and the byproduct produced, the billions
and even trillions of gallons of
byproduct that aren't being stored
somewhere in a tank at the chemical
industry facility or anywhere that
anyone can inspect it. There isn't room
to house that many gallons, billions and
even trillions of gallons of byproduct.
There's no land that can house it.
There's no room that can house it. It
has to go somewhere. And so since the
1960s, private deals, classified deals
are brokered. And the industries found a
way to get the chemicals out the door
and in the skies. Backlogs of old DDT,
backlogs of old agent orange, backlogs
of experimental chemicals gone wrong
because of the experimental process of
creating them. Someone figured out that
if they got it in the sky and thinned it
out enough and dropped it on everybody
that it wouldn't create a direct effect.
It wouldn't be like a direct runoff into
a stream or a direct runoff into a lake
where just in 10 years time, 15 years
time, the whole lake dies. The direct
effect is unseen, but yet seen every
single day by everybody's eyes as we
look into the sky. It's the ultimate
evildoing done in front of everyone, but
yet the destruction and the evil
despicable nature of it is underneath
everyone's noses. But yet, fakeipedia,
Wikipedia would say it's not true and
it's a conspiracy theory. And what
everybody's looking at are contrails,
which couldn't be further from the
truth. Now, let's talk about
geoengineering for a little bit. The
history of geoengineering is vague. And
if there is a plane involved in
geoengineering flying above you and it's
releasing a white trail and that white
trail is cadmium, that white trail is
barerium or that white trail is some
other toxin or metal, you're not going
to know if that's geoengineering. You're
not allowed to know. It's not like it's
out there where you know the plane above
you is just involved in a geoengineering
campaign, an experiment or science and
they're helping us out. No one would
ever know. No one's allowed to test it.
No one's allowed to feel it in their
fingers. No one's allowed to knock on
somebody's door, some bureaucrat, and be
like, "Hey, I would love to talk to the
geoengineering people, the people
responsible for the planes in the sky,
and is that plane above me
geoengineering? And what are they
dropping out of that plane? Can you give
me a container of it?" It's never going
to happen. It's impossible. Doesn't work
that way because in the end, they would
just say, "What you're seeing is a
contrail anyway." There are two kinds of
planes up in the sky that are dropping
all of the chemicals on us. If it's a
geoengineering plane, it's most likely a
military cargo plane, but yet it still
can be an old commercial airliner that's
hollowed out and not in use anymore for
commercial flights. But there's another
type of plane up in the sky, which
really is no matter what, a commercial
airliner, but an old commercial
airliner, one that's not in business
anymore, or leftover, beat up, worn out
planes that are not in use. But yet the
airliner company, the airplane company
is still putting out planes, still
flying people commercially, still in
service, but they're old planes. They
don't use anymore from the 80s in the
70s and the '9s, the early 2000s.
They're retired planes, and they're not
just sitting somewhere in a parking lot
or on some air strip getting dust and
dirt all over them. They're given or
sold to the chemtrail campaigns, the
chemtrail people. And then there's still
manufacturing of planes. There's still
the buying of planes for the purposes.
There's still military planes, cargo
planes being bought and sold and created
for the purpose of geoengineering, for
the purpose of dropping out all of those
chemicals, all those metals out in the
sky and all over us. And if you really
think about it, what is it really for?
Well, it's twofold. You get rid of a lot
of toxic waste that needs a place to go
because it has no more places to go. And
at the same time, you can hurt people.
You can make people sicker. You can make
people get cancer faster. You can make
people get ill quicker. You can make
people lose the quality of their lives.
And you can slowly alter life
expectancy. It's ingenious. The
evildoers got a great plan. They got a
great scam going for a very long time
since the 1960s. It hasn't stopped. It's
only gotten stronger. There are days out
there people report seeing people claim
to see hundreds of strips and streaks in
the sky. 10, 20, 30 planes flying by
within a half an hour and white streaks
coming from the back of the planes and
the sides of the planes. And let's be
clear about something. something that's
really important. It's not the jet fuel
that has all of this toxic waste, all
these toxic chemicals, all of the
different metals like in
geoengineering, all the different
poisons like in
chemtrailing. It's not in the fuel
that's being filled up into the plane so
the plane can fly, so the jet engines
can run. It's not to say that the fuel
isn't toxic and there aren't dangerous
chemicals being put into the fuel, the
jet fuel, the plane fuel. It's not that.
There always can be that. There's always
chemicals in fuels and it could even be
some additional ones. But that's not
chemtrailing. That's not what's
happening. These are planes hollowed
out. Plastic tanks are placed into these
planes, large tanks. They're being
filled with toxic chemicals. There are
small motors that pull the contents out
of the plastic tank, out a pipe, and out
the sides of the plane. The pilot has a
switch and the pilot clicks that switch
or flicks that switch or presses that
button and then the contents are
released. And this is the poisoning of
the people. people being poisoned. And
even though there's a lot of new
awareness when it comes down to
chemtrails, even though there's a lot of
new awareness when it comes down to
geoengineering, it's still going to be a
process. It's still going to take time
and it's going to be a long time before
those planes are not in the sky anymore.
Stay tuned for other episodes in the
geoengineering and chemtrail series.
Check out medicalmemedium.com for more
free information. You can check out the
medical medium book series. Many
blessings and God bless
you. It's unreal when you think about
it. There's these planes filled with
chem and they're up there in the sky day
in day out. They spray. They do it to
create a toxic chemical fallout. Who
said they're allowed to do this? They
should be called out. Someone should be
held accountable. No doubt. This is
flight 114 to the base. I just let out
20,000 gallons out the gate. Pretty sure
I'm out. There's no more. Over. This is
the base. Flight 114. Land out the
Arizona air strip. Get a good night's
sleep. Fill back up. Get back in the
air. Roger that. This is flight 132 to
the base. I noticed when they were
filling my plane, it was a different
color this time and it was reddish
orange. Over. This is the base, flight
132. It's no concern to you. Your job
isn't to understand the contents that
you carry. Just kick back, enjoy the
ride, and be merry. This is flight 222
to 132. I overheard and when I filled up
last night, the tank was green and the
tech was wearing a hazmat suit. I asked
him why. He just gave me a salute. Over.
This is flight 132 to 222. My guy was
wearing a hazmat suit, too. Over. This
is the base. Flight 132. Flight 222.
Having fun. Just do your job, sons. This
is flight 666. Caught the last part of
that. 132 and 222. Last time I had my
tank filled. Took a whiff and it was
bad. Got quite sick. That's why I hope
everybody down there isn't being
affected. Well, we're dumping on them,
including our families. This is the base
Flight 666. They're safe. They're fine.
Stop with the gossip. This is flight 666
to the base. And why is there skulling
crossbones on the tanks? This is the
base flight 666. Do as you're told and
the sky is the limit. Roger
that.
Original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. instead the opposite. Only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.