time
processed foods
that's the problem
it's got to be the processed foods
got all these geniuses out there and the
health scene
you get new people on health scene all
the time over the last few years right
and they all say processed foods
junk foods that's the problem
junk foods right you hear that too junk
foods are the problem fast food
right
you see stuff out there you see people
talking about you hear about
documentaries you hear about everybody
fast foods that's the problem that's the
problem in america it's the fast foods
it's a processed foods it's a junk foods
that's the process foods and the junk
foods and the fast foods that's the
problem
all around the world right you hear
about that right
and then
you hear people say well that's the
whole problem for obesity right and
that's the big problem it's obesity
but what about all of the neurological
problems
crippling anxiety depression ocd
depersonalization fatigue body pain
tingles and numbness vertigo
brain fog migraines
back problems neck problems leg problems
feet problems muscle weakness you name
it what about all the neurological
problems in a 20 year old
a 20 year old
what about all the neurological problems
and autoimmune diagnoses in a 15 year
old what about all the neurological
problems
in a 21 year old is it really years and
years of fast foods when you're they're
not 50 years old
is it really really the fast foods and
the processed foods
and the fried foods and the greasy foods
and the junk foods is it really that
that's creating that
so let's get a few things straight
junk food fast food processed food
yeah it's bad for you
why is it bad for you we're gonna cover
a little bit but yeah it's bad for you
it's true
it's bad
absolutely
yes it'll contribute to obesity it will
contribute to heart attack
your heart attack
it will contribute to cardiovascular
problems
it will contribute to diabetes right
type 2 diabetes it will make you
diabetic over time
okay
it can contribute to that
yeah all that grease and all that
processed oil and all that fried oil oil
and all that junk and everything else
and right
all that we dump inside of us fast foods
and processed foods and all that sure
it's going to bring us closer to obesity
it's going to bring us closer to a heart
attack that's why i always say butter
butter's like the heart attacker
butter
that's the heart attack bringer
right
but what about the raging
raging illnesses happening and the
autoimmune and the fatigue and the
seeing and that and the chronic fatigue
syndrome the
mecfs and the fibro and the hoshi so
wait a minute
fast food
gives you hoshis
what gives you hashimoto's is it fast
food that gives you hashimoto's
so
this is an important conversation
because i know in the health scene
i know for quite a while now in the last
10 years
all these people these brainiacs these
geniuses coming up in the health scene
feel like they found they found it all
they figured it all out
it's
all that fast food it's all the
processed food
it's going into the fast food
restaurants that's what's killing us all
that's what's doing it it's all that so
let's go we'll make some documentary
that oh we'll go and do we'll do this
about it oh we'll go and put some books
out about it
without even understanding why anybody
gets sick without even understanding our
knowing why or how anyone gets sick
anyone
young people get sick
right
how much fast food is someone eating by
the time they're nine years old
meanwhile they got thyroid diagnoses at
nine years old
they are crippling fatigue and brain fog
at nine years old they got crippling
eczema and psoriasis at nine years old
so what is it the 50 years of fast foods
and nine year olds nine years old
what is it the 50 years of processed
food that's what got the nine-year-old
sick 50 years does that make any sense
50 years of processed foods and fast
foods and greasy fried foods
and that's what made a nine-year-old
sick when nine-year-olds only nine years
old
norma said study just came out linking
ms to ebv and you've been saying this
all along published first medical medium
that's medical medium information public
published first and then science
poaches and steals medical medium
information
that's what they do
that's how they learn science and
chronic illness now they they go to the
medical medium books into the medical
medium lectures and all the medical
medium
work that's been done and they take the
information they extract it and they try
to advance forward with that
in certain areas
but don't worry they'll just be shut
down
down the road when they link that then
they'll be classified medical research
and science will stomp on them
like they were a turkey in thanksgiving
it'll just stomp on them
you know that's the one thing even if
they try even if alternative science or
conventional science takes medical
medium information about epstein-barr
causing multiple sclerosis which is
which is medical medium right and they
take that and they try to now do studies
to try to link it right
big bad wolf
up in the sky classified medical
research and science will jump on them
so quick and pounce on them and eat them
up
because they don't want that getting out
there so it's kind of a battle out there
and how that works
so what's making the eight year old
so sick they got thyroid disorders at
eight years old is it 50 years of
processed foods
no
they're eight years old
what's making the five-year-old get
raging eczema psoriasis is it 60 years
of processed food
and fast food and greasy food no
no
i love it documentaries on fast foods
and
and fried greasy foods and processed
foods all these things on that everybody
thinks you're a genius about it
but i'm scratching my head saying well
how is the five year old
right
how's the five-year-old
getting eczema psoriasis
i mean
we know medical medium information knows
why it's copper it's viruses plus toxic
heavy metals like copper right
but everybody's like a genius it's a oh
it's these processed foods oh it's these
fried foods these greasy foods it's fast
foods that's what's taking down america
s.a.d standard american diet
that's what's doing it
you can't package it like that you can't
you can't just package it like that i
just want to make an announcement before
we move on i'm going to be on rumble
later i know right now we're live on
rumble we're live on youtube we're live
on facebook we're live on telegram we're
live on tick tock right now just so you
know but i'm gonna be on rumble
exclusively at six o'clock eastern three
o'clock pacific later on that's my
announcement i'm also making another
announcement as we speak i'm making some
cookies
i'm making the gluten-free banana oat
from cleanse the heel
by the way on on the rumble talk later
it'd be an exclusive talk i'm not gonna
be talking about anything i'm talking
about now
just so you know
anyway you guys got a copy of cleanse
the heel check out that recipe right
there gluten-free banana oat breakfast
cookies i'm making them you see the
bananas all in front of me you see some
oatmeal right there if you can depending
on where you are
you guys
right
so i'm excited so i'm going to make some
recipes get them in the oven i got the
oven preheating at 350 degrees
good to see you guys it's an honor to be
here truly i'm happy to be at your
service in any way i can
like usual
so
talk about the processed food a little
bit yes processed food isn't good yes
yes fried foods greasy foods it's not
good it's bad
true
it'll clog up that liver is what it's
going to do it'll clog up that liver so
let's take a look
the more and more grease you stick in
you and the more and more fried
processed oil and grease you stick in
you okay
the more and more your liver has to get
overburdened overburdened overburdened
you kill your liver with that
well what that does that just leads
people to the obesity factor the weight
gain comes on because their liver is
being bogged down by all that grease and
all that that processed food right and
all that fast food okay and then once
that liver gets beaten down like that
you end up with type 2 diabetes now
you're pre-diabetic yes
and then
all that fat from those processed foods
and fried greasy foods starts to cling
to your arteries and your veins and
cling to your heart starts to get into
your heart right there right
and your valves
gets into the veins and arteries right
and so guess what yeah
you end up
gaining weight you end up
heart attack city down the road when
you're older
you end up diabetes diabetes too
diabetic right you end up all that
but what about everybody else
what about everybody else
when they're not tanking the fried food
they're not taking the fast food they're
not taking really any of that they're 20
years old they're on mattress island
they're stuck
with no explanations they're told they
have autoimmune it's genetic and that's
why they're sick and they're just stuck
in bed or stuck on couch island or stuck
on mattress island right what about them
yeah the fried greasy foods and the
processed foods are bad yeah they clog
up the liver
they do they clog up the liver which is
medical medium information
clogging up the liver part is
my son was on your banana
mono diet and his skin and digestion got
better it really works we are going to
do it again so proud of you incredible
that's the mono
the mono um
cleanse in here and that's the banana
version amazing you guys don't have
cleanse to heal make sure you get it
amazon.com us
16.99 51 off get it free at the library
right so we're making a recipe right now
i'm excited we're talking about
processed foods and we're going to go
deeper into it we got more to cover
cooked food actually some of the
minerals are cooked out and they can
cause the body to need some of its
minerals to simulate
my tongue gets dry with cooked foods
so
what happens with cooked foods is it's
like this right
you gotta realize where you're coming
from okay you can do like three six nine
and be all raw you can do the 369
advance and do all raw you can just go
that way you can use that protocol and
be all raw you can do the 28 day cleanse
medical medium new edition and go all
raw
right you can do that okay
there's a lot of people though they have
a difficulty difficult time going raw
and going raw
doesn't mean you're still going to get
better
like medical medium information like the
28 day cleanse or the 369 advance
they're raw
but they're raw designed in a specific
way to take somebody to where they need
to go take them to a finish line of
healing right but you can still heal
eating cooked
and you can still heal eating cooked
all the way
that's why the banana mono cleanses a
raw cleanse right in the medical medium
cleanse the heel book but there's also a
potato
mono cleanse which is your steaming
potatoes and you're actually able to go
all the way to on that level with
steamed potatoes
you don't lose minerals with cooked food
what happens is the reason why you feel
dried out with cooked food and you feel
dried out like that the reason why you
feel that way
is because
nerves that's a nerve thing so your
tongue can be dried out your mouth can
feel dried out you can feel dried out
overall when you're doing cooked
because the nervous system that means
there's a nervous system sensitivity
happening that's what that is
and
so so cooked food in general can
rub a certain way
on the tongue
and that's your vagus nerve all of that
your mouth your throat
it all depends on what's happening if
you have sensitive vagus nerve issues on
any level even if it's just sensitive
digestion sensitive vagus nerves what's
that whatever
cooked food can feel differently and it
all depends on what the cooked food is
too like what the cooked food is but
that's interesting i mean i'm glad
you're raw and you're doing raw that's
amazing
all raw is not the answer though meaning
any just raw is not the answer so i know
we're talking about processed foods and
everything else but it's interesting to
talk about this too
is that there's raw diets out there that
are high fat
and a high fat raw diet
still
can bring you
down on your knees sick and not healing
where you're like oh my god i'm all raw
i'm doing everything i can i found this
raw diet out there and i'm still sick
and i can't get better and i'm still
fatigued and i still have skin problems
and what is it
meanwhile you're tanking the nut butters
and you're taking all the oils and
you're taking the avocado too much and
you're taking more nut butters
and then you're doing more oil then
you're doing
more avocado and then you're doing
something else and yeah you're all raw
and then you're doing the olive oil hey
i got this great raw coconut oil and
you're doing all these oils and fats and
then you're just stuck still it happens
to so many people and then they get
stuck
you can heal doing cooked food you can
try that protocol and heal you and cook
food you can heal doing raw food as long
as you know what you're doing though it
all matters the details matter you can't
just be raw and that's the answer i
thought oats were inflammatory
oats are not
a food
that's like a healing food
but oats are not a herding food
so they're not a herding food oats
don't feed viruses
see that's important to know so oats
and viruses are inflammatory so that's
important to know right there
oats and millet are two
grains right there that medical medium
information says you can eat but it
doesn't mean you have to if you don't
want to do oats like in the protocols in
the book there's so many different
avenues like there's no there's no mono
oatmeal
diet in the medical medium book
for a reason
right
and oats aren't in the 369 cleanse right
meaning like the advanced cleanse
but oats are kind of like a filler do
they have nutrition in them yeah they
have nutrients in them okay but the key
thing about oats all right is oats don't
feed viruses viruses are why everybody's
inflamed
right and oats don't feed the viruses
so that gets them inflamed it's
important to know they're not an
inflammatory food
so they're not an inflammation producing
food
but gluten is make sure gluten-free oats
that's important to know there too
so let's start making this and we'll get
them in the oven and we'll talk more
about what's happening it's good to see
you guys it's an honor to be here so
what i'm gonna do is mash up two bananas
it's the first thing i'm gonna do
let's throw a couple of bananas in here
and
see that couple bananas
every time
somebody gets an epiphany right in the
healing movement say a doctor or
something they want to start a podcast
they want to write a book they want to
start teaching they want to start
lecturing about health foods or health
healthy living and all that they get
this epiphany where
they want to lose some weight
they want to do better things for others
they are in conventional medicine they
want to back down off of conventional
medicine a little bit and they want to
head to a place of like an awakening
happens
wow
fast food and greasy foods and fried
foods and processed foods that's the
problem all this time
that's what it is
or it's the lectins and oxalates in all
these foods
or it's bad foods like fast foods and
some other food issues too but they get
wrapped up into this whole thing like i
found the answer i got the light bulb i
got the answer
everybody's sick because they're eating
bad
do you see how it goes you guys
anybody jumping into the health scene
green
jumps in like
oh my god
i figured it out
all these years of just doing my normal
stuff going into medical school and out
of medical school eating what i wanted
drinking alcohol on the weekends all
these years i figured it out because i'm
starting to gain a little weight around
my waist and as a doctor i started
figuring it out you can't have processed
foods all those people are bad at the
fast food restaurant line you guys are
all eating fast foods that's the whole
thing and they have this epiphany this
awakening like oh they discovered
everything they discovered it
then they start telling their patients
shouldn't be eating fast foods and then
they want to write a book let's write a
book and make sure we talk about how all
these greasy foods are killing americans
or killing europeans or killing whoever
around the world right
and they think i'm mashing two bananas
in here because i'm making these oatmeal
cookies right now
and then they think they discovered the
holy grail
they actually discovered atlantis
the lost city of atlantis
they discovered it
they figured it out after all these
years everybody's sick because
they're just eating all this junk food
and fast food and processed food that's
why everybody's sick
we just we just figured it out
right
and
real i'm gonna put some cinnamon in here
too
okay a little bit of cinnamon in this
i'm gonna put a little bit of maple
syrup in here too if you guys don't mind
robin says what's the difference
between gluten-free oats regular ones
what makes oats gluten-free
processing is the big one
okay so processing is a really big one
the processing right the facility
i'm going to put a little maple syrup in
here facilities that are also churning
out wheat
germ
they're churning wheat germ out
they're churning
what else are they churning out wheat
germ
um
bagels
loaves of bread
loaves loaves of processed bread white
bread right they're churning all this
out
and then also they're going to run some
oats through the machine well we ran
oats through the machine after we just
ran all the those breadcrumbs those
white breadcrumbs to the machine and now
we're packaging up oats oh oats are
gluten free right
christina says won't oatmeal bananas and
maple syrup spike your insulin a lot
well that's
that's what people believe
so let's go into that you just you just
you just
set the pace for a good diabetic talk
for a couple of seconds including
hypoglycemia and other issues like that
blood sugar issues let's just throw some
raisins in here i'm gonna be spiking my
blood sugar i'm gonna be spiking my
blood sugar really bad right here
this is gonna throw me into major
diabetic like coma
or something
i'm gonna put a few raisins in here
that should be good i'm gonna put some
so let's go into that
sugar
doesn't create insulin resistance
carbohydrates does not create insulin
resistance it's fat so i'm looking for
the fat here where's the fat
where is it
fat are you in there
where are you
where's the oils
where's all the oils where's the fat
where's the olive oil
where's the coconut oil
where's the nut butter where's the nuts
where are you guys
how come you're not here
are you guys in here where are you
huh
hey wait
i can't find you
so all i'm seeing is oats raisins
bananas
and cinnamon and maple syrup
i'm not seeing any fats
this can't spike your insulin
this can't jack up your a1c
this doesn't create diabetes
okay
very important to know
what this does is this helps to fix
those problems because guess what's
missing out of here there's no oils
there's no nut butters there's no fats
there's no grease there's no lard
there's no crisco there's no nothing in
here
very important now
okay so i'm gonna go with a couple of
cups
see a couple cups of oats here
a little measurement
just one cup there
go with another cup
roughly
i think that might be good see what we
got
all right
this is important to know right here
okay you guys critical point
when you eat fat
which i call radical fats right
when you eat the nut butter i'm not
saying nut butters are bad for you i'm
not saying avocado is bad for you i'm
not saying healthy fats are bad for you
i'm just saying that when you have fat
even when it's chicken or meat or nut
butters or oils or anything like that
when you eat the fat it stops sugar from
entering your cells
it holds up the insulin the insulin just
gets all caught up in the bloodstream it
can't get sugar into your cells
it's the fat that's doing it it's not
the sugar
this is a really important time for some
of you guys
that have been brainwashed about the
whole sugar thing and the whole diabetic
thing in the whole in the whole you know
hypoglycemic thing and the whole
hypersonic hyperside
heart glycemic thing sorry it's
you just need to know this is like an
awakening moment right here because
wait a minute it's not the sugar what
are you saying like what are you even
talking about it's not the sugar
no it's not
it's not the sugar at all i'm going to
add a little bit more oatmeal to this
ice cream
jacks up that blood sugar
ice cream's the a1c nightmare ice cream
is the diabetic nightmare i don't care
if it's coconut ice cream i don't care
if it's vegan ice cream i don't care if
it's planet mars ice cream i don't care
if an alien ship
arrived from pluto
and dropped off
a new batch of ice cream for everybody
that ice cream is sugar and fat combined
and when that ice cream is sugar and fat
combined you got the diabetic nightmare
you got the blood sugar nightmare you
got the insulin resistance nightmare
and that's why everybody on the
processed foods eventually gets the a1c
and the diabetic nightmare and
everything else
that's why the processed food thing the
fast food the greasy fried food that's
why i was trying to tell you guys all
the genius doctors or genius health
professionals or genius health
influencers when they get that epiphany
in awakening and they're like i'm not
supposed to eat processed food anymore
oh dear lord i think i found the answer
everybody everybody it's processed food
now i'm gonna go hit the circuit because
i'm a genius now i'll come out my new
book here's why you shouldn't eat fast
foods and processed foods and junk foods
and what happens is because
yeah you eat that stuff you're gonna end
up a diabetic you eat that stuff you're
going to eventually have some weight
gain you eat that stuff and you're going
to get a heart attack
but that's not why everybody is sick
it's not why everybody's sick you guys
already hashimoto's neurological lime
since when has neurological lyme in a 12
year old yes a 12 year old neurological
lyme disease have anything to do with
eating 50 years of junk food and
processed food and fast food
it doesn't have anything to do with it
do you see how it goes that's why this
talk is important today all right so
i have these cookies ready i'm gonna
start making them
let's do this
i'm gonna move some of these bananas
over
right
so
i'm gonna make some of these cookies
i'm going to put them like this
now you can flatten them out a little
bit more if you want
you can
make them a little bigger if you want
you can make them smaller
i was in the mood for some cookies today
you know i was like you know what how
about if i make some cookies today
this is this is really
a great thing to help you guys with
because i know so many people this is a
treat you know it's a treat i know so
many people
are just they're they're like
they're slaves to
the junk food the healthy junk food
the healthy junk food out there and that
that's not what this is this isn't junk
food right
but they're they're trapped because all
of a sudden they'll give in to something
and they'll just be like okay i just
fell off the wagon right now i just did
it i'm i'm i'm off the wagon again let
me just have these cookies here
here's the problem there's all this fat
that's in all the treats out there
all that fat and all the treats is how
people are going to get in trouble
one way or another they're going to get
in trouble
and that's important to know
so i already have six cookies on the
tray if you guys can see
let's put some more cookies in here i
might be able to get nine cookies right
here
right
if you guys just got on here i'm gonna
be exclusively
live on rumble at six o'clock eastern
three o'clock pacific i hope you guys
join me it's not going to be about this
topic about processed foods fast foods
greasy foods fried foods
might have some zingers
you never know
okay i think we did it i think we're
gonna do nine good sized cookies here
is what we're gonna do
i'm just going to add a little bit of
this extra cookie mix to
some of these cookies
but not go too big because you go too
big then we're going to be in trouble
i think i made two really big cookies
pop this in the oven
so i'm just showing you guys the before
telegram what do you guys think
you guys subscribe to telegram on there
i do private audio messages with
everybody you guys i'm popping this in
the oven
let's get them cooking
so i got some cookies in there
exclusive exclusive on
telegram so exclusively i do these audio
messages on telegram so it's just really
cool it's really great been doing that
and then on rumble subscribe to rumble
because rumble is is a great
place for medical medium information i'm
doing some cool stuff on there doing
exclusive lives on rumble so be there
six o'clock eastern later
three o'clock pacific time
so
we got the cookies we're working on i'm
hoping they look like this i can't wait
to eat them i'm really excited
so when someone has als
right
is it because of processed foods
then
how can how come somebody else who had
processed foods all these years didn't
get als just curious
if someone has
alzheimer's
dementia
right is it because of the fast foods
and the greasy foods and the fried foods
they had all these years what about the
other person who didn't get alzheimer's
dementia
and they've been eating the fast foods
processed foods and greasy foods all
these years
what about that
what about the person right
who has crippling depression
suicidal thoughts they don't want to be
here anymore
they're suffering and agony
and they've been eating processed foods
and fast foods and greasy foods but what
about the other person who's been eating
fast food processed foods greasy foods
but they don't have the crippling
depression on a level
or that they're in that condition
so you know when this whole epiphany
happens to like a health professional
where they wake up one morning and
they're like whoa it's the processed
foods doing it
someone said which book are you are the
cookies from i just want to answer that
it's cleanse the heal suzanne cleans the
heel
amazon.com us 51 off
it costs more to print it it's a medical
textbook get it free at the library you
can get it free at the library
don't even have to do like honestly if
everybody just went to the library and
got it for free i would be happy because
i want people to have the book
so when we have this whole thing happen
in the world of health and i've watched
it for years
i've watched these awakenings happen in
health professionals for years
where they think they have now all the
answers so they start there
but it's way more complicated than that
it's way more in depth than that it's
way more
important to know what's really
happening there's so much more people
don't know
so why do we get that crippling
depression we get it because of toxic
heavy metals in the brain why do we get
that crippling als because we get toxic
heavy metals in the brain plus viruses
why do we get multiple sclerosis because
of epstein-barr virus
also people with multiple sclerosis are
high in mercury and epstein-barr right
we get these other problems because of
these reasons and yes fast foods
processed foods and and
and
junk foods are not helpful on any level
but it's not solely the problem and
let's go into that a little bit why can
someone eat all that junk for years and
then they get their heart attack
when they're 50 or 55 they get their
heart attack when they're 60
but then someone else
right
someone else
got sick with something else
what's going on there right when someone
didn't get sick with something else and
they have this heart attack later on
like how does that happen so let's cut
into it and let's go into it
right now
what you're going to see is neurological
problems on the rise more than ever
before in history it already is and has
been i've been talking about this for 35
years but we're at a place where
neurological problems are going to
dominate in such a way that no one can
even imagine
so it's not just depression anxiety and
ocd
and all that all the mental health
right
complications that people suffer from
but it's gonna be the fatigue the muscle
weakness the dizziness more than ever
before the vertigo the balance issues
right the tinnitus the burning skin the
jabbing jaw pain the neck pain the back
pain unexplainable back pain feet pain
right sleeping problems insomnia
restless leg syndrome it's going to be
all this times a million it's just going
to be all this times 10 million all this
times a billion is what it's going to be
and it's not because of a processed food
so what do we have to look out for or
worry about it's viruses
and bacteria
toxic heavy metals poisons right
so
i i saw the other day
right a friend of mine showed me
something and said look this this really
smart doctor guy who writes a book said
it's radiation in the airports we got to
look out for well that's medical medium
information i'm the only one that talked
about all the radiation in the airports
for years and years and years so okay
great and he's saying that's the problem
like that's not the problem
that's a contributor
that that's a trigger but that's not the
problem it's amazing how we can just we
it's what we attach ourselves to right
it's what our psyche kind of gravitate
gravitates to it's like if someone's
like totally gets jazzed up on whoa it's
the processed food whoa it's that then
that's got to be the answer it's a fast
food then that's what they're all into
right or whoa you're right there's
radiation in the airport that's what
it's got to be it's the radiation in the
airport and they get attached to that
they're like whoa that's it
but it's just more than this
you can take someone
who gets radiated
they breathe in all these fragrances and
candles and clones of perfumes
they get exposed to pesticides
insecticides
right
and they still
stay okay for a while they still stay
okay for a while and then you get
somebody else that breathes in a little
bit of pesticide breathes in some
scented candles freeze in a little bit
of mold somewhere and they go down
because you have to have the pathogens
internally
you have to have the pathogens
they have to be there
and that's why people got the
hashimoto's and hyperthyroidism and they
got the cysts and nodules on the thyroid
and that's why they got the fatigue and
that's why they got the cfs
and that's why they have the skin
disorders and the excellent psoriasis
you have to have the pathogen somewhere
that's advanced information you have to
have the viruses the epstein bars the h
the hsv1 hsb2 you got the shingles you
got to have the hhv6 cytomegalovirus you
have to have the pathogens and viruses
is what you need
can be hard said sounds like lime and
bartonella bartonel is not a lyme
problem barnell is what you've been told
a long time ago is is a cause of lyme
it's not neurological lyme is is viral
so that's
the viruses and maybe that's what you
were leading to
it's what you're alluding to with that
right barnell is not superbug barnella
doesn't create
doesn't create neurological symptoms
right burnell is a bacteria that doesn't
create bacteria doesn't create
neurological symptoms very important to
know i talk about that in the books like
if you go into the lyme section of
cleanse of heal you'll see that
so neurological problems are caused by
neurotoxins produced by viruses
and that's how it's done
barnella is not as strong as mrsa
but people can kick mrsa
right merce is a superbug
created by
um classified medical research and
science
deliberately put into hospitals
just so you know
mrs a super bug
and they can still kill mrsa off people
have a better recovery rate with mrsa
than bartonella
so you got all these people with
neurological lyme suffering
and they can't get rid of this
bartonella barnella dies instantly with
penicillin
with penicillin
i'm not talking about all these other
design crafted antibiotics
that they have to use for super bugs
barnella dies with penicillin never mind
doxy or anything else
and bartonel is not the cause of lyme
so that's important to know the cause of
lyme disease
is something that creates neurological
symptoms bacteria doesn't create
neurological symptoms
lisa says burnell is a virus
and mrsa is a bacteria
well
for
25 years they've been saying
bartonella's a bacteria so maybe they
flipped it
because they don't know what is what
anymore so but barnell is bacteria
borrelia's bacteria babies is a hybrid
in bacteria and merce is a bacteria
i don't know what else to tell you
and those bacteria aren't why people are
sick with neurological lyme or lyme
disease
that's why they've been antibiotic to
death for years and decades and decades
people lost their lives from antibiotics
because they were told it was bartonella
people's lives were destroyed and ruined
because of that
if you want to have some compassion for
people out there that lost their lives
from being antibiotic to death
for bartonella and babisia and borrelia
then that's one place to go because
that's where i go all the time because i
feel horrible for people who lost their
lives from that
i can't tell you how many people walk
through the door in my office and how
many lime doctors called me up at my
office throughout the last 35 years
and they learned the truth about what
caused neurological lyme and they're
like so what do we do i said we need
your lysine
you have to have your zinc
you have to have your antivirals you
have to have your licorice root
and all of a sudden the neurological
line you have to have your cat cat's
claw and all of a sudden the
neurological lyme patients we're all
getting better at these doctor's offices
and they're like oh my god this is
unbelievable because we've been
antibiotic doing the antibiotic thing
with our patients over and over and over
again because we keep on thinking they
have borrelia and bartonella
they don't
and if you want to learn more about that
just so you know
they never see bartonella
and they never see borrelia if you read
about lyme disease you'll learn how the
lyme labs work
they don't see bartonella so here you
are be like here you'll be like and
listen this is no disrespect i i've a
lot of respect for you for being here
talking about this this is a great topic
what people don't realize is at the lime
lab they never see bartonella they don't
see it did you know that
they don't see it under a microscope nor
do they see borrelia when you get your
blood sent to
the lab
they just test for an inflammatory
marker and they plug in the name
they put the name in
it's the biggest scam
ever in our history
probably one of the biggest scams in our
history pretty pretty incredible really
checking the cookies you guys
cookies aren't done yet
when you get your blood tested at a lyme
lab they're just doing an inflammatory
test
it's kind of like an a a
it's a c-reactive protein
okay very important to know
so and
that's the trick of the trade so the
lyme disease labs never see
they never see your bartonelli your
borrelia your your your lovisia they
never see any of that
that's what's sad about it it's been a
scam running for a long time and a lot
of people lost their lives over it now
but you know what's funny
and amazing now there's lime doctors now
using protocols using medical medium
protocols right but they're plugging in
the cats cloud they're lowering the
antibiotics and they're getting people
some results first time in history
because they're using medical bean
protocols i taught about this for years
i talked to dozens and dozens of lyme
doctors all through the east coast all
through the country
and i got the lyme doctors to test for
epstein-barr and what the lyme doctors
were doing they're like oh my god
this patient has epstein barr
anthony william was right
i think we're on to something eureka
we're onto something
why do you think
they talk about anybody with lyme
disease now that goes like public with
it that might be like a big public
figure or a celebrity and they talk
about their lyme disease why do you
think they say i have lyme disease and
epstein-barr
that's kind of funny
which you really have is epstein-barr
and that's what's causing your
neurological symptoms and what are those
neurological symptoms tingles and
numbness fatigue brain fog don't feel
good
yeah that's your ebv
that's your ebv
antibiotics ruined my gut
kristen i feel for you truly i've seen
antibiotics kill people
for years and years and years with lyme
disease
they get so weak and here's the thing
too okay they get so weak
and the sicker they get
they take more blood the sicker they get
they take more blood and that's how a
lyme disease patient dies
they die
from
getting blood tests
faster
and more vials and faster and more vials
and more in between and more in between
meaning
one week apart one week apart one week
apart two weeks apart one week apart
let's take 27 more vials let's take 30
vials let's take 40 vials let's take you
know let's take 50 vials right
and that's what they do
so they're just
taking blood let's give you more
antibiotics oh you don't feel good well
it's not the antibiotic that's that's
making you not feel good something else
is wrong we're going to keep on taking
more blood from you this is how tens of
thousands of lyme patients died in the
last 40 years it's from all the blood
taken
and the game
the chase for phantom bacteria
when really they were viral if they had
less blood drawn and they had a viral
protocol like in cleanse to heal
they would still be here now
and thank god enough people got to me in
my office throughout the years that
enough doctors talk to me to save enough
people with neurological life and that's
why you see the world of lyme disease
changed right now because the medical
medium work
that's why you see cats claw in the
protocols that's why you see them lower
the antibiotics
it's important to know
i'm gonna check out these cookies hold
on you guys
they're getting there
so
i just want to let everybody know
that on rumble six o'clock eastern three
o'clock pacific i'm gonna be exclusive
there talking about something different
a different topic
we're not gonna be talking about lyme
disease we're not gonna be talking about
processed foods but this is good stuff
we're talking about now i'm excited
so let's
go a little bit longer
have some more fun
where can we get tested for ebv
with a family physician you just ask
your doctor for an fc bar test
that's that's a great way to start
said nadine that's what you can do you
can actually start that way
you just ask for it
that's that's what you can do
family physician should be able to write
that one up
they can they can write that
prescription for that blood test up
okay have them test for past and present
infection so keep that in mind past and
present infection past infection means
you still have epstein-barr
so that'll give you the answer right
there
so test for past and present
infection that's important right there
in medical medium book one which is the
new addition now when that hit the scene
it broke the news about what
epstein-barr caused it causes all these
neurological symptoms it's not the fast
foods it's not the processed foods and
the junk foods
what about having lyme and ms
well if you read in the cleanse of heal
books you'll see that multiple sclerosis
is caused by epstein-barr and mercury
and you'll see that neurological lyme is
also viral too which sepsis and bar
a lot of people have one or two
varieties of epstein-barr they'll have a
shingles virus too
and they'll be high in mercury as well
mercury is hard to test for it because
with mercury it doesn't mean it's in
your bloodstream it's in the organs it
could be all in the organs so you can't
you can't get a good accurate test
through the blood because of that
when it's sitting inside organs it's
hard to actually get a test
so
basically it's like this if someone
didn't have a
pathogen they can eat all the fast food
they want all the junk food they want
all the processed food they want until
they get their heart attack
or their diabetes
or their hypertension into a heart
attack
important now if someone does it or a
stroke if someone doesn't have
if someone doesn't have the viruses in
them
they can spend a lifetime of processed
junk food they can be pulling up to the
fast food restaurant every day give me a
double bacon cheeseburger please
i'll take another pizza give me a bacon
double cheese dog give me a bunch of
onion rings give me some fries with with
bacon bits on top bacon give me more
bacon
and they can do that for year after year
after year until
they drop dead
until that artery gets clogged until
they have a heart attack and that
diabetes comes on
until they have
that
stroke
from big hunk of fat getting dislodged
and floating up to the brain the point
is if you don't have the pathogens you
can eat all you want bring it on bring
it in
and you can do it until you die
of a heart disease issue or something
else
if you don't have the pathogens
when you have the pathogens the game
changes
it completely changes you guys
that's when you get the hypothyroid
that's when you get the hyperthyroid
that's when you get the cancers that's
when you get the als that's when you get
the ms
that's when you get the ra that's when
you get the lupus that's when you get
the neurological lyme that's why a 12
year old can have neurological lyme
that's why a 12 year old can have ra
and fatigue think about that
children's rheumatoid arthritis
they didn't have 30 years of fast food
but they have ra
at 11 years old nine years old 14 years
old they have debilitating ra
and they don't have 50 years
of junk food in them
they have
you know other things going on
right
and they have colitis
right they can have debilitating colitis
leukemia they can have other things
they can be suffering with other
disorders they can have
eczema that's raging and debilitating
psoriasis
but they don't have 30 years of pulling
up to that fast food restaurant and
ordering all those bacon double cheese
dogs and burgers
in all those pizza fries or whatever the
heck they're giving out there and all
those buffalo chicken wings
they don't have that in their system
that's for the person who's not quite
viral who's not quite pathogenic who
maybe isn't pathogenic yet they don't
have enough bugs in them yet and they
can go and now they're 40 and now
they're gaining weight yes and they're
gaining weight and now they're heading
to a place because of the processed
foods and all the pizzas they're eating
and everything else they're eating and
the buffalo chicken wings and everything
else
now they're getting to the point where
boom they can have their heart attack
they can have their stroke they can have
their fat clogging up their arteries in
their heart and everything else and
guess what if they get a pathogen
they'll have that too
you'll have lupus and heart disease
you'll have multiple sclerosis and heart
disease this is important to know right
here you'll have neurological alignment
heart disease you'll have ra and heart
disease you'll have autoimmune and heart
disease right if you have pathogens and
your tank and the fast processed foods
in the greasy foods you can have your
diabetes heart problems and your
neurological symptoms from all the
pathogens do you see the details matter
and that's why
medicine is so off right now they can't
even differ in differentia they can't
even figure it out and be able to divide
any of that they don't know any of the
difference they're just like okay well
you have autoimmune it's genetic okay
what else do you have oh you have heart
disease okay maybe you should back down
on the processed foods that's pretty
much it
but they don't they don't know that whoa
you got hhv-6 you got shingles you got
epsine bar you've got sediment virus
you've got simplex one the fever blister
and it's causing all your jaw pain and
your neck pain and your head pain and
your eye your eye problems and your eye
pain
and they don't know that these things
are causing reproductive problems too
you can have endometriosis and still get
heart disease down the road you could
have pcos from viruses and still get
your heart attack later on too you could
have a combination
and
but all the
all the
people with big ideas in the health
movement i think they figured it all out
found the holy grail and they figured
they they found it all out the big
mystery they found atlantis
they think it was just
you're just eating all the wrong foods
and once you clean up your diet
you're gonna be all good that's not true
sometimes you gotta dig deep and you
gotta go for the gold because if you got
enough pathogens and you you could be
very young and you can clean up your
diet and it's not enough you can clean
up your diet as far as you want to go
as far as the parameters they give you
out there and it's not enough and then
you have to learn what you're really
doing and looking out for within that
diet to get better
that's why i see it all the time the
vegans in a plant-based people they go
plant-based and vegan they stay sick or
they get sick
and then they run back to animal protein
thinking they are missing nutrients you
know i just saw it recently someone was
showing me something and it was like
they're saying check this out check out
this influencer here they went vegan one
time in plant based and now they're
talking about how they were missing all
their nutrients
they went vegan and plant-based and they
were missing all their nutrients right
now so now they're back on animal
protein to make sure they get all their
nutrients they're eating cottage cheese
and they're having lots of yogurt
and bovine yogurt and cottage cheese and
they're having like raw cheese and
they're having eggs and they're having
salmon and they're having other fish
and now they're getting all the
nutrients they knew all the nutrients
they need because when they were vegan
and plant-based this influencer was
vegan and plant-based they weren't doing
good
it's like
whoa well i'm gonna feel really bad for
that person because they're gonna do it
real bad now
meanwhile
there's all these people eating animal
protein eating all the same thing and
they're sick out there i love how that
works it doesn't make any sense right
billions of people are eating animal
protein and a fraction of people are
they're plant-based right fraction of
people and think about how many people
are sick hospitals are filled with
people eating animal protein including
clean animal protein diets protein dyes
including healthier animal protein diets
right
meanwhile they'll have the same problems
that you know they'll have the same
problem
as the plant-based people right that are
sick too that happens plant-based vegan
person can be just as sick as an animal
protein person they can have both the
same sickness as hashimoto's
they can have thyroid problems they can
get told by their doctors their hormones
are off they can have all the same
problems everybody's worried about they
can have fatigue animal protein person
can have lots of fatigue and a
plant-based person can have lots of
fatigue
okay
i'm waiting for the cookies to kind of
get nice and toasty in here and they're
just about done i guess another couple
minutes we're almost there
we get lost and we run back and forth
you can still heal eating animal protein
and you can still heal eat being
plant-based okay
you could still heal being plant-based
right
anybody who's plant-based or vegan i
recommend staying plant-based but
learning how to do it anybody who wants
to be animal protein you know what you
can heal too
just got to learn how to do it
another thing too you could be on a
plant-based vegan diet and eat a lot of
junk food
definitely can eat a lot of junk food
you could do a vegan cheese
that vegan cheese is rough on the system
if you're trying to heal it's really
hard on the system if you're trying to
heal
it's just as bad as the regular cheese
in so many ways so keep that in mind
right
michelle l says if you take the wrong
b12
it won't absorb
and it's true the details matter
everything matters you can be a
plant-based vegan person and thinking
you're missing b12 somehow and take the
wrong b12 and not get better
the right b12 matters
you guys know i use the vimergy b12
that's the one i use and and i'm not
sponsored
but the stuff is the best it's a
vimergy.com if you want the best b12
since michelle
was talking about it
so
i think what happens is the minute you
get sick
somebody gets sick and they're a newbie
and they're not seasoned
all they need is to hear a doctor or
somebody say hey get off your bad foods
meaning get off the junk foods and the
processed foods and then everybody
thinks they're they got it all sewed up
but that's not reality
reality is it's so much deeper than that
the reason why we're sick is so much
deeper than that
and the details matter to how we can
heal and recover right
someone's dealing with low iron they're
having a low iron issue that's viral
because
epstein-barr eats iron i talked about
this for years so that means there's a
low low-grade viral infection low-grade
viral infection you'll hear that now
people say low-grade out there low grade
viral out there low grade viral
medical medium information for 35 years
is low grade viral infection you can
read medical medium book one and you'll
see it all through there low grade viral
infection but
the low grade viral infection
is the reason why people have low iron
because of a low-grade viral infection
so they have low iron
the more toxic heavy metal in them and
the low-grade viral infection the lower
the iron goes because epstein-barr feeds
off of iron
that's how it works so unless you get
rid of the epstein bar and work on
getting rid of the epsilon bar and
breaking it down and getting it out and
cleaning it up that's the key is
cleaning that ebv up and getting it out
your iron can come back up and come back
up i'm gonna get these cookies out you
guys
let's take a look at this
cookie deal here see what we got
we've got some cookies
make sure they don't slip off here
what i'm going to do is i'm going to i'm
going to slide this right on right on
here
like that
i was gonna move piggy but i didn't
these are really hot right now just so
you know
don't grab your cookies okay i'm just
moving them around a little bit
don't grab your cookies when they come
straight out of the oven like this you
guys in telegram can you see this
at all
i don't know if you guys can actually
see that on telegram
up there tick-tock you guys see that
right
rumble you guys see that
so these are them they're toasty brown
on top i'll show you a cookie
i'll show you a couple of cookies you
guys
tell graham you see that
goes on youtube
tick tock
rumble
facebook
now what's incredible about these
cookies i'm just going to tell you right
now
is there's no oil on these cookies
that's where we get in trouble
it's the oil and everything
it's the fat in everything that's where
you get in trouble so you're allowed to
eat a cookie
when the oil is not inch all drenched
inside of it in and out of it because
that's when we get in trouble it's all
the fats so keep that in mind so these
aren't insulin resistant creators
these are diabetic busters you know
these are the kind of this is the kind
of food the kind of meal is a fat free
meal which
gets rid of diabetes in people that's
how we get rid of diabetes in people
that's how we get rid of type 2 diabetes
is you lower the fats when you lower the
fats and you have meals that don't that
aren't drenched in fat then you can get
rid of the type 2 diabetes
right
okay
if you're really sick if you're dealing
with some kind of intestinal disorder
if you're dealing with some kind of
digestive problem read the book
and and see what's in here okay maybe
maybe oatmeal is not you know going to
be something that you want if you read
the book and learn okay this is just a
treat this is a great treat for people
so it's really it's a healthy one i'm
going to bite into a cookie in a second
too
looks delicious right raffi
you guys
i'm heading over to
rumble at six o'clock eastern three
o'clock pacific
i'm gonna do an exclusive live i'm going
to talk about a different topic i hope
you guys all come on in there make you
make sure you subscribe on there too
um meet me over there later that would
be awesome so we'll be on rumble later
on
but in a little while i'm going to turn
on instagram telegram and tick tock
we're gonna make cookies again
we'll talk about some other stuff maybe
some other questions will come up
all right so i'll see you guys soon
looking forward to it