this that's what i'm gonna make but not
just pee hummus i'm gonna do apple sauce
not just applesauce i'm gonna do cashew
nut butter
cashew nut milk and i'm gonna do
something else celery cilantro juice
and i'm gonna make a mango sorbet is
there anything else i can do this is
what else would anybody like it would
you like a bowl of mango sorbet would
you like a pea hummus would you like a
cashew milk i am gonna be making it so
this is gonna be the uh hey it's like a
bar right or food bar
all kinds of cool stuff elixirs whatever
so look we're here
we're live right now it's the mm 1500
just showing you how it works doing some
cool stuff i'm excited to see you guys
coming on that's great christy hey
ichoda came on everybody's coming on
here austin good to see you awesome
centaurus healing good to see you
everybody's coming on here yvonne
awesome so you guys let's get started
let's figure this out this is great
so
what's incredible about this is i call
this a medical machine right medical
device because it's creating things that
move us forward right so not only does
it juice the celery which is incredible
all on its own
right now it does that and then we're
going to be doing other things but it
makes really healthy food which kind of
keeps keeps you inspired to move forward
with your health and all that so i love
these they're like medical devices
medical machines it's the mm 1500 it's
80 off you get the free
cleanse the heel book
with it so it's on sale right now
meganjuicers.com check out the link in
the profile link in the description the
mm1500 you get the free cleanse to heal
book with it so let's start making some
cool stuff you guys good to see
everybody
all right let's go i'm gonna fire this
thing
up yeah i know
let's go
we're going to make to start with
some
mango sorbet so that's the first thing
we're going to do good to see you guys
on tick tock good to see you guys on
telegram we're live on telegram too
we're live on facebook rumble youtube
incredible
so check this out right
i'm gonna take some frozen mango right
here so you're gonna make some mango
sorbet some mango ice cream
is what we're gonna do so i'm excited so
let's get some mango in here
that's the plan
i'm gonna fire this up
see if we can see this you guys
drop some in
there we go
so this is frozen mango you can just buy
frozen mango in the store
and you got yourself some frozen ice
cream this is extra frozen right here so
icy cold i'll tell you
so if you can take a look at this can
you guys see a close-up on this as it's
coming out which is really cool
check that out and tick tock you guys
this this actually looks really cool
right now
frosted at all so this is just coming
out straight from the freezer
icy icy cold
sometimes you might want to give it like
10 minutes
out of the freezer
these like little rocks coming out
but there you go you got your sorbet
right here you got your mango ice cream
coming out
[Music]
there we go
you know i love doing things live
so i'm just dropping some
frozen mango down in here
there you go getting your frozen mango
look at that
perfect
amazing
so
what happens when you do frozen fruit at
all you have to keep in mind that you
want to defrost it a little bit i didn't
do that i just pulled it out of the
freezer
so it is like ice
cubes i'm making some incredible mango
sorbet right there
amazing
so there we go we got the mango sorbet
and
this is gonna give you a brain freeze
i'm just gonna warn you if you have this
this stuff is is cold but
amazing
so that's mango ice cream right there
you can make any kind of ice cream with
it any kind of sorbet any kind of frozen
fruit sorbet right
i'll show you guys the mm 1500
and you can you can smooth it out like
that
80 off right now megajuicers.com check
out the link in description best way to
get get that there but
you can um but you want to let it thaw a
little bit more
before you make your ice cream that's
the goal right there you want to make it
you gotta thought a little bit i pulled
it right out of the freezer
freezer's right over here i didn't even
give it a second
so let's make some apple sauce that's
the next thing we're gonna do okay we're
gonna move the sorbet over
[Laughter]
all right
laughing about a couple of things you
guys one is we're so centered right now
it's ridiculous
i guess i'm just such a threat to be
making applesauce
what a threat
so i gotta censor me on making making
applesauce on facebook they gotta censor
me on facebook actually that's where
they're censoring me right now
i guess my applesauce making is a little
too uh
a scary i guess or something or
threatening in the health world all
right let's make some applesauce that's
next just a little bowl for the
applesauce right here
and that's why i'm laughing
right
harmful to the world as i'm making
applesauce and mango sorbet
so this is steamed apples right here
this is themed apple so i'm gonna put
this in here okay
you put your apple pieces in here
so
[Music]
this is the applesauce we're making
the apples are steamed
okay
you guys the mm 1500 is 80 off right now
you get a free cleans a heel book right
all right so just made some apple sauce
there we go
all right
so i don't know if you could see this
you guys on tick tock see that i made
some killer applesauce right there with
this machine
which is great you guys can rumble
right and the five people that are on
facebook right now you guys see this
because they know music because facebook
censored me today telegram can you see
this this is the apple sauce right here
so already we've done the sorbet we've
done the mango store base he just came
on here and made mango ice cream
basically mango sorbet which is really
incredible right so i'm excited about
this in fact
i would love some
amazing incredible
add some applesauce right here so let's
move on let's make some more things
so i got my applesauce
i'm just not going to have pork chops
with it okay so i'm not going to make
pork chops
that's not a wise thing to do is to have
pork chops and applesauce you don't want
to put those that's a terrible
combination you won't have the
applesauce you don't want to have the
pork chops
all right
unless you want a heart attack if you
want a heart attack have the pork
it's like if we want a heart attack we
have the pork and then we can get a
heart attack down the road
if you don't want a heart attack stay
away from the pork
kathy why does some produce smell like
perfume lately
kathy
because everybody's wearing perfume
and they're going and they're in the
store and they go in there fresh in the
morning and they got their perfume all
over them and they're touching
everything and they're wiping perfume on
everything that's why including people
who work in the grocery store they're
loaded with perfume
every now and then i get a checkout
person right check out persons loaded
with perfume and they get perfume on
every single item so that by time you
got your bags and you go in your car you
literally smell perfume and that's
that's what it is and that's how bad
it's been getting out there yeah it's
like okay that's what i want i want to
smell your perfume all over my food
so great mmm this food's so good
perfume perfect perfume pesticides and
fungicides and perfume and dangerous
chemicals that's what i want i want
perfume in my food all right
you gotta stop fooling around you guys
this is the mm-1500
i was asked to do more than just the
celery juice thing people were like well
what about nut milks what about nut
butters what about other things what
about this and that was like okay all
right let's see something santara's
healing said the worst right isn't the
perfume stuff the worst
here's the funny thing they're making
air fresheners now that activate
when you
touch them
so that they smell for centuries like
they smell forever they make air
fresheners now and they even make
perfumes that last longer it's like dude
you don't think your perfume is lasting
long anyway
i mean my great-grandmother had a
perfume it's still in her old house and
she's been gone for a decade like for a
decade
and she was like you know 102 and boom
and
whatever it's like the perfume's still
there the perfume's still there
[Music]
all
right
it doesn't go away
so but they're making them longer
lasting all right so check this out
check the link is in the bio the link
link is in the uh description it's the
mm-1500
right and you guys on tick tock it's the
mm 1500 it's 80 off i'm not gonna try
not to fool around too much but we can
talk about all kinds of fun stuff like
perfumes colognes how toxic they are and
air fresheners and all that i love
talking about fragrances and how
dangerous they are anyway you get a free
cleanse to heal book now this isn't just
a book it's not like this isn't just a
business card because a lot of books out
there they're just business cards for
authors that's what they are so they can
put something out and whatever but this
is a medical textbook so this has saved
lives around the world so if you guys
want to know on tick tock this will save
lives around the world neurological
symptoms so i just want to give you the
rundown on this book you get this book
free with the mm 1500 right
right now so check this out this book
has over 200 symptoms and conditions
about how we got sick why we're sick
cleanses to heal this is an incredible
machine along with the book by the way
so
this is about cleanses on how to heal
people with gastroparesis heal their
guts with this book people with all
kinds of conditions multiple sclerosis
all kinds of lupus lyme disease heal
with this book there's protocol
supplements and dosages in this book
you just need to know that this book is
known to be a life-saving guide right
now out there it has a history to it
this isn't just a brand new book and it
was a test run to see if someone would
get better
this book has been healing people
worldwide now millions of copies of this
book has have sold around the world
and you get this book with the machine
free or if you just want to go to
amazon.com 51 off and get the book
right now or go to the library and try
to find the book but the point is the
book comes free with the mm-1500
but if you want to know anything about
this book
eczema psoriasis and lupus and
fibromyalgia and thyroid and thyroid
problems and symptoms conditions vagus
nerve issues all this stuff
people healed their neurological
problems with this book and it's known
that you do that so i'm making pea
hummus i just made applesauce i made
mango sorbet with the machine i'm just
showing you guys what's going on you get
the free book it's 80 off the machine
let's make the p hummus next
let's get into it we're going to make
cashew butter cashew milk this is just
so fun today okay i'm excited
and you guys know i work with omega on
this juicer
so
all right let's do it
let's go and do it this is fun let's
have some fun
so the next thing we're going to make
next is going to be some celery juice
and some cilantro some celery cilantro
juice
all right so it's good to see you guys
on tik tok we're having some fun stick
around this is gonna be you know a great
day and we're having some we're having a
good time we're gonna make a whole bunch
of different things with this machine i
can't wait to show you
check out cleansing hue when you can
comes free free book with the machine 80
off plus the free book if you just want
the book check it out all right let's go
all right
so we're gonna make some celery juice is
what we're gonna do
celery cilantro juice fancy that
celery cilantro juice that's what we're
making right now
so let's run a little bit of cilantro in
here
this is cool i'm pumped up about this
right
yeah you go to the store and perfumes on
everything now
because you know someone who wears
perfume thinks that everybody should be
wearing their perfume
so what i'm doing is i'm running
cilantro through here it's gorgeous
cilantro
wow
right
what a leafy green this is an herb okay
you're witnessing herbal medicine being
made right now you're witnessing herbal
medicine being made right now okay
i'm running cilantro through this
machine
i'm gonna run some celery through this
machine too
that's the pulp right there okay
that's the cilantro pulp
that's a cilantro pulp right there
coming out look at this comes out like
like a dry rope you see it comes out
like a dry rope
look at
that okay
this is the celery end cap i have right
here
so this is the celery end cap i'm gonna
put a little more cilantro in there
all right
put another celery stick in there
making celery cilantro juice
good to see you guys
so we're doing
making a little bit of cilantro
celery juice so let's do this now
this is a leafy green but it's an herb
celery is an herb what you're witnessing
right now is herbal medicine
so you're witnessing herbal medicine
right here
that's what this is so you have to keep
that in mind
when you're doing this you're making
herbal medicine
when you're combining now here's how it
works celery juice is best on its own
for celery to do what it does right
so we're making instead of different
kind of herbal juice we're doing a
cilantro juice and we're adding
celery as a carrier
that's what we're doing
so we're making a cilantro juice
but adding celery as a carrier
we're doing a different kind of herbal
medicine technique with this juicer this
is what we're doing
right
adding a little bit of a lot of cilantro
we're making a very strong
pretty interesting
there we go
we have very wet cilantro
okay
all right so here we go
so we have a really really potent
very potent juice right here okay you're
looking at a cilantro
celery juice now the pulp in in the mmm
is much drier than other juicers out
there and the reason why this rope is
dryer is because it has that end cap on
it that that you know saves us money
because you get to squeeze so much juice
out there so this is the mm-1500
check it out link is in the description
you guys link is in the profile so
that's the that's the rope right here
and
it's drier
than other juicers
that pulp is nice and dry and that's the
whole point it's not soaking wet down
here where you have juice in your pulp
dish right you know that's the problem
because what happens is in other juicers
when you take the pulp out i want to
show you this in other juicers you see
juice at the bottom right you don't see
juice at the bottom see i took the pulp
out you're not looking at juice see i'm
not pouring juice that's just pulp fiber
there i'm not pouring juice out of my
container and see what happens is with
the other juicers out there you end up
pouring juice
out of your your pulp container you see
that and i'm trying to show you guys in
the close-up you guys on tick tock and
telegram you might not be able to see as
good right so that's the difference so
what i love about the mm
and of course the 900 you're not doing
that
all right so we have a really potent
juice on our hands right now
so
i'm going to grab this jar
going to strain it
right here
now this juicer comes with a strainer i
just forgot to put it in
it comes with a little strainer
i forgot to put that strainer right
there
so i'm just showing this juice really
quick because
we're trying to buzz through this
there's so much to make and so much to
do you guys
so that is one potent juice right there
that's a cilantro juice with celery as a
carrier
that's herbal medicine right there
that's why i call these machines
medicine makers these are medical
devices medicine makers medicine
machines
right there
yeah you're indestructible and
you're young
maybe you don't need herbal medicine yet
but everybody gets sick
everybody gets sick that's just the way
it works okay let's move this over
okay
check out the medical medium newsletter
you guys i got exclusive videos on the
newsletter that i send out once a week
i'm doing the root canal video i'm
sending that root canal video out to you
tomorrow
so sunday i'm sending that root canal
video out make sure you get on my
newsletter it's in the link is in the
description and the link is in the
profile for the newsletter
and um
yeah tick tock snapchat so check this
out on tick tock i'm doing different
videos too on tick tock now i was just
doing a vegas nerve one that i did the
other day
snapchat i'm doing exclusive videos for
snapchat
telegram exclusive messages for you guys
so try to be in you know
connect it to all the other platforms if
you can so you can catch the other
material
i'm doing
audio messages on telegram right
exclusive audio messages on telegram on
tick tock i'm doing these killer videos
i talked about the vagus nerve right the
different nerve problems
and yeah
snapchat doing like exclusive videos
there
okay you guys doing the next one
i got a lot of videos coming out i got a
lot of informational videos on symptoms
conditions and diseases coming out
like for real
a lot of them for real
i am not kidding
at all making a pea hummus now which is
fun i really love p hummus you guys it's
it's so much easier on the system if
you're somebody with some kind of gastro
pro you have gastric problems you've got
intestinal tract problems maybe you're
somebody with all kinds of issues with
um intestinal issues inflammation maybe
you got celiac crohn's colitis ibs
whatever is happening there or maybe you
just have cramps and gastritis and
problems the pea hummus is a much easier
food than bean hummus
so pea hummus is easier on the system
than bean hummus easier in the system
than chickpeas and garbanzo beans
and black beans that's hard for a lot of
people and they have gastric distress
and all kinds of gastric problems so i'm
going to make a pea hummus which is
really awesome so let's get into it now
lorraine so much is going on i know
totally lorraine l
all right
we got some steam peas over here
hold on
we are trying to
we are trying to find what we need here
here we are
all right
so
there we go
we're gonna run some peas through here
so right now we're making a pea hummus
and then we're going to spice it up this
is going to be fun
and we're going to grab a spoon
all right
thank god i'm a mind reader
we have some pee hummus happening let's
get a close-up on this too
we can
there we go
so what we're making is hummus right now
you guys so check this out
yeah
we are
making a pea hummus as we speak right
now
yeah i think i'm thinking
[Music]
all right
this is really cool we're making it
we're going to spice this thing up
so easier it's so much easier on the
system than a bean hummus for so many
people
[Applause]
right let's drop the rest of these peas
in here
[Music]
it's also incredible for baby food
all right
let's get this going
guys it's 80 off right now it's the
mm-1500
[Music]
facebook censored us today
they're upset they think my p hummus is
going to like cause a problem
psycho just psycho
all right
let's go
you guys we have the pea hummus right
now let me get it in a bowl
we're gonna get it in a bowl over here
and we're gonna mix it
up so what i'm going to do is dump this
in here so take a look right there okay
now we're going to add some spices you
can put what spices you want in your pea
hummus i'm going to put some garlic in
here
this way everybody thinks i smell really
bad
from garlic breath really bad garlic
breath
if you eat garlic in the household make
sure you like somehow sneak some garlic
in the other people's foods
so that they won't know that you smell
like garlic really bad they won't know
it because they are smelling their own
garlic
from their own breath so then they can't
smell it off of you so you actually have
to kind of like slip garlic in anybody's
food in everybody's food so that
everybody has garlic in their system
then they won't tell they can't tell i
just put some cumin in there
just like i would at a hummus this is
the m1500
we're making nut milks we're making
sorbet i got mango ice cream right here
made applesauce we're making herbal
medicine which is cilantro celery juice
which is so cool got some paprika here
and maybe even some hot pepper too let
me drop a little bit of that
nice
let's get a lemon in here as well
right
we got a lemon right here
[Music]
that's what you have to do you got to
get garlic in everybody in the house so
that no one thinks it's you
when you actually smell like garlic
and everybody's upset
we're putting a little lemon in here
right
now we're going to mix up that hummus
right here and we're going to get this
in a nice bowl this is going to look
amazing that's cayenne pepper
that's cayenne pepper in there you can
put a little bit of salt in there if you
want if you really wanted to
just want to show you something you guys
i'm going to set up this really cool
plate right now okay so i'm going to put
it in here
this place is getting crazy
let's go
so i'm going to put the pea hummus
oh
yeah we're going to get this in the
check it out
you guys on tick tock i hope you can see
this
you guys
a rumor went around that i'm like the
fruit and vegetable guy uh
i only discovered what caused multiple
sclerosis which was the i've seen bar
virus and published it before science
researched it
and not just the fruits and vegetables
guy not to mention you could say i'm the
wild foods guy and the leafy green guy
and the fruit guy i guess but not the
fruits and vegetable guy
all right
i don't know if i'm the fruit and
vegetable guy when there's over 200
symptoms and conditions including what
herbs and supplements to take in the
right dosages for the symptoms and
conditions with millions of copies sold
with these books around the world so
people are healing including the heavy
metal detox
smoothie and heavy metal detox cleanse
the mono cleanse and everything else so
when that rumor goes around oh he's just
for fruit and vegetable guy okay and i
guess
i guess that's just you know not totally
accurate there all right check this out
you guys
do i look like the fruit vegetable guy
now yeah maybe
yeah i am the fruit and vegetable guy
man
yeah at the same time i'm micro dosing
and doing all kinds of yeah
uh-huh you pass me that joint
okay
so anyway
and you guys know i'm against smoking
weed i don't believe it's a good thing
for your brain so i don't do it and
never did
okay but if you do it i still support
you and make no judgment at all in fact
i want to help you i want to help you
get good stuff in you so you can heal
and heal your brain all right look you
guys that's the pea hummus right there
it's incredible and if you really want
to use crackers
you can do crackers of some kind if you
really want right
but check this out that's the pea hummus
i made with this machine
right and there's the crudite you got
the peas you got the carrots you can dip
the red bell pepper orange bell pepper
in there you can put the radishes in
there too that's something you can do
too i mean this is just incredible
this is better for you easier
on your system than the bean hummuses
so much easier right i'm going to try a
little bit of this
hey man did somebody sneak something in
there man
oh my god
i think i'm getting like
who puts who spiked this oh my god man
dude somebody spiked this
um now i got the munchies
i got the munchies now
yeah
that's really good all right listen
you guys
that's the bee hummus let's move along
i can't be fooling around all day
give me a run down if you just got here
all right
this is the mm 1500 it's on sale 80 off
you get the free medical textbook right
here
all right cleanse the heel incredible
book
this is not a book
about watermelon
this is a book
with several cleanses cleanses in it
this is a book with supplements dosages
protocols for diseases and symptoms this
is a book with incredible information on
how to heal it's got the heavy metal
detox cleanse in it
you learn the causes of over 200
symptoms and conditions you could learn
what's wrong with you
this goes free with this free
all right we just made mango sorbet
earlier
tick tock check it out telegram check it
out mango sorbet
all right
okay
and you guys on rumble mango sorbet
right
youtube mango sorbet
we got
the applesauce we made earlier
with this machine incredible check that
out
i mean
your own applesauce
and we got the juice too
the herb
the herbs
it's this kind of herb right here
that you want
to heal with
it's the cilantro celery juice right
celery as the carrier which is an herb
and then lots of cilantro
okay so that's it and you that's a
celery cilantro juice potent herbal
tonic right there okay
all right
we're moving on
making cashew milk you guys let's do it
cashew milk's next
i'm excited about this
guess what's in guess what is in
people's cashew milk
carrageenan msg natural flavors msg
citric acid total poison
that's what's in nut milks
it's actually garbage it's msg and
poison is in everybody's nut milk when
you go and you buy a nut milk
it's toxic they throw toxic stuff in
there and they expect everybody to buy
it and drink it and everybody buys it
and drinks it
so we're gonna do cashew milk let's go
and do this now so i got some cashews
these are soaked
overnight
they're not sprouted they're just soaked
overnight and then you drain the water
that's what you do you drain the water
they're soaked overnight and then you
drain the water
right
is everybody mad at me now are all the
potheads mad at me
listen
it's okay i'm not upset or anything like
i'm not saying anything bad i'm
i'm just fooling around making a joke
that's all so i'm doing is i'm making
cashew milk right now
my best friend's a pod head
he's still sitting on the couch after 20
years his wife left him
doesn't mean he's not the coolest guy
doesn't mean he isn't a good friend
wife left him she said she couldn't take
anymore he wouldn't even take out the
garbage
he was just smoking weed all day on the
couch
playing on his phone
so she walked out on him
he's a great guy i love him
i told him that that would happen
i knew him since i was a kid and i told
him it would happen if he didn't quit
and he just wouldn't quit smoking dope
on his couch just every day she would
come home from work and she would say
did you work today and he said yeah he
had a few things in the works like he
was and that's what he always said he
had a few ideas he was working on stuff
all right so what we're so check this
out you guys
so
what we're doing now is we're making
cashew milk right now okay
that's what we're doing
we're making cashew milk
all right
okay
all right so i'm going to drop these
for making cashew milk
all right so i got the cashews right
here
all right
[Music]
so i'm doing is dropping these cashews
in here
yes anyway
i called my friend the other day
i said what are you doing he says he was
he said he was wondering if i was hiring
i said
dude i can't have you work for medical
medium you like you don't even have
socks on right now
did you do your laundry it's like yeah i
did my laundry
i said we work our asses off dude we
work our asses off at medical meetings
we do 20-hour days
i said we we don't take vacations
we kill ourselves so p we make sure
people get information the chronicle
gets information
all right
sorry about the coffee talk you guys
let's just get this done let's get this
going on so i'm making some nut milk
right now i'm making cashew milk as we
speak
okay and
what i love about nut milks
when they're homemade is you don't have
the poison in there that's what's
incredible you don't have the poison in
there it's the poison it's that
carrageenan it's that msg it's the
natural flavor it's just like okay i'll
take the store-bought nut milk here
what's in this thing i don't know what
carrageenan is it's msg right msg builds
up in our brain it starts to build
deposits in our brain that's what msg
does and then we short circuit later on
and when you get an mri when you're 50
60 years old and the doctor says we
don't know what we see we see something
in your brain and that's an msg deposit
because it builds up inside the brain
and it stays there forever so
in when it comes down to nut milks every
time i'm in the store i'm just looking
you know i try to wear a disguise
i wear that doctor's disguise with the
gray hair and all that you know you know
and i take dr nesbitt with me and i go
into the store and i kind of
right wear the scientific jacket and i
kind of
so no one recognizes me you know
all right so we got the nut milk right
here let's get a glass of nut milk
the thing is there's look there's people
that love medical medium
there's people that hate medical medium
it's the most
diverse right it's either you i hear it
all the time you either love medical
medium stuff or you either hate magical
medium stuff and then when you ask
somebody why you hate medical medium the
stuff they say has nothing to do with
medical medium just mixing this up here
there we go
so if i'm out i gotta look out and make
sure i run into someone who actually
hates my medium
all right you guys it's like why do you
hate medical means because that many
people healed around the world that
couldn't
okay so that's a nut milk that's cashew
milk right there which is incredible so
there it is
that's the cashew milk so i'm excited
about that right there
okay
next on the list is the nut butter we're
making nut butter you guys
eighty dollars off right here this is
the mmm fifteen hundred eighty dollars
off comes free with the book check link
is in the description all right
it's a juicer but it does a whole bunch
of other stuff that's what we're doing
but we're also trying to have some fun
we're going to make some cashew butter
next
let's do it
cashew butter
all right
guys making cashew butter
so these are just lightly rinsed they're
not soaked when you make your nut
butters don't soak them
don't soak your nuts when you're making
your nut butters
okay
so i'm trying to keep consistency
dropping them in
so i can get these beautiful
see those beautiful pieces of nut butter
there now listen this is critical to
know
nut butters in the store no matter how
organic or healthy they are they add oil
oil that's not even from the nuts
they're using it could be the same type
of like nut oil but it's not even from
the nuts that they use it's like you
have a nut oil from a different part of
the planet some cheap nut oil and then
you have the nuts that you use and then
they mix it it's almost like it's it's
kind of almost like dark
when you think about it it's not a great
practice so what i like doing is real
nut butters are not supposed to be
filled with oil and grease
this is really important to know i'm
just being honest here about how it
works in the industry the only problem
is if i make fun or not make fun if i
point out
problems in the nut butter industry
then i'll have more
people in the industry that hate on
medical medium what's interesting it's
is what happens is when you point all
the stuff out
people like to protect their interests
and everything and then they just like
send out the dogs man
they send out the dogs i can't tell you
how
much crap i have to deal with
do you write on the package which oil
they add do they write in the package no
they don't
they don't have to
food in food and drug administration
whatever all the different they don't
have to
okay so that's that's the cashew butter
right here so let me just show you right
here
that's the cashew butter it comes out
and these these beautiful like cheese
sticks right
so
i'm just trying to say to you guys which
is really important that even if they
add cashew oil it's not even the same
oil from the cashews they used so even
if a nut butter company says we use the
finest cashews sourced on the planet
like we use the finest cashews there
ever was on the planet in our homemade
farms cashew butter and they have a cute
little picture on their cashew thing and
you're in the store you're in whole
foods or somewhere and you buy it
just so you know the cashew oil that
they put in there is not the cashews
they use they used a cheaper oil
somewhere else that was on another place
that they bought bulk and they mixed it
in that's why you get all that oil in
your nut butters so you have all that
oil in there that's just it's like
some crooked going down so
and i'm not trying
i'm sure i'm going to get now you know
going to get more heat
but
it's like you either protect the
chronically ill or you protect yourself
protect a chronic allele or protect
yourself what i notice people do out
there in the health industry all the
gurus they protect themselves they don't
give up about the chronic leel
all the people in all the gurus you see
i could name them
it's like doctor
all these guys they don't give up
about anybody
they don't they care about their bank
accounts and their popularity and their
advertisements
that's all they give up about
and then
when it comes down to like so with
medical medium if anybody's new here if
you want to sum up medical medium in
just one sentence
if you want to i don't know if we can
but if you wanted to
he cares about the chronically ill and
doesn't care about himself
unfortunately i guess maybe that's
really bad that's bad
it's like
the plumber's toilet doesn't work
but the plumber makes sure that
everybody else's toilet works but the
plumber's toilet doesn't work so the
plumber's wife has a clogged up toilet
right
well
i don't know or whatever it's like
medical medium doesn't care about
you know himself
but he cares about everybody else
doesn't care if he sleeps but he wants
to make sure everybody else is sleeping
doesn't care if he gets whatever but
whatever i don't know trying to sum it
up you can't sum it up okay back to the
nut butter
by the way if you guys just got on here
this is the mm-1500
it's on sale
we're gonna do we're gonna put the nut
butter right here in the jar and you
keep it in the fridge and you store it
all right so we're gonna put the nut
butter squares in here right protect
them right and you can press them down
in the jar that's the whole point you
can press them down in the jar so you
can actually put them down in the jar
and it is a nut butter in there take a
look okay
it's just that you guys are witnessing
something no one ever knew
you're witnessing
how much bs is happening out there in
the markets
right
your nut butter is never supposed to
have
a half a gallon of oil in it
your peanut butter is never supposed to
have that that's cheap oil thrown in
your nut butter
do you know why
so the nut butter companies can save
bunny and they don't have to use a lot
of nuts
that's how it's done
see so i'm actually showing you guys
real nut butter
and i'm going to get a lot of crap for
it i could feel it coming
whether anybody likes it or not
the voice i hear lets me know
now it's a nut butter people
it was the ionizer people the alkaline
ionizer water machine people when i told
the truth about all that metal particle
that comes off those metal plates and
the ionizers
i'm going to tell you right now if
you're doing the alkaline eye natural
water machines i don't care what brand
stop doing it
that would that's what i would do i
would stop doing it that stuff will make
you psycho down the road you will lose
your mind your mind will start falling
apart
that you will go crazy you will be
literally
like you will lose your mind
down the road
from that water from that broken water
and the stuff that comes off those
plates
but you know i get crap for it
fragrance industry they give me crap
all right
enough woe is me
we are now
that's your nut butter right there
in your jar that's your nut butter right
there okay that's your nut butter and
you're noticing something right
what you're noticing is where's all the
oil where's all the oil you can pour out
where is it where'd all the oil go you
guys
and you can do any kind of nut nuts you
want in this machine to make nut butter
where's all the oil you're pouring out
and that's mixed in
talking about rip off rip off and then
use cheap oil
and it could be the same oil it could be
peanut oil but guess what peanuts from a
real cheap source
from a whole other different place i had
it all in
whatever
all right
we got the cashew milk we got the cashew
butter
we
got the mango ice cream
and i'm in the mood to have some
got the mango sorbet
man you do too much of that you get a
brain freeze
but you get a brain freeze from that
that's freezing cold
and then you got
the apple sauce right here
right just don't do the pork chops
unless you want a heart attack
i still run into people that don't know
pork will eventually give them a heart
attack down the road they're like why
would it give me a heart attack
i was like yeah it's it's gonna give you
one down the road
maybe when you're 80
whatever
so there's the juice right there and
then there's a hummus let's get the
hummus out
well that's right the hummus has spiked
dude
i do
what did you put in this hummus
hmm
what
no no i was
what does 111 mean
1-1-1 dude did you know that i saw one
one on the clock this morning
i was still up
and i looked at the clock
right
dude
and the clock said one one one
so i called my friend summer
i called her up i said summer
dude
summer
what does it mean when i see one one one
on the clock
and then
uh-huh
and she said
dude it means a lot
like if you're seeing one one one
everywhere
but i also saw eleven eleven
and when i saw 11 11
isn't it just that everybody's looking
to see the number one one one so that
when they see it oh my god
no one's seeing one four one knowing no
one's seeing one
what if they see like 131
and then they convince themselves that
131 is a special number you know when
you see 131
you're like dude 131
131 man oh my god dude that's like
spiritual there's some spiritual
going away who puts so much thc in this
freaking pianist man
is there mushrooms in this
oh what is this
all right
and that's the p hummus
that's the pea hummus
um
777 that's a number to look out for
right there
that's a number to look out for those
are the numbers you want to look out you
want to look out for all the sixes and
you want to look out for all the sevens
because all the sixes and the sevens
they're at war with each other they're
at war with each other it's a spiritual
war i've always been saying that and now
people are saying it now
they don't say medical medium said about
it
anyway there's a spiritual war going on
right around us okay and above us
right
so
yeah there's darkness trying to stomp
out the light
and ruin people's lives and ruin their
souls and break them down but they can't
break their souls man they can't they
can't have their souls
right they can't have their souls the
darkness can't take your soul
even though it wants it but it can't
there's this war spiritual war of
darkness and light
and they're at battle with each other so
you look for seven seven seven baby and
that's the number you look for
and then you gotta look out for the six
six six
but yeah
and you also want one you want one for
four
that's number two you look out for the
144 that's what you look for
people are looking for 111
no you look for one four four that's the
number to look for right there you want
a protective number you want a holy
number you want a powerful number you
look for one four four forget one one
one
it's one four four
anyway um cali what's coming this year
oh dear lord
uma you're the greatest by the way your
videos are awesome
they always make me laugh they always do
they cheer me up all the time
anyway michelle says wrong
wrong
that number right there
is the number that actually that the
light
depends on
in order to battle evil
i'm just telling you right now one one
one only means three three is the
beginning of something but it doesn't
mean it's that powerful
one four four
okay
is a nine
but one four four is a holy number
and it works only for the light and
that's used as a tool to battle darkness
but nobody knows that
but
how are they going to know that
you know
spirit of compassion gives me this
information but they'll take it now and
then people will talk about it whatever
but spirit of compassion tells me about
how all the numbers work and how does it
work with the numbers maybe i'll leave a
telegram
you guys i'm going to leave a telegram
message
um not right now because i'm gonna do
another live coming up but i'm gonna
leave a telegram message about 144 and
how the darkness and light works
so you guys know on telegram
because
facebook will just censor me more and
more and more because they don't like my
p hummus
so i'll do an exclusive telegram on 1 4
4 and y 1 1 1 1 1 1 isn't that big of a
deal
um
and then
i will do and anyway you guys know i'm
doing exclusive tick tock videos man
tick tock's awesome doing exclusive tick
tock videos on there snapchat exclusive
videos which i'm excited about check out
my newsletter get on my newsletter for
exclusive videos there
i'm working and working and working i'm
at your service right here
so i will deliver this for you right
here and
would you guys like some hummus i'm at
your service
got a root canal video coming out on the
newsletter
tomorrow new letter video tomorrow root
canal
anyway
god bless you
and uh i'm gonna go live again in a
little while i'm gonna turn on instagram
so i'm gonna turn instagram on i'm gonna
turn on tiktok back on i'm gonna turn
telegram back on you guys know i love
you
you guys know i love you dearly okay