it's on medical medium heavy metal detox
launch party did you register medical
medium.com go there medical.com or check
out the link in the bio Link in the
description and make sure you get your
name in there I'm actually excited about
it I'm beyond excited about I'm trying
to contain myself and keep myself less
excited the best I can but what's going
to happen is I'm going to be there I'm
going to be there in person I'm going to
sign books I'm going to be there in
person it's going to you some free
gifts and irwan is putting the medical
medium heavy metal detx smoothie on the
menu I can't even believe it I'm so
blown away and excited so yeah all the
airwan stores are going to have the
metal smoothie in it the hmds I am
pumped but it's going to be the detox
launch party I got to contain myself but
it's hard it's hard are you coming are
you coming it's definitely once in a
lifetime I've never signed books outside
of like you know a relative or something
saying aw please sign a book for my
friend you know what i' be like okay
I'll sign a book but I've never done a
book signing ever ever and Never
official book signing it's been 10 years
it's been a decade almost and I've never
done the official book signings like
authors do and I don't know if I'll ever
do one again but either way guess what
the heavy metal detox launch party at
Iran June 15th June 15th and it's free
in the sense where you don't have to buy
a ticket to get in like a $100 ticket a
$200 ticket you don't have to buy a
ticket to get in Kelsey box says on
YouTube I booked my flight in hotel
already 10 explanations points right
there I saw that you guys I'm excited
and I just want to say a little bit more
about it if we can before I go on
because we're we're talking about
something really cool about our brain
we're talking about Metals in our brain
but you don't want to miss this cuz this
is actually a really cool talk but if
you guys just came on here I'm just
telling you right now um You might want
to be there I'm going to be there in
person I might there might be some cool
stuff going on there so I'm pumped so
anyway you guys June 15th ear Wan yes
the medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie is going to be on the menu I
hope you guys get one I'm excited I'm
going to have one
I I'll get one last and but the whole
point is though is this is a book
signing I'm going to be there I'm
excited going to give away some stuff
like how cool is that I am so pumped and
I'm trying to keep myself trying to keep
myself calm about it but it's hard it's
hard Thrive with Natalie over there and
IG says can't wait flying in from
Toronto I hear a lot of people are
flying in from Canada I hear a lot of
people are flying in from Taiwan
from Japan from China from Germany from
Australia and people are from all over
the world are flying in I mean how
incredible is
that Cosmic right there Cosmic medicine
over there in IG High lovely Anthony
with a heart so excited to travel from
Switzerland to you on June 15th on the
15th of June it exactly says I am
excited from Switzerland I hear people
are coming out of Austria Australia
Switzerland Netherlands people are
coming out of like all over the place
Africa there's people coming out of
Africa like a whole bunch of people like
this is actually an incredible time an
incredible time it's a once- in
a-lifetime thing I I've never done a
book signing I haven't done an event of
any kind or gathering I mean in in a
very very long time so this is
definitely
unprecedented and it's going to be fun
so I'm excited you guys so I hope you
come in medical me.com you could
actually just you know put your name in
just put your name in medical me.com you
don't have to get your credit card out
and buy a $200 ticket to actually enter
irwan to be here on this incredible
launch party all right you guys and whoa
lailo Susan says says I am flying in
from Canada too you're flying in from
Canada and okay let's see someone's
asking on IG where is this happening
it's happening in La Culver City irwan
and Culver City La June 15th you guys
you
guys it's it's going to be fun so anyway
check it out go to medical.com or link
is in the description link is in the bio
um and I'm going to be there in person I
will be there so I'm excited it's going
to be fun all right all right let's get
in let's get on to things here but
seriously though I mean once in a
lifetime for me I don't know if I'll
ever do a an official book signing as an
author as a number one New York Times
best selling author I never talk about
that I don't you know when when
someone's like a New York Times best
selling author it's like they say it
every second they say it every second
everywhere every every everever right
because it's like it's like credentials
and stuff and I never say it it's rare
it's like right and um but yes uh as as
the number one New York Times
bestselling author of these nine
incredible medical Bibles that are
saving lives all around the world you
guys see it out there you see when
someone like when when a health coach
gets somebody feeling better or a doctor
on social media says they got a a few
people better and they're like they're
saying they're her heralding it is the
greatest thing on the planet and
everybody getting better is is the
greatest thing right
but the medical medium books have saved
lives gotten people out of wheelchairs
turned lives around people with
debilitating neurological problems the
medical medium books have changed lives
around the world the heavy metal detox
is literally the leading detox in metal
removal in on the planet right now and
the most popular first for women said
that is by far right the most popular
first for women said that it is you know
the right the publication it is is by
far the most
incredible heavy metal detox there is
and it wasn't man-made it's information
from above and it's here in our hands
and people's lives have changed from it
like Mania OCD like bipolar anxiety
depression mad depression like anger um
you know depersonalization deep sadness
gone in people's lives from the heavy
metal detox smoothie gone in the heavy
metal detox right
it's been incredible what has happened
people with multiple sclerosis and ALS
and chronic illnesses of all kind and
tingles and numbness and aches and pains
and panic attacks and anxiety all of it
gone because of medical me heavy metal
detox it put it on the map before the
heavy metal detox you know what you
heard out there kation therapy chilation
therapy that's all you heard it was
chilation therapy and it was BAS
basically for someone if they swallowed
an entire bottle of lead or they ate
lead paint chips or something like that
it didn't even work the kation therapy
right there was no there's wasn't the
heavy metal detox and when that came to
town years and years ago and people knew
what to do cuz they found out what the
information was right the heavy metal
detox the medical medium and they moved
migraines away they moved all kinds of
different conditions away and symptoms
away it is historic it is absolutely
historic what the medical medium heavy
metal detox has done on this planet
historic and honestly s so delivering
that information so people can know what
to do instead of the hacks out there and
the copycats and the poachers trying to
put their Twist on things and make their
own heavy metal detox because it got so
popular around the world because of mm
and they're all trying to say no don't
use this but do that don't do cilantro
but do this and they're all just trying
to make their way to bank and meanwhile
sorry but the heavy metal detox the one
and only has reversed conditions and
symptoms in people for years turning
lives around so guess what yeah irwan
having the heavy metal detox the one
that first for women the publication set
is amazing right the one and only one in
ear walk on is a big deal on the menu so
it could be made fresh for people people
going right in people in the area go
they got a bunch of stores I think they
got like 10 stores people just going
right in they don't have to make it at
home they go right in on the Run they're
driving around they got their kids in
the cars they could just get all of them
for the kids like it's going to be there
and helping people heal it is
unprecedented mindblowing mind numbing I
am so so excited about this for people
and have an ability to get it there and
it deems it absolutely deems a medical
medium heavy metal detox launch party at
irwan June 15th it deems this for sure
because it's that special I hope to see
you guys there I'm sign a bunch of books
I'm excited I'm excited J over there on
YouTube says Anthony we book the flight
coming from Europe yeah coming from
Europe I'm so excited for you it's going
to be in La Culver City June 15th Ed IR
Juan boom I'm pumped up and excited
flying from Miami amazing oh Lena I'll
be coming from Canada incredible JW
Jones we're flying in from William 10
North Carolina amazing and Sonia coming
from
Arizona incredible incred oh Christina
flying from Germany Nick Taylor flying
from New York City whoa Debbie so
excited flying from Virginia to see you
incredible like I I'm it's just yeah
love South Africa Aurora yeah whole
bunch of people coming from actually
South Africa that's what I heard
Jennifer LTI over there on YouTube on
the phone now booking by flight watching
you incredible make sure you you also
write your name on the registry right
link is in the bio link is in the
profile um go to Medical mem.com if you
want and you can fill it out right there
it's right on the
homepage how exciting how exciting
anyway all right incredible you guys it
is very special it is something I never
thought I would do but but I would only
dream to do only dream to do Nazi over
there in YouTube flying from New Orleans
New Orleans that is an amazing place and
then some Lauren over there on YouTube I
have to book my flight from PA
Pennsylvania boots McGee good to see you
on YouTube hi Anthony flying from New
York City NYC Boop to La New York to
LA One Way Nat over there on YouTube I
am coming from Vietnam to
incredible Andrew over there on YouTube
coming from Cleveland Ohio whoa Beth
pige coming from
DC no way that's too cool
Aton over there on YouTube my family is
flying out from Wyoming to come whoa
Wyoming Blown Away Blown Away blown away
okay michon over there michon J whoa
YouTube flying from Miami love it love
it Bon over there on YouTube coming from
Texas that is awesome I love Texas too
cool Carolina driving from
Fontana amazing M stubs coming from
Atlanta could that be Atlanta Georgia
amazing James over there YouTube coming
in from Canada as well a whole bunch of
people coming in from Canada whoa Al
over there on YouTube coming from San
Antonio nice that
is that
is phenomenal that is
phenomenal absolutely
phenomenal all right let's get down to
some talking let's get down to some
metal talk all right I'm excited New
York City Nelly's coming from New York
City and you see all you guys a lot of
people are coming A lot of people are
coming all
right depression anxiety dep
personalization bipar OCD all kinds of
obsessive thoughts thoughts that people
can't get out of their head that com in
and out all kinds of different things
that people go through skin problems
Vitiligo eczema
psoriasis right all kinds of different
autoimmune conditions that get spurred
on Metals Metals
Metals chenine says over there in
YouTube I'm only 20 minutes away but
excited to be there 20 minutes away I
when I get out there are going to be 20
minutes away as well from Culver City
so when I get out there and I'm staying
out there and I I got this little spot
out there that I'm staying right that
I'm that I'm renting for for that like
week
and I'm only 20 minutes away as well
excited from Holland
yeah
incredible Josh says I wish I could make
it
bummer
god well listen for anybody who can't
make it I completely understand I
totally understand and there's got to be
reasons why you can't make it and um I'm
honored that you're even trying I'm
honored that you even care and uh for
anybody who can't make it totally
understand completely understand okay
and I'm behind you 100%
100% all
right what happens is there's a battle
in our brains you see it out there
people are lost and
confused and it is isn't just from
stress somebody can be lost and
confused and there's no stress very
little stress somebody can be under
tremendous stress and not lost and
confused what do I mean by that doubting
themselves
fear just fear deep down
inside
doubt right feeling like they're the
problem that's something that happens
all the time and then PT PD that won't
go away so many people have that as well
and then there's people that have
anxiety Panic
nervousness their feet sweat all the
time there's PE then there's just people
that have like the sweating
conditions where they're sweating all
the time everywhere they're drenched
they don't even need a reason to be
drenched and their body is drenched with
sweat whole bunch of people go through
that too metals Metals Metals Metals
yeah even with all that hyperhydrosis
even with all that sweating and
different things that people deal with
and then there's the people with
migraines and headaches and migraines
and
headaches I say that over and over again
because people go from migraines to
headaches to headaches to bad migraines
back to migraines to headaches and they
live with their headache and then turns
into a big migraine
again and then there's people with all
kinds of skin conditions they got eczema
really bad and psoriasis really bad and
other types of skin conditions too and
Vio as well and then there's the people
that are emotionally and mentally
struggling like there's a battle in
their mind and a battle in their head
and they got the
OCD and the dep personalization where
they're so disconnected and they feel
numb but they don't know why and then
there's people who feel like they have a
decent life my life is good my life can
be better
I want to be productive my life is is is
going good but I am disconnected and
numb numb and I don't feel anything
there's so bunch of people that just
don't feel
anything where they're just like they
don't feel anything nothing excites them
nothing feeds into passion or turns into
passion nothing they can't even find
compassion they have it somewhere they
can't even find compassion for for
someone or for something that's
happening at there they can't find
compassion because they're so numb and
they're they're so disconnected they
feel they have this deep
depersonalization that they can't they
can't connect and they can't make that
connection and bypass it they can't
overcome it and they can't supersede it
and they live with it and they wake up
the morning and it's back to that again
they're numb they wake up in the morning
and they're disconnected and numb and
it's back to that every single day they
go to bed depressed and sad or they get
angry as the night goes on do you know
any of those
people as the night goes on something
can trigger them and they get
angry or
angrier here it is midnight and they're
angry now and they can't shake it before
they go to bed anybody ever seen that or
gone through that or over there says on
YouTube is profuse sweating from weak
adrenals or Metals let's get into that a
little bit you see this right here why
is this
here oh why is this
here because I was going to talk about
how toxic heavy metals weaken adrenals
because they put pressure on the nervous
system forcing the adrenals to react all
the time creating a sweating problem for
a lot of people hyperhydrosis
bunch of sweating problem profuse
sweating yes also adrenaline surges
happening all the time heart rate
increasing happening all the time toxic
heavy metals inside the brain can make
it so it's putting stress on the central
nervous system causing
problems causing
problems stress on the nervous system
causing
problems making it so the adrenals are
pumping too much so the adrenals are
cranked up too
much so what happens with a lot of
people they get this nervousness from
the toxic heavy metals the nervosus all
all falls into adrenals pumping like
crazy adrenaline pouring
out pouring out every day feet sweating
hands sweating it's not even just that
heart going a little
faster okay let's get into it a little
bit the battle in our
brains your brain is
electricity and within that
electricity we have
obstacles a lot of people have a lot of
obstacles to to overcome with
electricity in the brain let's hit it
for a second
here put a little board right do a
little brain stuff really quick okay you
guys let's get a brain
going all
right get a little bit of a mid midline
Canal okay and then we got a
brain instant brain here we
go okay we got our brain let's go let's
get some metal deposits can you see this
got a metal deposit Mercury a aluminum
cadmium lead
arsenic copper copper is a bad one real
real bad
one it is okay we got electricity
running through the
brain electricity runs through the brain
see this you
guys okay electricity is energy it
radiates off your
head electricity in your brain has
energy radiating off your head that's
why this electricity is radiating
somewhere out here you see
this okay here's a metal deposit here's
an electrical impulse here it is
electricity boom it hit the metal
deposit right there short circuit
happens and then the adrenals so let's
get some adrenals going really quick
all
right then we got some adrenals down
here you guys see
this right
electricity hits the metal
deposit the neurons are under stress a
signal goes to the
adrenals here the adrenals are and then
the adrenals release
adrenaline there it is
Metals in the brain can cause anxiety
fear panic panic
attacks depression
anxiousness all in one go or even just
little bits and pieces of that from
toxic heavy metals in the
brain toxic heavy metal aluminum Mercury
electrical electricity running through
the brain
hits the copper deposit yep copper
deposit you see this puts stress on all
the neurons and gleo
cells and then the adrenals release more
adrenaline do you guys see this there it
is okay and that's just
something that happens right there
that's just something that
happens all
right we're going to hit something
really serious
here
living
Metal Dead
metal living Metal Dead
metal in your
brain lies living Metals metals that are
alive
vital soft
metals good
Metals even tiny
traces of heavy metal that's not toxic
toic it's in Trace forms like
gold gold inside our brains tiny Trace
forms of gold that come from our food
sources and Gold's a heavy metal that
resides in our
brain but it's a living
metal it's coming from the food we grow
it's in its Trace form and it's a living
metal and then
you have dead Metals industrialized
Metals copper that was industrialized
Mercury that was industrialized aluminum
that was industrialized people say he
doesn't know what he's talking about
aluminum is not a heavy metal it's
light i s first of all since science is
taking lots of medical medium
information for instance right long flu
you guys years ago I did a video all
about how the flu can knock the immune
system down creating chronic illness
long after the flu is gone and I talked
all about that the medical medium
information by the way and now science
is doing articles they're talking about
it where it's long flu right they just
took it from medical medium that's just
one example life expectancy I
predicted Spirit of compassion
did predict it that we were dropping in
life expectancy the numbers were
dropping dropping the years someone
lives was dropping everybody ignored it
out there the industry science all of it
ignored it they thought we were living
longer and that the expectancy was going
longer and longer turns out they're
wrong so they went to Medical meme
information published information they
remove the part where life expectancy is
dropping so because of this and long flu
is in medical medium book one by the
way right here the new
addition because of this science keeps
on stealing and robbing information from
medical medium books including the cause
of multiple sceris which is epen
bar so what happened
was Spirit of compassion deemed aluminum
Heavy
Metal the reason why is because of the
extensive damage it does in someone's
life for one too much aluminum in the
brain can cause a problem creating a
situation where their body doesn't
function like it should creating a
situation where people feel like their
legs are made out of lead and their body
can barely
function it's heavy damage substantial
damage on people's body and
brains all kinds of different issues in
the brain that people have different
conditions they have because of aluminum
aluminum is dangerous when it sits
inside of our brain and
corrodes and outp
pockets and leeches
so medical me books have deemed aluminum
a toxic heavy metal versus a light metal
because of the substantial damage it
does and probably 5 years from now or
seven years from now they're just going
to call it a toxic heavy metal which I
actually saw they've already done that
recently anyway the whole point I'm
trying to say is that we have living
Metals inside of our head and we have
dead Metals inside of our head and these
dead
Metals interact and they battle the
living
Metals so we have metals that are useful
in their form they're soft
Metals they're heavy
metals but we have them in Trace forms
from our
food and they actually sit inside of our
brain and they help to make up a
neurotransmitter they help to support a
neurotransmitter and they help to feed
and keep alive neurons and allow neurons
to have electricity run through them so
here's how it
works
okay if you
have right if you have a
neuron right here there's lots of
neurons in our brain you guys all know
that you have a neuron so I'm just
making a big
neuron okay if that
neuron
if that neuron is
filled with living
Metals soft Metals heavy metals but
living metals that come from your food
supply if you got living Metals in here
in this neuron that neuron is going to
do this when electricity goes to it
ready here's electricity again here we
go there's an electricity right here it
is Boom it hit that neuron that neuron's
packed with living Metals it hits the
neuron the neuron takes that
electricity places information on that
electrical impulse travels to another
neuron that is also filled with all
these living Metals the living metals
are the conductors they're the
conductors of that electricity inside
the neuron so they can travel with
information from neuron to neuron but
when our neurons are lacking living
metals and they're filled with dead
metals
that's when we're in really big trouble
when they're filled with dead Metals so
what happens when these neurons are
filled with dead metal so let's make a
neuron and we'll put a nice big neuron
right here nice big neuron right there
put one here
too all right the neuron is filled with
dead Metals copper Mercury aluminum
arsenic lead
cadmium there's more but we could sit
here all
day okay here they are dead metals are
in here get ready when the electricity
heads their way electricity is heading
its way here it is electrical impulse
that's your life force electricity in
your brain here it goes it's going to
hit a neuron neurons filled with all
these dead Metals
boom it's like hitting a brick
wall and then you're
like I just don't feel good something's
off I better make another doctor's
appointment I better sign up to this
course that says they're going to cure
you of every disease for
$5,000 I better just go see this I
better go see this person I better fly
around the world and dip myself in some
crazy hot spring somewhere but something
happens where you just you're just like
something's wrong with me 50 doctors
later nobody knew that you had
a
neuron you had nerve
cells and they were filled with dead
metals and when the electricity hit the
the the neuron with all those dead
Metals in
there problems occurred it was like
hitting a brick a stone
wall see alridge 741 so when they say
lesions are on your brain are they
seeing heavy metal
deposits all right let's go into the a
little
bit when they when they see lesions on
the brain they don't know what they're
seeing they could be Heavy Metal
deposits that have been um leeching
causing tissue damage gal cell damage
and so forth brain tissue damage it
could be an MSG deposit you know many
people have MSG deposits in their brain
it leaves all kinds of marks now and
these better
MRIs and the way they scan brains now
they're starting to see stuff all the
time I called this shot a long time ago
they're seeing all kinds of different
white spots dark spots brown spots gray
spots and I talk about it I have a whole
chapter in it in brainsaver right here
so if you guys want to know what book
I'm in I'm in brainsaver make sure you
get this book amazon.com us go to the
library get it for free whatever but
that's the book right there bring the
information to your doctor ask your
doctor if it's right for you take the
book to your doctor show your doctor
whatever you're looking at in here
including the protocols but it's very in
depth about toxic heavy metals
extremely
comprehensive really really
comprehensive a lot of people have MSG
deposits in their
brain a lot of people have salt deposits
in their brain you ready for this all
that excess salt people are eating they
eat so much salt a lot of the road salt
they eat because they're at restaurants
and they think it's a healthy meal and
there's a lot of road salt meaning
really cheap processed
salt and even if you overdo it with like
too much of the higher quality salts and
you're overdoing it it's got to go
somewhere you
guys it can become like a salty soup
inside your body and then your liver
can't handle that much
salt and yeah your bile can't handle
that much salt your HCL can't handle
that much salt you have so much salt in
you this isn't like celery juice that's
different that's an entirely different
sodium right and then you got all this
salt in you but high concentrations of
it because you wouldn't believe how much
salt you can throw on food it's insane
how much salt you can just bury in food
restaurant food they pack it in Salt
right pizzas packed in salt took all the
salt off the pizza you'd be like why am
I eating this You' be like this is
terrible that's how much salt is on a
pizza so what happens is salt deposits
grow and they collect inside the brain
and they
crystallize and crystallizations from
salt deposits show up on the MRIs and
they're like what is this they don't
know and they're not going to cut your
brain in half they're not going to say
we're going to experiment and cut your
brain in half and we're going to go try
to find out what this is and they're not
going to go and look for that salt
deposit that MSG deposit salt deposit or
that scar tissue or that
calcification that's another thing too
we're on such acidic diets that we lose
so much calcium out of our bones the
calcium ends up hoarding inside brain
tissue and becomes
calcifications and then we get an MRI
when we're in our
50s 40s or 6s and on the MRI there's
this calcification they don't even know
what it is they're like we don't know
what this is Mr
Jones and you have this calcification
that's in the brain it's a
calcification it's
calcium that had nowhere to go that
leeched out of your bones that stored up
in the brain tissue you can have you can
be someone that has literally like it's
it's a whole smor sporg of all these
different spots in your brain from an
MRI you can have brown spots in the
crystallizations you could have white
spots you could have what looks like
Crystal
you all this stuff and then lesions what
looks like lesions dark spots black
spots and it's like MSG deposit sodium
deposit yeah calcification Scar Tissue
Mercury and copper that's that's how
crazy it is right
there so we got these dead Metals we got
these living Metals but there's a battle
that
happens yeah
okay now if your brain is full of
electrical currents what must be
involved Metals that's right so good
metals like I said they're part of the
electrical currents but what happens is
these good Metals include these
beneficial non-industrialized forms of
gold calcium copper calcium soft metal
copper pottassium but the good stuff
from our Foods magnesium chromium
padium right and more one reason these
beneficial metals are Theirs to control
electrical currents so we have all these
crazy minerals that are living metals
that reside in our neurons inside our
brain and they're there to protect us
because that's how our electricity just
swims along right it's incredible Rogue
toxic heavy metals residing in our brain
with the good Metals wreak havoc they
create a battle in our brains and that
battle can be like the battle we have in
our mind I hate myself I don't trust
myself you know I can't stop these
impulsive actions I know I have good
intentions but I'm suffering and people
think I have bad intentions I got so
much fear I can't get out I'm just lost
I got sadness coming out from the pit of
my gut and I don't know what it is or
what why I'm so sad I don't do anything
right I can't get anything
done and it's just this battle in our
brains right there it's good medals and
bad metals and it's this battle that's
happening from having this in our
brain yeah which one of your books are
you working with right now I think Mary
said I'm working with brain saver right
here okay I know I don't put there's no
advertisers I didn't make any Advertiser
deals on my podcast all the podcast
Giants they all have advertisers right
you guys they make deals so they can
make like a million a year 5 million a
year whatever it is I don't do that no
advertisers on my podcast so I have to
be my own Advertiser okay here you go
you got the brain saver right
there these are the toxic heavy metal
books right here brain saver and the
protocols books you should have these
right
here you should have
these I just want you guys to get free
clear podcast listening without a bunch
of commercial on there I just that's how
I feel okay by the way medical medum
podcast at Apple podcast I just want to
tell you there's a food poisoning
episode on there underrated food
poisoning is undercovered food poisoning
under
appreciated under respected food
poisoning is under reported and
underrated so what people don't realize
with food poisoning is it's killing
people every single day out there people
aren't being worn
they're not being warned they're not
being educated about food poisoning it's
like Russian Roulette out there it's
like ticking time bombs out there people
go into restaurants and yes they can die
how many people have died from food
poisoning a year a lot you couldn't even
believe go listen to the episode
subscribe on Apple podcast right um
because you know subscribe there to my
medical meeme podcast at Apple podcast
because every Thursday there's a new
episode every Thursday Did the pharmace
itical exposure episode did the tattoo
episode that was a good one right there
I did the coffee and coffee enema
episode and now the food poisoning
episode and there's even more than that
so please check it out
okay
wonderful give this video a like and a
thumbs up if you like if you hate this
video give it a like and a thumbs up or
give it a middle f finger if that's what
you want to do one or the other you give
it a thumbs up or a middle finger but
either way yeah hit the like button if
you can okay Rogue toxic heavy metals
residing in the brain with the good
Metals wreak havoc they create a battle
in our brains a battle in our mind I
can't wait to read one thing to you
living metal against dead metal check
this out you guys lifegiving medal
versus lifet taking
medal isn't that sick isn't that sick
it's a sick World lifegiving medal
versus life taking
medal how crazy is that yeah life taking
medal you don't think
so it's a lot of people suffering and a
lot of people have lost their lives so
yes LIF taking medal time heels over
there on
YouTube I brought the brain saver book
to the doctor with my concussion she
looked through the protocol I walked out
with no prescription for the first
time
incredible when this book came out right
here oh there it
is and that book came out years ago
almost a decade this is the new edition
but when the original book came out
almost 10 years
ago everybody brought it to their
doctors it's all you would hear out
there it's everybody's doctor being like
what's this medical medium book and they
got blown away when they found out what
was wrong with every body was incredible
concussion though concussion is in brain
saver that's the protocol is in here all
right check this out you guys got a
second listen to this living metal
versus dead metal life-taking medal
versus life-giving Medal
okay good versus
evil good versus evil isn't it
interesting think about that right now
okay think about that
so I want to I want to do this for a
second I want to make a new brain real
quick can I do that can I make a new
brain there's a new brain okay midline
Canal
squiggly new
brain
okay metal deposit metal
deposit metal deposit metal deposit okay
all right get
ready good
metals good metal
deposits good Metals
deposits good
Metals
okay bad Metals ready
evil
ready
good right
there
okay on a physical level there is good
versus evil inside our
brain you don't think that can play a
role in
anything it can play a massive role is
it possible that when metals are so bad
in somebody's brain they go and they
stab 10
people is it possible metals are so off
putting in a bad way in somebody's
brain where they do something that they
no one thought they would ever
do is it possible that metals
in somebody's
brain right the good and evil battle
that's happening can get somebody to
hate
themselves
terribly H despise themselves yes
definitely because what you have is good
versus evil industrialized
Metals right here Mercury aluminum
copper
that got into us through all kinds of
different Avenues including Pharm
pharmaceutical exposure to our waterways
to the trails falling out of the
sky
evil and then good Metals trace minerals
from our foods from celery juice from
the heavy metal detox trace minerals and
our food that we
eat right there
Encompass good and then Mercury
aluminum cadmium lead copper
industrialized that got into our body in
ways that it's not supposed to but it
did and it got in here
evil short circuits neurons and you got
OCD OCD can create
thoughts that don't stop making somebody
literally suffer a terrifying suffer
u a suffering people can't explain or
understand unless they've gone through
it themselves with OCD alone and then
same thing with bipolar being like okay
for one minute and then feeling so lost
and sick and feeling so like so sick in
their body the feeling of being so ill
and then feeling better for a minute and
then not feeling better and then
depression anxiety
attacks because that industrialized
metal right there am I yelling loud
enough that industrialized metal right
there is causing
pain and that's the
evil yep the Mercury demon and so forth
and then the good is the minerals we got
to get inside our brain to sustain us
and someday override so that the Battle
of evil and good is not so much of a
thing where it's less and less and this
battle is not
so massive it becomes a little battle
instead and a little battle because the
more good minerals you have right here
the
battle you
win Terry Johnson dead medals would be a
great name for a rock
band it
would I wouldn't doubt it if there
wasn't one out there at some point in
time
throughout our history I know the
Grateful Dead is one that uses the dead
and I know there's a lot of metal bands
out
there okay so check this
out it's a physical battle going on
inside our brain on top of the battle of
Life on this planet it's the problem
that was never meant to be here was what
you see right here this battle right
here was never meant to be here on
planet Earth is it somewhere else on
another
planet is there another planet out there
where there's a
humanoid
species civilization on another planet
out there in the
galaxy in the universe or in some Galaxy
in some solar system is there another
planet that's harboring a species of
people are they battling the same thing
is evil on their Planet making sure
Metals get into everything from children
to everyone to women is there an evil
evil doer Force hierarchy illumination
somewhere on another planet doing this
to those people and those humanoids
versus here or is it just here it's
question I've asked Spirit of compassion
and I do have the
answer over there on
IG lady bear says is there any way to
test to see how much of good medals and
bad Metals metals we have the problem is
with
that okay is that everybody has
exposures every single day so when they
take blood from you they're getting that
new
exposure metal deposits can stay in your
brain and very little ever be in the
bloodstream metal deposits can stay in
your liver and very little be in your
bloodstream testing is never accurate
when it comes down to chronic illness
derived from toxic heavy metals so guess
what is accurate though
guess what the accurate thing is Guess
How guess what the best test there ever
was and ever will be it's when something
works but I mean Works You've Been
Everywhere you tried everything you've
done
everything you learn you got metals
because you're learning this information
of what creates your symptoms conditions
and then you use the heavy metal
detox three out of the five ingredients
minimum or five of the ingredients five
out of the five ingredients of the heavy
metal detox right here out of this
book and in these books that heavy metal
detox you use and you watch your
problems go away and as your problems go
away that is right there that's how we
do it we do it where you're riding your
problems that is the example that is the
street cred That's The credibility where
the problem goes because sure you can
get your your different tests and hey
you might have medals you might not have
Metals but are you getting better what
are you doing get better and when you
use something that works and it makes it
go away that's the ultimate test because
we're exposed to every day they can't
test organs they can't cut open your
liver and dig out the metal and say oh
you got this much metal in your liver it
stays embedded in there and then your
bloodstream can be somewhat
clean where the metals aren't really
floating around but your liver's
compacted in metal because it's your
filter it's holding the metal down in
there it is your
filter
we can't just test an organ and cut the
darn thing open I've said this for
decades they're just now starting to
share that information the medical me
information they've taken it poached it
and now guess what so-called brand new
metal experts in the last year in the
last 6 months one even running ads 247
to the medical meme Community is stolen
medical meme information yeah totally
taken it and there L like you you can't
test for Metals in the blood it's
interesting cuz you weren't saying that
a few years ago ago in anything you were
doing and you weren't saying that 5
years ago in anything you were doing
interesting but you're saying it now in
the last 6 months for the first time
ever in your career and they're like
yeah you can't test for Metals in the
blood cuz they're in the organs that was
just poached recently and then it's
being like slammed at the medical me
Community every single day in
ads yep your lab test will not be able
to determine if you have high medals
because they're in the organs in the
brain that's medical medium information
right there and so to answer that
question no it's not easy but you know
how you know you got Metals is when you
actually do something for those Metals
longterm or even shortterm like the
heavy metal detox the medical meme heavy
metal detox and you're watching these
symptoms dissipate and go away and
that's right because your metals are
going away whoa you're coming from
Switzerland I just saw that
whoa
you guys June
15th coming from Connecticut Lisa June
15th Gabriel says Hey aw from Romania I
hope we'll get the US Visa in time in
order to meet you on the 15th of
June
incredible from Romania I hear they're
coming out of Serbia Romania Austria I'm
here they coming out of Germany France
they're coming out of London there's a
lot of people coming out of London a lot
of people coming out of Great Britain a
lot of people coming out
there from out
there you
know I mean only problem is if you're
coming out from England you're coming
out from London I will I won't be I
won't have a
Victorian um silk Victorian antique
chair with a tea set there ready for
you I wish I could that would be so cool
imagine that all Victorian chairs we all
got tea sets and
crumpets
okay and you know I'm just
kidding I'm excited but a lot of people
are coming from England a
lot okay you guys we're covering alloy
brain we're moving through material
if you just got here I mean we're really
we're really doing Darcy Lee over there
on YouTube aw thank you so much for
teaching me how to heal and heal my
babies and family I'm honored you're
here truly and thank you for being here
seriously Darcy
Le it's an honor please share your
stories of what the heavy metal detox
the medical medium heavy metal detox is
done for you okay please tag at medal
medium
in your stories and hashtag if you can
and your posts do both so I can see it
please share your stories I would love
to see
them if IG allows it I would love to see
them anyway I just want to say a
reminder for everybody who just got on
here I see a bunch of people starting to
come on June 15th don't miss it I mean
if you can't come you can't come I'm
going to be there in person I'm going to
sign a bunch of books I'm going to be
there and it is the medical M heavy
metal detox launch party in Culver City
irwan and medical medum are
collaborating and it's going to be on
the menu and I am just blown
away Blown Away the the heavy metal
detox medical me heavy metal detox has
tremendous credibility around the world
for changing lives first for women
talked about it it is literally the Top
Dog in heavy metal detox and it's going
it's going to continue to be because it
worked
anyway I'm going to be giving away some
free gifts I'm going to be there in
person at this launch party I'm not
selling tickets for this launch party
it's free in the sense where you you
don't need to buy a $200 ticket or a
$100 ticket to come in please come if
you'd like I'm excited you guys all
right so we covered a lot of intense
information good versus evil dead medals
against living medals right residing in
our brain neurons that get contaminated
they they leech they outp poet they
become a problem electrical impulses
that swim through the brain so
electrical impulses that go through the
brain right an electrical impulse goes
through and it hits one of these
deposits it blows up it it it um it
causes a problem where boom now we're in
some OCD we're in some kind of emotional
turmoil we're feeling
sensation we're dealing with a struggle
we're dealing with ticks and
spasms yeah you can even have ticks and
spasms Tremors people get Parkinson's
there's so many different varieties of
Parkinson's happening where people get
all these different kinds of conditions
with um jerking and and all of that and
and Tremors and Shakes and shakes toxic
heavy metals we got to get them out so
the neurons can restore and here's what
I love about the Heavy Metal the medical
meme metal detox I just want to tell you
guys here's what I love about it it's
restoring while it's getting Metals out
while it's removing Metals it's
restoring tissue it's restoring brain
tissue it's putting more back in more of
the good stuff back in it's actually not
just cleaning up and cleaning out but
it's restoring and putting back in
that's what has to happen that's why
people heal
metals have to come out but everything
has to be restored at the same time
right so that's why it's so incredible
that's why the five ingredients in the
heavy metal detox are so powerful and
you can check them out in the medical
medium books
right it's it's so powerful because it's
restoring tissue as it's
removing and guess
what the heavy metal detox is the
ultimate
binder the ultim
binder it's got the wild blueberry in
there and nobody even talked about the
wild blueberry nobody even talked about
the wild
blueberry nobody
did it wasn't on the
scene medical medium information had to
make sure people knew that the wild
blueberry was that powerful and part of
it's part of the heavy metal detox and
it's the ultimate binder and that's part
of
it but if you can only do four out of
the five you can only do three out of
the five you're doing something if you
can only do the spirulina the barley
grass cheese powder and the
douls if you can only do the cilantro
the sparina and the wild
blueberry if you can only do the barley
grass cheese powder the cilantro and the
douls Whatever It Is three out of the
five is the minimum to try to get some
of that to move some of that out you get
four out of the five you're moving more
out you get five out of the five you're
moving it
out check the information out learn
about how it works in the books Iona
YouTube finally got the right kind of
wild blueberries and wow what a
difference
yep what a
incredible yes I saw somebody say why do
you have this here and this
here because
those are mine to drink
today and they're here in case I want a
sip which I do I'm going to have a
little bit of grapefruit juice if you
don't
mind I got these killer grapefruits
right now so I can't help
it all right you
guys I hope to see you there medical.com
check it out register medical.com link
is in the profile link is in the
bio
register put your name
in so we got an idea of what's going
on if you can um if you're bring in
family you bring family if you're
bringing more than one person you bring
more more than one
person I saw some people saying they're
bringing five I saw somebody say they're
bringing eight
people eight
people get in the medical medium newslet
so I can give you
updates the one thing about the medical
M
newsletter you know it's it's about
making sure you guys are updated on
stuff and so not only do we put cool
stuff in there and everything but it's
it's also about being updated so you
know what's going
on I'm trying to like keep myself on the
down lad and contain it but I am so
excited about this this party this
launch party I I don't even know I'm
like bursting
bursting follow me on telegram by the
way so I can leave these exclusive like
private messages and so forth follow me
on medical medium insid scoop on IG you
know the broadcast follow me there too
if you can follow me on YouTube but you
might not get the
notification check out medical medum
podcast at Apple
podcast and check out food poisoning
that
episode it's mind information and I'm
going to do another food poisoning
episode because there needs to be even
another one it's that
important all right
guys I think I'm signing
off June 15th event I'm going to be
signing books I'm going to be giving
away free
gifts and the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie is going to be on Iran's
menu I hope you grab one I'm grabbing
one
and I'm going to be really announcing
something about that too interesting
stuff about that that you guys in the
medical medum community are going to
love I'm not kidding when you hear it
you guys are going to be excited because
there's a
secret I haven't told you guys
about about the heavy metal detox movie
your one there's a secret something that
involves the
community
something very helpful anyway I love you
guys super excited