just released a new episode called food
Wars medical meeting podcast at Apple
podcast you don't want to miss it before
that it was alcohol which is an
incredible episode you don't want to
miss before that it was micro doing
which is an incredible
episode I highly recommend it filled
with information it's really powerful so
it's micro doing then it was alcohol
then it's food Wars today three episodes
at the medical medium podcast at Apple
podcast please if you get a chance check
them out it's an easy listen great
information could help move people
forward could help save a life too as
well medical medium information is
saving thousands and thousands and
thousands of lives and over the years
Millions so yes definitely check it out
medical mean podcast at Apple podcast
also check out the older episode called
the blood draw check that one out as
well too all about blood testing and so
forth never miss out on that episode
it's so powerful it's packed with
information that can save a life letting
you know today's food Wars and what you
see in front of me is a whole bunch of
food whole bunch of food that a lot of
people do eat a lot of people don't eat
right what does it matter we shouldn't
hate them we shouldn't hate
people but people do people attack
people people attack people and then
people attack people and then people
attack people you haven't seen it I'm
not talking about trolls on social media
I'm not talking about bots on social
media I'm talking about just people in
general they attack people and other
people attack people and what comes down
to it is judgment on food it's all about
judging people about what they're eating
and what they're doing but really what
it's all cracked up to be or what it all
amounts to is is two sides of the aisle
that's what it amounts to so food Wars
means there's a war between the
plant-based vegan movement against the
animal eating movement the animal
eaters they judge and hate the
plant-based eaters the plant-based
eaters judge and hate the animal eaters
that's the food Wars and then the whole
bunch of crap in between Queen and
everybody's also dabbling and flipping
over and everything else here flipping
over there flip flopping there flip
flopping there so everybody's doing all
of that
too and then when it comes down to
people being sick that takes us to
another level which we're going to talk
about as well people with chronic
illness people who are suffering and
struggling and where that leads them
when it comes down to eating and what
kind of eating where and what and how
you don't want to miss this episode
let's cut right into it now okay now I
don't know what side of the ID aisle
you're on you might be on the
plant-based aisle you might be on the
animal protein aisle maybe you're
somewhere in
between but years and years and years
ago there used to be just a small amount
of plant-based people it's so small like
a grain of rice to a silo of rice and
The Silo of rice is the animal eaters
right or a grain of sand on the beach
would be the plant-based movement vegan
movement
and then the rest of the beach filled
with sand tons and tons and tons of sand
would be the animal eating movement an
animal eaters right so that's what it
used to be and then over time the vegan
movement got a little bigger and a
little bigger and there was a vegetarian
movement in the middle but remember the
vegetarians just ate basically
everything except for red meat so
vegetarians ate everything except for
red meat that's what the old days was
like by the way so they ate cheese
vegetarians ate cheese they drank milk
they ate every o yogurt they did
everything ate fish and then the only
thing they didn't do is like I'm
vegetarian you know what does that mean
oh I can still eat everything except
meat right the vegetarians you guys
remember that whole thing there's a few
of those old dogs out there there are
there's a few of those old dogs left
right where they're eating everything
eggs dairy cheese milk butter they're
eating everything all of it and they're
like but I don't eat red meat you know
the vegetarian thing am I just like
entertaining myself on that I mean think
about that that's really funny do you
guys remember and there might be a
couple of you guys who are still doing
that but overall okay the vegan movement
grew and it grew and it grew a little
bit more a little bit more okay and then
as it grew all
right
a bunch of vegans and plant-based people
that were in the movement decided to run
back to animal base and then the animal
based movement is interesting because
it's changing and changing where people
are trying keto then they're trying low
carb then they're trying all these
different things and then there flipping
over to vegan for a little while but
it's become like a dabbling situation
where it's a blend a h Posh of everybody
pretty much eating anything at any time
now there are some staunch vegans out
there still left and there are some
staunch plant- paced people still left
out there sure but for the most part
most vegans and most vegans and
plant-based people they just went boom
into eggs they went back into eggs and
back into cheese and they go into that
for a while and then they say I got to
be plant-based again for like a week or
two I have to someday then a year later
they're plant-based for a little while
or they're vegan for a little while and
then boom they're back to eating animal
products do you know anybody like this
back to eating animal products then
they're back to being plant-based
because they're like you know I need to
go plant-based I need to clean things up
I need to and then they're back to
eating my animal products right and then
there's a lot of Animal product people
they're like I'm going to go vegan for a
while I'm going to try it out they try
it for a year something happens where
they were doing good for a little while
then something flips a switch Clicks in
maybe they get a symptom they don't feel
good maybe somebody told them they need
protein you need protein you need more
protein they freak out they freak out
boom they're back to animal
products and then there's pressure peer
pressure from friends and peer pressure
from family peer pressure from the
internet telling you you should be going
one way or another and then someone
chimes in it's like this and this and
this and everybody gets
confused it's the wild west out there
still till this day and really
everybody's flip-flopping and not
certain where they want to go and what
they want to do because they might be
vegan or vegetarian or S vegan
and plant-based for a couple of
years and then they're back to dabbling
into animal stuff they're over there and
the animal stuff all over again right
and that's what they do and the same
thing goes for animal as well but the
vegans and the plant-based people have
it harder than the animal people because
the animal people usually stay animal
for the most part don't really flip that
much into vegan vegetarian or
plant-based
long but the plant-based people take the
most heat they take the most heat still
till this day and they're desperate for
science to somehow some way back them up
and support them so they can shove that
science right up the animal eater asses
and that's what they try and want to do
desperately out there is the plant-based
movement are desperate for science and
have been forever it's like a desert and
a drop of water falls into the desert
and that drop of water is there's
protein in Spinach there's protein in
Greens I'm going to go to all those
animal protein people and scream it out
screaming out to them there's protein in
this there's protein in this there's
protein in this and the plant-based
people and the vegan people kind of
picked it up from the old vegetarian
people that stopped eating red meat that
Fe felt like they were getting their
protein from their soy or their
tofu and their tofu and their soy beans
were giving them protein so they always
felt like I'm getting my textured
protein I'm getting that protein in some
way Gina says over there on Facebook
this is so true a friend of 20 years
posted a nasty video about plant-based
eating that was directed towards me I
was like what the F this is important to
understand when you're you're struggling
with chronic illness so I want you to
know this isn't just this isn't just a
rant on you know what you eat what you
don't eat what's going on on the
internet I I'm not trying to do that
today what I'm trying to tell you is
when you're chronically sick that's when
everything shifts and we're going to get
into that this is why this is so
important right here
okay so the plant-based people in the
vegan people I find this really
interesting you guys they're
desperate
desperate for Science and they have been
for
years because they somehow need to tell
all their doctors and all their family
doctors that I can be plant-based and I
can be vegan and here's some science
right here doctor
doctor give me the
news doctor I have protein in my diet
here's a study there's protein in here
here's a study there's vitamins in my
greens there's study there's vitamins in
my beans and this has been going on for
years and years it's a despera livity to
teach and to try to like let people know
there's protein here now I want you to
know that I am on neither side of the
aisle thank you I'll give you a curtsy
and a bow
anyway um step right up on this side of
the aisle please oh would you like to go
on this side of the aisle here sir ma'am
would you like to be on this side I'm
not on either side of the aisle medical
medium welcomes animal protein people
into the community and lordy B that is
what probably 70% of the medical medium
Community is animal protein
eaters okay very
interesting medical medum information
welcomes anybody who's plant-based into
the medical M Community or or whatever
you'd like to be I'm on either side of
the aisle very important right here I
welcome animal protein eaters and
plant-based or vegan eaters
alike anyway it's the end of the day you
it's the end of the day I'm doing my
best okay let's go into it a little bit
food Wars we hear moderation often as
advice about food itself we don't see a
lot of moderation in how people debate
about food it's very common to see
people go to extremes and Def in their
chosen food belief system and one thing
I'll tell you right now this is
incredible the plant-based and the vegan
movement on the animal based movement
think they're so far apart they think
they're so different from each other
they believe they are opposite people
opposite Everything But the irony is
they're closer to each other than
anybody knows and the irony is they're
more alike
than anybody can ever
imagine and they're very similar in so
many ways we're going to cover that that
anyone ever imagines imagined either if
you guys just got in here just quickly
medical medum podcast at Apple podcast I
released a third new episode called food
Wars don't miss it it's an easy listen
packed powerful information you really
have to check out medical medum podcast
and before that I did the alcohol one
and before that I did the micro doing
one catch all three listen to all three
don't miss out medical Me podcast at
Apple
podcast Corney says that love love love
these lives and I love being here
definitely so I want you to know that
there is a war out there and the war
does exist and you can end up on one
side of the other or just eating alive
in the middle of
it if you're somebody who's chronically
sick that's when we're susceptible to
the BS that's out there within this war
that's going going on the war that
ensues right now with the plant-based
people against the animal-based people
the animal based people against the
plant-based people they don't care who
gets hurt in the middle and they don't
care who gets hurt in any way possible
this is important to know they're just
so gung-ho and stuck on their darn food
belief system it doesn't matter if you
get confused or you get persuaded into a
different direction or you get hurt that
doesn't matter because no one
cares let me repeat no one freaking
cares that's how it
works because right now there's this
like industry war going on right now
okay and it's all about the money money
money money it's all about the ching
ching ching is what's happening right
now okay so you got the plantas vegan
people and they're just rising up trying
to sell [ __ ] 24/7 in programs and
courses and everything else rightfully
so everybody's doing that just sell sell
sell sell sell they got the food belief
system they think they figured it all
out they think they got it down out
there and they're out there and they're
screaming their their their their Roar
screaming the Roar and you got the
animal based people and they're like
boom trainers and fitness trainers and
boom protein and everything else and
they're rising up and they're selling
everything under the sun and they're
doing this and this but what you'll find
out that many of the people that are
making the most noise are the least sick
they are not in a place where they ever
got sick enough yet they just partially
got sick for a little while cleaned up
their diet and thought they discovered
Atlantis I want to read something for
you right now and I'm a medical medium
brain saer get it free at the library if
you want looking for Atlantis one reason
to not so sick can find it so hard to
understand the sick ready because even
though they experienced limits in their
health to some degree with conventional
medicine they haven't experienced being
really sick where alternative medicine
is not helping them where holistic
medicine functional medicine alternative
medicine hasn't helped them and that's
the problem what people don't realize
okay the people making the most noise
out there haven't been sick enough yet
chronically ill enough to understand
that even even alternative medicine has
limitations holistic medicine
alternative medicine
intergrative medicine has
limitations and so what happens that the
people screaming out there on both sides
of this aisle of plant-based and vegan
then animal protein right both sides
right of the aisle they're taking all
kinds of signs that they're desperate to
fling at the other side and post and put
out there there and scream in people's
ears they're desperate to throw their
Sciences back at each other over and
over again they're desperate to say you
shouldn't be eating animal protein and
you should be eating animal protein and
it's back and forth and they're into
that whole thing we'll go into it
deeper and what you'll find is these
people screaming and part of the
industry now are hobbyists that never
got sick yet and when they do get sick
everything changes but they never got
reled sick yet this is an important
piece of all of
it for example the not so sick that's
what they are may know that the ant
asset given to them at the conventional
doctor's office didn't work they know
that and they know that they can maybe
take some apple cider vinegar shots and
see if that could make their problem go
away in alternative medicine they know
that if they get rid of some some
processed food some fried greasy Foods
or whatever they know that if they get
get rid of some of the junk Foods they
get rid of some of the pizza that they
can start feeling good maybe they can do
a little bit of intermittent fasting and
they can start picking the pace up and
they're feeling better and they think
they found the Holy Grail they think
they found
Atlantis so people in the plant-based
movement and vegan movement know that an
anti-acid maybe didn't help them at the
conventional doctor's office but yet
they found a little bit of intermittent
fasting get rid of pizzas every day and
clean things up a little bit get
exercising a little bit more and now
they are a guru now they're a guru same
thing in the the animal-based People Too
cut your carbs down a little get rid of
the fried greasy
Foods maybe they'll do some carnivore
stuff I'll do some carnivore stuff where
I pretty much get rid of everything that
is bad for me and then I'll just focus
on some mono eating some chicken for
like a week and then I'm starting to
feel a little bit better and then boom I
found the Holy Grail I found Atlantis
deep underneath the ocean the bottom of
the ocean I found Atlantis but what you
have to understand is they were never
really that sick to begin with so now
they're gurus though I'm Guru I'm a guru
now I figured it all out I did a little
intermittent fasting for a month I
picked it up in the gym yeah now I'm
doing it I'm I'm talking to my
alternative medicine people I'm online
figuring some stuff out maybe I can make
a business out of this so you got
millions of these people now in the
world doing this very thing it's two
sides of the aisle you got the
plant-based people and the vegan people
and then you got the animal based people
and the carnivore people they're all
thinking they're Geniuses they're all
thinking they got it down and they all
think they're actually the experts and
gurus now because they fixed their
little problem that they had easily by
just cutting out the processed
food drinking a little bit more
water and EXC izing a little bit
more okay they hop on the internet they
do their alternative medicine searches
and they feel like they discovered
Atlantis these not so sick people have
full confidence that the alternative
medic medicine belief system is the
Panacea they got full confidence that
alternative medicine is the Panacea you
guys know what I'm talking about
here see car Caro said but they are
doing carnivore for years how is it love
this talk oh I'd love to talk about
Carnival carnivore the carnival diet
okay you ready check this out okay a not
so sick person may believe it's
sacrilege sacrilege if they hear a sick
person claim they haven't healed in
alternative medicine okay get this right
you had all these people and they're
healing their little problems cuz they
never got sick yet really sick yet with
just getting rid of processed foods
exercising a little a little bit more
and trying a little bit of intermittent
fasting cut their carbs down and so
forth whether they're plant-based vegan
or they're animal protein or so forth
and then they run across somebody who's
sick who tried everything and they treat
them like
[ __ ] they treat them like
[ __ ] they run across somebody who is
really chronically sick we're talking
like Ms we're talking about AOS and
maybe not even that we're talking about
serious thyroiditis real thyroid
problems we're talking about all kinds
of different things right aches and
pains neuralgia can't sleep good you got
pain in your jaw your neck you got all
kinds of different aches and pains
fatigue where your body feels like
sandbags serious brain fog migraines and
so forth and they run across these
people and they're just like oh do my
program my program gets rid of processed
foods it gets rid of this it does this
it's got a lot of protein in it check it
out D D D D D here's
$999 and get my program and then you're
like wait a minute you know I'm really
sick I tried this I tried that they'll
laugh in the face of the real
sick and they do and they do it every
day so right now the food Wars is people
who haven't gotten truly sick yet that
believe they figured it all out and they
are the gurus because they're
exercising they're do you know they're
showing off their body every minute
they're doing their selfies and they're
building up their social and now they're
trying to sell crap and they got their
brand going and they're building their
brand up you're just in the way if
you're chronically sick they're for
those people that just came out of
college been eating pizza and drinking
beer and staying up all night and they
get their first UTI and they're like oo
I got a second UTI now and a third utti
I better start looking into alternative
medicine now they look into alternative
medicine they clean up this this they
find some dude or some chick on the
internet on social it seems like they
got it all together they're doing the
training they sell the programs they got
everything and little do they know that
they're really not that sick either so
when they go and they start to shape up
and and get rid of all the junk hey
they're doing pretty good too now they
found the
Panacea but what people don't realize is
the chronically sick who man they got
lupus they got ptic arthritis they got
autoimmune times
10 they're viral low grade viral
infections high-grade viral infections
they're loaded with Metals they're very
sick they got ticks and spasms and aches
and pains and vibrations in the bodies
and Tremors and brain fog and dizziness
and vertigo and tentis in the years and
they're
suffering and suffering and an
intermittent fasting plan didn't work
and another plan didn't work and apple
cider vinegar didn't work and charcoal
didn't work and ionizer water machines
didn't work they'll make it worse those
things are those things are so bad for
you those things will destroy lives and
then you got they're doing all this
stuff it's not working they're trying
this person's program this person
they've already gotten rid of the
processed greasy fried food but they're
sick and they're really struggling with
chronic illness and they're in the way
of the food
Wars they're in the way because it's a
different situation nobody's identifying
it or acknowledging it or understanding
it and the chronically sick
person is dealing with so much more and
you got a whole bunch of ego ego Maniacs
in the
industry that are in the food War
screaming my science is better than
yours my science is better than yours
mine is and the wars between the
plant-based movement trying to prove
themselves all the time to the animal
based movement and the animal based
movement's trying to prove themselves
all the time to the plant-based movement
and that war is ensuing with a bunch of
people that never really got that sick
yet that thinks think they know
everything and they're the ultimate
gurus and then everybody who's
chronically sick is getting confused
confused confused
confused and don't realize that the dude
that's like oh I was sick before and
let's just do my program and look I got
it going on and I'm doing the
weightlifting the jam and I got the
selfies in my videos and by my programs
you can get as strong as I am and they
don't get it they don't get it that
person's got braak that person that's
chronically sick has got brain
inflammation that no one's picking
off they got cranial nerve inflammation
they got the ringing in the ears their
tongue is buzzing and vibrating their
eyes are going like this they get the
vertigo the dizziness or the eggs and
pains or the fatigue or the brain fog
and I could list a 100 other symptoms
but they got the nerve the neurological
problems and they got the metals that
are deep in the organs and they're
suffering and
struggling and they're just in the way
of the food
Wars a Noto sick person may believe it's
saage sacrilege
if you're complaining still after trying
to do alternative medicine
and that alternative medicine doesn't
have its limits that's what they say
that's what the people who are not so
sick it's like alternative medicine
doesn't have its limits I went to a
great alternative doctor I'm fine I got
off of all the junk food I did my
research I'm a researcher I'm a
researcher how many times you hear that
now you see that in people's profiles
it's like
researcher the not so sick person is
also unaware
that as much as a practitioner has
expertise in alternative medicine it
doesn't mean that they have all the
tools and knowledge that means
that just because you're an alternative
practitioner it doesn't mean you have
all the tools in the knowledge if you're
really
sick and you're not well and you've been
there you know that just because you're
an alternative practitioner it doesn't
mean you have all the
answers it just
doesn't
some not so sick individuals can get
very staunch about their remedies even
vindictive so what here's what it means
so in the food Wars some animal-based
people can be staunch on their
stuff on their remedies just staunch and
then the plant-based vegan movement some
of those not so sick people there in the
food Wars man they could be staunch
about their remedies even vindictive
they you can be quick to ridicule
anything that doesn't seem part of the
norm of alternative
medicine anything that's not part of the
norm Right medical medium is not part of
the
norm people who come to Medical medium
information have tried everything
they're not just going to go and come to
Medical medium
information just for any old reason oh
I'll just come to Medical medium
information I won't try the millions of
other alternative crap that's out there
they come to medical medum information
because they've tried it all they've
done it all they've been through hell
and back that's why they come
here this leads to Alternative Medicine
sometimes acting as a cult all doing the
same thing all saying the same thing so
what you'll notice in alternative
medicine and the plant-based movement
and the vegan movement is they all parir
it the same thing as if it's one big
ugly cult
same thing with the animal uh protein
animal-based people all
parting the same thing protein protein
amino acids amino acids it's like a
goddamn
cult that's what it
is because it's really just nothing but
like no protein protein that's what you
have to do families break up because of
the whole protein talk families family
members break up because of the whole
protein talk there's like Calamity that
happens out there that's
unbelievable about where you get your
protein it's one of those like epic epic
topics that just doesn't stop it just
doesn't
stop and so many people are up against
it and so they're up against peer
pressure which is
cultish insanely
cultish because what happens here is
that the people in the food Wars the
staunch animal protein and staunch
plantbase they stand with such
conviction that the other side is wrong
they'll do everything they can to prove
that point in somehow some
way and so they'll just go and attack so
the attacking
happens this leads Salter medicine
sometimes acting as a cult all doing the
same thing all saying the same thing all
belief systems tied together even if
there are subgroups where one Camp
believes in plant-based diet and another
Camp believes in animal proteins they're
still tied together with the same
cultish
Concepts this mentality can lead some of
the not so sick to quickly interrogate
and ridicule and even bully someone
who's sick and seasoned someone who's
been doing something else so what
happens is that there's a lot of
bullying going on out there and
social for whatever your belief system
is the bullying is insane like the
medical
medium
Community was about protecting people
from the bullying because it was so
harsh so harsh out there I mean people
scream at you if you're eating one way
they scream at you if you're eating
another way and that's what it's like in
Social out there medical me Community is
a supportive place for the chronically
ill people who are really chronically
sick this mentality can lead some of the
not so sick people who aren't that sick
people who didn't get really sick yet to
quickly
interrogate and Bully the person who's
really
sick at the same time some of the not so
sick exalt alternative medicine and
you'll see that out there the not so
sick out there they've never been sick
enough but they're building their brands
they're building up they'll exalt
alternative
medicine they'll say cold plunging is
the answer like cold plunging is the
answer and they'll just exalt it on a
pedestal they'll put it up there as an
idol to pray
to and if cold plunging didn't fix you
then you're just screwed
up if cold plunging didn't fix you
you're just yeah you're just screwed up
that's what you
are at the same time some of the not so
sick people exalt alternative medicine
they tend to believe that if the world
of alternative medicine did fail them
certainly conventional medicine would
redeem itself and be there to catch
their fall they believe this even after
having a spell with conventional
medicine that wasn't fixing them that's
another thing that happens in the food
Wars the not so sick people both PL
plant-based and vegan believe that if
they fail somehow if alternative
medicine failed them somehow then
conventional medicine will save them
they really believe that and then the
animal protein based people who are not
so sick right they believe that if they
ever failed and alternative medicine
failed them they believe conventional
medicine will then come in and fix it
and make all their troubles go
way both the not so sick and the sick
are looking for answers though at the
same time The Not So Sick can partake in
past present and future Trends they
usually won't realize the needles not
being moved and they're not making real
progress so if you're not that sick you
can still partake in everything cold
plunging breathing exercises any
meditation um and the list goes on right
this water that stuff you know water
fasting
juice fasting longterm whatever it is so
they believe that they can partake in
all of that but they don't know what's
moving the needle or not cuz they were
never that sick it's like taking
somebody who never got ill yet they only
had a couple little things that they got
better just by cleaning up their diet a
little bit and you just you could put
them through anything really for a while
you can have them try anything and they
really don't know what moves the needle
they just think it's working because hey
they're not
sick their good health or their health
that's good enough is overriding any
effects of anything negative that
they're doing all right so I want to cut
into a couple of other things too you
guys with this so if you guys just got
on got on right here listen to to my
episode food Wars It's medical beam
podcast at Apple podcast check it out
just released today okay check out the
alcohol episode that was before it check
out micro doing that was before that too
as well so if you
can all
right both sides of the aisle animal
based and
plant-based believe that protein is the
answer for
everything they
do they're married to the protein
concept the protein Theory the protein
belief
[Music]
system their
married for
life it's there in their psyche and
their Consciousness and you can't remove
it they learn it at a young age and they
take it from there when they go into the
alternative medicine world it's still
there it started in conventional
medicine it is in the alternative
medicine they think the reason they're
alive is protein so people believe
they're alive because of the protein
they're eating if they're plant-based
they believe they're alive because of
the plant-based protein they're eating
if they're animal based they think
they're alive because of the protein
they're eating is an animal based person
okay this partly comes from most people
being raised on animal protein vegans
and plant-based people won't adopt this
way of eating unless someone convinces
them in a confident manner that there's
protein in plant in a plant-based diet
so that's another thing
too what you'll notice is people moving
into plant
base the only way they're going to move
into plant-base is if they're confident
there's enough protein there because all
it takes is one boo one boo that's it
not enough protein and the person runs
screaming it's like you got somebody
that's starting off of the plant-based
movement a little bit doing plant-base
they're trying it they're feeling a
little better they're they're excited
about what they're eating they're proud
of what they're eating and then someone
all they have to do is just whisper in
their ear it's got no protein and they
will scream and go
running because that is a weapon it's
weaponized and that's happening right
now both animal-based and plant-based
folks are brainwashed to think it's all
about protein because protein sounds
scientific got to keep in mind that
anybody doing a diet of any kind for
their
health they they have to feel their
science behind it in some
way because science becomes like that
comfortable blanket they got a nice
comfy blanket it's a science blanket and
everything's going to be fine cuz
science has all the checks you know
marked off and it's all good and they
feel confident because they're in
they're basking in that warmth and that
comfort of science saving them so if
science says protein and proteins in my
food I'm good they have to feel that
their diet belief system no matter what
kind of name it gets to fancy it up is
science-based people believe if they're
going to be eating something different
or start eating things that are
different and start traveling into that
place of alternative medicine both
animal or or plant they need to think
that there's definitely
science-based within it all both sides
are also brainwashed for
confrontation before people who've gone
plant-based eventually revert to animal
products first they fight back
plant-based folks don't look at animal
based folks and say look we're all
sick inside each side seeks out their
weapons of choice in the form of studies
and research papers because that's
another thing too they
weaponize they weaponize science and
science studies and what you'll not Noti
in the science study Department which is
hilarious is that when someone throws
out a science study or science article
what's in the article isn't even what
they're talking about what's in the
study isn't even what they're talking
about people aren't going to take the
time they're not going to take the time
to read the study they may not even
understand the study if they ever did
read it so that's a weaponized situation
all on its own so when you see somebody
and they're like look this plant-based
diet and this here does this here's a
scientific study for it no one's going
to read it and if they did read it
they'd be like I'm missing something
here because that's not what the person
was even talking about but yet it's
weaponized and used to that
degree both the committed and committed
animal protein people and the committed
plant-based and vegan people call
themselves researchers now I covered
that earlier they spend a lot of time on
the internet looking around for
information so they're researching but
what are they researching searching
that's another thing all on its own star
catcher says over there on YouTube as a
vegan I don't feel desperate for science
we have tons of science behind it well
that's the whole thing that tons of
science behind it is that warm comfy
blanket I was just talking about and
that has to be there for you to actually
probably want to be vegan because you're
saying you have a ton of science behind
it now I'm not against vegan I'm not
against the animal protein that's not
what this is but what you just said
proved my my point that there's a ton of
science behind plant-based so you're not
desperate for science what that means is
this exactly what I said that's your
comfy warm blanket that there's science
behind it and everything's
fine they throw articles at each
other that are science-based so the
plant-based movement is throwing
articles at the animal based the animal
based is throwing articles at the
plant-based that's huge it's happening
every day right now they say well this
keto study says this when it isn't even
a real study it's a survey or an
uninformed observation or a theoretical
paper put together by health
professionals with limited experience on
the subject and if they do reference an
actual clinical study how reputable was
it who funded it was it based on a
handful of paid participants from the
same age and background monitored over a
very short time or was was it something
better than
that meanwhile they're all still getting
sick so let's go into this a little bit
plant-based and animal based people they
fall they might be not so sick to start
with maybe they're healthy enough but
they
drop they
fall over time it happens every day it's
out there and when they start falling
they doubt everything they've ever
done they doubt everything they ever did
what they used what they may may have
should have they thought used whatever
strategy they had whatever belief system
all of it turns into a mud
puddle the minute something happens to
you like you get the exposure or a virus
comes out of dormy and now you're sick
and you're really Doctor shopping
everything
is either on the table or everything is
either off the
table that's when it's like whoa and it
happens every single day I
know because at Medical medium we get
thousands and thousands of
DMS and in those DMS are I was never
sick before in my life I ate good I was
really healthy I'm a trainer of 10 years
I'm desperate in needing your help
because I can't function and I have a
brain fog that's making it so I'm taking
benzo as aines and I don't know what to
do
anymore I thought I had it down every
single day you know I had this one
symptom and it was doing great when I
started intermittent fasting and then I
you everything was great for about 3
months four months I was doing good and
all of a sudden now I can't feel my legs
anymore I've been to five doctors I
don't know what's wrong with me and if
they fall and then it all turns to
Mud every single week every single year
we see it thousands upon thousands of
people that had good health seemingly
everything was good they were
researchers they were connoisseurs of
alternative medicine they they many were
like I don't like Pharmaceuticals and
many were like I don't like this and
they all had this belief system and they
were on either side of the aisle they
were plant-based and vegan or they were
animal prot R and they
fell and many of them are like I'm an
Olympic Athlete aw and I can't even get
out of bed right now and I've been keto
all these years I've tried carnivore I
did good on Carnivore for a while and
I'm Olympic Athlete I'm a gold medalist
I need your help and I'm desperate and I
don't know what to do anymore and I've
been to my like 20th doctor every single
day it's like
this and that's how it works but the
chronically sick who are trying to heal
don't know they're not aware of all this
that's happening they're not aware of
the games in the industry whole bunch of
not so sick people building their brands
screaming science back at each other
confusing
everybody two sides of the aisle you're
either on one aisle or the other and
anybody who's chronically sick and
between you're just kind of like caught
in the mucket of all even if you don't
realize it it happens
I want to talk about how both sides of
the aisle are brainwashed I want to just
cover that one little spot right
here and the thing the thing you know
what happens is things change when
people find medical medium
information you know but I'm just
telling you this is what's happening out
there okay both sides are brainwashed
this is really
interesting the bottom line is that both
sides are brainwashed they're
brainwashed that they can trust the
science behind their
diet the brainwashed that they can trust
the science behind their
diet that one's one of my
favorites they're brainwashed that
protein is
everything vegans and a plant-based
people and the animal-based people are
brainwashed that protein is everything
even if you don't think it or believe it
they do they're brainwashed to comfort
each other
other here's another one too
right okay ready both sides of the food
Wars are brainwashed that intermittent
fasting is healthy all right so I want
to go into this a little bit here this
is powerful information part of this is
in the podcast so check it out if you
can medical Me podcast at Apple podcast
food
Wars all right so their brain washed to
confront each other their both sides are
Brainwashed the intermittent fasting is
healthy and you might hear that right
now and say intermittent fasting is
healthy because it is healthy it
is but it's not healthy medical me
information talks about why in the whole
bit why it's critical not to go too long
without
food because of what happens to the
adrenals and what happens to other
situations with your body so both sides
believe intermittent fasting is healthy
both sides are brainwashed that caffeine
is
good yeah that's right plant-based
doctors all have their caffeine every
single morning the plant-based podcast
doctors have their caffeine plant-based
people think cacao caffeine is really
good for you but the animal based people
believe Cacao is good for you carnivore
people even believe that now everybody
believes that cacao's good for
you
both sides are Brainwashed the quality
salt to
food is good and that Apple CID of
vinegar is good but there's such thing
as too much salt and both sides don't
believe that
now both sides are brainwashed that you
can fix all your problems through
breathing techniques or through
manifesting so right now and I'm not
saying other or different I'm just
saying that both sides plant B based
movement and the animal based movement
believe
okay that they can solve their problems
through breathing techniques and through
manifesting not saying manifesting is
bad or
good I'm just saying that's what they
believe both sides are brainwashed that
chocolate is plant
medicine and it's good for you so that's
one thing that's really interesting too
because it's just like the whole caca
thing but they even believe
chocolate which yeah it's cacao but it
moved into chocolate bars that's even
good it's not just like cacao and you
got like a high quality cacao which
still has caffeine in it still a problem
I know that people eat it fine they
could do what they want but even
chocolate bars like 90% 80% 70%
chocolate with sugar in it the whole bit
you know it's good for you it's plant
medicine people eat chocolate bars every
single day they think they buy the
organic healthy chocolate bars
sustainable and they're like all good so
that's one right
there both sides of the aisle are
brainwashed that you that they don't
create any waste with their food
decisions so whatever food decision
you're making and how you do your diet
and what you do you believe that you
probably don't create that much waste if
you're on one of these sides of the
aisle and both believe that if you ever
challenged
anybody if you ever talked with them or
interviewed them you think they'd be
like oh yeah I create tons of food
waste it's like if you talk to some
animal protein Guru and you tell them
like are you sustainable are you not you
know are you creating too much food
waste they say no way not creating any
food waste and the same thing with
plant-based people like are you creating
any food waste they'd be like no way
we're not contributing to food waste
both sides believe that they're both
brainwashed to believe that
Alicia over there on IG Anthony why do
you think
people bash
mm info after healing with
it so here's how it works with the
bashing medical meme information after
healing with
it it's about brands starting your own
brand okay so what they do is they have
to bash mm
information or people won't go and buy
their new product they're selling which
is like a course a class or some kind of
program so what I'm noticing is the
people that bash medical medium after
using it to heal they're all doing their
business and businesses I'm just telling
you how it is and how it works okay so
if you don't bash medical medium people
are going to be like why should I buy
your $500 course or your $3,000 course
when I can just get free information
from medical medium's books you can get
out the library or just listen to all
his stuff and get free you know lectures
every day from them or whatever it is
and free information and his podcast and
so forth and so what happens is they
bash medical medum information because
they want them to come to
them I'm selling a $3,000 course medical
medium can't do it for you it's it
doesn't work oh yeah know I did heal
from
it and then they changed their tune too
so anybody who's
bashing anybody who's healed using
medical medum information and then they
start their business on social and their
brand and then they bash medical medium
information stop saying medical medium
information heal them and they delete
all their past
posts so that's what they do too and
they say by my products you know by my
you know ionizer water machines and what
you'll notice is a lot of the people
that bash medical Med information their
ionizer water machine sales people the
pyramid
scheme and they know that medical medium
doesn't support the ionizer water
machines so they purposely bash mm for
that but it's about building your brand
and then stepping on the very thing that
healed you and then not telling anybody
it healed you
anymore and then leading them into your
feed and then trying to sell them
whatever program thing you're doing
that's $3,000 $5,000 or $2,000 whatever
it
is I got I don't care if anybody's
trying to make money and doing things
and selling things whatever it is that's
the world we live in that's what
everybody
does but yeah but that is what that's
how they're doing it so that question
you just asked I'm just answering it to
you know how it's done and there's a lot
more info along with that and I can talk
about that for like quite a while but
that's what they do it's about building
your brand hiring like you know taking a
course that teaches you how to take the
information poach it and not cite it
anymore and then re repackage it for
your own program and then [ __ ] on the
person who created that
information and then sell it to some
other people and then bash medical
medium in what seems to be like a kind
of like way where yeah well
it doesn't really help that much and it
didn't really help me that much and you
know try my stuff and a whole bunch of
stuff like that a lot of misinformation
people have mixed in with medical
medium info a lot of people don't
actually learn the info and read the
books themselves so there what's
happening out there too is they're
packaging up medical medium information
they're mixing it with a whole bunch of
other information and they're try to
sell it or they'll just take mm info and
pack [ __ ] up and and try to sell it so
that's what's happening and that's why
while you're seeing that people bashing
medical medium info it's it's a way also
it's a way to try to like get some
haters on board haters are like they're
screaming they just scream and scream so
it's like you get a few haters on board
the haters are now screaming and then
you get a few extra people in and then
you get lucky it's like and it's like
the scratch off tickets at the you know
at the at the liquor store and you get
lucky and all of a sudden you just won a
new person who buys your program for
$1999 and it's like whoa this really
works let me talk more crap about
medical
medium and then they throw a bunch of
like psychological warfare in the mix
where they're just like yeah medical
medium didn't really work it kind of did
but it did meanwhile PE they posted
hundreds of posts about how it saved
their life a like they showed how
literally everything from the celery
juice they Juiced every single morning
for two years changed their life around
they delete all of
that I'm it's just crazy also there are
people in the community pretending to be
a part of the community when they're not
and they're faking it so they can
mislead people and push them off to some
other place and ruin their health that
happens every day in the medical meme
Community it's a whole bunch of people
with fake accounts that are actually
trying to basically dismantle the
medical meme community and they have
like 20 fake
accounts and we know this and they're
out there and they're just in the
community trying to actually persuade
people to not do their hmds to not do
the stuff they need to do for
themselves yeah it's
crazy both sides of the aisle
unknowingly get too much blood drawn
when they get a blood test by the way
Uma over there on YouTube yeah we
witnessed that yeah I
bet it's out there every day both sides
of the aisle believe their food choices
now make them spiritually
enlightened okay so here's how it goes
with the spiritual enlightenment which
is
interesting I mean you see people out
there you can have somebody that they go
plant-based they go
vegan they start doing all this
meditating they start changing their
lives they're doing their yoga they're
doing everything everything and suddenly
now they're spiritually
enlightened right and you would hope
they're spiritually enlightened they're
plant-based they're doing yoga they're
taking care of themselves you would hope
that they're spiritually enlightened but
then what if there's somebody and
they're just an
[ __ ] seriously because there's plenty
of them out there I mean did you ever
run into somebody that's just like they
weren't really a nice person and they
kind of like they betrayed you or they
said something terrible they say
terrible things to you there's people
that get abused by people all the time
out there right there's people that are
gas lit by people all the time out there
okay so are they spiritually enlightened
CU I'm confused I scratched my head on
that one so everybody in a yoga class
every single person and I'm not anti-
yoga I love when people do yoga the
point is everybody's everybody that's in
a yoga class say there's 50 people in a
yoga class every all 50 of them are
doing yoga they're doing their Machi te
they're taking care of themselves
they're they're watching what they eat
they're like into all kinds of cool
stuff all 50 are spiritually enlightened
all 50 people in the yoga studio would
never stab somebody in the back every
last of one of those all 50 would would
be unconditional to other people would
never turn against them would never turn
against a friend would never let
somebody down would never be an [ __ ]
to somebody so every single person in
that yoga class all 50 are spiritually
enlightened and would never hurt
anybody I find that hard to believe
there's bad people there's good people
you see it out there and there's
terrible things that happen every day
out
there and you can have a bad person with
a cold heart doing terrible things
eating just right a little bowl of
berries a little dollop of yogur yogurt
on there or whatever anything like that
you can have a person that's just you
know eating what somewhat clean and
doing like what seems like all this
great
stuff and they're eating say plant-based
or animal based and they're doing it
really good and then they're also mean
and they're mean-hearted and they're
cold blooded and they just let people
down and do terrible things that's just
how it
works both sides believe very much that
they're different than the other
side I talk to plant-based people
right that are in the movement and they
believe they are so different than the
animal- based
people so different and I talk to
animal- based people right that are like
out there in the health
movement and they're doing stuff out
there and they're known in the health
movement I talk to them and they believe
they're so different than the other
side but it's laughable because they're
not they're they're very much
alike they are the same side the same
belief systems and they shop at the same
markets to get their
food and the only difference is that one
eats meat and the other
doesn't ly says you saved my life thank
you I'm honored I'm so happy you're here
so you guys check out the medical
podcast at Apple podcast if you
can on YouTube right there Yi says so so
true and you're the only one speaking on
this I love how you're inclusive and
only about our
well-being the thing is is like there's
a lot of smok and mirrors and there's a
lot of agendas out
there and it's not about the chronically
sick it's just about how people can
move you know
up in the world of The Healing Art
wasn't like this 30 years ago so much it
wasn't like this 20 years ago but right
now there's this game on kind of thing
people are stepping on people and
they're doing everything they can to
just climb up in the ranks of the
alternative social media market and
they're running hundreds of ads and
they're they're spending millions of
dollars a month believe it or not yeah
and they're doing all of this so they
can be like I'm your Guru I'm your
Guru and while all that's happening
there's this food war going on about
belief systems in the mix and in the end
nobody cares about The Chronic Leo I
could see it out there I see it out
there every day they don't really care
they want you to be
fine they want your health to be just
good enough to just buy all their
programs or whatever it is and or
whatever it is they selling and they
want you to just be you just do it and
shut up and no
complaints because they don't want to
know that you're so sick and you tried
everything and it's not working they
don't want to know that and they don't
understand the exposures and the history
of somebody and what they've been
through I mean they're poaching mm info
and acting like they're they do know
about all that I'm noticing that out
there these days but they
don't and it's it's just crazy
crazy if you're not aware of what's
Happening you can be tricked and
confused and that's what they're doing
so many DMS every day from confused
people who saw this video or that video
and this person's information or that
person's information so we get DMS you
know my team gets them every day they
pour in and it's people being confused
and they're just like I was just told
that celery juice is bad for me and when
you look into it the person that told
them that Cel is bad for them are
selling these like
programs these multi-tiered programs and
they're and they're doing all this other
stuff it's actually
deranged and that's what's happening out
there you
guys but look my job is to be a
messenger to just tell people who are
chronically sick okay about this
information out there and how it's
rigged because [ __ ] is rigged out there
see PC says I saw an influencer the
other day he claims that all physical
illness can be healed with positive
thoughts
alone positive thoughts are
critical we don't want negative thoughts
eating our brain
away they're not good for
us but when someone's sick with chronic
illness it doesn't mean that all these
positive thoughts are going to be the
answer to get them out of bed
it can be critical to sustain help
sustain them positive thoughts is
important but I've seen people where
like moms that have kids that are so
sick with chronic illness you guys and
the kids like the moms will tell me how
positive the kids are and all they do is
positive mantras and and happy thoughts
while they're sick and
suffering but they're sick and they're
sick and
suffering because there's so many other
things involved it's not negative
thoughts don't make
somebody sick with autoimmune and
chronic illness and fibromyalgia and
hashimotos thyroiditis and ra and lupus
and every symptom in between a negative
thought doesn't do
that but yes positive thoughts are got
to have positive
thoughts yeah totally get it what you
said youy guys all right check out
medical mean podcast at Apple podcast I
put out three new episodes recently you
probably already listened maybe you guys
didn't some of you check it out onig
vegan is not based on us it's based on
the
animals so it's a lot of different ways
to think about that one right
there so so vegan is not based on us
it's based on animals
animal so many people who claim that
they are vegan run back to eating
animals every single day um this is
Infamous
Infamous if that's the word of choice
for this that
works but so many plant-based people got
sick and then they ran back to eggs that
was the first thing they went back to is
eggs
and they're screaming that you have to
be on
eggs I'm not anti- plant-based I'm not
anti-animal I'm anti-
misinformation I'm anti- lacking
tools I'm anti missing the
knowledge and so you can heal
plant-based and you can heal animal
protein you can heal and medical medium
info is so laxidasical
in the sense where you can come into it
and try any of the tools and customize
it to what you want to do in your life
that's how unbelievable it is it's not
this one thing just got to do it this
way and it's one size fits
all it's the
only thing out
there that you can come into it any way
you want and just start applying it and
take it as far as you want to go even if
they say they are vegan and they did it
just for the animals not their health
the minute they get sick or too many
symptoms they run back to eating animals
and they run back to their doctors for
antibiotics to boot this is exactly what
has happened every day and still does
even people that go plant-based because
of it I can't tell you how many times
I've seen people that were plant-based
that started eating animal products
again and you know what they told me
they told me that they they were vegan
because they didn't want to hurt animals
all of that but because they're sick
they their body needed the protein I
swear to
God I heard that so many times if I had
a feather for every time I heard that I
would be able to fly that's how many
times I've heard that from vegans and
plant-based people that were vegan and
plant-based because they were you they
didn't want to eat any animals and they
were against that and again against
animal testing rightfully so they didn't
want to eat any animals and then they
used they actually got sick and they
used the whole protein thing to justify
it in their mind that their body was
missing protein that must be why they're
sick so they started eating animal
products
again oh my God have you heard someone
do that yet I mean I've heard so many
not judging them
but I've heard it and I've seen it out
there and I've seen a lot more than
that another thing too is restrictions
like
restriction diets and stuff you know
what you know what restriction
is I'll give you a couple things you
know with that oh also I want to say
this also behind closed doors people
don't always do what they should on
social
media even if they say they are vegan
and they say they did it just for
Animals yes even if they say they're
vegan or they say they're animal basted
and they're doing it a certain way it
doesn't mean behind closed doors that it
isn't different like the fly on the wall
if you could be that fly on the wall and
see what some people do after what
they've said you would be like oh my God
you can do a TV show on that
stuff easily a whole series on everybody
saying one thing and then behind closed
doors they're doing something different
it would be a hit show and a hit
series and it happens every
day Tara fruit fear restriction is
restriction yeah there's fruit fear
that's restriction there's sugar fear
that's restriction out there there's the
carb fear that's restriction
carnivore that's restriction you didn't
think the carnivore died restriction you
know what's happening to the carnivore
diet it's actually blown to shreds I
predicted it years
ago I think I haven't even on I have it
on video I predicted it where it would
fall apart because you can't just live
on meat you can't just live on this and
this only so they started adding things
they added like lemon and then they
added like honey and then they add it
like berries this carnivore diet is now
a keto diet carnivore diet is now back
back is now an Atkins diet that's what
the carnivore diet turned into it's
crazy now they're adding orange juice to
the carnivore diet so the carnivore diet
is basically what gets this
crazy and they're adding fruits now to
the carnivore diet there is no carnivore
diet you might get a few people left
over and they're bumping in the walls
they like I'm only on meat I can't I
don't have any energy
anymore and they're bumping in the
walls you might have two or three of
them left but everybody left carnivore
and they're all there're doing fruit now
with
meat he says yep I remember a certain
raw vegan influencers getting outed on
social media for eating meat when the
cameras were off I could name one
influencer I'm not going to name that
was caught eating fish when the cameras
were off and they're a very well-known
plant-based influencer and they were
caught eating fish when the cameras were
off
yeah
exactly but back to the carnivore thing
I can't help it I got to talk about that
a little
bit
yep the carnivore thing is like dead now
there's only a few left over just eating
meat everybody's now brought fruit into
the carnivore diets it's not the
carnivore diet
anymore but restrictions are like all
those things I was saying intermittent
fasting it's
like that's like restricted imagine
imagine telling your kids it's like
um you know you're little ones is like
um you're never going to tell your kids
to intermittent fast right you're never
going to tell your like 10-year-old to
intermittent fast where they don't eat
until
six but it's like Mommy has to intermit
and fast
I'm not going to eat until 9:00 tonight
the whole
day it's restriction I've seen you know
what's crazy is I've seen restriction
stuff okay this is what I've seen I've
seen people talking about medical
meeting being restrictive when it's got
everything like under the sun in it and
and animal protein people do it every
day and plant-based regardless of all
that I've seen
people say it's restricted W they're
showing what they're eating and what
they're
eating is crazy restrictive it was like
crazy it's like portions this big
portion that big portion that big
portion that big of something I'm like
yeah okay all right you guys spend fun
I'm going to eat this burger it's not a
burger all right you guys many blessings
God bless seriously check out the
episode if you get a chance sign up to
the medical medium newsletter please
because I'm going to be announcing some
things and letting you know about stuff
coming up and sign actually follow my
telegram if you get a chance please
check out my telegram putting out some
really great stuff on there and I'm
going to be putting out some good
messages inspiring messages powerful
messages to make sure you check out my
telegram get on my newsletter like I
said and you guys have