e
e e
hello and welcome to night three of the
medical medium Cafe Gratitude pizza
party live stream we are having so much
fun I've had a blast the last two nights
are you guys having fun watching in and
tuning in all around the world isn't
this awesome it's a blast we're going to
kick things off tonight with our first
guest
is going to come and join us now it is
hello I'm going to let them know at home
we're inside tonight because it's
raining and cold in Los
Angeles the weather is thrown us a bit
but we're going to make it work right
yes
absolutely now can you introduce your
name for everyone watching at home my
name is Michelle rlo it's so nice to
meet you and see you yes where did you
travel from to be here this evening I'm
from the Lake Tahoe Reno area beautiful
so yeah a bit of a drive but not too far
or short flight yes short flight yes
would you like to open up and tell us a
little bit about your healing
Journey well I've been chronically ill
for a long time even when I was a child
I had something called valley fever I
lived in the California um Valley and I
contracted it a couple times so I had
weak lungs and I also had weak joints
and I was never diagnosed with really
anything else than that growing up and
and probably my symptoms didn't really
start to be um really noticeable until
after I had kids and I started getting
really a bad chronic fatigue um I
started having few concussions from
accidents throughout my life and my
neuro fatigue was really really bad
where I'd had trouble with my short-term
memory and I wouldn't you know you walk
across the room and you're like what am
I doing over here and then I could never
remember I forget people's names and I
was young at the time and I just was
able to cover it enough where people
didn't really notice it cuz a lot of us
with chronic fatigue become um good
actors and actresses to not disclose
what's going on um but later in life I
was um had Peri I had trouble with my
periods my menstrual cycle um depression
and it wasn't until I got diagnosed with
Mero limes disease I started to really
look into maybe Chang My Lifestyle with
food I started changing different little
things at a time like eliminating gluten
eliminating Dairy and all those things
helped a little but it wasn't really
until I found the medical medium
information in 2018 on a social media
post and it talked about celery and I
thought wow I've tried hundreds of other
things and spent an enormous amount of
money on those things and did not get
any better and maybe some things even
made me worse so I decided to try celery
juice and I really was a dabbler at the
beginning cuz I didn't have the um
capacity to read the books at that point
or nor listen to it on Audible so I
would just look up like an encyclopedia
certain symptoms I was having and and
and do those protocols and little by
little I just it happened so quickly
symptoms were dropping um my allergies
went away my lifelong allergies I had a
nickel allergy I talked about
last night actually that went away so I
got my energy back I was able to work
out again my hair was I was losing hair
in my temples my hair grew back my
eyelashes grew back so just like these
little things started happening but it
wasn't until a little bit later till I
got deeper into the protocols that the
bigger symptoms went away like the
chronic fatigue and the um The Chronic
joint pain excuse me that I was
suffering with I used to be able to
drive without um with Braes on my arms
like this opening the refrigerator with
a
towel having my kids lift the pots up on
the pan up on the stove so all these
protocols using food and healing healing
food and herbs have really created a new
life for me can you talk about a little
bit about the first protocols that you
brought in where you really saw those
changes especially with the joint pain I
brought in a lot of protocols but it
really wasn't until you eliminate those
those brain betrayer Foods especially
like canola oil so I I really did spent
a lot of time in the kitchen PR prepping
my food and bringing my food with me so
that was really important to stay on
track and not not deviate with the no
Foods I also suffered from a caffeine
addiction from chocolate I was a really
big chocolate addict so eliminating that
addiction and the need for caffeine was
really helpful too did you feel that the
more that you fueled your body with
those nourishing foods and the protocols
he recommended
recommends it stopped those cravings for
the chocolate and things like that in
the brain in the Brain book he talks
about the brain shots so and he has a
craving shifter shot that's amazing so I
did a lot of those I did a lot of brain
shots and those are very
helpful what's your one favorite thing
about the medical medium
information well I love it cuz it's free
all the information is free Anthony
delivers all this amazing information to
us and it's right there at our
fingertips the books do cost something
but we they're encyclopedia books full
color for I don't know how they I don't
know how they're printing them for that
price so get the books if you don't have
the books but all on social media has
everything free um there's lots of
people in the community that want to
help other people too which is so
beautiful about the community what does
it mean to you to be surrounded by all
these beautiful people and to be at this
event at Cafe Gratitude enjoying this
pizza party in an environment that
supports healing will you won't find
them more compassionate
group they really are so really you can
say anything you want to these people
and they support you so yeah and so I'm
going to give that back and help other
people too yeah well thank you like so
much the the fact that you have been
brave enough to share your story with
everyone there was a lady I was speaking
to last night and she shared her story
and someone had the same symptoms who
was watching online and they watched
that over and over again for uh
motivation and just it helped them on
their healing journey by hearing that
that person had used these methods to
heal and it's just incredible right oh
yeah it's incredible cuz your body does
want to
heal it does can you share an example of
a specific memory of how your life was
impacted from those uh health issues you
were dealing with prior to Medical
medium information well I couldn't be
active
so I couldn't I did a lot of laying down
and resting resting my nerves um I was
able to do enough to raise children and
have it not be really noticeable that I
was really had chronic fatigue but in
the interim I would just rest a lot so I
think just being active and being
outside I'm able to get out in nature
more and Anthony actually told me last
night to get out of nature more but um
which I love hiking and walking my dog
so all those things have helped me be
more active I do Pilates I play golf now
I play pickle ball and I would never
dream of be able to do any of those
things prior do you have a new
appreciation on being able to do those
things after everything you've gone
through absolutely because I try to have
fun at those activities and not be
competitive and want to win I'm just
there to have fun because I know what
it's like if I can't participate in
those it's not fun at all so I try to
have appreciation for the things I'm
able to do now that's beautiful
yeah yeah what was it that made you want
to attend this
event well this is a community and and
meeting a chance to be in contact with
with aw so and be able to just have a
little brief interaction with him but
it's really the community it's all my
friends these are all my best friends
now all you guys and at home
too I think that's so beautiful I know
you mentioned the community before and
it just it really there is something so
special about this community you can
really feel it in the en here as well at
these events there's nothing quite like
it it's so uplifting and there's such
compassion that's what I love such
compassion all you guys that are
watching at home too just cuz you're not
here tonight doesn't mean we don't love
and miss you so you still get the light
blast yes still get the life blast do
you have an encouraging message you
would like to share with people who are
currently on their healing Journey well
I think just starts slow I started very
slow um in my healing Journey it's been
years um and you just slowly start
adding the protocols one by one and and
use prayer and meditation in the Angels
Anthony provides a lot of free
meditations on um Apple podcast he's
always putting more and more things out
there for us to listen to and i' I've
probably listen to the light meditation
a thousand times so you can still replay
those meditations over and over these
things don't cost a lot of money you can
use a lot of free tools to help yourself
heal too did you also find that on your
healing Journey you had a a lot of
spiritual lessons that you learned as
well good question yes absolutely um I
feel like the more that you clean up the
heavy metals in your brain the closer
you are to God and that's definitely
happened with me yeah cuz I have a
direct line to the angels now so when
you need help they're right there to
call upon so yeah so beautiful BR the
angels and God too yeah thank you so
much for shouting to us thank you so
much for sharing thank you Daniel thank
you so much beautiful enjoy the rest of
your night
thank you we're going to bring our next
guest over
now hello how are you I'm great and you
good thank you my name is daniielle
Danielle I'm elen so lovely to meet you
where did you travel from to be here
tonight uh I liveed in British Columbia
oos British Columbia Canada uh so I
traveled a few days ago I uh took the
plane from Spokan and here I am wow so
why did you want to be here this evening
uh I'm just uh I've been following
medical medium for about seven years
five seven years and it's done a lot for
me it's uh you know grounded me it put
it helped me with depression with
addictions with a lot of symptoms of all
sorts and I just wanted to to meet anony
and uh say thank you and I wanted to
feel the the energy and the uh
uh I don't know I wanted to as as a a
testimony of gratitude I guess to
Anthony he's been so brave doing all he
does and I watch all his videos and read
all his books and uh it's helped me
enormously I had to be here I was sorry
I wasn't here the uh for the Calver City
Event um but then I was relieved when I
was ecstatic when he added some events
and uh and you're here with us what what
is it about this collaboration with Cafe
Gratitude and medical medium that you're
most excited
for um I'm excited that the restaurant
there to uh promote Cafe gr promote
medical medium uh and I I used to live
here I lived here about 20 years ago
Cafe Gratitude was here on you know the
other location and I was excited to to
find out that they they sort of endorsed
him so I wanted to uh to be part of it
it's kind of com full circle yeah I've
been here for the last few days eating
here it's great place okay so what do
you think of the food what's some of
your favorite bits so far from the
medical medium menu here at Cafe
Gratitude well I've had all of it and
it's all great the detox smoothie the
antioxidant smoothie um the celery juice
of course and uh there's a there's a
bowl I forget what it's call but uh all
of it is great it feels it feels
wonderful it really does to to eat that
way to eat I mean it's not a special way
but it's a healing way I mean these all
these food exists and you know we've all
had them before just we we're you know
medical medium people make it a habit to
eat that way I I think so I I I do and
as you can see people are still setting
up for the night uh and we had to come
inside because it's raining right so
we're just going with the flow they're
going to be setting up around us because
we're excited for pizza party but at
least it's not windy tonight it was
windy for the last few days not windy so
it's not really cold no yeah well not
for you yes so I'd love to share a
little bit about your healing journey
and how you discovered the medical
medium
information um well a few years ago I
mean now I've been with medical medium
for seven years um I you know I got sick
when I was in my early 30s I sort of got
some I mean some healing because I
followed some diets here and there I
mean no Dairy no gluten you know the
usual and that helped me a lot and you
know ups and down a lot lots of
traumatic things have happened uh so and
I was still I mean for the last 30 I'm
67 for the last 30 years also I've been
looking for to to Really heal and I was
going down onwards because of some
addictions and and I was I you know you
you named the uh the the methods I've
tried all of them uh nutrition uh yoga
all of it uh I've tried it and I've read
many many books like everybody does and
Anthony mentions that a lot there's a
journey that we all go through and then
we we try different things and we go see
different doctors naturopath osteopath
Al theath we we try all of them and we
spend Fortune doing all of that and I
was also trying to not not only healing
myself but healing uh one of my sisters
that was uh that was uh whose he was
declining and she had no help uh really
from the medical community so uh I was
trying also to to help her and uh I some
naturopath mentioned that book I mean
she funny enough she didn't really
follow it but she mentioned it uh so but
I learned it was you know it was a man
talking to a spirit so I didn't want to
read that type of book
again for another you know for the ex
number of time so I you know I didn't I
didn't follow up on it but I happened to
see an interview with Anthony on
Entertainment Tonight I believe it was
MH and uh that's what hooked me because
what he said was um made sense made made
a lot of sense to me and then I I got
his first book and I read it and made a
lot of sense from what I had gone
through for what my sister had gone
through uh and
observing uh people around me uh from
far or from AF far from a closer uh what
they what their journey in into uh
disease is it made a lot of sense to
me um so uh I started celery juice and
it's hard the first the first few years
because you you have to to uh change
everything um I mean I was lucky because
already I was uh dairy free and
glutenfree but you know you fall off the
wagon you you get depressed and then you
you know there's always this back and
forth going on and uh watching his
videos and reading the books uh helped
me get get on track and um and
uh you know it was hard at first also
because you're sick and I was sick so
you're very tired and you're depressed
and uh brain fog you're
confused uh you have all these symptoms
I had menopause symptoms I had chronic
sinusitis uh you know I would go to the
emergency uh not being able to breathe
either you know it it was accumulating a
lot so you it's it's hard to go through
that and then and still uh hold on to
any method really but I held on to that
one because it was working it was really
helping and it felt very fresh and the
the um all the explanation about it
sounded very uh made a lot of sense to
me so unfortunately I couldn't help my
sister she passed away
thank
you
so I kept going it's still hard to think
about
her
so what was hard just to see her go and
I wish I could have helped
her better and I've
known medical medium before but you know
like life is such that the way things
happen it happened that way so but so I
kept going and I keep going for her and
for me beautiful that's so beautiful and
now you're sharing this deeply moving
story with everyone watching online and
helping other people heal isn't that
beautiful I I hope so I do want to help
anybody that goes through goes through
um disease and u
and ill health and confusion and
depression and all sort of symptoms I do
want to
help can we talk about if you don't mind
opening up and sharing with us uh could
we talk about the symptoms that you have
felt have healed from medical medium
information well depression confusion
although I mean it's not all 100% it's
it still is a a journey
uh so depression confusion brain fog uh
skin
issues uh rest leg restless leg syndrome
was a very brutal one because you can't
sleep you can't you always feel this dis
pain
um chronic sinusitis I've had that all
my life uh since I was I was operated on
I was 14 years old um so that was big
one um you have the the the nose strip
and you have all these symptoms you you
can't breathe and uh doctors don't know
what you know they're not sure if you
have Bron bronchitis or sinusitis and
and they give you a lot of antibi
biotics and it doesn't really work but
you know it
helps you know after so many years
doesn't help much but that's the only
solution that it's help offered so
um uh uh so rest leg syndrome uh
Depression was a big thing um yeah
that's incredible Sho was was big too so
and now you're here at Cafe Gratitude
surrounded by all these other beautiful
healing Warriors it's quite incredible
yeah I'm very grateful for that and it's
it's nice to be in this uh in this
atmosphere and to to have seen that I
was here on Monday and I I I I saw
Anthony and just to look at him and
having this the voice I don't know
there's something about his voice his
presence he so humble too and he's so
brave so I'm very happy to be
here thank you so much for for sharing
with us it's been beautiful can I give
you a hug thank you thank you for being
great thank you enjoy the rest of your
night
okay we're going to talk to our next
guests here like we were talking about
it is raining so we're inside they're
still setting up for the pizza party to
start hello how are you fine fine and
you good thank you nice to see you
hello hi she's
mil gorgeous I love this outfit can you
show your outfit to the
camera yeah oh beautiful look at that
bow
I might need some styling tips from her
thank you you you I think you're quite
good oh thank you thank you so can we
get you to say your name as well for the
C my name is Rio beautiful to see you
thank you so what was it about this
event that made you want to attend uh
well um um yeah like anony itself I we
want to meet him uh we we came also
yesterday with my husband and uh yeah
right now we wanted also to to get our
daughter to get the light blast also for
her yeah yeah like uh yeah yesterday we
we had it also and it was quite I think
it was quite powerful and uh yeah we we
were we are really excited also on
meeting all the people and uh yeah
trying the food of course and um yes
like um H yeah knowing all this
community that is is so so strong and so
and so so loving I would say and then
yeah you can share all the our all our
experiences and and um yeah you have
people that can understand you also what
what have you been through do you love
meeting up in a place like this where
you can share your experiences with one
another do you find that uplifting and
inspiring yeah yeah quite quite
inspiring quite uh yeah quite um yeah I
I would say quite amazing yeah it's it's
uh to to meet also new people but also
like to meet the the people that yeah we
have already met and we have already
been uh yeah we are staying also with
some uh friends right now and uh yeah to
share all this uh with with them it's
it's quite uh ni quite amazing yeah I
feel like there's almost like an
unspoken understanding between one
another in the community yes yes yes
it's is like for me is the first time
I'm coming to to California to one of
the eventss uh my husband is I think the
second or third and uh yeah like he was
telling me every all the time like yeah
you should come here everyone is really
amazing you you're going to H make a
connection really fast with everyone and
I was really really uh curious about it
and uh yeah now that I'm here I I can I
can understand it like with everyone
like that I have met uh it's it's a it's
a yeah immediate connection and and uh
speaking uh speaking quite open about
everything and like that they have
immediate understanding of of of the
situation and uh compassion I would say
about it because uh no one you you can
say that no one is judging no one is uh
wanting to be better than other person
is just just like pure love I would say
yeah what are some of your favorite
protocols with the medical medium
information yeah I would say the 369
yeah it's a we yeah I have done it quite
some times and and also my husband well
my husband is it's a I I always think
he's he's a extreme like really like
hardcore I say always and uh I I am uh I
am not such a hardcore but I do quite
often the the the the clanes and right
now with with the I'm pregnant so with
the pregnancy I do the simplified or
yeah like yeah so yeah that that one I
would say is the you can feel it in the
in the in the
cleanse you can feel it in the cleanse
that that yeah there all the emotions
coming out uh mostly at the at the first
glance cleanses you could feel all the
emotions coming out and all the yeah you
at some moments you were so you were
more I was more Moody uh yeah like
lately I haven't felt such I think uh
yeah that is already gone but uh yeah
the first ones were quite heavy I would
say with with the with the moodiness and
then sometimes if we we were doing both
the cleanses yeah oh my God it was quite
heavy but afterwards yeah you you can
see you can feel the difference um I was
yeah I I am still healing on that but I
am really I was really anxious and uh
really yeah I would say insecure and
this I I do see that it's getting better
better better sorry and and uh also I
had a lot of migraines and uh and acne
like really a lot of Anne and yeah it's
uh yeah it's improving it's it's
incredible does this little one does MAA
do any of the medical medium information
protocols nor she's more doing uh yeah
fruits vegetables like she does some
celer juice in the morning uh sometimes
and also the smoothies the the the heavy
metal detox smoothie yeah she she likes
it and The Liver Rescue smothie yes yes
yes and she she when she was born she
had the eczema and and now it's gone
yeah incredible yes you having fun on
your trip H she doesn't speak it she
doesn't speak English okay
okay she's having fun yes she's having a
lot of fun yes beautiful beautiful well
enjoy the evening thank you so much for
talking to us again I love that you all
do the medical medium information as a
family that's great and what an awesome
experience you get tonight with your
daughter thank you thank you very much
you
too hello how are you next
guest
hi I'm Danielle Athena I'm Danielle
hello my name is Nicholas so nice to
meet you so where did you travel from to
be here tonight of
Florida beautiful what made you want to
come tonight um well um pretty much all
the food and everything to meet Anthony
y meet Anthony
yeah you're going to have amazing time
it absolutely I'm definitely going to
have a great
time can you tell me a little bit about
how you came across the medical medium
information and how long you've been
using it for we have a little Echo here
don't we it's you can hear it's a little
distracting uh we've been doing medical
medium since 2015 and I found Anthony
looking for help to to heal him with um
heavy metals you know autism and
OCD and I mean it's it's been a
lifesaver so yeah so that's we've been
doing all the stuff since you know all
the books as the books have come out mhm
you followed each book as they've come
out wow incredible and what's are some
of the symptoms and conditions you feel
have benefited from medical medium
information well for me I healed my
endometriosis and um arthritis and like
for my husband doing the heavy metal
smoothie just within 3 weeks he had a
tremble and that completely like went
away and then for him just feeling
better all around you know better moods
and I've been recently I was also
recently like you know suffering from a
little bit of brain fog and social
anxiety and Riders block which is very
annoying mhm but you feel the heavy
metal detox smoothie and other protocols
help with that a little bit Yeah brain
shots and all the tinctures yeah yeah so
what are some of your favorite protocols
from the medical medium information that
you really feel help Propel your healing
Journey forward the cleanses for sure
yeah definitely the cleanses we always
see really good movement when we do the
cleanses we did a 30-day uh brain shot
cleanse and that one was amazing and
everything it's definitely
everything it's everything what are you
most looking forward to tonight um well
um like I said absolutely everything
like the food how about tasting the
sushi rolls yeah definitely tasting the
sushi rolls mhm those sushi rolls have
been a hit they're amazing yes wow it's
great have you enjoyed meeting some of
the community here tonight and
connecting with others absolutely it's
always wonderful to be around everyone
who has you know great warm souls and
everyone's happy to be here and it's
it's really amazing to be around a group
of people who are like that isn't it
beautiful to be in an environment where
people understand your healing Journey
isn't that incredible yep that's
incredible really is yeah it really is
it's very it's very uplifting and
inspiring and then to be here at Cafe
Gratitude where it's such a supportive
environment with this healing food that
you get to enjoy tonight you don't have
to worry about any of the ingredients
right and you can feel the peace here
it's just so calm and comforting and
it's uh very nice to be here yep it's
very nice to be here is there anything
you would like to say to the community
that is watching an encouraging message
to help them with their heiling Journey
just to keep going keep reading the
books keep you know revisiting and just
to keep on going and not to give
up I have the same message
beautiful message thank you so much keep
going guys yes thank you so
much we're going to talk to our next
guest who would like to share their
healing Journey with
us yes we're ready for
you we're still setting up behind us as
well we're inside tonight if you're just
joining us La it is raining here but
we're keeping nice and warm and cozy
inside at Cafe Gratitude yes and what's
your name Elizabeth so lovely to meet
you I'm Danielle Danelle where did you
travel from to be here today Orange
County so oh so not too far yeah what
was it about this event that made you
want to attend this evening well I've
been um following medical medium for
maybe 8 to 10 years so always try and uh
be in his presence whenever I can and of
course enjoy the wonderful food here yes
yeah and could you share a little bit
about your healing journey and how you
discovered the medical medium of
information absolutely yeah so um I have
made a career I'm a dietician by by
trade um so I'm always looking for um
the healthiest way we can take care of
our bodies and um a friend had tipped me
off about his book uh many years ago and
um definitely been incorporating the
morning cleanse for years the celery
juice it is a labor of love there's no
no denying that but uh it's definitely
worth it and what health benefits have
you noticed since incorporating medical
medium
information
um yeah um I've certainly come across
some challenges but again I do feel
fortunate I didn't really start in a
place of um uh major crisis so I use it
for maintenance Health
um keep my glandular system functioning
um
skin of course ball regularity talk
about that um and uh yeah if I if I'm
down and out def pull in the supplements
and um kind of buckle down do a cleanse
if I have something that is
pressing and what does it mean to you to
be here tonight to be surrounded by this
incredible Community yeah I love it
there's always such an amazing energy
and um I love hearing people healing
Journeys yeah and
what is it about hearing other people's
healing Journeys that that you love
hearing about them is it inspiring for
you what what is it yes it's it's
definitely inspiring I'm always like I
mentioned I I work in healthcare so I'm
dealing with patients non-stop every day
and just different ways I can
incorporate even pieces of the
information in other people's plans and
uh see how um powerful it can be when
wied and full it's always just uh it's
it's always amazing it's like seeing a
flower blossom to someone to heal and
recover and so that's incredible that
you're sharing it with other people too
I I love that about this community is
that I think when one person heals they
pass on the message and pass on the
information to help others so everyone's
healing together absolutely yes and of
course they they need to be open and
receptive so it's always I wait for the
cues and if I'm feeling it's the right
moment to introduce a piece of it um
that's always a good place to start so
exactly thank you so much for talking to
us really appreciate it have a beautiful
evening enjoy the night enjoy the
beautiful food you're going to love it
thank you thank you who would like to
share uh their healing Journey with us
next is there anyone else who would like
to talk to us
hello got someone coming over
now hello I'm Danielle hi Danielle I'm
Karen Karen nice to meet you uh where
did you travel from to be here a mile
away on Fourth Street you're just around
the corner I'm so fortunate yeah I'm so
gr grateful for this restaurant I've
been coming much more often since they
have the medical medum dishes it's so
great and the staff is wonderful
everybody's everybody's great here
they're amazing here and isn't it isn't
it amazing that you can just walk around
the corner come here you can get a pizza
you can do a cleanse you can get the
Smoothie you can get the cookies the tea
so much it's it's one of the very few
restaurants that I will eat at and it's
my favorite yeah and it's great that if
your friends want to go somewhere for a
hot drink you can come here you can
suggest here yeah absolutely where they
all if we go out to dinner with me they
know where they're coming yeah yeah and
you know what one night um they were
passing out zinc Anthony sent zinc after
the fires bottles for people who were
you know near the fires it was so it was
just unbelievable wow yeah I didn't know
that that's incredible that you were
here and and he was doing that that's
Anthony wasn't but he sent you he sent
that yeah that he was weight staff was
asking if we wanted Zink bottles so
beautiful yeah like the incredible human
he is yeah I I call this a match made in
heaven yeah literally yeah right it
truly is it truly is so can you share a
little bit about your journey and how
you came across the medical medium
information yeah so I um I was I got
severely constipated that was my first
symptom right for a long time it took me
I I just tried to everything and and
finally I became a colon therapist right
and then you know we were seeing a lot
of this was about 14 years ago and one
of the um one of the other therapists we
were seeing a lot of lime patients com
in at that like lime clients coming in
at that time and um one of the Bri one
of the other therapists sent me a um the
goop article that the first goop article
on lime and my jaw just kind of dropped
and and so so I just I I thought okay
I'm going to try this celery juice so I
bought it every day for like a week and
I I just couldn't believe that I was
like what cell re juice who would have
guessed who would have known that like
it just started working and I was just
like couldn't believe it wow and so then
I got the first book came out and I
start because I other I had other
symptoms that had come upon up after the
you know I had the constipation for a
long time but then I fatigue hit me and
then the brain fog and I I would come
home and crash you know I'd only be able
to do the basics which thank God I you
know I was headed towards mattress
Island but not there yet but um and IID
wake up my head with was a neurological
fatigue I guess my head would feel heavy
like a bowling ball and I couldn't think
straight and I couldn't remember my
daughter's name one time I couldn't even
remember if she was a boy or girl she
was in the other room I woke up I had to
check my
email so and I thought they're going to
somebody's going to you know get me for
early dementia or something and I didn't
know you know what was going to happen
and
um and so thank God you know just right
about that time I got that medical
meeting book and the heavy metal
smoothie and all the other stuff and
within a few months I was I realized oh
I'm I just did four loads of laundry and
I'm still going you know
isn't that a beautiful moment to have I
was like I'm back I'm alive yeah yeah to
know that the turning the corner yeah
did did that happen do
you I mean I've got I've got other
things that happened to me when I was
younger but I haven't really shared them
yet but I I have had moments where I've
really noticed that and this morning
even I just did the celery juice I went
to Cafe Gratitude in Larchmont I had the
celery juice and I had the heavy metal
detox smoothie just to make sure I was
energized for today to keep on top of it
yes yeah
so could you talk a little bit more
about the symptoms and conditions that
you've healed now with this medical
medium information okay well besides the
um constipation The Chronic fatigue the
the brain fog um I had tentis and I had
some insomnia and I had um tinling
feelings and I had and I I was born with
really really dry skin and that was one
that you know very very
flaky when I was younger it wasn't so
badad you know it was definitely dry
skin but as I got older it it was just
so flaky I can send pictures I I should
post that you know before and after soon
and so this Skin Potion that came out a
few you know a little while ago that
helps me so much I mean I still have to
do some liver cleanses some more liver
cleanses I've only done a few um but I
need to do some more of those to really
get the skin you know but the but the
Skin Potion just helps so much to just
manage it you know at least
so yeah that's I wrote some of the other
symptoms down because I forgot them I I
can't remember what the other ones were
but I I I didn't have you know I wasn't
like one of the list of 50 I had maybe
10 or so but still it's lifechanging
it's it's completely life-changing yeah
yeah I will I'll never go back to you
know anything that I was eating before I
I love eating this way so um and yeah
yeah do you love being surrounded by
this community and eating in Cafe
Gratitude I know right yeah yeah what an
incredible night we're going to have
tonight can you describe for people who
are watching at home can you just
describe some of the energy that's
here you know people are waiting out in
the rain and I mean they're not in the
rain but I knew there was going to be
still you know even though is raining
just nobody's not going to come and
everybody's really excited about it I
don't and yeah I don't know it's just
it's just everybody's friendly and
everybody's asking you know questions
about what what your experience is and
things like that yeah it's beautiful
everyone's making friends in line I
think the people behind us are getting
started having a great night yeah I mean
it's not a new atmosphere to me because
I come here a lot so yeah but beautiful
to have it with so many people that have
flown in all around the world to be here
I know I want to go to Germany did you
notice how many people came from Germany
yes there many and they have that um a
huge healing a huge medical medium
Community there and they have that Spa I
think it's in Austria that does the
cleanses I want to
go it's beautiful all these places that
are just helping people's healing
Journey yeah yeah it's it's what the
world needs he's changing the world yeah
that's true yeah thank you so much for
talking to us really appreciate your
time thank you for your healing journey
and sharing it nice to see you yes our
next guest that is ready to join us as
you can see some people are getting
seated at the tables here keeping warm
in the rain but uh we're having fun
we're enjoying it hello how are you I'm
Danielle Jo Cheryl so nice to see you
yes where did you travel from to be here
this evening um down the
street okay you're the second person
with the other she's your friend I'm a
mile away oh wait did she introduce you
to all of this saw I knew about you
became friends through the community or
well actually I had
um actually we met in a parking lot
about 19 I mean 2015 oh and then we
started talking about nutrition and we
just kind of loosely stayed friends but
then when we got back together you know
she told me about the events and I'd
never done that before so and then I
wasn't really doing the full thing so I
got a little more she inspired me she
inspired
I love that everyone's inspiring each
other to be on the right track keep
healthy and and help them with their
healing Journey so can you tell us a
little bit about your healing journey
and some of the benefits you've had from
using medical medium
information well I probably have a
pretty unique story because I've been
suffering wait I don't like the word
suffering I'm going to say I have been
challenged by
PTSD for a little over seven years and
um it was it's a pretty extreme event my
family was killed in a mass shooting and
10 people died 26 people died but 10 of
them were my family oh my God and so
yeah it thank you but anyway I I mean
you know um it happened like my dad
said I don't know if I can say this he
just died a few days ago but um anyway
he said um what today is today and what
happened happened and we don't like what
happened but I
know I know how the story goes and it
ends
good so
beautiful sorry I didn't know I was
going to say
that anyway so um but I hadn't been able
to sleep and I've been having panic
attacks and and my adrenal glands are
waking me up in the middle of the night
and shooting out adrenaline and then I'm
so wak up I never was sleeping and we
were all my friend Karen and I were
already buddies but you know I was
telling her about that and she goes well
have you done the celery juice thing and
I I said well no I really haven't and so
she said okay well I'm going to start
making you celery juice for a while and
then and then um the heavy metal
smoothies and then and then we'll um see
how you like that and before that like I
was like already going to get celery
juice before before she made it for me
cuz I couldn't wait and I was doing it
every day and gradually I okay this is
the biggest thing you know I I I slept 5
hours at a time once I hadn't done that
in over seven years and um now see my
mind freezes so that's one of the things
that's actually it was better until my
dad died so I'm a little bit but um okay
so um I also was able to fall asleep
without listening to something because
when I don't listen I think about what
happened but now I can just close my
eyes and go to sleep
peacefully I'm a little bit I'm a little
bit discombobulated from the current
things that anyway that's okay you're
doing amazing you're doing great thank
you I'm doing the adrenal support and
other
um that's where you know like I'm just I
have like a long-term plan but I'm doing
it one step at a time so I don't get
overwhelmed cuz everything overwhelms me
right now but that's okay and one step
at a time is great
and I mean just the celery juice the
heavy metal detox movie can do so much
for you well and I'm doing the adrenal
stuff too because that's that's where I
have that's where I can feel I can feel
it like my body is telling me my adrenal
glands are telling me we're so tired
please help us so I'm like okay I got
you I got your back I got your back
back so anyway what is it about this
community that you're enjoying so far
this evening um well I mean I love Cafe
Gratitude it's like a place been coming
to for a long time and um but the
medical medium Community is just like
people helping people and I like that
and people sharing ideas people sharing
experiences people helping each other I
already said that yeah no but it's true
and you have such a wonderful friend
that brought you here tonight and the
fact that she was like I'll make you the
celery juice and the smoothie and get
you st isn't that beautiful do it so
that you see and then you don't have the
the stress of starting something new and
it EAS me into it and already then I the
results gave me um the momentum to take
over and start doing it myself and then
where I go by my sorry juice cuz I I
don't have a juicer yet but like um I do
but it's old and I wouldn't use it um
but when I go to buy them they're like
we're so proud of you like you've really
stuck with this you're here every day
and so they notice yeah that's incred
that's big yeah do you have an
encouraging message you would like to
share with the community through that
camera yes through the camera right oh
that made me not
think um I would just say you know our
bodies are our vehicle for
awakening and um they're very sacred and
that everything that we can do to
nourish and help our body allows our
body to help us and if a lizard can grow
a new tail I can grow new adrenal
glands that's beautiful thank you so
much you're so brave and thank you for
sharing that beautiful
oh thank you love you bye bye thank you
so much WoW the stories tonight are
just I I've been holding tears back uh
that was incredible isn't she an amazing
human such a beautiful soul to open up
to us this evening I'm going to get our
next guests now to share their Journey
with us as
well hello hello I'm good thank you I'm
Danielle Danielle I'm Keith Keith my mom
oh so nice to meet you both so what made
you want to come to this event today
well we wanted to experience the whole
medical medium um Gathering and the
blast and just tell our story how we got
here my mom is the one that actually
helped me find the medical medium and it
started about um 2 3 years ago after the
post-pandemic uh covid shots and she
developed like a bloating feeling
discomfort and she
we took her to several doctors even the
several uh primary physicians to get a
second opinion and the second doctor
told us
like she said we don't know what your
symptom is or you're diagnosed or can
anything to help you but if you find
with the answer come back and see me and
I was like okay so I started researching
online and then I found a a psychiatrist
on the one of the online events and she
said something with it's maybe cuz we
tested her for every like um the colons
and everything and nothing was like
everything was normal so she was still
belching and had the bloating feeling on
and off it goes up and down so finally
um I found an online lady that said that
it's could be related to anxiety and
causes like a a tightness in the air and
breathing and everything so then I still
was researching about anxiety and I came
up on a medical medium on Facebook with
one of the I I've seen it before but I
never really looked into it because I
always see the flashes and finally I did
a research and I didn't even know he had
like a uh what is it called all these
books and podcasts and even their own
website so as I started more research I
found deeper into understanding it and I
started putting my mom on the celery
juice and and also um the lemon water
and the morning cleanse and after that
she started healing with her belching
stopped and then her also anxiety and
depression started to
fade yeah and then we were here last uh
summer during the Culver City so we had
the blast and after that it jump started
me into um giving me a boost into I did
the 28 day cleanse right after I got
back for some reason it just like
brought me into like this higher Spirit
of doing it for myself because um the
only thing that really bothered me was I
had acne so I did the the 28 day cleanse
and it healed my acne as well too are
there any other um notices that you felt
you know health benefits that you
noticed after doing that 28 day cleanse
that you may not have been going into
the cleanse to heal but it just happened
anyway yes a lot I had my brain started
going faster was shooting faster the way
I think and talk and everything and then
also um I was feeling a lot happier too
I guess I had a little slight anxiety as
well because I was helping my mom and
dealing with her her anxiety her
depression so I was like oh this will
helped me as well so we both came on
together through the same journey and we
both benefited so both hailing together
yes and my mom is like the most
important person in my life so that's
why I wanted to make sure she heals and
be happy that's so beautiful that you
went into into this helping your mom
with such a pure heart and then you end
up healing as well yes yes and so I'm in
I'm from Vegas so there's a lot of
people I work with also they have their
symptoms so then I'm also helping them
like heal with certain telling them what
to eat and they're starting to also heal
and do the lemon water and the celery
juice as well so it's like it becoming
like now they look at me like I'm like
the person to help them also and I keep
referring everyone to go to Medical
medium and Anthony
Williams to find out more but a lot of
them I think they're just too lazy to go
research on their own and read and so
they they account me to do it depend on
me to do it and then they just listen to
me but I gave them all the information
and where is at to show them how to find
the information as well but that's okay
I think everyone it comes at you know
when it's the right time for them as
well but they'll see you and you'll
Inspire them you know like you already
are yeah it's beautiful what are some of
your favorite parts of the medical
medium information the favorite favorite
parts of the medical medium information
oh man favorite part I I really find I
listen to his uh podcast a lot and just
listening to his stories and all the
information relates to how I'm thinking
so it's the same mindset like I've
because I always been in the health
industry testing a lot of supplements
and everything but I didn't know exactly
like what's the proper the right way
which one is good for you and my mom was
taking collagen too this was the part
that really also helped and she uh we
took her to get a lung CTI chest x-ray
and they found um what is it called
nodules in her chest right in her lungs
so as after that all we started doing
the cleanse and I think we went and got
back a retest 6 months later and it went
away too that how we knew and because we
stopped the collagen I think it was the
collagen that she was taking non-stop in
a lot of collagens cuz she thinks it's
good for her skin a lot of people take
that for their skin yeah they don't nor
right so I we I stopped it from reading
the celery book I have the celery juice
book and it said no collagen on there
that's how I found out and I told my mom
to stop immediately and then after that
uh 6 months later we went back for the
CT scan and her her nodules went away
too that's incredible that's huge
yeah yeah even her stomach the bloating
everything went away even and The Poets
too she got a colonoscopy all the pops
are gone as well w wow H and this is
only within like we just started last
summer since cover City this was our
journey so that's why now we're just
excited to be
here and on top of that not just the
healing and the health benefits I love
anony Williams passion and the the way
he teaches like us to believe in
ourselves and give us hope to help
ourself you know and that it he teaches
us to love life again and love one
another that
compassion it's just everything that
I've that's like who I was before too
it's just around the people sometimes
where you work or you run into a lot of
people those energies kind of drain you
and pull you down but with Anthony
William it's the opposite he gives back
the energy to help us uplift and become
who we truly are so that's what I like
about the medical medium community no
it's incredible and a lot of people talk
about their healing Journey being one
that where they're healing their health
but also very spiritual did you have any
spiritual lessons I certainly did after
my 28 day cleanse it's just like they
were saying in the book it was almost
like going backwards I was going reverse
like back to my 20s and then high school
I had all these memories like all these
uh almost not trauma but the discomfort
it slowly like came out and it just
keeps loosening and fading away and I
was like wanted to keep going on this
spiritual journey with the after the 28
day cleanse and so even today I'm still
I'm excited about the spiritual book
coming out for in March March March 18
all right all right we know the date
we're excited yeah so thank you so much
and isn't your mom so lucky to have you
to introduce you to all this incredible
information from medical media you know
before the medical I was praying and
praying to the upper realm to help my
mom and then all of a sudden it just
came I feel like medic like Anthony just
answered our prayers and because I know
a lot of people run into medical medium
on Facebook and social media but it's
not in their head yet it's like it has
to like grasp you for you to catch it
not anybody can just accept it so it
takes a type of um I don't know like a
um like you have an Infinity with it to
for them to reach out and just grab you
to accept it it's not that easy so it's
almost like a pebble sand in the big
vast river that you know you can accept
this kind of learning and teaching and
stuff so really well uh we're still
setting up inside here for the pizza
party as you can see people are getting
seated and ready for it to begin we're
going to talk to another guest and I
just wanted to thank you both so much
for your time and talking to us thank
you thank thank you so much we're going
to talk to our next guest everyone's
chatting in here I don't know if it's
loud if you can hear that on the live
stream but it's so beautiful cuz
everyone's talking making friends
they're having a great time we're having
a blast if you'd like to join us over
here hello welcome welcome welcome I'm
Danielle nice to meet you nice to meet
Brenda I'm Danielle Wendy so lovely to
meet you where did you both travel from
to be here tonight I came from Northern
California Santa Cruz ni I'm from West
Hills California here in La great great
so why did you want to attend this event
tonight um well we actually met in line
at the last event and so um yeah yeah so
I definitely want more healing obviously
I love being with the medical medium
community and just getting a chance to
see Anthony and be part of a light blast
again so amazing and I've never been to
Cafe Gratitude since my first time
eating here yeah you're in for such a
treat tonight the food is incredible
great what are you most looking forward
to this evening uh the same I mean the
food I love that you know in La we have
such health conscious restaurants
available I've been to cathic gratitude
with the fact that now I have options
that I canot have to worry about always
cooking for myself I can just order and
grab it for a single mom that takes care
of her mom it's so thankful that I have
options I could just go and grab it not
have to stress about you know
sacrificing eating fast food or that is
not healthy for me so to have that
option is I'm really grateful for and
listen to Anthony tonight to be around
like-minded people I met so many people
last time when we were in Aran we met
amazing people we got connections we
became friends she's staying at my place
it's just meeting like-minded people and
making friends that you can support each
other on your journey and encourage each
other and just don't have to worry about
explaining certain things that people
some people don't understand or get no
judgment just really nice to be around
like-minded people that way and then
obviously to hear Anthony because his
presence is just so positive and
uplifting and healing and um he just has
such great you know um things to share
with us knowledge to give us that I'm
just excited to be here and a part of it
and you're staying at her place yes so
awesome and I can't believe the fact
that you met at the event and now you're
here this beautiful friendship has
developed it's so cool it's awesome yeah
we just met in line and we ended up
hanging out at the Culver City right the
one in Calabasas area arowana and
Calabasas yeah yeah yeah and I woke up
that morning and looked at my Instagram
feed and was like oh my gosh she's here
I want to go and I just happened to go
and she was there and she was behind me
in line and or or in front of me in line
and we just started talking we talked
the entire time and then afterwards we
got our shakes and we went hung out in
our cars and drank them talked and yeah
and then we went to the eating thing
afterwards the meal and we danced there
and we ate and we met other people and
we got their information and we've
contacted them I've been around with
William and hanging out and talking to
them and just bringing people together
and um learning things more learning
more things she checks on me I check on
her like I said we're trying to you know
do our best to eat healthy and make
better choices in our lives so it's
great when you have that community and
other people that are like-minded and
also check you on your stuff you know I
had a bad day well it's okay tomorrow's
a new day start over go from here you
know we're not perfect we're just all
trying to get through it and do our best
every day the community is huge it's a
huge part of it yes and it's already
knowing the people that think this way
you already know there's things you
don't have to worry about you know
already just positive uplifting
supportive loving and they just want the
best for you you don't have to worry
about any arguments any like negative
ideas or I you know any judgments like I
said it's just it's a great Community
yeah how long have you both been using
medical medium information
for um preco so I found um actually one
of my physical therapists gave me the
book and I put it on the Shelf I went to
Mexico had some more healing saw one of
the books again I was like hey I have
that book at home started reading it and
I've been doing it ever since yeah what
about you mine was about Co time right
during covid um my ex-husband was
military so he left and I became a
single mom and I was on a lot of
caffeine and I got to where I just felt
awful and my friend had said you know
there's this guy who does celery juice
and I started from there and I mean my
life changed from that I got off
caffeine I've been off it about 5 years
I used to get um eczema and milia that's
all gone never had a problem with that
my energy is through the roof I'm 45 and
I run people around me under the table
my kids that are eight can't keep up
with me my friends that are 20 I go
dancing I dance them under the table
they they cannot keep up with me nobody
I know my age or younger or older can
keep up with me and I tell you and they
they're always shocked when they're like
you don't do caffeine I'm like no just
saler juice and water saler juice and
water yeah incredible incredible so what
are some of the health benefits you've
also noticed from doing using the
medical medum protocol for sure um
salary juice is my go-to I go to Costco
and people are like why do you have 10
bags of celery I was like oh medical
medium I'm always telling everyone about
it whoever will listen and promoting him
and his you know protocol so it I had a
lot of um digestive issues skin issues
um it's just headaches I mean it's hard
to remember all the symptoms I used to
have that I no longer have and the heavy
metal detox I've been really good about
that the lemon water fruit breakfast you
know I just try to add on more and more
the supplements and I play with
different protocols I have all sorts of
things to work on so I just kind of
shift focus and but it's great to get
about the medical medium information you
would like to share you know I just love
that anything that you're going through
like you know I have kids too and one of
my son has been diagnosed with different
things and instead of looking for that
in in medicine looking through that in
food and healing and I feel like also as
being a single mom there's so much on
her plate and there's so much
information and Miss confusion out there
and to be able to have someone who says
let's do it in a way we're not putting
junk in our bodies we're putting
something healing in our bodies um his
recipe books are go-to for me I love to
make those things and have food to go to
to eat throughout the week um and then
just this positive attitude on
everything like when I go on my feet and
I see him he's always talking about
something that I could help you know in
better in your situation whether it's
mental physical emotional it's just like
from top to bottom he's got you you know
I love that I love all of it I mean
there's there's no one thing it's just
and like I said when I meet people that
are like-minded it's just the energy is
just so alive and and um supportive and
loving and I just love to be around
people like that so yeah so many things
honestly to say we got people crossing
back and forth here but as you can see
it's busy it's busy they're setting up
for the pizza party but we're working
with it because there is a lot of rain
outside uh and we're just going with the
flow everyone's in here nice and warm um
and getting set up for dinner so uh
speaking of the recipes that you
mentioned do you have a favorite recipe
you would like to share so the tahini
and the garlic dressing I put that on
salad I put that on any sort of food I
also love the the chili uh the sweet
potato and I've made that for people who
don't like eat me and they're like this
is the best thing I've ever put in my
mouth I love the potato salad as well
the one that has the radishes that one
is one of my favorites I eat that all
the time I mean there are just so many
of them you know like and the teas too
just and then the broth I love to make
that and then store that and then add
that to any of my stews or my pastas or
my soups that's amazing too there's a
ton of them but definitely I think that
tahini dressing was my favorite I can
put it on anything and eat it do you
enjoy the medium recipes as well oh of
course so she mentioned a lot of them
but I love the spinach salad with the
banana and strawberry that's to die for
I I make that for everybody and
everybody loves the different salad
dressing
options um there's so many um I recently
made the guacamole with the sweet
potatoes and so that is you're feeling
like you want something kind of um you
know fatty and yummy but still super
healthy and good for you that's my new
go-to it's been my new favorite have you
guys tried the suet pay dip no I have
that one's really good too yeah yeah
yeah I love to also on the feed there's
more recipes which I'm like okay we need
to get a book on that like there's new
stuff like every couple days that I'm
like I you there's not you can always
find something you're never going to run
out of options for food he's always
looking for there was a pasta one the
other day I was like oh I got to try
that but there's just always new recipes
so it never gets where you're not that
you would get tired of them but if you
did there's more options so many options
someone was saying the other day they
just put in like if they've got potato
they'll just put potato in the website
and then it will give them options for
all the different potato recipes or
they'll just put in the ingredient they
have and then work around that with all
the different options that are online
that's amazing I'm going to do that
thank you for the tip they great tip see
everyone's sharing things we're all
learning here right yeah what I love
about this community we're all here to
support each other thank you so much for
your time enjoy the night enjoy
connecting with everyone and making new
friends thank you thank you so much
really appreciate it thank you so we're
going to get our next guest now to talk
to us we're having a lot of fun uh and
as you can see before people were
crossing back and forth because we're
getting set up for the pizza party to
start uh and food to come out shortly as
well people are sipping on teas they're
having a great time keeping warm hello
Hi how are you hello it's okay it's okay
see we're getting seated it's all
happening inside and we're just going
with the flow we're having fun we're
having a great time right sorry
Patrick oh how are you what's your name
my name's Tracy Tracy and Noah Noah so
nice to meet both of you where did you
travel from San Diego oh nice it's not
too far but a fun trip to LA right yeah
yeah you having fun so far yeah yeah
awesome so how did you discover the
medical medium information so about 9
years ago I had a severe um stasis
outbreak where I ended up losing all the
skin on my hair on my scalp down my neck
down my chest my stomach and then like
sores out throughout my legs and I did a
couple things um that healed me a little
bit and then I found medical medium
information about 9 years ago started
the celery juice and all the protocols
and now like I have no I mean I used to
like ooze Puss In Blood I had to peel
the sheets off at night it was like
terrible and then I feel like it's you
know everything's so meant to be a
couple years ago four years ago now our
her little sister my youngest daughter
were was diagnosed with lymphoma and
we've used medical mediums information
to help support her through her cancer
journey and through all of her
chemotherapy treatments and she had a
bone marrow transplant and so we've just
like been able to
feel I don't know like at peace like
we're doing the right thing and
everything um to support her in the best
way not just through like the
traditional metap side of things
so that's beautiful that you're doing
all together as a family for the most
part like they are on the no they don't
do any no foods and they're vegan plant
forward vegan um but she's not a celery
juice fan
yet and uh you won't do the heavy metal
detox smoothie yet yet but I will tell
you that anything else I mean she'll eat
any vegetable on the table she cooks a
lot yeah that's huge and tonight you're
going to have some delicious food are
you excited to try the pizza yes yes you
got pizza and then at the end there's
going to be some cookies you've got a
tahini cookie and a gingerbread cookie
the ging oh they're so
amazing cookies and tea are you excited
yes yes yes yeah so what is it about the
medical medium community that you
love I just I love how everyone's just
so like at peace with his information
like they know that it comes from above
they know that it comes from a good
source and they just trust and like
everyone just feels to e and flow with
it and there's no within the community
judgment I feel like against other
people and what their journey is even if
they step off the track for a little bit
and they get back on everyone just gives
everybody
Grace so and so does he you know he's
not even you have to be vegan you have
to be this it's like these are things
that you can do to heal while you're
eating other things that might not be as
good for your body I like how he says
it's not a one- siiz fits all yes yeah
that's definitely why I mean I I follow
his protocols pretty strictly but for
other people in my family and in my life
it just feels like it could fit in a lot
better you know yeah yeah and what are
you most looking forward to tonight with
this pizza party just honestly enjoying
it with my daughter it's her birthday on
Monday so it's her birthday present wait
you're March 10 birthday do you know we
have the same birthday we do we do we
have the same birthday oh that's so rare
my Pisces sister here yeah yeah and you
look so gorgeous in your dress I love it
this is early birthday present what a
beautiful night she loves medical medium
she listens to his podcast almost every
night when she falls asleep you fall
asleep to the podcast what's your
favorite one tell her what's your
favorite podcast what's it called I
foret what's called which one is it the
bridge one the what the bridge one oh
you like the bridge meditation mold one
she likes the mold podcast and then the
Bri um what's the meditation um where
you walk across the bridge the bridge
meditation I that so yeah that's amazing
I'm
so so so what a beautiful family thank
you so much happy early birthday I'm
going to be celebrating with you I'm
going to think of you on my birthday too
on our birthday yeah thank you okay okay
we're going to talk to our next guest oh
it is we're having so much fun isn't
that awesome that she's coming here
tonight with her mom to celebrate her
birthday what a great birthday gift and
the fact that she listens to the
meditations it's amazing amazing our
next guest no come in come join me you
don't have to wait I'm Danielle how are
you what's your name Kathy Kathy and
Alicia Alicia you're rocking the hats
there looking good love it keeping warm
in this rain trying to since we left the
umbrella in the car oh okay it's all
good well where did you travel from to
be here this evening San Diego nice San
Diego you know there's a few people from
San Diego you should all connect that
would be
beautiful why did you want to come and
attend this event
tonight just because we love him so much
and everything he's doing for us and
everyone else yeah it's an honor to be
here with him and all of you who um have
put on this event yeah it's means a lot
to us thank you for the opportunity
there's a lot of amazing people that
work behind the scenes as we can see
even just the camera guys here that work
so hard to put this on and aw and
everyone just he they work very very
hard they do an incredible job as you
can see people are still being seated
we'll just let it we'll let it calm down
for a second and then we'll get back to
your story but how did you discover the
medical medium
information through
Alicia um my husband and I she was
very uh excited to tell us about it
which she did on more than one occasion
but one day she brought over her phone
and sat down on the patio table with us
and let us listen to one of his podcast
and something just clicked and we were
both on board I we bought a juicer and
we started doing the sey juice every
morning the supplements you know the
lemon water all day long every day and I
really feel like it's it's been a
wonderful experience it's been very
beneficial wow incredible and you're
doing it as well yes um I found him
through Hay House Radio back just before
his second book was released the
life-changing foods and that last uh big
event in La which at the time I was not
in a position to go and kind of
regretful for many years so what a
beautiful blessing it is that we are
getting that opportunity to see him in
person and experience the gift of a the
light blast so thank you such a blessing
such a blessing and what were some of
the symptoms and conditions you were
dealing with uh prior to using medical
medium information and have you felt
that you have healed some of those oh
absolutely uh my knees you know they're
a lot better
sciatica is a thing of the past my
husband had bladder cancer and had his
bladder remov and he just sailed right
through the whole process because of
this
so we're just most grateful yes yes and
what about you did you have any uh
health benefits from using the
information I have done a lot of healing
and I still have a lot of healing to do
but uh I had severe neurological fatigue
among other things I have severe brain
fog um but I couldn't I couldn't take a
shower um I had little ones I had four
children and they were all young at the
time and I couldn't uh wash my hair
without having to stop and hold on to
the shower bar and take a break and just
physically exhausted and I had have to
go lay down among many many other things
I had Bells Palsy um Migra migraines
severe migraines
debilitating um a lot of things tingles
numbness um so many things it's hard to
remember I'm sorry s it's okay this is
incredible and what a journey you've
been
on Inc thank you for being brave and
opening up and sharing your journey and
inspiring others that are online
watching especially if they're going
through this as well yes thank you I
just remember um when I first found um
his information oh I'm story um it just
burst into tears and I could feel I
could feel that it was true and um what
I've been looking for I feel like my
whole life I had been looking for him
sorry and I
have anyway there so many lopus and like
if you would look at the symptoms of all
I had so many and so many different
categories and they've helped me so
thank you it's incredible it's
incredible I want to give you
thank you to share share it with
everybody we
can about about Anthony William and and
uh the beautiful community that has
grown and it's so beautiful and helpful
so beautiful what are some of you know
you you were going through quite quite a
lot uh what was some of his protocols
that you really felt helped your journey
celery juice there was a point where I
was juicing six six heads of C six
bundles um in the morning um and I had
to we went camping for 2 weeks to Bass
Lake and I brought an ice chest of just
celery and I had to juice every morning
before we were able to go and uh
personally I did to the lake to I I
couldn't function without it so the
lemon water the celery juice the heavy
metal detox smoothie watermelon the
watermelon so it's just been so
um helpful to learn all the new things
that each book brings and I we have them
all and love them all and it's a a gift
and now you're well enough to join us at
these
events it it is a blessing yes yes it is
thank you so much for all that you do
and how you inter so beautifully and
share their stories and I watch at home
on the live stream when I'm not here and
it um it's inspiring so thank you it is
it's very inspiring and because of all
these Brave beautiful Souls opening up
sharing their Journeys you're helping
other people heal and we actually ran
into uh a lady who was watching One
woman's uh healing journey in particular
over and over again and they met last
night in line and that she found it so
inspiring to hear that Journey because
she had the same symptoms so this this
helps people in ways you you can't even
imagine it's incredible right that was
amazing yes cuz you feel lost I I did
all of the I had so many Health that's
all I used to read was Health books and
all the traps and fads and trying to
heal trying to feel better trying to be
able to function and nobody else nobody
else that I knew was like that um so it
was it was hard and lonely and this
makes you realize that you're not alone
and
that you can heal and it gives you hope
cuz
honestly I felt like I was slowly dying
and I remember when I read that in his
book that your liver slowly dies before
you do but I don't feel that way anymore
so she comes with us no it's okay don't
be sorry at all you're incredible this
is amazing thank you it's fantastic to
learn how to eat
correctly yeah which I dream and the
things to stay away from it makes sense
I stayed away from fruit and the the
alkaline diet and the all the wrong
wrong things that made me worse yes very
interesting but now you're here you're
going to celebrate your health enjoy
this incredible four course uh pizza
party with all these other healing
Warriors yes thank you yes I'm going to
say thank you I'll give you a quick hug
thank you so much I'm going to see if we
have our next person thank you so much
take care going to see if we have our
next person it is loud in here I think
everyone is having an amazing time oh
it's just there's so many people making
you friends just enjoying the community
it's
incredible hello hi I'm Danielle so nice
to meet you nice to meet you I'm
Danielle Stephanie so lovely to meet you
where did you both travel from to be
here tonight being phix Arizona yes
Phoenix did you drive or fly we flew
nice why did you want to fly out here
this evening to attend this
event um I mean the medical medium is
awesome and this is a great community
and it's just lovely to be here yeah we
really want to meet him and receive a
light blast in person yeah and just meet
like-minded
people it's a beautiful evening what are
you most excited about with this
collaboration between Cafe Gratitude and
medical
medium oh man I mean the food looks
amazing so I'm excited for that and also
to me Anthony and yeah
exciting yeah definitely the food is
exciting so how did you discover medical
medium information how long have you
been using it for um my mom got me into
it um I've been doing it for about 5
years now and then I started in
2018 like when his right after his first
book came out is when I started reading
and dabbling into it so what compelled
you to get into this what were you going
through at the time um I had eczema that
had just spurred all of a sudden and I
didn't know how to get rid of it I had
seen so many different doctors and
dermatologists and nobody could get rid
of it so I was interested in seeing if I
could help that was initial and then why
share it with your daughter she had some
really weird H situations that I just
like we don't know what was going on so
a l thankful that it was able to help
her I mean that's even more important to
me that helped you and not just
me yeah I had a lot of like heart
palpitations and anxiety and stuff and
my anxiety is almost gone now heart
palpitations are a lot better ever since
I started doing it so just feel
healthier overall so it's great that's
incredible and what are some of your
favorite things about the protocol I
personally love the celery
juice yeah it is good it's refreshing
and it's just a great way to start the
day yeah and did you stop just with the
celery juice or how did you start
implementing things mine was just celery
juice at first and then heavy metal
detox smoothie and then slowly adding
things in and it's just it's really
interesting to see how your taste buds
Chang and all of a sudden vegetables are
just tasting so much better everything
tastes really delicious fruit is amazing
and tastes better than it used to
because your taste buds
change and then can you talk a little
bit more in depth about your health
benefits that you experienced uh using
the medical medium information mhm well
I had developed anxiety and I didn't I
had no idea why and looking back I think
it was related to me taking out some
metal cavities merre cavities so um that
went went away like 95% so that was
really awesome and it was just weird I
would get so anxious and I didn't know
why and then it just all went away and
then right when I started the protocols
I was um just starting to need readers
for vision and then uh with doing the
heavy metal detox then I no longer
needed them so I never really had to use
them so my eyes just improved just
enough where I don't need them I mean I
do use contacts for far away but I don't
need readers so that's incredible yeah
so that was really exciting do you have
an encouraging message you would like to
share with the community watching
online um I mean just start somewhere
and then you'll eventually start to see
the benefits and I mean it can't hurt
you so yeah yeah it's really special
when you start to see some small changes
in your health and the way that you feel
and that other doctors don't know how to
deal with so yeah and now you're here
now you're here after being on your
journey you're here with other healing
Warriors it's great isn't it yes yeah
we're excited to be here have you met
some cool people waiting in line and we
have yes it's a great Community very
nice people very genuine they yes well
I'll let you get seated for tonight's
dinner thank you so much for talking to
us really appreciate you both thank you
thank you uh we have our next guest
coming over the more and more people are
arriving being seated for tonight's
pizza party it is Electric in here it's
we're having so much fun it definitely
is a party hello hi did you want to talk
to us
hello hello yes thank you what's your
name my name is Christina brki I'm from
Germany oh we were just saying earlier
that there's so many people from Germany
here have you met any other people that
have flown in yeah yeah we we came like
this whole bunch of us are here and on
she wants to tell you
something okay yeah the this whole bunch
of us is here we're like seven in the
apartment like in the Airbnb and we have
like I don't know it's like big we have
a big Community you have the second
largest community of medic median people
is in Germany I guess we had the
festival two two years ago and last year
and this year we'll have again one so
medical medium inspired Festival yeah
that's so amazing yeah we have like this
really strong nit Community how
beautiful what was it that made you want
to fly all the way here to attend this
event tonight who was it
Anthony one word is all that's Ned yes
yes I came to the book signing event in
Calver City and then all the other ones
I did online I stayed up in the night
you know 2:00 3:00 with my mom I woke up
my mom and we did both the light blast
every time beautiful yeah and we did
other online blight blast but you know
coming in person is like
Beyond of course it's a whole different
ball game it's yeah it's a different
level how did you discover medical
medium information and how long have you
been using it for I discovered medical
medium in um
2016 I had uh a breakdown in 2014 in
January like I I couldn't function
anymore I was like on metress island I
didn't know what was wrong with me I
tried you know the whole story I tried
everything I I have like this big of a
pile of like medical records of
alternative medic Med medicine I had my
teeth uh I had my my my my jaws drilled
because I thought maybe it's from there
I had an heart inflammation and nobody
took it serious it was really horrible I
thought I was going to die and I think I
would have died and I had serious you
know
also neurological self going on panic
attacks as well and I was so miserable
and the worst thing was that I had a
child I had a young child and that's how
it you know with heavy metals so he was
very like he cried a lot as an infant
and that really I'm a single mom and
that
really pushed me off the cliff I tried
to recover I didn't know I did all the
things wrong like I went on a keto diet
at the end because I was like okay maybe
it's the sugars I eating way too much
sugars so I cut the sugars out and there
was they gave me the last push Chuck
that was it I I just grumbled and
nothing went and I had to to give him to
my parents you know he was like three
four years old and I couldn't function
anymore it's really horrible it's a
really horrible time and you know we
suffered so
much and then 2016 I discovered Anthony
I did a lot of things before that we
already in line I took supplements for
the first time in my life before it's
like vitamin C artificial like I'm never
going to take as corbic acid never so
then I was like okay you might I might
as well try this and then I just look
for the best one and
I had like other supplements that now I
know were coming from my com medium and
somebody told me oh I think you have um
um adrenal issues as well because you
know I had to get up in Wake up in the
in the night because my baby was crying
like 16 times at night and yelling in my
ear and as was like what what oh okay my
baby so you know my my adrenals were
like gone because this was went on for
years that I was so stressed out I
couldn't sleep anymore cuz it took came
so long to fall asleep that I just I was
a mess and my adrenals were a mess I
thought I was going to die next moment
and I took you know ashwaganda for
example I got this book on adrenal
fatigue and I know now that everything
was inspired by medical medium of course
where did they know that ashwaganda
ashwag is for the you know I took but I
took all these supplements how do you
call it this this adrenal from cows I
took I took liver cow's liver
I did everything my vitamin D high do I
did the B12 shots I did everything I
could get my hands on and nothing worked
at the end I did gon Gerson Therapy is
like a you know so I resonated with that
and they took also B12 andum um I
whatever I I took I was in line with
doing at all yes I was doing that and I
was just the coffee Animas like already
hard this heart inflammation like this
low grain infection and I could not
tolerate it I like was going to have a
heart attack so I stopped the thank
goodness I stopped these coffee Animas
because now we know from medical medium
this is like really damaging for the
liver that's the nervous system whatever
I guess too so I I did this and people
were telling me why do you do GS and you
don't have cancer I'm like yeah but what
do I do I don't know what to do well
something's wrong like seriously and I
don't know what it is and no doctor
believes me they all say yeah you're
crazy you know it's just like drawer put
me in the drawer and
so yeah so I found him online one night
because I went to get my jaws like
excavated because I thought maybe
there's an infection in the gum cuz I
had also serious pain jaw pain and the
that dentist I went three times to have
like riew serious surgery and he said
you won't get uh you won't get better
until you have every all the teeth
removed I was like all right then I have
like all my teeth removed I I would have
I was like but wait you know I'm I'm
still looking on I'm still looking and
thankfully I have like my last in my
front that I kept yeah and I found
medical medium and I and there was a
lady sitting next to me like I'm I'm on
uh if you can't work anymore how is it
called again like a disability yes I'm
on disability because of Epstein bar
virus and before that I went to a
practitioner he diagnosed me with
some whatever methods EP bar was among
other things like EP bar is all right
and then when she told me that's the
reason why she was this disabled like oh
this must be serious I'm going to look
into it so one night I went on the
internet AB Ste bar virus I Googled it
and I found Anthony's book Anthony's
website I'm like this is like weird
picture there's this lady lying in this
lawn I was like oh this is very American
but somehow something attracted
me I mean I was
praying Jesus Mary God you know help me
find something I need some something I
can't go like this anymore so then I
don't know a couple of weeks later
probably I found this website I found
Anthony and this book had just come out
in German too the first book and I
ordered it in English because I didn't
have much money it was cheaper thank God
I did because the German translation is
really oh no it's horrible that book my
mom later got it in German the first
book horrible whatever so I took the ger
book I got the English version I open it
I'm like okay that's it you know I doing
I'm doing everything I did right I was
already juicing because of G on I had
all the tools I had the vitamins for my
mom cuz she's very health conscious she
did the green smoothie things and stuff
long before so I started everything
celery juice hmbs the all the
supplements whatever I put my hands on
but I didn't take this the the no foods
that serious so it took me a long time
to really get off the no Foods because I
also because I was feeling better so my
son came in back into my life like I
could I could take a take care of him
more and more and of course he was
eating no Foods you know like a gyro
stuff so I'm like no this smells good
you know have let me have a bite but
then I realized later that it really
makes a difference if I cut out the no
foods and I went fat free and saltree I
mean now I'm I went back a little bit
but I I have that leeway now and I
really I'm so grateful I can't even say
I this saved my life or this knowledge
saves my life and incredible and now
you're healthy to get on a plane to
travel all the way here yeah yeah and I
also I feel the difference between
coming here the first time in June to
the cver city book signing and now like
every time when I have reference points
I feel like it's going up like this and
it's going up like this since 2016 like
every day and it's it's it's a miracle
because I have so much stress in my life
my mom has dementia my son is now a
teenager with tons
of heavy metals in his brain and the
behavior is really like a teenager like
hardcore and I'm a single mom I'm under
so much stress you have no idea and I'm
still healing yeah I'm still healing
it's it's you're doing incredible with
everything yeah you're healing you're
here yeah and I know you've got stress
but isn't this amazing that you're able
to be be healthy enough to handle all of
this and I cured so many symptoms that I
didn't even know I had so what was some
of those yes for example I always had
cold feet always and I was freezing so I
could not
tolerate extreme hot or extreme cold not
even extreme cold little cold I couldn't
tolerate it at all I got much better all
my jaw pain left it's gone you know I
could have just not I could have saved
myself a lot of money and a lot of pain
and my teeth would have still been be
there if I would have found Anthony
before if I would have found him before
my son wouldn't even would have stopped
crying because now I know if I had
detoxed him as an infant we would have a
had a beautiful life so I had to go
through all
this hardship I don't know for what for
a Sal gold maybe I don't know but it's
okay you found it now you're here now
yeah and I'm so like I'm never going to
leave this path yeah it's on my path
it's it's amazing does your son now do
it at all is he open to it as a teenage
boy well he did he used to until uh
about a year ago I guess he fell off the
bandwagon like big before he was even
hardcore than me more hardcore than me
he was like Mom no you don't need that
salt any anymore I'm like no just a
little bit salt for my potatoes you know
he's like no let's put it away and so
and fat like completely fat you don't
need that fat so he was like really on
board doing everything with me even
getting up early in the morning I guess
school school starts at 7:00 so you
would even get up earlier than that like
earlier than 600 just to do the heavy
metal detox everything but then all all
of a sudden he got he fell into the
protein trap mhm and now he's like oh
meat you know meat is fine because meat
can be part of the medical medium diet
but then he started gluten even SED eggs
ouch but then he got sick from the eggs
like scratchy throat and he felt like
okay so I think I should leave the eggs
also I worked on it really hard he just
takes the eggs out but he eats gluten he
eats milk Keir he's he feels nauseous
all the time he's like you know what but
it's just because I ate too much but
it's okay everyone's journey is
different and this is a this isn't a
one-sized fits all uh and he's and I
just pray every day that he comes back
and I know he's not completely off
because when he's sick then he asked me
you know he's taking supplements and
then he asked me to do him a celery
juice yeah and Beau yeah well not not
that but you know he's taking like
whatever but I'm sure you're an
inspiration to him as well you know and
right now he's in opposition but he yes
uh two days ago also Anthony told him
that he was here oh oh yes one day one
night he was here beautiful so beautiful
light blast I'm going to send him
tonight yeah well you're an inspiration
to your family and I'm sure people
watching as well everything you've
healed and your journey has been quite
incredible and you're so beautiful to
open up and share that with everyone
watching thank you so much I really hope
that I can inspire people and I can just
say this is incredible this heal the
healing that's going to come from that
is beyond like it's it's coming from the
Stars this knowledge is like not earth
made it's like God made it's it's
incredible it's swee yes well thank you
so much for your time thank you have a
beautiful evening lovely to meet you too
yes thank you so much dinner thank you
yes yes the life Bloss for sure yes
we're going to grab our next guest I'll
see you a bit later on
yes there are so many people here we're
in Cafe Gratitude in Venice it's a
little bit cold outside tonight and
we've got some rain but everyone's
coming inside warming up with some warm
tea some drinks here hello we have this
lovely family here how are you can I get
you to go say your names for people
watching online what's your name Daisy
Daisy David David Rosie Miriam beautiful
beautiful what a beautiful family so
where did you travel from to be here NC
oh okay and are you loving your time in
Los Angeles is he having fun yes yes how
did you discover medical medium
information do you my mom got really
sick and then she started doing
it and do you notice if she feels better
from doing it definitely really yeah
does that make you happy yes yes do you
join in and do some of the juicing um
sometimes sometimes a lot a lot oh
aren't you awesome can we get you to
move a little bit because the audience
might like to see your face in the
camera you can wave say hello to
everyone hi do you want to inspire some
other kids to get juicing and feel good
right yeah yeah yeah so what made you
want to come to tonight to this event to
meet Anthony and for them to meet
Anthony I already met him once well
aren't you lucky you get an extra time
and you get to come here for the pizza
party are you excited to be here in Los
Angeles for a pizza party yes yeah and
you're going to have cookies and tea yay
oh exciting exciting so what are some of
the health benefits you've noticed from
being on medical medium information um I
mean
everything yeah like got me out of bed
and were you suffering from a lot of
fatigue
and and how did you discover his
info I can see a
just picked up a book at no I on goo
went a poucher on goo yeah yeah and it
it's really helped him as well he brows
up if he has any no foods and it's he's
done a lot of um CLE cleans 369 cleanses
data you want to tell them how it helps
you yeah Inspire some other kids well I
just do the 369 it's pretty hard but if
you really do this
it gets less and less hard
and it just makes me feel better in
every way yeah yeah got lots of energy
do you feel super human you got
superpowers from doing the
cleansers basically
yeah so he's healed a lot of things that
he was dealing with well we're not
healed yet but
yeah yeah if he yeah he's very if he has
any no Foods he will just grow up
straight away so we just can't eat any
of that stuff yeah and what's it like to
do the protocol as a family with the
kids it's a lot of work a I don't do it
perfectly we're not
perfect we're not perfect yeah do you
have fun in the kitchen do you help Mom
in the
kitchen
sometimes it can be fun helping her
juice you should put some music on and
dance around the kitchen you know yeah
yeah we'll get them into that yeah yeah
yeah so what are you most excited about
tonight the light blast the food
probably meeting Anthony and the light
blast yeah I've been eating so much Cafe
Gratitude I'm like stuff right now we've
been eating a lot yeah what have been
some of your favorite foods you've had
from Cafe Gratitude so far some medical
medium Foods I like the sushi is my
favorite yeah what about you guys what
sushi sushi it was really good what did
you like did you like the sushi
um wait actually no the burrito bow I
mean the potato whatever that bow is
yeah with the beans and avocado and
whatever yes well you guys are going to
have so much fun tonight you're in Los
Angeles you're here for a pizza party
you get to meet aw there's going to be a
life blast you're going to have so much
fun there's cookies there's time tea so
many things you going to have a great
time yes yes do you want to say anything
into the cameras you want to say hey to
D hi
hi thank you so much for talking to us
we're a beautiful family thank you so
much thank you we're going to get our
next guest to come and have a chat to us
hello hi I'm good thanks lovely to see
you nice to see you too I'm Danny I
heard you're Danny Danny oh I know this
is going to be great it's going to be
amazing where did you travel from to be
here tonight I came from Orange County
so I wasn't too far um yeah so local
what made you want to attend the event
well I am a big medical medium fan um
and I am just so excited to get the
light blast meet aw in person I went to
The Canyon Club events and I missed him
at airwan right before that event by a
second just a Min minuscule amount of
time so just for the whole experience to
have amazing food pizza no seed oils
everything so yeah I'm so excited such
an amazing night and like you said to
have the food don't worry about seed
oils to be here with everyone such good
energy such good vibes it's just an
amazing community so all all positive
how did you discover medical medium
information um it was through my mom and
my best friend Dalton who I've known
since I was 6 months we joke that we are
souls that flew into Earth together and
uh both of them around the same time in
2018 were like hey you really need to
look at this you know page on Instagram
and at the time I had been searching for
a very long time for some healing I had
done every fat diet at one point I was
doing avocados with bacon because I was
told your brain was made out of fat so I
was doing like the I mean I was trying
everything you know and um just started
doing lemon honey water and started to
feel so good and learned you know the
effects that it had on your liver and
that the lemons detoxed it and the water
rehydrated it and the glue and the Honey
gave you glucose replenishment and I
just got really into it and then started
doing celery juice and then cutting out
the no foods and then doing the vimergy
supplementation and the meditations and
now it's just you know completely
transformed my life I'm living my dream
uh now doing a totally different career
living my purpose and just feeling so
good so much energy so I'm so grateful
that uh my best friend Dalton and my mom
brought me that information and now we
have our own Community you know doing it
so it's just been awesome that's so
awesome how incredible what are some of
the health benefits you've really
noticed the difference uh of healing
from medical medum information I was I
always had a very addictive personality
from a very young age and so when I was
younger I had eating disorders and then
when I was in college I just felt like I
couldn't keep up I started taking
Aderall and then I started smoking weed
and obviously reading the literature and
reading the scripture of the books I
realized that that was heavy metals so I
started detoxing the heavy metals and
now I am free of all of that and I just
wake up myself and with so much energy
and um don't have those chains of
addiction anymore so that would be
something huge but I was telling Amber
on an interview too there's so many
peripheral healing that has taken place
as well like I used to hate to travel
with my husband because I would get such
high travel anxiety and it just then I'd
be on the vacation and it wouldn't be
fun you know i' I'd have anxiety or um
whatever it may be all that's gone I've
gone now I've done two trips to Italy
I've gone to Cabo many times I am
excited to travel and have these
experiences so um it it's just so
incredible um the list of healing is so
immense but obviously freeing yourself
of addiction is huge reconnecting with
My Soul living my dream and you know
being able to experience life in such a
fuller manner has just been and
lifechanging say reconnecting with your
soul were there any uh spiritual lessons
you learned on your way your your
healing way well I think it's funny that
medical medium says that not a lot of
people pray to the angels because I feel
like I got a direct line every day I'm
like Angel of Mercy Angel of the unknown
Angels you know so I am so connected
with praying to the angels and calling
on them for help and and God as well and
um that wasn't as woven into my daily
life I was always you know a believer
and spiritual but it's just deepened
that relationship for myself um and then
also the meditations like there has been
times where I've done the full moon
emotional wounds healing meditation
where I've just balled and I could
literally feel um you know pain and and
toxic energy being pulled out of my body
so I mean all of it it's all been so
amazing um for me so what is one of the
most profound lessons you've learned on
your journey of healing these these
conditions you are dealing with most
profound lesson from
healing I think that God gave us
everything we need to
heal and there's evil out there that is
trying to keep us sick and if you keep
searching I was around 30 when I started
sou searching in FA medical medium I was
really trying to find a way to heal um
it's out there and that your body wants
to heal you know your body really does
want to heal and it works I tried
everything so I know this works so um I
think the biggest lesson is just God is
good and the tools and the resources are
out there and there's a path to healing
for everybody you just have to be
patient and disciplined and use your
free will to get there beautiful
beautiful message you know what it's
time for dinner we're going to cut to
dinner now so we're going to get seated
start enjoying some of the food it is so
there's so much life in here what is
yeah can you can you describe to the
people who are watching what the energy
is like in here just as dinner stops
love compassion healing light light
light light that is that is it right
everybody is so excited and just really
amazing Souls everybody here has gone
through the healing Journey so I feel
like there's just an essence of
gratitude here which is so perfect for
the place right it really is and would
you like to send a nice message to
people watching at home I just want to
say to all the people um watching at
home uh specifically my best friend
Dalton and my husband I love you guys so
much but for anybody that's looking to
heal um take it for me I literally tried
everything I was I had to quit my job my
corporate job and because of the medical
medium information because of the
medical medium tools I have literally
risen From the Ashes I'm living my best
life now it is an amazing Community full
of love compassion and gratitude and you
can heal too you absolutely can heal too
and anybody in the community would be so
happy if you reached out to them we're
we're willing and ready to welcome you
with open arms so if you feel like
you're suffering right now um the
answers are right around the corner
start looking in a medical medium and uh
you will find Healing absolutely wow wow
what a beautiful message we're going to
head uh over and enjoy some dinner uh
take you to dinner with us we hope
you're having a great time watching this
live stream thank you so much for that
beautiful message uh we'll take a break
for now and just enjoy some beautiful
food here at the pizza party night three
we're having a blast W I love it bye bye
[Music]
guys e
[Applause]
spe
e
[Music]
e e
you
e
e e
[Applause]
schle wasn't so e
okay
I feel
that yes
[Applause]
[Music]
these are individual
okay thank you
over
[Applause]
right
e
[Applause]
e e
[Music]
inter
e e
hear
she
table
minut
[Music]
e for
actually
[Music]
e
e e
[Applause]
you
spe
e
e e
[Applause]
s
we are having so much fun tonight we're
here they're just finishing up the
beautiful sushi rolls how were they oh
they were just awesome I love the sushi
yes and my most favorite and the energy
here is just incredible you know what's
up next though the meet and greet with
aw are you excited for that I cannot
wait I'm always that's the most exciting
part for me of the evening I mean
besides the
food it's just a great night guys let's
go over and check out that Ma and great
now let's have a blast oh yeah let's do
that let's do it
guys thank you thank you so much that
was
fun to meet you I know close right here
I know right there well it's a pleasure
and I I'm right now I go to UCLA really
and I'm really excited to meet you
because I feel like more young people
need to have the opportunity to do these
things early before it's too late wow I
love that I love that no it's true right
I mean younger people need to take care
of themselves before something happens
but it's not how things work you know
right it just doesn't seem like that's
how it works you're indestructible
indestructible and then something goes
wrong right hopefully trying to share
more of that before everything goes
wrong I learned it from my parents all
the protocols who are you kidding yeah
no way it's it's fun my parents and I
have got to grow together in some ways
wow so they never told me you should do
this because this is good for you they
were just like that's the book I read
picked it up went actually he has a
point and and it works and it's lovely
and all the energy that I've rece I'm
blown away man I'm Blown Away seriously
it's really lovely and I taken after you
I wrote a book myself you did tell me
about it I wrote a little book of poetry
called what's real who it's all about
going through like what is real for us
and what do we care about whoa so um
it's it's where can I where where can I
read that book I have a copy that I can
give you if you'd like yeah I'd love a
copy later okay sounds good all right
amazing pleasure thank you for coming
okay enjoy the food thank you lovely
okay amazing thank you for coming I
appreciate you
right hey how you doing
good to see you I'm not crying today no
you're not amazing doing better I just
want to let you know that you are like
the only one over the years you've never
let me down I've like listened to your
voice as I'm going to sleep the
meditation is the moon meditation
everything so you've been there with me
through th then a lot over the years so
just thank you for being a trooper and
listening to the podcasts and everything
and everything that is great that is
great
I I doing it I'm doing it all M oh bless
your heart that's amazing you want to
get a picture yeah I would love to yeah
here step forward a little bit yeah
we're good how's
this well you know I'm proud of you
right I do seriously I hear you all the
time and just your positivity yeah and
you're doing the protocols you're doing
different things for yourself doing it
all reading all the books doing
everything cool there a lot of info in
there it's just like and then you go
back to them like wait
where was that yeah exactly you always
miss something that's I keep rereading
all the time and listening to the
podcast over and over all the time too
just always hear something new every
time too I'll try to keep them coming
I'll try to keep the podcast com I know
it's so much work well thank you you so
much Anthony I love you so much thank
you for coming tonight okay all right
have a good night too with the food and
everything how are you hey pleasure to
meet you nice to meet you yeah my entry
into the health world was through
fruitarianism and and my girlfriend Abby
speaks all about you and all thetical
medium and you really changed her life
and I'm just you know expressing did you
bring in some leafy greens did you bring
those in no you are you're bringing
those in yeah no it's it's it's a more
incom more incompass and diet so okay
yeah I just started like less than a
month ago really yeah that's perfect I
love that I love hearing that okay just
a month that's amazing right but you're
probably going to stay on it I can tell
you're going to stay with it yeah I can
I can feel it I know you're going to
yeah it's happening as we speak well I'm
proud of you okay want to get a picture
sure thanks so much pleas have some
great food yeah all right thank
you Christian how's it going get over
here brother how you doing huh how you
doing doing great come on how's my buddy
doing all right good good good life is
good life is is good yeah man you're the
best you're the
best so what's happening um I've been
working on music really tell me about
tell me about it so um yeah if it wasn't
for music I wouldn't have found my
median my gu really yeah my guitar
teacher told me about you play guitar
yeah I love guitar what kind of guitar
you got lus Ian yeah what kind ianz wow
that's cool that's cool that's amazing
that's I love ivanz guitars and I sing
too and you sing too yeah I sing the
best thing I ever heard and I actually
wanted to play drums before that guitar
really yeah really wow I'm blown away
okay I'm going away well keep on playing
for sure you got to you got to I got to
hear some of your stuff someday man for
sure I got some good songs all right
cool cool I'm looking forward to that
let's get a
[Music]
picture you're the man okay all right
love you too love you too brother
thank you you got it yeah let's see if I
do hello Anthony what's going on what's
going on Lara 1444 how you
doing how do you know
this okay um so I just wanted to thank
you for everything and that you're so
strong and that I can heal because of
your information and I wanted to ask if
um Spirit of compassion is maybe a
message for
me what is your favorite thing to
do I don't know do you know what your
favorite thing to do is you don't have a
favorite thing I don't know it now right
now no
no no spirit says you got to find that
favorite thing you do and and you got to
like you got to do it okay okay it could
be his smallest thing okay right but it
but that's what spirit's saying you want
to get a picture yes you're the best
amazing amazing you're having some good
food tonight
yes okay thank
you Anthony hello to see you good to
good to see you too Anthony um seriously
I have um I wrote a poem for you I want
to hear you got it right here I have it
right here I hope it's I get is it a is
it a big one it's it's a little one I
try you want to read it or no it's it's
okay when I yeah yeah
okay I was lost so sick and blind traid
in the darkness hope behind then a voice
so clear so true come through spirit and
through you you spoke of angels unseen
light of battles fought beyond our sight
your words broke change and set me free
broke back back my soul my destiny and
now I Rise Unchained set free a light
Warrior strong Clarity the war is real
the light must grow and thanks to you
now I know Anthony for all you do no
words are enough but really thank you I
love you for that thank you it it it
truly truly touches my heart it does it
does thank you so much for everything me
it means the world it means the
world you're an amazing poet too an
amazing to get my English a little bit
better how did you how did you do it
like you you feel like it came from from
some place did it did it come from an
angel did it come from above from The
Ether that's amazing so I I tried to get
a little bit help and I
tried to through this to improve a
little bit my English to get more into
it because I get the feeling to bring
the right words together it's amazing I
was trying to say just thank you and
it's amazing okay I love you for it
thank you so much for everything to do
thank you have a good time
I had to come one more time hey how are
you it's been so
long it might be a better picture we
never know I know
exactly sure absolutely hi what's going
on here you guys nice to meet you nice
to meet you look at you how you doing oh
my God amazing you helping us and
helping my daughter how are you doing
how are you doing great oh thanks to you
thank you oh I love hearing that a but
you're doing you're doing the work is
this for me thank you so great do you
guys want to get a picture together okay
okay here step up here want AAL medium
sandwich yeah yeah this is
amazing there we go sorry
oh amazing you you're going enjoy the
food tonight yes we're super excited I
can't wait to read this thank
you hi Mr William you what are you doing
you got a book for me I have a book for
you to sign my name is Melinda this a
pen right here yes
yes I love it thank you so
much thank you for for your gift a and
thank you for the healing this book so
you're reading this book and you're
you're finding things you like in here I
love this book this is this is this is
my Bible as you can tell yeah know it it
it's really it's wonderful it's it's
it's worn so I know you're using it it
is yeah thank you very much I have a few
of those where they're so they're so
beat up and yeah yeah and I don't want
to food is all over them just everything
Pages thank you so much you want to get
a picture do picture with you
amazing enjoy the food
tonight all right you're up thank youth
nice to see you again tonight yes I'd
like to answer ask question for myself
tonight so I'd like to ask for myself
tonight um for my teeth they're falling
apart so much because of all the stress
I had the last couple of years so I
really last couple years have been very
stressful yes and I think the adrenaline
just is e heating them up and what do I
do to stop it is the stress continual
yes and so your adrenaline's always
going up and then when you finally relax
it it goes up again and it goes up again
yes I used to have hot flashes from all
this stuff too I guess but now that
after the light blath it it really like
the hot flashes were gone okay and um
that's good we're going to do another
light blast tonight I know I know but I
what about my teeth like am I what can I
do like in the night put something on it
I'm doing the protocols and everything
but what what can I do to stop the
they like they're like time capsules too
you know from years ago I know and then
I know that but adrenaline tends to
knock all of our nutrients out and
everything I know are you doing more
filler foods are you doing some of the
med Med real medicinal are you doing the
parsley shots for medicinal I try but I
have so much stress that I cannot do
them every day so yeah try to get those
going that's going to help the parsley
shots yes yes so many nutrients come in
from that alone okay for teeth yes oh
yeah very good and I have the house I
live in like is there like we have mold
I think and I don't know do we have Rock
W is there like contaminant still in the
house like is there something wrong with
the house should we move out of this
house or what do we do I'm not I'm not
seeing a big big problem in the house
okay let's get a picture
yes thank you so
much try to get some good food can I ask
you one question about my cat I have one
cat she's so he's so sick and he I think
he has a virus and he didn't die because
of all the supplements but like is there
his name is blueeye you did the B12
right cats the2 okay make sure that's
happening for cats I tell people they
got to have the B12 thank you so
much hello hey so nice to meet ni me you
to see you thank you for coming thank
you very much for doing this I really
appreciate it no you're welcome I've
known about you since 2016 2016 so
basically almost 10 years yes and uh
when I found out that ulra kitis which I
have is from shingles the weight on my
shoulders that I didn't even know I was
carrying just lifted off so thank you
knowing an answer having an answer is so
important yes absolutely are you doing
the the medical medium stuff
periodically through the years have you
been staying consistent when you can
there are just like maybe a handful of
things I'm consistent with and I know
that I can do more but even those few
things like the lemon water in the
morning and no fat till 12:00 noon
that's as far as I can go have certain
supplements that's incredible I'm so
happy to here just want to get a picture
I'd love
to thank you enjoy the food quickly if I
could askes uh does s so have any
message for
me well one of the things is try to stay
consistent like what you're doing with
the basics that you do some of those
Basics don't don't get you know don't
stop those right and then every now and
then just bring in something a little
different okay okay thank you so much
you're wonderful
thank hello I'm Vivian thanks for being
here a lot of people need done a lot of
more of your time so I can just take a
picture with you thank you for Happ here
that was my sister
that she came here from New Mexico I'm
here from Dallas Texas oh my God it's
incredible hey
Mikey I'm not talking his ear
off thank you for coming enjoy the food
thank you I am it's been
Del hiy to see Lisa how are you hey Lisa
honored to see you thank you thanks for
coming yeah I'm happy to be here oh my
God amazing I've seen a healing miracles
in my life Wow and then when I saw you I
was like wow he's kind of onto one so
she's my friend she invited me no way
you want to come in here too she's with
me she took me but really that's amaz
you guys want to get a picture of
together how long you been doing medical
medium um on and off for quite a few
years I came to your event at uh aan
cbus oh no no way yeah that was so sweet
that was like one of the most generous
cool events
my God I can't believe you're a C thank
you for coming that was amazing so cool
what you did I mean in all the we did
the ice packs outside we did umbrellas
it was
100 yes I really wanted to thank you
for that and I just wanted to see if you
have anything that Spirit wants to say
to
me I mean you you're no straight around
health and wellness okay but spirit says
you can do there's some some things that
you know you should be doing I don't
know what they are right now cuz we
would need a little time but there's
some things that you know that you could
do and you're like well no don't want to
do that right now so think just think
about what this might be okay thank you
so much close your
[Music]
heart what's going on what's happening
dude every nothing you came you came out
here for a dinner yes what about you
what's going on uh not much not much oh
no really not much that's okay hi hi
anony good to see you good to see you
got all the kids amazing do you guys
want a picture together what do you
think Mikey how do we do
this okay you ready
I'm Rosie Rosie look say
hey guys excited for some good food
pizza what about
pizza I'm I'm
excited I ate a couple of them last
night and I'm ready for another round
tonight so what else is going everything
else is good oh you have pict how far
did you guys how far did you guys come
North Carolina North Carolina you went
from North Carolina to here yeah are you
kidding what was the plan flight right
how was it was it like we about missed
it you you almost missed it the plan
flight everything went wrong yesterday
oh you just came in oh my God you guys
are Troopers okay is there anything
Spirit of compassion has to say do you
guys do the wild blueberry stuff are you
guys doing it what's your favorite
medical medium
stuff mine is
probably do you do the Frozen pop do you
do the do you make any frozen popsicles
done like
969 yeah what are you
kidding what you're doing 369 cleanses
which one simplified simplified that
simplified ain't simple
it's I named it simplified but it's not
simple we don't perfect especially when
the rest of your family is not doing one
with you yeah yeah no then it makes it
even harder you guys are amazing thank
you for coming thank you for coming you
guys are going to have some good food
yes seriously and we making that trip
from North Carolina okay you know I love
you guys for it right than you
Anthony wait what's this no way really
what says on that what's on here speak
out
loud it's read on the B you can read it
on the oh no really it's a house on fire
and that means the body's toxin
wa and it's the fire fighter is the
healing foods put W that is
incredible seriously we just get you
guys to
get you want to get a picture of hold
these do you guys want to hold
these all you
ready amazing should I take these are
they
mine you're the best have anything to
say about
me um you're take you're taking care of
yourself you're you're focused on it
yeah yeah everything definitely do you
do nature stuff do you get out cuz
that's what spirit says you got to get
out a little bit I mean you don't have
to go crazy on some Trails or something
but maybe get yeah getting outside in
the yard more okay thank
you I'm tripping over you be careful be
careful hi don't love you good to see
you I just want to share that I just
celebrated 4 years following the
protocols years and I healed so much and
I've done 22 Advance or 22 cleanses 12
being Advanced but this past year 12
advanced in the rest Advanced uh 369
cleanses yeah no no the Advan like oh
the 369 Advanced not the simplified not
the amazing 22 and 12 were Advanced oh
my God ad this past year I had some
setbacks because my dad passed away and
the greef you know kind of Sidetrack me
but you know one thing that I my heart
it's hard when you go through something
like that it is so hard okay you know
what I never forgot that I was empowered
and I wasn't lost I wasn't confused I
wasn't looking for answers I had already
got the answers I prayed for my prayer
had already been answer because I found
you but I did want to ask if s so had
one tip for me yes go go go do you have
the tip do you have a question now does
S have a tip for me okay okay
[Music]
so do you look at the moon at
night spirit says you you sometimes
spirit says you you you kind of stopped
spirit says don't stop and that's what
Spirit say okay so you stopped okay now
I know why spirit said that okay you got
to get back into that okay okay let's
get a picture but I want to say
Christina borison from Norway says hello
okay she does she does oh my
God over more over I love her over
I wish she was here I wish she was here
I wish she was here can I get a picture
with Joel
too I love the
pictures thank you good thing we got him
dressed up can't take me anywhere but
dressed up move up move up Joel a little
bit move up a little oh we're going
we're going here which one we're doing
we're going here
it's good it's okay thank you w God
bless you bless your heart thank you for
have a good
night thank you all right you guys are
ready very nice to see
you what's going on hi hey it's great to
see you good to see you how are you good
good I'm I'm great I'm great I'm I'm
here I I feel good I'm happy I'm with
everybody this is amazing awesome you're
doing good it's been really rough it has
it's been really rough for four months
since I last saw you oh no yeah but
we're hanging in there we're surviving
okay okay a lot of stress a lot of
stress it's been terrible life is just
not easy I swear it seems like there's a
lot of dark interference I don't know
maybe the spiritual book could help with
some of it I think I I I believe it will
okay I believe it will yeah no I I
understand the challenges uh they just
seem to be always there especially when
you have a very bright light okay then
you get challenged more unfortunately
yeah the better of a person you are the
more you get
challenged keep that in mind
too and if you're a truly truly
you know sacred soul with the utmost
integrity and compassion you'll get
challenged even
more it's just the way it works here
it's so strange it's so strange you get
people that are not good people they
never get challenged until they like
some have a heart attack or something
down the road whatever it is they don't
get challenged the same
way but just you know keep on fighting
the good fight me thank you you're
working for God right I work for God
okay okay amazing let's get a photo here
step but hang in there thank you okay
keep the faith can you talk about the
soul tonight yes I will thank you so
much I
will hey good to see
you love you Jackie thank you so last
time I was here talked about being an mm
husband getting dragged into this you
know I
remember and I I now you're really
dragged into this well so so I went back
and listened cuz I recorded I I
downloaded it I listened to your talk on
Diane Ray's show before you even had
your own show 10 years ago today not 10
years ago today 10 years ago this month
and yeah I had I had my show but I
hopped on her show I remember that and
Jen heard that she heard you on that
that's what are you kidding show that's
house it's 10 years yeah that's Hay
House amazing years my favorite
publisher and I was like holy
crap the information he says has not
changed Timeless it's expanded it's
expanded because I'm only I'm only human
I can
only you know retrieve so much from
Spirit of compassion and try to get it
out there I was really and it always it
always it can't go out sloppy it can't
go it has to go out exact ly the way
it's it should be so it's not
contradicted nothing like that and that
that says something the world has
changed so the information different get
that yeah yeah and the other thing I
want to do I I said it last time I'll
say it again thank you for this thank
you for Michael this guy everybody here
um when I come to
these this is what keeps me going you
know sometimes I got to say I'm not
really happy about doing mm F but I've
been doing the protocols for 10 years
sometimes I'm not happy about doing
anything mm okay it's the people it's
the people that bring me back and I
appreciate you because you made this
community what it is so thank thank you
for hanging in there for a decade okay
yeah love you for it right
here you got
it amazing get some good food get some
good food bless your heart bless your
heart what's going on hi nice to meet
you nice to meet you 5 years ago I was
in a wheelchair and now I am here schol
oh my God thank you so much what's going
on here yeah I got my legs back thanks
to God to Jesus my one and only so and
you thank you so much oh my God okay all
that matters to me you're an inspiration
all right unbelievable you were in a
wheelchair yeah I was and that breaks my
heart to know you you were even
suffering like that it was horrible
you're walking faster than me and you're
moving your legs faster than me okay
yeah I get so emotional I I feel like I
want the lotto cuz I can help my son now
and that's all that matters to me yeah
and and it's better than the lotto
better than the lotto yeah and I wanted
to ask if it's possible if um s so has
anything that could tell me that I could
do to help my son he does a lot of your
protocols but he's a little stuck with
depression and um it's takes time takes
time to get those those little sparkly
things out of the brain it takes time
okay so just you know just keep the
faith like you do and and you don't need
to hear that from me okay you don't need
to hear that for me that's like an
insult me saying keep the faith okay
because I know you have so much of it so
but yeah yeah this let's get a
photo you're going to get some good food
oh we got one here yeah yeah okay you
got
it probably got me where I was like
thank you so
much snap snap
snap hi so nice to be good to see you
guys thanks for coming yeah thanks for
doing this and everything that you do
did you try the food yet yes working on
it working on it amazing you're already
working on it now we got got you in here
is that what it is no I know good to see
you guys yeah thank you I mean where
where did you guys come from how far
Oregon really yeah that's a
hike minor hike compared to other people
I I don't know it's it's a trip that's a
trip well thanks for coming you know
want to get a picture we get a picture
together
amazing how
camera is that a Droid a Droid it's a
Droid you don't know how to use a
Droid
out thanks guys seriously thank you all
right just point and shoot right yeah
what's going on hi I'm back good good
good you should be back come on does S
have a message for me I would love a
message what was so's message
yesterday um that it takes a while takes
time because I was asking how much time
should I 369 cuz I 369 for 8 months
straight and I didn't get a whole lot of
results that I thought I would for 8
months so I was just wondering how or
you got some results you didn't know
about yet yes I believe that too sure so
I would keep on going keep on going
let's get a
picture
amazing oh oh we got one here all right
right all right get some good food all
right bless your heart thank you for all
you do bless your heart hi what's going
on I'm Mindy Mindy what's up nice to
meet you you look so handsome today oh
God I wish I wish thank you I just want
to thank you so much your Protocols of
help improve my health so much oh my God
and I share share with so many people no
I know you do I know you're on social
you're I know I know I've SE I've seen
yes I know and um I just wanted to tell
you that I had the most powerful
experience with your life last about two
years ago you did it over the Internet
oh my God that one was crazy that was
powerful yes oh my God I remember I was
I had to sit down and do that light
blast because it was so strong that I
started standing up and then I was
sitting down with that one that was
really well I had vertigo for like 6
months before that and the next day
after that light last it was gone W
completely gone did you tell Danielle I
didn't no oh my God if you can catch her
and tell her that's so amazing it's
inspirational it was incredible that
that it and lately I'm just um I was
affected by the fires I I can't live in
my apartment it it affects my lungs so
oh my God all the smoke yeah so I'm
going to have to find a new place to
live I'm in a hotel right now I just
wanted to mention that to you you poor
thing God but I'm so happy to be here
and I just I love you so much thanks for
hanging in there with the fires and all
that and just can I give you a hug yeah
of course of course thank you I love you
so much best the best you want to get a
picture
yes
amazing thank you thank you some good
food okay you got a pen you're good
what's going on what's what Jinta Jinta
good to see you amazing you got some
books right there you want me to sign
one of course of course be my greatest
honor okay you wrote this one right no
no you didn't no but that that's funny
because this one's been around a long
time it's a good book then that's a
great guy there that's amazing it's
really
weird I'm going to try to read that
sometime thought that he wrote this no I
know that's so funny thank you so much
let me see this one's mine though this
one's that's a you sign it anyway yeah
do okay do cuz you were here all right
and I'm
here me you want to get a
picture yeah like it's a it's a food
Bible so it's
[Music]
white that's okay let's do this Mikey
let's just open this oh is that what you
want yeah we'll open this have to do it
that's what he
wants
benefits amazing look how that look how
that opened up right to there that's
interesting good to see you get some
good food good to see you too thank you
for taking the
trip okay what's going on here what is
up what is
this you have to open it what are these
you have to guess and open it
you can open it is this maple syrup is
this maple syrup yeah yeah you ever see
you ever see the movie Elf no no you
haven't seen the movie El where he's
drinking the maple syrup and he's
pouring it on the spaghetti and
everything I'll have to show that's kind
of what I do all right I take the maple
syrup and I'll just guzzle it like this
okay I don't recommend everybody to do
that but I'll do that I'll drink a whole
bottle of it this is amazing it's from
Canada okay from Canada a where did you
guys where did did you guys travel from
Canada we're kind of we're traveling
everywhere right now but yeah we're
originally from Canada oh my God wao
look at that you guys got me this are
you kidding that's like a shot I could
send down that's like a brain shot in
met medium brain shot right there I can
send those down now he's going to
remember you as a medical medium brain
shot yeah these are good thanks guys you
want to get a picture yeah but we
love oh my God like come on what's your
F what's your favorite medical medium
stuff what favor is it
blueberry is it avocado what do you love
oh my God avocados I love
avocados avocado potato mashed up with
that's a delic pot potato hot like
steamed fresh the steam where the
steam's coming off and then you take a
nice avocado and you kind of put mix it
in a little bit oh man and then she left
what's what's your favorite potato and
dill sauce sauce sauce for oh yeah
she'll eat that SAU plane with hot
potato that's her favorite
amazing oh that's good what are you and
what's your favorite stuff with the
medical me what are you doing it's mine
I love potato and avocado too I think
it's because of him I was doing that all
when I
was are they doing are they doing the
hmd at all yeah you guys doing hmds okay
okay that that's that's yeah keep that
going that's the spirit says keep the
hmds okay guys thank you so much guys
turn around you're going to look do you
want to hold the maple syrup do you guys
want to hold the maple syrup you guys
want to hold one can take it out you
want to take it out yeah I'll take these
out Joel you can put these in your back
pocket so they can see your
faces my God thanks for coming of course
oh my God for want to give him a hug
give want to give me a hug what's going
on I'm big guy want give a hug a hug
over here or hug hug you want to give me
a hug over here oh my God you guys are
amazing oh you almost took this these
are
mine all
[Laughter]
right what's going on you want to give
me a hug yeah how are you it's
infectious how are you good good good to
see you thanks for coming how far did
you travel um I'm with them so we oh my
God you're with them You' be just oh
amazing oh thanks for coming yeah yeah
um okay I have a couple questions for
you shoot come one what do you think
about like changing foods but for the
babies like simple simple version they
need it like a baby board book you know
what I mean I think that's really
brilliant it needs to happen Okay um Dy
noted Dy noted I would help you if you
wanted help um also are there any words
of wisdom from so for
me what's your favorite season my
favorite season
yeah spring but I had to think about it
how come you're thinking about it cuz I
don't know yeah you got to get in touch
with your favorite season spirit says
let's get a picture
okay it's always going to be something
shocking oh have some good food thank
you thank you so
much hey hey Luke good to see you what's
going on good to see you
thanks for coming another night are you
kidding it's good to see you kiddo
Taurus Moon yeah oh with Jupiter no
way you want to get a picture it is
powerful get a powerful of course it is
yeah right here step up a little bit
good job good
job amazing I'm proud of you okay thank
so much and I tried so many other things
before I I found medical medium I tried
paleo functional medicine regular
doctors ayurveda Chinese
medicine each year was a new thing for
me oh my God and then I found medical
medium and it was like sticking with it
10 years now that's incredible 10 years
I haven't looked back that's incredible
and you mean the world to me and I I
just I love you so much I feel the same
okay I feel the same all right and thank
you for doing that thank you for like
doing this that long and taking care of
yourself I'm proud of you okay you know
I love you
man hello hello there nice to meet you
nice to meet you I'm that's my wife
Barbara we're from Massachusetts and
she's very skeptical really really
Flatlanders
Flatlanders in
Massachusetts well thank you thank you
for doing this nice seeing you I
appreciate everything you've done I I
appreciate you being here how did you
get him here that's that's all I want to
know how did he get me here oh really oh
my God okay okay I had it backwards
unbelievable yeah usually it's the other
way around so that's what I was hoping
to hear okay that was what I was hoping
to hear so how how long you guys been
doing medical medium 8 years for me8
years eight
years and I had a Health crisis but
we're we're beyond that now so oh my God
I'm proud of you okay I'm proud of you
he's thrilled to be here you know you
still got to keep him on track with
other things okay I try all right to do
that thank you so much we get a picture
oh yeah let's not forget let's not
forget I want a
picture thank you very much you're the
greatest hey it's an honor it's an honor
seriously seriously it's an on want one
more want one one more you got it
[Music]
thank you thank you for coming and
making the trip seriously has to be
exhausted you guys take the flight when
didd you get here
[Laughter]
December Anthony hey what's going on how
are you nice to meet you what's
happening much we're just happy to be
here I just recently started your
protocol and working on things so and
even more recently cuz she got me enjoy
yeah so bring my mom into stuff but yes
and it's already I'm seeing great things
I'm super excited
in the beginning of it but yeah that's
okay there's nothing wrong with that
that's amazing be at the beginning of it
that's good she reads your book from
really so you're a reader it's like
nothing for you could just like a
student she's a real student she always
was medical medium book one New Edition
I'm doing cleans the heel cleans the
heel oh I love that book yes that's one
I have I just when I got it I called her
and I said wait a minute this is a
textbook I
said Thank you for doing that okay I'll
be thinking about that you got really
you're doing CER juice every day how
many ounces I know I'm so 16 is it just
whatever comes in when you're juicing it
is it one
bunch is it one Bunch or is it whatever
no no no it was like 16 o 16 o no matter
what I do 32 so 32 I wasn't feeling good
today music to my ears I did 64 it
wasn't feeling good at migraine they
took it away yeah she came up here SE my
house but she's all better now thank you
for doing thank you let's get a picture
abolutely thank
you all
right amaz you guys are the best enjoy
the tonight nice meeting
you you got a book there hi too what's
going on who's this guy my husb husband
yes
sir I like your hat yeah thank you I do
I do so what's going on you guys just
very thankful to be here okay so cool to
meet you you do hey it's an honor to
meet you guys you don't want to grab
this B I hear your voice all the time
when she's listening to all your medit
poor guy no I love it I love it she gets
me to do your medic bless I love that
man awesome God bless you okay cuz I
don't know if I could stand hearing my
voice anymore so thank you oh thank you
amazing aming us all man that's really
cool stuff you you know I appreciate you
guys do you want to get a picture yes
how long you've been doing medical meme
is this your favorite book it is she
really I just love knowing all the
information for all the fruits and
vegetables and the herbs and everything
it's I love it so all right well I got a
little surprise eventually on its way
something to do with this book just see
you know yeah that's exciting so since
it's your favorite that's good for me to
know you want to step forward a little
bit
[Music]
amazing you guys going to get good food
yes we are thank you oh honor to meet
you seriously okay seriously enjoy the
night thank
you hi what's going on how are you how
are you great to meet you again oh it's
an honor it's an honor to see you
kidding me are you kidding me no it's
opposite way around I'm I'm really happy
to see you thank you how you doing thank
you I'm
I am okay I'm thrilled to be here um
yeah that's my short answer I also had a
question what's your question should I
read it to you or show it to you what
kind of question is it it's read
nefarious it's just like I knew I was
going to get I knew I was going to get
so
nervous that it's not ambiguous it's not
it's
not it's because you have to
I don't have to I just really want no no
like is do you have to do that pipe or
is there any other options I i' be open
to other
options I have I have agency here but I
have fear about where are you from are
you in I'm from here you're from here
and you got those pipes is that what it
is and you want I have a galvanized pipe
I'm going to replace it uh because it
could leech lead and so now I have a
choice you had to if you had to see if
there's other
options I very weird question it's not a
weird question at all I I it's not you
want to step forward a little sure
sure proud of you you going to enjoy
some food oh I am thank you thank you so
much take care good to see you good to
see you
what's going on here so you got a book I
was grabbing the book yes try to knock
the book out the books but this one is
actually going to one of my parents in
Hawaii and this is the best starter it
seems for them when oh it's a good star
book They're for the parents yes and so
they're like honey I don't know if we
want to do this this is too typical wait
a minute start with this it's been
several years so they've been watching
and they've just been watching me really
better so are they are they do what are
they doing well actually one of my
mother was doing the celery juice
usually I have a sibling who makes it
for her okay nice so I have two like
three siblings one has done the 369
plans he really is benefiting so he
started making the juice for my parents
we got celer juices for tell him I'm
proud of him is he watching right now no
but my sister is watching your sister I
didn't tell him yet CU you didn't tell
him well he we got the cameras on you
right now so difficult for him and it
was really
years I've been doing this I'm proud of
your family and so I mean thank you so
much because I've actually stayed well
all these years I got into it because of
my my mother when she got ill and there
is no answers and um yeah and it's just
been amazing and so I've stayed healthy
but then they listen only because I can
stay healthy so it gives me more
motivation and so they all love you my
sister watches who's probably watching
she watches all of your all of your
videos online she shares it with people
and uh yeah so it's amazing and just
want to say thank you and thank you for
my family proud of you it's really I'm
okay but seeing them it's really diff
tell tell them I said hi and my mom was
just in the hospital actually she she
just got out
again so let's let's get a picture let's
get a picture
amazing so thank you so much plus your
hey
Joel make sure make
sure nice to meet you good to meet you
good to meet you too I just want to say
thank you so much you have literally
been keeping me alive with the
information that you provide I really
appreciate it um during the times that
I've been at my worst your information
pulled through for me and it keeps doing
that and I keep giving it a try and I
keep going with the cleanses so I'm
really hoping to live for the rest of my
life until I get I'm proud of you I
can't believe in it thank you for doing
everything you're doing thank you do you
want to get a picture yes let's get a
picture are you excited about the food
tonight I am I'm super
excited amazing amazing
thank you so much seriously have a good
one
too what's going on here hi I'm Kenya
nice to meet you to meet you Ken thank
you for coming yeah um okay I have two
questions yeah yeah shoot number one I
feel like I heard somebody say that you
were talking about how there's going to
be a big earthquake in California can
you just let us know like a month that's
in so I can get out of
here no I know I know and it h it has a
lot to do also with free will believe it
or not so it yeah so there's some free
will connected into that whole thing I
talked about that on the podcast yeah
yeah yeah no I
mean it it's it's it's a difficult it's
a difficult call but I promise I will do
everything I can please warn us I will
do everything I can okay so I can go to
Miami that week um and um oh pictur you
want get a picture yeah
and I'm going to talk about that more
too I might do another podcast about all
that yeah and then I feel like you have
so many female audience like so many
women that listen to you so i' also love
to hear you talk about any like uh
beauty stuff like any toxins and like
Cosmetics or your opinions on that in
the future like for a future podcast no
I should I I should at some point all
those things I just don't how many of
women are going to listen to me if I'm
talking about you know me that I will
listen I just don't know no I will
listen so there's a lot of influencers
out there about all the best products
and everything you know but I get it for
toxins and and the bad stuff and the
good stuff yeah that would definitely
and also just I think part I think part
of it is all the companies they're all
like all the all the makeup company the
cosmetic companies are owned by these
these influencers and entities and if I
start cutting into it like this one's
got this in it this one's bad for you
cuz of this I'm sure they're going to
come at me like nobody's ever seen you
know because cuz that they love to I got
a kick me sign in the back just probably
why I don't really go there but I think
there's something I can do I still think
there's something I can do don't do this
brand this Brand's you know or or just
like even treatments that you recommend
or like not recommend no you're right
there's things to cover there's things
to cover definitely and also just think
also just uh wanted to say thank you I
I've healed from a lot of digestive
issues that run in my family because of
the books so thank you what your heart
no I really appreciate
that
[Music]
what hi are you guys are together yeah
yeah amazing yes hi can I give you a
little hug yeah of course of course good
good to see you you too you too um I so
I'm always giddy whenever I see you
but we had to drive through LA traffic
so I took a crap load of Gaba and a load
of lemon BS so I thought that I'd be
nice and calm but I'm still kind of
giddy
excited oh well well I'm glad you made
it I'm glad you made it you're here
amazing yeah amazing good to see you big
guy yeah good to see you man yeah I hear
a lot about you you're a big guy in our
household where's this where's this
accent coming from here yorshire
Northern England yorshire yeah oh my God
unbelievable they did some great things
for my wife so along with me and I I try
to implement as much of your work with
him and he complains but I he secretly
loves that are you guys are you guys
living here you guys made the trip from
there no we actually we we're about we
drove about 3 hours okay good good I
like I would do that for you I would
come over the
Atlantic are you kidding
absolutely yeah we would make that Triad
amazing can we grab a quick selfie let's
get let's get one okay you ready okay
let's
go amazing you want to get a picture
right here come on let's get one right
here you get the middle you get in the
middle I get in the middle you get in
the middle jeez what are you 65 64 64
I'm shrinking with old age 64 now don't
forget about you don't want to make him
jealous the
photo you ready yeah ready
amazing I'll see you guys enjoy enjoy
the food okay bless your heart you guys
are
amazing hi what's going on pleasure to
meet you pleasure to meet
you this is my husband Dave hi nice to
meet you nice to meet you seriously nice
to meet you got the LA hat on love hat I
love it I love it great hat get a little
nervous to to meet you cuz I've been I
don't know I'm just nervous for what how
long you she been following the protocol
for years well yeah not super strictly
did you get him on it or did did he get
you on it how did it work it was me all
really it was me I was diagnosed with uh
Hashimoto and
then I I was really like amazing at it
in the beginning like first few months I
was just all rubbing in went back then
you kind of up and down up and down
that's normal that's normal then you get
back on the horse you know what's his
favorite thing out of all of it what
have you gotten him to do anything
occasionally a glean he'll do some
celery juice yeah do celery juice some
of the the uh the liver detox good good
good I like that liver wise for him yeah
liver yeah very important okay I know I
I tell them all the time okay good good
you guys want to get a picture can we do
a picture then a selfie you want do
selfie first shoot come on thumb uhoh
we're running out of
time going do can do
1 two three one two three mais want to
get one real quick you want to step up
here
sure enjoy the food you guys thank you
so much nice to meet
you hello hello what's going on how are
you I'm Danny I'm so good I'm so happy
to meet you it's an honor to meet you
thanks for coming where' you come from
Orange County w nice perfect I did the
um Instagram for a while I'm not doing
it as much but medical medium Army oh my
God that's right
heal yes yes so I had so much fun
learning your information I when's the
last time we met I haven't met you yet
my mom met you so it's on social I met
it's your mom that's what it is and you
were I saw the ponytail walking away at
Cal now it's now it's making you said
you you said that's right now it's
making sense so I'm finally here so I'm
so happy to meet you you're just amazing
and your tools have changed my whole
life Liv in my dream right now just I
feel so connected I'm proud of you
seriously thank you I'm I know you've
been added for a while too you've been
doing medical meeting for a while now
since 2018 yep exactly and I'm basically
celery juice every day you know I if I
miss it it's lemon honey but I'm on it
hey look I miss it sometimes all right
like some days I can't it's just not
possible and then some day you know I
get it it happens but I just you're just
awesome thank you for everything you do
I know that you sacrificed so much of
your own life for all of us but you're
really changing so many lives and well
you know the fact that you see that it
warms my heart okay and you know that
that's amazing do you want to come in
and what I don't want to leave you
out I didn't wanted to leave me
out board here we get a good picture
well you know I'm proud of you right
thank you I am I am I am you got a good
sense of humor too by the way oh thank
you I know you do I know you do I
dressed up for you for Halloween that
one time that's what I mean that's why
I'm saying this the older soul is who's
the older soul Who's the older Soul we
know it's me it's fine oh no no no I'm
not sure don't know I think I might have
been her mom in a previous life Grandma
the
Soul you are you are I knew I wasn't
sure but I but I got the
message you
guys hey what's going on just grateful
to be here I'm glad you're here just you
save my
life this is so nerve-wracking that I
just wanted to meet you this is like
it's a nerve-wracking way to meet me
right yeah but the food's really good
and the food's the food kick ass right
yeah it's like great you know I don't
know what's going to come out of my
mouth sometimes I don't even know but
listen I I'm glad you're here okay thank
you thank you all the help with
depression and mental health it's just
there's a lot of that there's a lot
there's a lot of stuff in the medical
medum information from so for that yeah
so much stuff and you know and I'm just
happy you found it because it's not when
you suffer from depression it's not easy
to find find no but you know what you're
a fighter
because how did you how did you climb
out of that depression to want to do
something it was just what's inside of
you to do that my daughter okay okay you
know you're my hero right you're mine
you're my hero okay okay you're my hero
thanks you got me choked up sorry
I promised myself I wouldn't cry tonight
I didn't cry last night like you know I
didn't cry night before but you don't
know what's going to happen are you get
you're going to get some good food today
yeah I got some already and I'll get
more all right bless your heart okay
thank
you hi what's going on thank you so
much thanks for coming what's happening
oh um I just have a question so I've
never been able to visualize and also um
I don't listen in her voice and I was
just wondering you you can visualize
you're talking about like visualization
like I close my eyes and it's just black
I don't see anything but you you you
know what you're trying to
visualize do you know what you're trying
to right when when mean if I think of
like I'm trying to visualize an apple I
won't see anything you won't see
anything it's there it's there that's
okay but I was wondering is that metals
or is that the no you might be like even
Beyond visualiz ization you have to
understand like it could be bigger than
that it's not about medals for that like
you might not be able to visualize
because you're you're maybe seeing even
more than you
know there's some I've seen stuff like
that happen and spirit tells me it does
exist where there's a reason why you
don't see the image because you're
seeing all these other things around it
out there so just liart okay think about
that like don't don't look for the image
look for the edges of everything when
you visualize okay I don't know if it's
similar but not hearing an inner voice
like it's just kind of silent I don't
have like chatter or anything I don't
know if that's that might be a really
good thing okay let's get a
picture because with me I'm either
hearing Spirit or my own thoughts so
yeah so um if I'm not thinking about
things I'm hearing spirit if you're not
hearing chatter that could be amazing
but L heart L heart keep on doing all
the good stuff you're
doing you got a book for
me is this your guy here or no are you
coming in or you going to stay out
there we're going to leave you in the
rain is that what we're going to do
no thank you very much no of course of
course how long you guys been together
how long you been married we're not
married not yet we've been together
seven years you're
married yeah yeah don't worry about that
good to see you good to see you thank
you oh there you go did you try the food
you tried some of it for real oh yes
amazing are you going to have some more
we'll get you back in there you want to
get a picture yeah I wanted to see a
spirit of compassion had a message for
what part of my body I should be working
on to
heal um
reproductive if that makes any sense
that's what spirit
says yeah yeah here step forward
here are you doing the 369 from Liver
Rescue which we're getting that that
helps us reproductive okay all right
thank you okay thank you
hi Anthony hey you got thank you so much
no of course of
course
amazing thank you so much for all that
you do I'm sorry for everything you have
to endure oh bless your heart
appreciate oh my God you guys touch my
heart incredible and we can't soak up
enough of everything you have to say oh
my God and share yes I'll remember that
I'll try to say more okay I'll keep it
going I'll keep it going you you're
keeping it going and it's just helping
millions and millions of people thank
you for this opportunity you don't even
have to do this and be here tonight and
thank you for everything that's all I
can think of every time I hear you talk
I just can't thank you enough means the
world you guys it's a dream come it
means the world okay it does
truly is this mine this is from our
local
uh farmers market in San Diego where we
liveway this is this is San Diego honey
yeah wild raw Wild Flower that's insane
that's amazing I will drink honey and
maple Sy thank
you oh I'm sorry
I they're all
great thank you you guys bless your
heart we're going to do a light blast
later
thank you we're going to we're going to
try we're going to do
it look at you how you doing kiddo how
are you you okay yeah always get
emotional when I see you you're here
again this is
amazing food still good still good it
didn't change y want to get a picture
again come on I would love that
fantastic you're thinking about all the
medical medium stuff that you you that
you're doing yeah and you gave me a hot
yesterday so I'm going to I've already
got my grocery list ready to get that
going as you're blowing my mind so thank
you for getting me pointed in the right
direction I can tell already it's going
to be I'm proud of you seriously I'm
proud of you
okay you have time for one more question
what do you got cooking I wanted to know
um I wanted to help Humanity while I'm
here and I want to see if um you have
any hot tips about what I could do to be
helpful for just give me that question
one more time for S so um I would like
to help Humanity um have uh make this
life a little bit easier here on this
planet and I um I was wondering what I
could do what happened to like the
creative part of you why was it put on
the Shelf spirit
says yeah okay people heal with
creativity and art meaning people who
see it you got to get back to it oh wow
it's been a long time I'm so honored
thank
you what what's going on again proud of
you thanks for coming one last night I
appreciate you coming here and I'm just
I feel so blessed I'm glad you're back
okay yeah and I do have a question I
don't know if I'm allowed to ask what do
you got what do you got cooking I just I
always think about um my faith and like
the afterlife and like I know you're
going to talk more about that in your
spiritual B right I am it may not be the
funnest stuff but you know that yeah
mean in a sense where it's so intense so
I don't want to I don't want to say oh
yeah it's all great it's fluffy in that
that audio in that like audio book but
when you hear it yeah I really want to
know like I just I I want to know the
purpose I want to know the meaning of
life like I just want to know big part
listen the meaning of life has a few
things all wrapped up in one and one is
having compassion for animal life oh you
know like think like like having
compassion for Seals having compassion
right for animal life animal life dogs
and cats yeah and in there's because
people have they they shut that they
they they act like they have compassion
for animal life but they have a shut off
switch in there and in the end they care
more about themselves and you know and
how and the meaning of life is to of
course have uh respect for yourself of
course all that's involved and but
having that true compassion for animal
life that is one of the secrets to the
meaning of life thank you for sharing
that you want to get a picture yes thank
you so much for sharing that
get some good food thank you and thank
you
to he what's going on what's Happ to
hands cold hands
tonight they're not in my pockets
they're they're out here
tonight so so wonderful to meet you it's
amazing and I I'm so happy that I heard
what you said about compassion and the
meaning of life keep going so
compassionate for for I love I'm too
emotional about about that's a big piece
of the meaning of life that is a very
big piece it's it's uh having the utmost
respect for life itself and I I think
that's lost I think that's you know
missing in Believe It or Not people
enjoying their life doesn't mean that
that's what that means you know of
course you want to enjoy your life but
people get confused where enjoying your
life becomes the meaning of life it's
more than that
it's having that respect for life itself
and that's something different and and
and that's part of the meaning of life
and there's more too I I might talk
about it soon okay want to get a picture
least yes let's get a
picture maybe I'll talk about it tonight
a little bit yes I'd love to I'd love to
I it's okay
is eating
animal well I mean it's it's look it's
it's it's all a preference to people and
how they feel and I can't judge someone
and say well you're doing something
wrong if you eat that or what but but
but yeah there's there's no animals on
the diet
tonight there's no animals on the menu
tonight good to see you oh it's so
wonderful to see you and meet you
finally good to meet you I'm Patricia
Patricia hey good glad you're here where
did you how far did you come to get here
just Phoenix just Phoenix still it's
amazing yeah we're sweating our balls
off every day yeah it's
awful uh what's the worst month there um
boy uh 112 dry oh 120 something you in
the shade because you taught us that
right oh yeah no it's yeah the shade
temp the shade when they say that you're
right they never they've caused the
industry whatever that weather industry
is they've caused so Much Death and
turmoil because they never say that is
the shade temperature they never did
that how many people are like oh it's
only 96 98 I'll be fine let me let me go
up that mountain in they dead no I know
because you're not saying that's 98 in
the shade and you know 15 you know I
know I know do you want to get a picture
before
so you listen to my stuff cuz I said
that you have been like Darkness has
tried to take me down and you have been
like
yeah sorry you just got to you yeah you
got to Envision that light right when
the darkness wants to take you down you
envision that light you know darkness is
really weak it's it's pathetic it's weak
just seems like a roaring Dragon but in
the end it's not you just got to stay
strong like you are okay I'm proud of
you okay thank you does um so have a
message for me that was it you just
remember how weak that darkness is okay
it's not it's not it's not as it's scary
but it it's it's it's weak at the same
time you're strong you got the light
behind you okay thank you for keeping me
strong get some good food thank
you hello I don't know if you remember
me at Chelsea's house and I made the um
stuff zucchini sh remember about years
to see my God good to see remember are
oh my God are you guys friends we're
friends oh my God good thank you for
coming for many years how many years we
College 35 40 was her dance teacher 35
40 years years that's right that's right
what are we 37 years 37 37 years we're
37 years you guys are 40 years yep you
guys got us beat by 3 years yeah okay
okay amazing Chelsea couldn't come so
I'm here for oh thank you for coming
okay you want guys want to get a picture
sure let's get a picture then I'd love
to ask a question you okay okay you got
it amazing what's your what's your
question throw it at me I don't know if
you have a sense of somebody who is a
distance away but this is advice for me
an adoptive mom of a 21-year-old drug
exposion utero weed addict just just
brings crisis after crisis after crisis
into his
life you got you have to Envision light
around them all the time have to okay
constantly because um because the light
was shut out keeps he keeps it shut out
because of some kind of internal despair
but so you have to keep on putting the
light around so that eventually uh he
can grab on to it and then start to
climb out okay thank you you guys are
amazing right going to break my heart
here
okay hi Wendy good to see you good to
see you too I was that arowana and
Calabasas I I remember I do I do to see
you again um thanks for surviving that
oh yeah it was so great I met a new
friend actually so we met there we were
in line and we've been friends since and
she's staying with me you guys have been
friends since and now you're here y do
you guys live in the same area are you
guys in different areas Northern
California Southern California she came
in and how incredible is the medical
meme community that you guys can meet
and become best friends yes how insane
is that it makes sense though because
it's like minded people very loving
nonmental you know that just you bring
those people together do you guys want a
picture together or no you sure all
[Laughter]
right
amazing oh this is
incredible so and we'll get one too
ourselves my God thanks for coming again
of course thanks for did you did you get
to the canyon when we were in Calabasas
did you end up did
end where they had the the big meal and
we were dancing I you were dancing so
you stayed to
dance she got two of the of the light
blasts I only got one cuz I came later
but yeah that was great it was an
amazing time all right this is
unbelievable thanks thanks for coming
for than for having us thank you well
awesome want to ask real quick has
anything to say to me I'm I'm a new part
of my life and some lots of changes have
been happening and I just want to know
if there's anything well you have to see
things is new brand new because you you
you know you know that feeling when
something is new and then it wears off
you got to get back in touch with that
you have to and bring it back no this is
fresh this is new okay that's what
spirit says thank you thank you so much
good
good thank you oh my gosh thank you so
much Anthony sfc and tomorrow's my
birthday and this is really happy
birthday an early happy birthday yes I
can't think of a better present and so
I'm just curious if s so has a message
for
me if s so has a message for you let me
see
here what do you usually do on your
birthday anyway what happens on your
birthday um I celebrate with family
friends okay okay okay good and and
um when were you born was it
what part of the
day I'm not sure spirit says find out
okay and that's what spirit says okay
that's why spirit's asking me I don't
think I've asked anybody that ever I
don't know but that's what that's what C
say okay find out when that is okay get
in touch with those numbers okay okay
let's get a picture thank you all right
awesome get some good food yes thank you
should I do the cranial protocol um I'm
trying to figure out which doing I've
tried a lot the brains saver book
yeah did you match up the symptoms in in
the brains saver book um I have
neurological symptoms yeah did you match
it did you match any in the book um yeah
well there's the Vegas nerve and the
cranial nerve I wasn't which one do you
want to do um
cranial then that's then that's yeah
okay thank you're in touch okay
you got a book for me what's going on
how are you nice to meet you nice to
meet you too can you grab this cap for
me yes of course the light comes through
right nice to meet you you too thank you
yes I'm the good old smell of the per
permanent marker I'll need the good old
I'll need my toxic uh exp fragrance
exposure shot
yeah um I uh read this book in 2019
actually my friend um introduced me to
told me to um she's an intuitive so she
was like check out medical medium stuff
and and she's got a book too yes yes so
we're friends and we were so excited to
come meet you and um thanks you for
clearing up all the stuff with you know
the protein Mist the fruit fear the
caffeine I was so confused I didn't even
talk about caffeine I should talk about
that tonight so it's so nice to be
everything cleared up and my symptoms
have cleared up I've been doing it for
several years now love love everything
about it proud of you amazing get some
good food in the whole bit you I
appreciate it
Mikey amazing and um take a picture with
of course of course come on I would love
that actually want want me to sign a
book real quick yes thank you want to
grab that yes oh another perm me
perfect ah the good old smell of a
permanent marker you know I'm teasing
okay I use I use these periodically so
thank you grab a picture together and
then I'll let want to get a picture
together you guys come on here step
forward here
though and for anybody out there in live
stream land do not sniff those purposely
just because I acted like it was a good
thing you good to see you thank you so
much it's an honor to have you here oh
thank you your information me a lot and
I know I need to do this one this is an
amazing book this is this is U becoming
my favorite book of all
books it blows my mind what's in here
the information in here is just it's
unbelievable yeah exactly I mean
information about mystery fears and
worries you don't have any of those
right oh
yeah I wonder why I opened it right to
there yes they're very good okay here
let me see the permanent
marker just put a little
little initial on there okay so you know
where it is you want to get a picture
yes
definitely step forward
here amazing thanks so much enjoy your
food
okay good
yeah hello atha and see you good to see
good to see you how are you how are you
thanks for coming it's an honor to have
you here it's an honor to be
here to be here yes we would love to ask
if um Spirit might have um anything
wisdom from Nicholas CU he has a hard
time you know and we're doing the heavy
metal smoothie we're doing all the good
stuff but maybe he might have some
advice or he's has a really powerful
Soul he a very powerful soul
a very old soul so there's a lot of
information in his soul from past lives
is that okay if I say that yes it's
definitely okay it it stopped MH with a
lot of
experiences and so just so you know
you're a very special
individual yeah I can clearly tell you
need to know that it's important okay so
when things are bothering you or things
are stressful just kick back you've
already been you've already been through
it all
wow you've already been through it all
many many many many many years okay
remember that kick back and be like you
know what I can enjoy the show thank you
so much you guys want to get a picture
sure
thank you amazing do you guys like the
food so far it's fantastic incredible
incredible hey how you doing how you
been we're back you guys are back from
Monday what are you amazing
yeah incredible good to see you guys I
had a question for you and I answer it
tell me you want to ask over here here
come come forward a little cuz I'm I'm
hearing spirit in this ear so when you
talk in this ear it's going to
both going have am I going to have
children keep on working on it keep on
working on
it yeah keep on working on it lots of
good stuff get the toxins out okay okay
very important can we what is this you
want me to sign this this amazing I hope
it's not as strong as it smell as a
Sharpie you can use my
back so less both of you guys no joke
you guys got old souls both of you guys
okay
like
years I mean well over a thousand okay
th okay I I'll tell you right now I'll
tell you right in here let me get you
over here I'll tell you right now um
here this is yours thank you okay photo
photo photo oh let's get the photo okay
that's okay y yeah
both of you guys between 1 and 2,000
okay that's a big deal okay she's got my
phone so oh you got I'm going to take
I'm take a photo of him okay okay hey
how are you good to see you good to see
you I just want to thank you for all
this and for your family and for your
work family for all the sacrifices and
all the hard work that they do bless
your heart how much love they they
they're they're watching my family's
watching t
okay and they they hear that and that
that means a lot and i' I've healed like
over 30 things that's a big deal seven
years next month that's a big deal okay
over 30 things over 30 things I probably
have over 30 more left but but that's
amazing right now in the health world if
somebody heals out there somebody heals
one thing they Herald it is the biggest
thing on the planet and you got 30
down yes okay I'm you probably want to
get a picture I do but um does Spirit
have any messages for
me you got more than 30
down something like 34 or 35 yeah yeah
so which what are those five that are
gone uh
Addison's because you you You' really
that's like a big one right it's amazing
I think you have more conquered than you
know let's get a picture okay okay here
move up
here there we
go amazing get some good
food hey you got a book I want to read
when I WR you you want to read okay I
want you to read this message I wrote
you can you read it to me yes when did
you when did you write this your it was
your intro in
2018 I told Lena about you and I am I
you said and the truth about healing is
now in your hands and I said and I am
profoundly moved by how much each word
of your book resonates with the deepest
part of me thank you Anthony that's
incredible I wrote that in 2018 you
wrote this in 2018 my friend took my
original book and then I had to buy
another one oh my God and I do have one
question if that's okay hope I didn't
write on you just now I love it right
all over it so you have profoundly
impacted myself and Lena my friend um
one what message does a spirit of
compassion have for me keep on doing all
the good things that you're doing just
you know keep on moving forward it's
amazing I think you don't I think you
you don't know how much you really
accomplished really yes so try to get in
touch with that if you can okay because
you've accomplished more than you know
and you don't give yourself enough
credit you don't give yourself enough
credit very thank you
thank you thank you I love you so love
you too love you
too oh my God how are you what's going
on
here what's going on hey look at you
what's going on here come on this is my
son my hasus been in fago I don't know
if you remember no uh no I don't
remember you guys come on
um I'm blank right now but um so am I so
am I no no you guys you guys are very
dear to me I'm so so proud of all you
guys okay I'm proud of all of you right
you know that right your whole family
okay we live in California so anytime
you come we're going to be here cuz like
I love being and sharing time and seeing
you to me
it's the most precious thing ever well
thank you you live in California you
guys can get down here when we do these
that's amazing and also I know last time
I told you that tho was non-verbal but
you know I was someone that couldn't
Express herself in the past and after
some of your light blast you know I've
been able to access words that in the
past I wasn't able to and I that's me
very important and Powerful because I I
need to advocate for him I am his voice
and he needs me to speak for him whether
that's at a doctor's office what that
has to do at school it's very important
to me that I am able to speak for him
and for his safety and for many other
reasons so that means the world okay
that does that does that I found also my
voice voice with your with the
information you're the best mama bear
okay you are all right and and and
you're the best tiger than
you okay I'm proud of you guys thank you
Anthony thank you for everything that
you do let's get a
picture I had a dream that um I give you
a hug Anthony that look over there
that's a powerful dream okay it's a
powerful
Dream It's okay if he
doesn't you're such a good
mom thank you so much H thank you guys
get some good food oh yeah yeah of
course be my greatest honor are you
kidding
amazing yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh where you
going no oh yeah we I might have to see
second just all right I'm on I'm on I'm
all miked up
okay oh no
no e
good to see you good to see you yeah
we're going to fly back tomorrow okay
okay back to Germany all right that's
okay how long were you here um we came
Monday and fly back tomorrow just for
the event all we came Sunday you know I
appreciate you coming right and making
this long journey yeah thank you um I
love Germany yes
talk we talked about exposure you told
me about exposure right no I remember
yeah um so am
I in general really sensitive to all
kinds of toxins so do I have to be
really careful was it in with the spirit
say environmental
yeah temporarily it's temporary but m i
Tren compared words H am I really
sensitive compared to other people to
heavy met you're a sensitive guy yeah
but this my brain how how long have you
been sensitive since you were a kid
probably what do you
think probably yeah so I have to be
really careful with my surrounding right
yeah but you also got to keep it light
heart okay I'm a sensitive guy and you
know and I get exposure all kinds of
different ways and stuff you got to keep
it Li heart okay yeah but can I do
something about it something you already
are no way you already are you already
are let's get a picture and you coming
in here what's going
on hi Anthony good to see you see you
guys want to get a picture yes okay here
step forward a little
bit amazing how are you doing okay yeah
good good all right good to see you
again you too can I um is there
something we can do to support mod any
more I think you I think I'm over
here um I think
um I mean you already do a lot of things
already when he gets in that zone okay
try to try to try to
um try
to you know get him move him in a
different spot try to do something a
little different take a bath okay okay
when he gets in that zone you know what
I'm talking about yes I I do yeah right
when he gets in that place time to take
a bath okay we'll do that okay God bless
you Anthony thank you so much you want
to get a picture you and I I
guess
okay my running off the dot am I going
back
[Laughter]
here all right what's going
on what's Happening good to see you how
are you how you doing I like your
hat that's really
good she don't speak English but she can
a few uh colors here in English oh my
God are you having fun are you having
fun here is she having fun yes yes okay
okay that's all that matters we got to
have some fun here yes when get a
picture uh yes I want uh some questions
two questions you got a question maybe
we can do one really one okay only one
okay I'm a
natural PR and I want ask you if I do
the right therapist or is there anything
else what I can do what's good for me or
may
way um let's say it one more
time I want to be able to hear it too my
own business I make um natural PA you
don't you know what uh medicine Metro
medicine okay and in Germany we make U
how long you been doing it uh
2013 amazing yes well keep keep on
working hard like you are it's beautiful
yes but uh can you say you're helping
the world yeah I hope so oh I know so
but I do the right thing or is there
anything else what I can do better or I
don't know about that you you're you're
not you're not new at this you
understand a lot of things you do
medical medium in there right yes I do
uh and that's better than so many that
are out there doing this work so I'm
proud of you okay just keep on fig you
know expand where you can okay let's get
a picture
okay amazing you want to step forward a
little bit more
oh my God you want to look this
way listen I'm very proud of you just
know that for doing that you're in
natural medicine yes 2013 right you said
yes no just keep on doing the good work
you're doing are you happy with the work
yes okay no that's good can you of
course I can of course I can can you
pull the cap right there yes I can
wait this is a letter for you from a
friend she had also a question maybe you
can answer one time is this for me or no
uh is that for some no no no no that's
for somebody for
me and this is for you okay thank you so
much thank you for thank you for being
here yeah thank you bye thanks for
making the journey
thank what's going on you I just wanted
to have a love with you again oh my God
amazing I don't I don't mind I'm happy
to be here do you want me to sign a book
yes and it feels like home being very
close to you and this is from my
friends look at this book oh my
God that's amazing God exactly
exactly what can I do for my health what
can I do better for my he what's your
favorite what's your favorite medical
medium tool B2
that's amazing that's good are you doing
other things yes 28 sometimes 28
supplements oh my God are you doing the
foods yes you're doing it you got to
give it time got to give it time think
about all the things you're actually
stopping oh I stopped a oh my God think
about all the things you're stopping
okay and then you keep on moving forward
okay
oh of course of course
amazing can I give this to you please
sure sure thank you so much thank you
thank
you careful careful careful careful yes
we got to be very careful would it be
okay to give you can I take
this
than amazing thank you oh thank you your
voice is so we might have to move a
little bit over where we go sorry okay
thank
you I want to make sure that where the
camera can can see us okay thank you or
we're going to be off the camera I
listen to te the you know at night when
it's very very that's your thing um when
you're very very soothing to me and it's
very very healing oh amazing and I
support you
100% thank you thank you I want to give
you a oops it's not a queenex there's
aex not for me that's all right I got my
own don't worry got your own okay thank
you thank you take care of people no I
know I know I'm honored okay want this
amazing compassion you want to get a
picture with the book yes yes yes with
the book you're very compassionate
person thank you you are
to time out here oh no uhoh let's get a
picture here let's get get you
here thank you so much hi spirit thank
you oh bless your heart you're going to
have some good food still yes yes and
you too
okay I'll just give it that later hi
good to see you good to see you glad you
came back I just need to tell you how
grateful I am at my wife she would have
she said she would have died without the
information and me I would have been in
an asylum or would have offed myself I
to tell you me meeting huh and being I I
I understand like you know yeah well I
mean I don't I don't take those words
lightly okay mean it and and when I hear
those words you know about the the Des
spare you were in okay I understand it I
do I do you you gave me hope she gives
me purpose you know what I mean you give
me purpose okay and you give me hope too
okay yeah all right all right thanks man
love you you know I love
you amazing amazing I just got to take a
break for one second are you did you
already eat some yeah of course right
you need to get some I can't wait yeah
love you love you
too oh my God
[Music]
here
for
[Applause]
e
for
[Music]
[Applause]
e e
[Music]
[Applause]
ch e
I
[Applause]
than
[Music]
told
spe
[Music]
whole
to
[Music]
hey hi hi how you doing good to see you
good to see you again thanks for coming
thank you for coming do you want to get
a picture uh no I want to ask you a
question please okay um does Spirit of
profession have a message for
me well spirit says there's a couple of
things that you know you should be doing
what were
they they were on your list and you
didn't do them okay about something with
my new job very
possible what was the what was the
apprehension apprehension I don't notice
um word apprehension you know what's the
intention was
yeah okay to help people okay okay to
have women are you doing that yes but I
have also a a bread job because I have
to pay I have also a bread job to pay my
rent so to pay the rent for the flat
okay mhm okay probably it's um too less
time but how hard are you working yeah
too much too much no that's okay that's
okay any time for yourself at all yeah
for my meat preps every day okay every
day medical medium prot okay good keep
on that okay and then keep on working
like you're doing okay what's your
favorite thing to do when you're Pas
time in my in my later time you mean or
my yeah um I love to go with my dogs
walking and yeah spending time with them
okay good um when you do that okay M are
you recording your dogs are you videoing
them yeah spirit says keep on doing that
okay but watch the videos okay cuz you
don't watch them all okay okay may I may
I show you one photo from my new puppy
yes I do want to see it this this is the
this no this is the big sister that's a
big that's a bear that's a big sister
that's not a puppy that's a bear the
puppy's coming this is the bear again no
that's a
bear there is the puppy that's a puppy
you have a you have a you have a big pup
that looks like an actual grizzly bear
and the cutest thing I've ever seen
let's get a
picture just a
moment okay
Mikey H and this for you amazing let's
get a picture of it
amazing get some good food proud thank
you so
much hello how you doing good to see you
I'm fine good to see you you're back for
the food again yes of course very
good maybe uh maybe a c
Spirit a spirit has a special message
for me what was what was the last one
the last one I didn't get a message from
Spirit no no you didn't have a dream
last night no I don't remember you don't
remember the dream I never remember my
dreams do you when do you ever wake up
in the middle of the night
ever yes but I I don't remember you got
to take a
pen and you got to write okay when you
wake up okay okay okay that's what I S
it's important to remember some of your
dreams let's get a picture okay thank
you because you have messages coming
from above in in your dreams but you're
never you're never getting them you have
to you have to try to get them I saw the
thank you very much thank
you what's going on how are you is that
a
butterfly I'm here by the grace of God I
took a fly from New York for something
going on tomorrow and I came straight
here on the airport without a ticket and
I got in the second person how did you
do that second person in line oh my God
had like some only one ticket and they
needed two so they gave up their ticket
I paid for it and here I am this is
amazing it's meant to
be totally beond it is thank you for
coming thank you I have a question is it
possible to get rid of a virus to wipe
it out of your body or is it not yes are
all of them possible to wipe out it's
possible Poss some go dormant you know
when they go to sleep and you heal and
that's it and some you can get rid of
allog together can you get rid of herpes
or probably not it depends on where it
is what else is happening in your life
and how much you're doing it's it's it's
a job it's a job okay but it could be
done okay you want to get a picture uh
yes I also want to know if Spirit has a
message for me especially for my eyes or
maybe for something that'll push me to
work
when you when you look at night how do
you see at night terrible that's thought
the spirit is saying you can't see good
at night it's not and it there's I had
lens exchange surgery that probably
shouldn't have and it's affecting my
distance and my night when there's a
bright when there's a bright sky can you
see it at night when there's a bright
moon or when the stars are out when the
stars are can't see at all I see I see
Halos and okay and everything is
distorted still do that though still
look even if you can't see yes yes don't
strain but still look every night that
that you can and it could it could just
go away it can help it can help
here thank you for coming
to
what no way yesterday I couldn't find my
words that well so good to see you okay
good to see thank you from the bottom of
my heart because I'm honored I'm honored
this isn't the first time I saw you I
know the third time was it Calabasas too
yeah calabas you were up on the stage
yeah yeah you were up on the stage you
you you were called up yeah yeah it was
good to see good to see you up there let
me tell you I loved it I loved it good
to see you amazing thank you very much
because yeah my husband is back because
of you like he's back yes he's been
through hell this guy has been through
hell I know I I know I know some of his
story I do and he's been through a lot
he was bad off and he tried a lot of
things and you know he thought he
thought he was dying yes no I know you
need to know it's more than that
now the work is to help people heal with
this community now where we are with
everyone this time I could bring my wife
it's the first time I'm here because he
was like to see how amazing it is there
oh my God this the first time you're
here yes oh my God this is unbelievable
and our daughter is here but she's
sleeping already we came no let her
sleep let her sleep how far how far did
you guys come from nether from the ne
from you're from the Netherlands that's
right she's from Mexico
she but um we want to both ask you a
question no go ahead shoot okay okay I'm
yeah like do you have any tip or does s
so has has a tip from you something
you um you're very heavy on yourself
you're very you're very tough on
yourself you feel like you you're a
perfectionist okay and then but you're
hard on yourself when something doesn't
seem to work you got to laugh you got to
laugh more okay I know you're giggling
here but you got to laugh more yep okay
you guys are amazing let's get a
picture our Do's here I want to ask a
question if maybe Spirit can help us out
but she has fear of water she's four
years old almost it's that that'll pass
and it's like no that's a stage put ey
drops or swimming or it's a stage that's
a stage no no no come on up let's get a
picture come on thank you so much step
step up here a little bit
further thank you Michael thanks enjoy
the food seriously it's so good to see
you I love you man know I love you come
on there how you doing good good to see
you man good to see you thank you for
all you do thank you for putting your
life on the line for the chronic Leo I
really really appreciate speaks to me
man thank you your words are powerful
seriously thank you and I honor that I
do I do how long you been doing mm stuff
uh since 2017 on and off that's a long
time battling with addiction so so I go
do really good and then jump off the
wagon that's okay that's okay I'm trying
yeah but you're succeeding you are yeah
you know I'm proud of you thank you stay
strong stay strong thank you we'll do a
light blast tonight okay okay let that
light hit you and it's going to help
it's going to strengthen you okay all
right you want to get a picture yeah I
have someone who's this here we met nice
to meet were you guys met because of me
because of you yeah actually oh my God
that's the most beautiful thing I can't
believe it how how how long now you guys
been together uh 2 and A2 years 2 and A2
years yeah is is it cuz you were doing
medical medum stuff or it happened in a
different way how did it happen we
actually this C were you in the same
year and years later you you both came
here and then you met when you were uh
years ago with your first book 2016 we
started your information and then 3 four
years ago you reposted him he was into
fitness I was into doing a m and then we
connected that way and you said look at
this
guy I could see his soul you could see
his soul you see it right there his eyes
you're like this guy's
amazing than you guys you guys are very
special okay very special do you want to
get a picture together what do you say
come on let's get a picture together
love
you I can pray for you about when I talk
to God any prayers just is is well
received okay you all right but just you
know
um it could be simple could be like you
know God look after that God but but
either way okay I'm going to send some
out to you guys too cuz I I can't unmeet
us this you we we met now I'm not going
to forget all right all right I love you
guys
you doing good good good good Matt hey
how are you good to see you again you
know I'm proud of you right yeah it's
good to see you it just always blows my
mind about the iasa thing like you know
and people don't realize that out there
it's no matter how many times I shout it
out there they just don't hear it they
don't know and you you're a survivor of
it you're a survivor of like Tourette
you're Survivor of all these I mean I'm
OCD I mean you're un a lot a lot of
symptoms
of symptoms you've been through yeah
you've been through a lot I want you to
know that I know yeah thank you I really
appreciate that I never get a chance to
say so I have you here right now and I
wanted to tell you that thank you and
you're the only one who gave me hope and
how to answers for those things the only
one that talks about you know especially
the psychedelics oh yeah oh my God I
there's so much push back on that now
yeah you get a lot of hate a lot of hate
micro doing stuff if I go against it I
get a lot of hate I get a lot of hate
for all that yeah so I really appreciate
you sticking up for us and um I had a
question to follow up with from last
night yeah um so does a person's soul um
before it reincarnates on the earth does
it choose to be gay or
straight so it's a really good point um
I think what's happened right now with
gender and everything else I think that
there's so much confusion still I think
we're in the baby stage is of the world
understanding any of it kind of breaks
my heart a lot of confusion a lot of
misconceptions and I never got I never
got to uh into a place yet where I've
been able to talk about it I've been
doing all these other
things but whether anybody likes it or
not
um a soul can come into a different
gender body and be a different gender
soul
and then that happens I mean there's so
many things and what about like like the
same sex attraction would that be a Soul
Decision before they
reincarnate it yeah absolutely it can
absolutely okay is that a couple of
answers apprciate that thank you so much
let's get a let's get a photo do it
so much I love
you hi Anthony hey look at you look at
me good to see you good to see you I was
wondering yeah is it available to us to
learn the technique that you use when
you're doing your energy clearing
swiping is that available us for us to
learn in the community to help ourselves
our pets and other people I'm going to
do some stuff with that okay because
there's ways of doing it I mean I'm
using Spirit of compassion doesn't mean
it can't be done a certain way and I
want to I want to show how that could be
done I think I'm going to do stuff okay
I I want people to do be able to do more
with light so I'm going to work on it oh
I'd really appreciate that so other so
thank you so much blessings to you
thanks for having us tonight want to get
a picture yes yeah
[Music]
picture thank you so
much Anthony okay what's going on here
this the first time I haven't cried oh
my God that's amazing I need to start
getting all my books done from you
because I need more light I like the
celery juice book yeah me too I love it
it's a great book it's great for viigo
and I need to remember that um I had a
dream a few weeks ago with you in it
okay and um all right I woke up feeling
really validated okay and um I don't
know I just had to say that but
uh if you had it if if if if you had a
dream with me in there there there's
definitely like I have my whole life is
I have dreamed and I've time traveled in
my dreams I have
um I sit up in my sleep and I do
readings in my sleep on people I haven't
met all these things do happen so I
don't doubt that if you had a dream with
me in there that something didn't
just in The Ether but um dream oh my God
okay well that's that's pretty intense
but I had another question um it took a
lot the last two times there's been a
lot of Darkness following me to get here
and um wondering if Spirit can just kind
of give me any you know that the whole
Angels the whole Angels um and spiritual
Angel team spiritual tosm I think you're
going to really be able to use okay okay
let's get a picture
get some good food thank you hey and um
can you also talk about albanism I
promised um somebody had asked you that
question what's the question albanism
like what causes it okay I'll have to
eventually yeah
okay
hey nice to see you good to see you it's
been a while yeah yeah thank you for
coming thanks for having us and making
this all possible and you know you did a
post I mean you do a lot of great posts
before you did a post that then had
great meaning to me I remember I still
haven't forgotten okay yeah I mean you
saved our dog's life without the
information you brought we would have
been lost and confused and we had a way
out as to what you thought thank youon
every day
we um and I just wanted to also say what
you've brought has given my life so much
purpose and meaning and I feel like
since I found you and resonated with the
truth of it I've done my best to make
your purpose my purpose and just lift
people up as best I can't ask for
anything better I can't ask for anything
more you know when I was a little kid
and hearing Spirit of compassion I could
never imagine that okay that we'd be
standing here together and I'd be
hearing that from a beautiful person
like yourself so it means the world okay
the ripples that we're all helping to
create through what you've made is just
yeah I'm just honored to be part of you
guys do you mind if I ask you one yeah
shoot um so um I wanted your thoughts on
like the most
effective things actions we can take
like individually and collectively to
shift the world in a positive direction
in addition to like healing ourselves
and helping others to heal like what can
we do to just you know darkness is
darkness is afraid of light and darkness
is behind so much on this planet look at
all the destruction yeah right just just
in Vision you know how darkness is weak
and it has no strength yeah it's all a
facade yeah and because light can stomp
it out and you just you just see light
when you want to see light you just send
light where you want to send okay
believe it or not that is so powerful
people don't know that if everybody did
that the world would change but okay
thank you let's get a picture yeah
sounds
good thanks so much super quick too AA L
said God bless you um she wanted me to
say that L yeah she said God bless tell
her tell her love
okay hey oh my God last time I met you I
didn't I was speechless so today I come
with a few words you come with a few
words I will listen cool I will listen
after I see this little doggy right
there look at you wants to thank you
because uh she was really sick she had
arthritis and she started getting a lot
of
flareups uh little a lot of flareups and
the vet didn't know what was wrong with
her really I got some help from some
friends that said let's do the morning
Clans and give her the heavy metal detox
you you had a little bit of hmds did you
huh yeah a celery juice with a syringe
on aren't you adorable huh so a week
later she's back to normal she's here
today she wanted to thank you and I
wanted to thank you for helping her and
having the information for her oh bless
your little heart you're so adorable
look at you how are you feeling tonight
huh are you okay you got Dad Dad here
huh She's So Cal and you got Dad Dad
right here that right here that four
four right
here but uh I wanted to ask you do you
think there will be more podcast on pet
health or more information yes and and I
it's long
overdue I'm going to have a vet friend
on it's long overdue okay great cuz yeah
going to help so many people I know it
is it
is oh my
God Coco yeah Coco look at oh she
go so cute oh you're so adorable love
you man love you man
okay
I'm what's going on again it's been a
day that's okay happened in that day
what happened but in the last we that
beautiful light Blast from yesterday
that um really it kicks or some
resurging chronic fatigue to the her
after last night amazing we doing it
again tonight feel it and it's been and
I'm so thankful and I wanted to even
though I wanted to ask about sension and
all kinds of stuff instead I wanted to
tell you a funny story that will
hopefully make you feel happy a little
bit in return because you do so much for
us okay and I want you to know that I
brought the medical medium bar in the
form of wild blueberry juice
shots bringing it to potluck at work
okay and pour it in these little red cup
shot glasses and I put it on a tray I
was hoping this would make you laugh cuz
ites it does I'm already laughing and I
carryed around and I say shots shots who
wants shots and everybody stands up
because they think it's alcohol right
and they're really horrified because
you're really not supposed to have
alcohol at my work because it's a prison
and it's illegal to do that so they
think I'm running around like breaking
law but really I'm not I just tell them
it's a super antioxidant buzz and I hook
everybody up with their blueberry juice
and you're and you're you're healing
them yes okay that's amazing I got to do
more aw Barn Grill stuff you just
reminded me it has to be done oh my God
where has the time gone by I haven't
done an aw bars in Barn Grill in a long
time thank you for coming thank you for
that story you cheered me up good thank
you okay what's going on so good to see
you I love your hair thank
you I just want to say again thank you
so much to you andc you are absolutely
incredible so
grateful you are here andc chose
you so did choose me thankful for that
oh bless your heart you want to get a
picture
absolutely and I just wanted to ask you
you're amazing is there anything I can
offer to you or S just prayer once in a
while once in a while whenever you only
if you have a spare minute okay
absolutely I will do that sure thank
you hi hell how are you good good to see
you good to see you too and I I just
wanted to say thank you that's I don't
want to ask you anything cuz you already
give us everything we need so I just
want to say h I'm but what I would like
you to do for me yes is make C hands for
the picture really let's do it okay see
you can can is it this one so one let's
see now you're going let's see how are
we going to do this ready I will that'll
work that'll work here
let's all right we got to straighten it
out though does that look like a heart
this might be my first I love
[Music]
that thank you so much for everything
You' helped me a whole lot thank you I'm
honor I'm honor I'm going to go take a
picture of my friend oh you got a
picture you got a friend you ready hi
look at you how are you thank you how
are you how you doing I'm doing great
thank you so much again for doing this
again no of course of Wonder and I just
have one little question okay shoot can
we freeze freeze the brain Marine shots
yes oh good freeze away oh good thank
you BR away great I didn't see that
anywhere thank you so much and this is
so wonderful I'm so grateful of you and
spirit of compassion and Cafe Gratitude
I get to come here every day I mean you
know I just live a mile away so I come
here all the time now I like the sushi
and the everything thank you I'm honored
okay I'm proud of you too thank you you
want to get a picture yes thank you move
forward here here okay
and I want to tell you thank you for all
your support I know you do support cause
you support medical medium information
and I know this okay thank you so much
yeah no it's wonderful to be able to
share it with everybody justk thank you
for the social media support everything
all right cuz I know you do
that BL your heart and your skin is I
know it is amazing but it I try I try oh
and by the way thank you for the Skin
Potion that help me so much oh no no I
love that I live by that I have to post
my before and after pictures yeah I I
live by the skin po
yeah oh there you
go hi how you doing oh great thanks to
you I'm here otherwise I couldn't be
here I wouldn't wasn't hardly able to
walk very special very special to me
okay turn around the camer very special
it's very special for me to meet you and
can I ask you is there something
non-toxic for dogs and fleas for cats
and fleas the best thing I've ever found
with fleas I mean when if they haven't
just exploded in the entire house just
like it's just trying to catch them on
the on your pet if you can catch them
and kill them on your pet after qu a
flea comb do a flea comb and you you
know and you toss them away you can you
can eventually win win War un really
okay I'll try it yeah definitely cuz I
stopped using Di's earth oh oh no don't
you okay thank you because of your
podcast oh my God I don't talk enough
about that okay all right if anybody's
on the live stream we're not saying two
used diet ma Earth no no stopping to use
it okay I just don't want a mistake
happening yeah okay all right thank you
so much we get a picture okay yes please
yes please
[Music]
amazing thank you for coming here thank
you
Joanna how are
you um yeah I'm I'm okay I didn't eat
until now to to be on running on other
so I could be able to talk thank you
thank you for coming okay yes I'm I'm
very grateful to see you in my lifetime
you have somebody with you see you we
just met amazing needed
support amazing thank you for giving her
support she wants to read you something
okay you want to read me something yeah
is you know I'm proud of you right very
proud of
you I lost I lost it's okay go go
ahead you can try to find it this is
what I do on my phone like can't find
anything on
there I wanted to read that you mean so
much to me I have hope of feeling
content in myself just by being near you
knowing you and meeting you now it helps
me find the strength to keep going and
my body feels happy and wants to embrace
life means the world okay it does you
know I'm proud of
you cuz I know how hard you're working
and you don't have it easy and I know
that all
right and and and does does Spirit have
a message from me am I someone that you
need to help directly in order to
heal are you if you are you somebody
that's you need does Spirit have a
message for her am I someone that you
need to help directly in order to
heal no you can heal you have to
remember
that even myem emotional um
disconnection you can heal people get us
set up you can heal okay you can all
right only with the books I know you can
okay you can all
right you you want to get you want to
get a picture together all three of
us you want to do
that come up come up a little further
okay hang in there
you're a trooper you're
tough you're tough you've been through a
lot you're tough I know you are it's a
very strong
person she is yes the very strong
person and should I write down the
question for the um wisdom te or does
Spirit know what to talk about I'm going
to I'm going to talk more about it I am
I I haven't ever talked I don't think
I've ever talked about wisom teeth but
I'm going to okay I need to write them
down for you or it does very no no I'm
going to do a big thing on it okay I'm
going to do a podcast on wisdom teeth at
some point okay okay we'll get you
going can I say hi hey how you
doing hi thanks for coming tonight yes
I'm so happy to be here you know there's
always so much that I want to share with
you with everything that you've helped
me do I don't want to keep up the line
um she called me me like I just felt
called to help her and I love that
that's what this very caring person yeah
I love that that's what this community
is and you've done a lot of really great
work to help all of us this community is
is is beyond anything that's ever been I
mean out there ever in health and it's
just
it when I even think about it I can't
believe how like who's in this community
and the souls and the people and their
intentions and it's the most beautiful
thing the most beautiful thing you
shipped one and it's just a domino you
can influence I've influenced my
children they are influencing their
peers just so amazing so yeah thank you
thank you you want to get a picture yeah
yeah okay now it's me no just
kidding no it's me it's me me me sorry
you're the greatest thank you thank
you okay
okay Joy from Montana I'm back really
Montana love it love it and I want to
thank you that's a place to be it's
really been there 22 years Big Sky yeah
it's gorgeous and I want to thank you so
much for Calabasas and I wish you had
brought I asked him if he brought his
guitar today so you guys could sing for
us but I got a I was the first in line
at the buffet cuz I love food oh my God
and I saw the buffet and I started to
cry and I'm like this is for us you did
this for us everything you do it's for
us and I just really really appreciate
that and I wanted to thank you for that
thank you it's a least I can do in any
capacity I can do something I'm trying
to do it yeah uh you have given yourself
10 time a million times over and thank
you for that thank you um I do have one
question okay okay um I want to quit I
want to want to stop drinking coffee cuz
I feel like it's really holding me back
it tastes good to a lot of people hard
to quit it's not even just the caffeine
it just tastes that caffeine I think my
adrenals are like so I don't even think
I get that from it anymore but I want to
want to qu you're going to be able to
quit what's what is that what you want
the light blast to focus on
tonight do you want the light blast to
focus on that let's do both okay all
right let's get a picture and the other
thing is after Co I um I still have
strap I think it's strap
it's a trigger it's such a trigger for a
lot of people and then other stuff just
comes up is that the 28th day would that
help me with that I mean with that that
would be amazing do you do the spinach
soup ever have you tried it keep it
going cuz that is a healing tool for
that kind of thing you do that do the 28
day cleanse if you can that's amazing I
would do it um and then um and then look
into the books and check out the
protocols like you do I know you do tons
of knowledge yeah it's yeah read the the
supplement chapter again okay and see
what hits okay bless your heart one
more thank you for reading a letter I
gave last time about light and an
eye I'm so sorry for causing problems
and trying to figure out maybe who I am
like with with a person I mentioned if
it ca I mentioned somebody I did not
purist intention did not mean to cause
any problems with How would you have
caused any trouble I don't know I just
felt cuz there was i' mentioned someone
I don't know no way you didn't cause any
trouble you for taking time to read that
that I just want to show support instead
of like needing something I want to you
thank you I love you for that okay you
know that right thank you it means the
world that was that was my intention to
be that that that intention is wonderful
okay thank you want to get a picture
yeah thank you here we'll have you step
up a little bit here okay
okay thank you so much enjoy the food
than
you how are you I'm Keith Keith yeah
from Vegas and this is my mom land
that's your
mom wow what a fine son you have thank
you we just want to come here and thank
you so much for all your information and
we learned so much and I've been
trying to figure out a lot of things
because I've always tried to study
nutrition and stuff like to take the
vitamins but with your guidance I
finally was able to take the correct cuz
she's been on taking a is it collagen
for a while so after listening to your
information you finally like you figured
it out and like okay exactly wow I'm
proud of you guys seriously that's
amazing are you so you're deep reading
the books you're just like the brain
saver have you read that one yet not yet
I just started the first book but I've
been listening to all your podcasts and
all your videos thank you thank you and
then I think because of your uh celery
book cuz I found the information with
the collagen she uh had an x-ray just
x-ray had some uh was it nodules and
then after I put her on your protocol
they went away after six month keep up
all the good stuff that's why we're so
keep up all the good stuff it eats
things up in the body in a good way it
eats things that shouldn't be there just
yeah and even the PO toxins build and
they build they build and got to get
them out I'm proud of you guys you want
to get a picture yes
okay let's get a
picture okay you
ready amazing I'm proud of you guys
thank you thank you thank you so much I
love
you hi how you doing my name is
Alexander Lang Alex Lang yep and um I
never introduced myself before so
um I've seen you on I've seen comments
on social yeah yeah I know I know it's
an honor to meet you it's an honor to
meet you well I have a card for you I'll
take it I uh do a little thing a dubs
adubb yeah I love it and uh thank you
it's an ADB card you're welcome I want
to show you one thing he dubs my every
time I tell somebody they're like What's
your name and I meet him I run into
somebody on the street that doesn't say
know who I am aw they're like What's aw
like a dubs like win like dubs you know
like w win yeah it's like A&W Root Beer
like what's the aw thank you what do you
got there so my friend Drew a portrait
of me with wild blueberry juice wow why
is that so like incredible she's an
amazing artist her name is Diana Blanca
blany yeah so that's an
unbelievable drawing
painting that is blown away I'm Blown
Away thank you let's get a picture
together
okay big got it I'm on it big
HS I had one quick question I've had a
lot of nausea lately okay and I'm just
wondering if so has any message for me
of to do you I mean you're you're a
sensitive vagal Vegas
nerve you know person so just you know
when you're in the books and everything
just look for anything like nervous vas
nerve all that stuff frenal that's all
just support
that love you my
brother hi I'm Maran from
Austria we met yesterday good to see you
good to see you you asked me yesterday
yep y um what kind of medical medium
tools I like the best and I answered my
first thing I said was propolis y I know
I'm so sorry about
that that's my that's one of my favorite
it is a medical medium tool cuz nobody
knew what to do with that and uh spirit
of compassion new and so it is my my one
of my favorite tools but it just didn't
doesn't give you justice actually for
all that hard work you do for us and I
just wanted to thank you from the bottom
of my heart I'm uh 100% into medical
medium and I'm but I know that a to
supporter yeah let a picture let's get a
picture thank you and is there any
message from so for me oh no you you
know what you're doing keep up all the
good work with everything you got going
on you're very positive person keep that
there don't don't let that waiver okay
very positive person just always stay up
at that level than
pleas
how
was like oh I want to like yeah
seriously and my boyfriend know he but
he
[Music]
Prov off
hey
w
[Applause]
[Music]
so good
[Applause]
hey Anthony nice to see you again and I
I don't know to what to say much then
just say thank you thank you I can be
here thank you that you bring us all
together I love it and so now I'm is
saying is so saying
something about
me
um there's a lot of things about you s
so says you're a very special person you
always help people thank you true how
long have you been doing that where you
meaning I'm not talking about just with
this yeah I mean like you'll do anything
for people you know you'll take your
shirt off your back for someone just
know that's very special oh thank you
let's get a picture no do you want to
have a picture of me yeah course should
I
[Music]
do amazing get some good food thank you
for the message thank
you hey good to see you how are you look
at
that keeping me safe right no I oh my
God love you know this airplane
travels good to see you thanks for
coming I have a question I would like to
know if Spirit has anything to say to me
if there is anything I can improve in my
life to be of better help to others to
yourself or to others so how can I
improve my skills so I can help
others I
mean what do you think what do you
believe you do that helps the
best cuz you you're already working on
things like what is your favorite thing
that you think you're help people with
the therapy is massage huh the massage
therapy do you do massage
therapy that's a extremely powerful
purpose so how long you been doing that
um I've been doing it for about 13 years
but at the same time um are you are you
when you're doing it you're teaching
people too I'm trying you're doing
that's what it is it's not well received
because I have a lot of it is here's
what it is it's not well received in the
moment but then later on they'll
remember so kind of leave them with
a you know you know in your in your
thoughts leave them with the
understanding that they're going to come
to it down the road so it acts as a
beacon okay let's get a
[Music]
picture amazing get some good food thank
you for coming
okay what's going on what are you doing
what you do I can't leave you I I'm
always here thank you for being here
okay so much thank you for thank you I'm
proud of you thank you that means a lot
seriously coming from you what is the
significance of 353 353 yeah and there's
a few things you can do with that I mean
you can add the numbers right yeah so
what are the numbers when you add them
up oh my gosh so it's 6 + 5
11 353 yeah it's 11 right plus yes a two
basically that's a two yeah okay what
does two have to do in your life yes for
sure just it's going to take time to
think about it but think about it over
time what does it mean to you okay let's
get a
picture thank
you hi again hey made it again good to
see you look at that smile on
you you have a nice smile too you got a
big
smile thank you for coming out here
thank you I'm here thanks to um Gabriel
from Romania he he gave his ticket to me
no yeah no really uhhuh and I asked I I
wanted to repay him but he said just
just give Anthony a warm hello I know
who he is I know who he
is tell him thank you yeah thank you
thank you for everything he's a big
supporter he is he is he's a big
supporter so you know I've had a lot of
brushes with death you think that means
something I've had a few yeah yeah I've
had a few the same are in the same boat
now if you've had some
brushes I had some brushes throughout
the years so I I meaning I
understand they might be different br
es but still do they mean anything yes
it always does is it in the will it be
in the spiritual
book it's very possible and and yeah
brushes with death is a very special
thing okay has tremendous meaning all
right oh let's get a picture
together here you can stay right there
if you like that's pretty good right
there
special people have brushes with death
oh and you know and now now you're in
life okay you're in life so I I like wow
that's um okay I might talk about that
okay cuz when I like I fell off the
cliff and I knew I wasn't going to get
hurt like I knew I was going to land on
a cloud that kind of that's incredible
that's powerful that means something it
does of course it does you're very
spiritual person stff okay I guess I'll
just be patient hopefully it it when
things like that happen to people and
they happen to us um there's greater
meaning that we discover later on in
life oh you have to know that it doesn't
happen now you're not going to know why
now later we do in this life yes in this
life okay thank
you so good to see you again good to see
you good to see you I'm so thankful for
the information you put out for
Spiritual um information
I love the information on the Angels cuz
I like to call on them every night and
it helps me out greatly I'm so like to
call on them too I'm so happy yeah yeah
it helps out greatly is there anything I
need to know about my healing Journey
are you asking the Angels about your
healing journey I I yeah I ask my soul
information every day yeah okay make
sure you keep on doing that ask Angels
different questions that you wouldn't
expect to ask oh okay let's get a
picture sounds thank you up here okay
oh
okay thank you this have a message for
me I mean you're you're on the right
track okay you're on the right track
you're not you're on a wave yeah if you
were off the wave Spirit would say
something and then I would say something
okay you're you're on the wave okay okay
it feels good so yes no you you are okay
thank you all right my man what is going
on here yes is this your guy he wants to
goone he wants to go alone he's Brave
he's Brave there's all these cameras you
know we're on the cameras right oh my
God you want me to sign this yes who am
I signing it to oh you want to grab the
cap right
there who am I signing is to
Alex A L E X yes
can I write a little
note
yes amazing do you like this book yes
really this is one of my favorite books
of all time did you ever read the story
about my dog August in the beginning of
the book
somewhere is it is it in here where it
all begins
that's part one oh my god there it is my
story with August my dog is in here
right in this coming up I think and then
Spirit yes amazing
amazing why is he so cool why is he I
mean he's
cool well you want me to hold on to this
still I'll hold on to it want to take a
picture with me can you take a picture
you take a picture with
[Music]
me you're so cool thank you Mom you
coming in here wait are you going or you
want to stay over here with
us
guys Squad how you do oh wait we got a
big family wait that might be
yours I don't know I don't know
together it's a pleasure man my God good
to see you guys you guys all came
together hell yeah how far did you
travel oh it's from Fort Lardo not that
bad 6 oh that's a good trip that's a
good trip hey it's worth it oh thanks
I'm honored I'm
honored can please sign a book yeah
which which book do you have oh my God
the Brain saer book we got all of them
didn't bring to go we got some brand new
ones just for this man that's incredible
she got a collection me like three of
each swear to God
God every day I'd be at work just
blowing up my phone Hey listen to new
podcast listen to new podcast that's
amazing I'm blown away okay I'm slacking
I got to do a better job her though dude
I I I dude I love your chain thank you
man I love
that you guys are amazing you know
something I love this book it's so
there's so much in here that every time
I read it I get my mind blown me too all
of them are
amazing right waiting for the new one so
want alens hopefully you guys still like
me after that one okay never know always
I know thank you you want to get a
picture a whole
family where we going to go we're going
to go here you want to come on my side
all right Mikey can we can we get us
all K Katie K
you guys like the food do you like the
food cookies I can't be them can't be
them did you have the pizza absolutely
both scuffed them
down yes give me a hug okay got a little
baby hug here standing in line jumping
like
this amazing it's an honor okay be good
be good bye all right bye all right oh
yeah you're the best you know that right
don't forget it don't forget it thank
you anthy it's a pleasure love you
guys nice to meet you again nice to meet
you yeah been a long time I met you
years ago in Santa Monica um and uh yeah
I was wondering trying to improve like
this years ago s oh my God yeah yeah
around uh Revolution wow yeah yeah yeah
well nice to see you yeah yeah I was
wondering I'm trying to improve I have
I've been tested for heavy metals in the
head and um digestion problems and then
just getting rid of all emotional stuff
so I have all your books and uh what
would you think would be a good thing
for me to do to to improve on all those
area you doing The Liver Rescue Med
meditations for the liver no no I
haven't I start doing that yeah let's
get into that okay it's so powerful um
you know I don't I I mean I don't think
people do enough for those because I
mean they came from Spirit of compassion
they heal the liver they heal an
emotional piece of our body the liver
gets so emotional there's so much gets
trapped in there I would do it okay want
to get a picture yeah yeah
yeah amazing thank you for coming
okay hey what's up nice to see you again
you my grandma this time you got Mom not
my grandma my grand
what
how a lot of
[Music]
work she said she admir oh you know
Spanish I know very very little little
bit very little I mean I know enough to
just get me by I could slide by but
that's it that's serious question doesc
have any tips for MEC does he have any
tips for me well listen you're doing all
the good stuff mhm you do it every day
yeah every day okay okay what what what
you what is your favorite what is your
favorite at all then hmds for sure does
it make you feel better yeah I have a
lot of medals that's why I'm trying to
get rid of it did you ever do the Advan
yeah I'm doing that one currently you're
doing it currently yeah you're brave
ibly need to do the shock you're
brave how's your energy levels oh it's
better it's better I I've healed so many
things because of you all right you're
on track you're on track my brother
you're on track you know I appreciate
you coming you know that right because
you know you could be home relaxing and
not out here waiting in line so I I'm
honored I love
that all right thank you thank you for
introducing me to the Lord Jesus CH okay
okay thank you
hi I'm happy to be here good to see you
let's go I don't have a I'm you're just
happy to be here you want to get a do
you want to get a a picture let's get a
picture come
on that's
good amazing did you try the food today
I'm going did you try the food yes they
were all good I
hi Anthony good time I I just want to
ask you you you put some light into
those necklaces yesterday am I supposed
to just wear them and never take them
off or can I just take them off the
light will stay in there even if you
take them off okay you're allowed to
take them off put them on your
nightstand okay so just keep it near
near here right and I want to thank you
for everything you've done I love you I
love you so much and as I see and all
the Angels I'm Jewish but I just started
to talk to angels you know it's okay and
of course I would like to know the
message but everybody ask you and I just
don't dare to ask you about the message
it's just I don't know I know you don't
have time about a message what I'll do
is give me your necklace again I'll just
give it a refresher okay
yeah the other
one I so appreciate
that okay CL your heart
okay you know I'm proud of you right
yeah yeah okay thank you oh we get a
picture oh yeah let's get a
picture thank you thank you so much
thank you right what's going on here
hello I'm so happy to see you happy to
see you yeah and this time I'm not going
to cry okay well thank you good good
good but uh you know I I've been trying
not to cry but uh it's not easy yeah I
have a question Anthony yes so I was
thinking what question I want to ask but
the only thing I just want to say is
there any message from assoc to me any
message why are you so
worried I don't know you worry a lot
because um that's what spirit says he
says you worry a lot
Financial okay
okay you got to keep a li heart you're
safe okay okay you're still safe you
don't you don't feel like you're safe
but you are don't lose that okay okay
right and one more thinging for my
friend so she's Medical on medical
medium and her grandma got a stroke
recently and she's has chronic fatigue
and she needs need to take care of her
now and it's very hard for her like is
she doing the the stuff out of the book
one uh the book one for chronic fatigue
a little bit no she's doing five years
she's okay but she's Tak care she's
taking care of her grandmother but the
stroke yes and it's hard because she's
bedridden now is she is she is she know
about dirty blood syndrome yes she does
have her look into the dirty blood
syndrome for her
grandmother uh I think she's feeding her
like medical medium now good good good
good good but it's been only several
days because before when she was okay
she wouldn't eat medical medium you know
okay yeah so what can we send some light
for her we're going to do light blast
directed there uhhuh okay thank you very
much amazing of course of course thank
you for coming okay thank you thank
you Hi how are you hey what's going on
what's Happening
hi hi questions for you do you have any
questions no questions I guess like what
do we need the most right now like
what's our next step or what message do
you have for our family for us who you
guys are doing all this good stuff right
every day okay what's your favorite
thing to do um play outside and do GYN
outside nature is that your favorite do
you like trees do you like trees yeah
yeah you love to climb trees do you know
you do do you know that the the tree uh
meditation in in medical meeting book
one no you you do do you ever do that
one she does the bridge meditation a lot
oh you're
brave
I'm that's a scary one for me to do I
know I get rid of anxiety I get I when I
do that one want to get a picture yeah
and I want you to pray for our daughter
Abigail who has lymphoma okay thank you
okay are you going to send some lighter
away yes
defitely
yeah thank you for coming out here you
guys okay thank you I appreciate it
bless your
heart I got sood I got so excited when
he said hi in Russian last night to
somebody I'm Russian too so you know why
you heard me talk Russian last night you
said 3 up I did yeah you got remember oh
did the so say I remember I remember oh
I wanted to ask any
words oh
Victoria I love you m I love you um any
words for my sister for me I'm
I'm my God I
mean if there is time no no no no
spirit's talking about exercising why
why is we talking about exercising oh I
don't Tak enough
walks no I guess not no you're not
you're not even walking a little bit oh
a little bit we going to get you walking
okay right let's get a
picture thank
you all right hi I'm back without the
chicken oh my God good to see you good
to see you
quick question my RO water I had it
tested and there was a little bit of
copper and I just wanted to make sure
it's safe we drink spring water
sometimes the tap water but I want you
have a good RO system is it an old one
is it a good one it's a good one it's
from the last like seven years or so
seven years seven eight years I think
maybe look into another one another look
into other ones that you know sometimes
they could you know all all filtration
systems sometimes need to be upgraded
take a look okay yeah let's get a
picture thank you
okay thank you thank you thanks thank
you okay what's going on here anthon you
got the medical medium hat that's
amazing I do I do what do you you got a
package you got a button from Ulan TOS
who got engaged in October and they
wanted me to bring this to you okay and
otherwise D yes and otherwise I I spoke
to Spirit um yesterday before coming out
here and I asked I asked for um some
help
okay what as far as with what you're
what you're going through yeah
like
um what's the area that you want the
light to go to tonight do you know
I'm never sure and then I always take
guess
okay we're going to do more than one
light blast so try to do in between
switch what it's
switch okay this next one coming I want
it here not originally
here okay let's get a
picture thank you
Mike you're going to grab that you you
want that out
of you don't want that in
there I have eyes closed thank you so
much well you might had your eyes open
for one of those I hope so I think so
hello good to see you thank you from
Germany in town honored to meet you
thank you for coming did you take the
trip from Germany to here yes I before
for a long time but I moved back to
Berlin to be closer to my parents but
I've been in I'm in town for 2 weeks and
I tried to get a ticket and I couldn't
get a ticket and then thanks to well how
did you get this is amazing Gabrielle
Gabrielle uh S I should say hi from him
he couldn't make it and he um this
afternoon I messaged in the group and he
said he will gift me his ticket because
he could make amazing thank you Gabriel
you want to get a picture yes can I ask
one question well here let's try to get
a
picture I was exposed to mold and I have
histamine intolerance since then so over
time over time you'll get rid of that
sensitivity keep on doing all the good
stuff when I drink celery juice my I I
get ECM little bit at a time little bit
at a time little bit everything's a
little at a time cuz you got sensitive
so you read the chemical chemical
sensitivity section in the book yes you
just do a little bit of a time okay
thank
you what's going
on I have a note you have a note what
does it
say are the black lines on my teeth have
a metal what it's going to take I don't
want to be single
forever I mean did you ever have any
metal in your mouth years and years ago
in my in my mouth
uh no what could do that any Dental
metal at all not what I'm aware of no
fluoride treatment oh yeah prob prob oh
yeah probably yeah yeah are you doing
are you doing the hmds yeah it's 6 and a
half years every 6 and a half years
every day and advanced lately and extra
how long how long Advance oh good good
good that's what I wanted to ask four
months of extractor keep up keep up all
the good work keep up all the good long
how long will it take
there's a lot of metal takes time month
or years everybody's different so it it
would take a little more for me to
answer that but just keep on
going hi Anthony how you doing what's
this well um a note a question um how do
I protect myself when I give
massages uh when I do my massage therapy
how do I protect
myself from you're you're going to
you're going to learn in that audio that
I have coming out oh but also the
medications people's medications and
things I'm not I have I'm more worried
about the other
stuff that's in The Ether got it when
you're working on people and it's coming
out of
them but yeah all right wash your hands
always in between I do always in between
the people okay all right we go
amazing thank you for
coming what's up man hey thank you
thanks for coming yeah I've been here
for a while been with you for a while
man so I had a question about um like
the brain retraining you like dispenser
and why he get so many like you and
dispenser both get so many healings
which are kind of two different
modalities and I know you kind of
touched on the brain retraining like
dnrs and you know those guys and but you
never really went into detail why it's a
bunk or what's wrong with it like are
people really healing from that are they
not well I mean you know it's like
this um look there's people that heal
from all kinds of
things all kinds of
techniques okay in The Healing Arts in
the healing real they heal from yoga
there's people that get healed from
doing yoga okay there's people that get
healed from doing you know getting
massage therapy and then there's people
who who heal they go to their ACU ACU
pressur and they're getting ACU pressure
and they heal and then there's people
who um they heal doing
meditations and they heal so there are
healing but then there's people who are
on death
store and that's
different so you hear out there people
healing or people
healing but we can't get that confused
with people
who
are so bad so sick and healed it's two
different worlds but yes in all the
Healing Arts people heal doing different
things let's get a
picture
than but I I I but as far as like the
different techniques and stuff I I'll
talk about them sometime okay and just
seeing do you know add insight to it
yeah if you get into like more men's
issues health issues absolutely guys out
there
absolutely thank you for coming
toight hi what's going on how are you hi
I brought you this again really yes oh
no these are great I know I have they're
like I know it sounds weird but it
reminds me of like cereal L they're like
they're so sweet so good this is amazing
thank you for this I'll guzzle this
later yeah thank you for everything um I
just have one question I wanted to know
if uh spirit had any specific messages
or suggestions to give me at this
time okay okay
um H
okay so with you do you do you like
water
I struggle with drinking water okay
spirit says you don't have to drink a
lot of
it but Spirit knows you're struggling
with something around
water so um just do a you know just make
sure every day there's just a little bit
a little bit here a little bit there you
don't have to do a lot but have you have
it in okay there's something that's
going on that's in your life since you
were a child that makes you kind of
struggle with water just just think
about it a little bit that alone can
help is is it like drinking water or
being around it's everything I've been
told that before actually that's so
interesting well thank you for Spirit
knows there's your phone you're welcome
have a great night thank you so much
thank you hey Anthony hey how are you
look at
you I would love to know from s so if
there's a gift or a skill that I should
focus on on to make a positive impact in
the world during my lifetime you're
you're not into art art yeah course sure
yeah well are you doing anything
artistic that can help heal others yes
that's what you got to keep on focusing
okay thank
you you're
amaz How We
[Applause]
Do
e for
[Applause]
spe
[Music]
for
[Applause]
for for
[Music]
got a question hey you're welcome thank
you you got a quick question yeah so I
got a very dear old sold friend of mine
from the military and he's paralyzed uh
and all the follow on problems come with
that uh he's a great spirits good morale
but can I is there an Angel that's
available to him can I share a guardian
angel with him I want to send him some
light tonight cuz those ask for the
unknown Angels try to get three of them
there by his bedside every night every
day just every night it's if it's night
time his time get the Three Angels there
three unknown Angels by his bedside
every night okay let's get a picture
let's do that tell him I got a lot of
respect for him okay thank
[Music]
you thank
you hey hi you want to get a quick
picture we're kind of running out of
time tonight yes
thanks for
coming there you are you know I'm always
proud of you you know
that I'm always proud of you and every
all your support you give me and
everything so just keep that in mind
that I know that here let's get a
picture here thank
you
okay
okay amazing thank you so much hey
hi I'm going to sign your book yes
please I I had it on this this white
page you like that one here
yeah thank you so much I appreciate you
and everything you do I can't even tell
you I'm
just serious thank you so much let's get
a picture yeah okay I'd love
to oh
sorry
sorry thank you so much
Take Care thank you so much for
everything healing just being
here I didn't know if s has any message
for me I I can't we're running so out of
time right now I'm not going to be able
to do a light blast oh let's do a light
blast I would love to but we're like
yeah okay just take a picture now all
right all right good good good I'll give
you a hug okay all right fine all right
can you tell me one thing about my dog
Theo I can't right now okay no it's okay
it's okay than
thanks all
right hi good to see you I just wanted
to say I pray for I pray for you thank
you I just want I'll take every prayer I
can get okay do you want to get a
picture
always it's so nice
here okay thank you thank you for coming
tonight thank you well please enjoy some
food oh did you get
picture thank you you take care
tonight were no questions tonight oh
that's okay good to see you okay good to
see come here give me a hug all right
how you doing kiddo good you doing all
right did you enjoy the food yes it was
very good let's get a picture together
come on we're like running out of time
it's
terrible wave to my parents oh watching
oh my God hey you
guys I'm Charlotte of course hi
Charlotte thank you you're the best see
you hi hey you want to get a picture yes
of course please come
on
um can we have selfie very quickly I
can't we can't we ran out of time
tonight oh really nice to meet you I
this photos can we do that I just I just
want like it's good to see you yeah it's
good to see you well apparently we can't
ask questions because we have we're
running so late
it's
okay can we get a candid photo as well
just right like right now now okay
yeah he got
one or I'll give it to you myself one of
the you're hey good to see you thanks
for that prayer okay means the world
let's get a picture real quick you mean
everything to
me thanks for coming
here good to see youing me of all my
terrible diseases and so well thank you
so much bless your heart it means the
world it does oh my gosh I wish we
weren't rushing today
course I was really going I was really
going thank
you hey good see want to get a picture
yes yes thank you thank you so much for
all your guidance and
everything thank you for coming tonight
okay okay
hi you thank you for coming back thank
you for doing this no I'm honored I'm
honored want to get want to get a bit CH
here amazing thanks so good to see you
okay
okay a whirlwind whirlwind
not
[Applause]
[Music]
all right so everybody having a good
time
tonight amazing amazing what's going on
back here this is incredible you're
having fun back
here that's better that's better that's
more like
it all right amazing amazing we're going
to do a light blast in a little bit just
just just making my rounds
right food hey is the food good back
here all right all right look at you
guys
amazing nice and warm back
here all right how's everybody in
here all
right hey
guys guys hear me okay I'm trying to
hear myself
right amazing amazing did you guys
ever you guys hear me
still what is going
on uh you want to talk about the soul
for a couple of minutes can we do that
right
[Music]
you know one of the things that always
blows my mind is that we're always
governed by time here I mean right every
every minute it's about what time is it
time for your appointment time for this
time to wake up time to go to bed it's
always about time time there we go is
this for real I can hear
now all right all right you know we're
governed by time that's what it is
everything we do it's based on the
minute based on the
hour right we age every day it's time
that's how it works okay the earth goes
around the sun right and then every
minute clicks by all around the planet
time owns US it owns US physically it
really does and and that's hard because
human beings being owned is is never a
good feeling but time owns us here
physically on the
planet and but what happens with our
soul is time doesn't own our soul so it
may own us right now physically you wake
up in the morning you're like crap it's
8:00 in the morning I'm I'm
late you go to bed at night it's like I
went to bed too
late right oh I'm one of those people
that stays up through the night because
I everything comes to me at that point I
seem to come to life at night the world
is quiet I come to life at night right
you know that feeling but time owns our
physical body and all the things we do
here but it doesn't own our soul it has
no no Authority on your soul which is
unbelievable when you think about that
and our soul right is in us it's there
every day it's here but time time
doesn't run it time doesn't own it it's
its own thing so much
so okay that when we leave here time
doesn't own it then on any level or
control it on any level it doesn't
matter what planets are going around the
Sun Mars going around the sun earth
going around the Sun it doesn't matter
there's no rules those rules are gone
there's none of those time is over your
soul has that power it has that ability
it can it can put control on time versus
time controlling our soul it's one of
God's laws one of God's laws is hey your
soul can't be messed with it can't be
touched and time doesn't rule it
unbelievable really when you think about
it but think about how powerful your
soul is with everything and anything you
got to kind of get into that zone where
wow I didn't know my soul was that
powerful I didn't know it held so much
it holds information from past lives do
you guys believe in a past life or you
think this is your first time around no
right you believe in in in the past
lives right your past lives your soul
holds all this information all this
truth all this
Justice all of it so if you you feel
like you've been wronged how many of you
feel like you get wronged once in a
while on this planet you guys you feel
it you feel it you feel it right yep yep
but your soul no way that right there
can't be touched nobody can mess with it
it's not possible it's yours holds a
vast amount of information and light it
holds energy you ever see those things
like some miraculous thing that's caught
on video somewhere do you ever search
through the web and you see something
where someone dies and all of a sudden a
white orb lifts up or something did you
ever see anything like that you guys are
on the internet too
much you guys are on you guys are on
guys are playing with your phones too
much
okay do you
ever do you ever hear that kind of thing
and you see that kind of thing okay
exactly you know our soul it has this
power and this light and this frequency
and what you do when you're doing
medical medium information is you're not
just physically healing but you're
strengthening the frequency of your soul
how powerful is that you
are yeah you're making it stronger
you're making your soul even stronger
with everything you do here in the
medical medium information you're making
your soul even even more powerful so
that when it leaves here someday and
look whether we like it or not or
whatever 100 years from now 150 years
from now whatever it is our soul does
have to head off it's got to go back
behind the Stars somewhere it's going to
go way up there to the kingdom right
where does you where do you want your
soul to go do you want it to stay in a
house somewhere and just be a ghost no
you want it to go up all the way you
never know what's going to come out of
my mouth when I when I'm live like
this dear
Lord
so but our soul it holds this power but
we have to know that we have to remember
that we have to honor that we have to
see that it's important to see it really
is
one of the things our soul has
information about is food Believe It or
Not Century after Century after Century
what did you eat five lifetimes ago what
did you what did you eat two lifetimes
ago were you somebody that lived in the
woods and you just ate rocks and dirt
and a soup of some seaweed and some
other stuff to survive what did you eat
did you eat twigs and berries what did
you eat in all these past lives right
our soul has all this information in it
about what you did last lifetime the
lifetime before that and far beyond that
it has all this incredible information
like books and books and books and books
worth is just all tied into
it but we have to know that and realize
it because we can go through a life
without even understanding our soul even
the a fraction of it did you know that
we a whole life can pass and we don't
even know any of this we're just living
our life walking around you know like
okay I'm living my life on planet
Earth yeah but we can't connect unless
we understand we should unless we
realize it we have to know a couple of
things the rule the rule that our soul
rides over time it rules over time time
can't touch
it another thing we have all this
information from all these lives
beforehand and sickness did you know you
could have healed before in five life
times ago two lifetimes ago last
lifetime ago do you know you may have
already healed did you know you could
have been sick already in a past
lifetime you could have been on mattress
Island and then a thousand years ago you
could have been on Hay Island just a
bunch of
grass with some kind of like wool
blanket thrown over you and that's it a
little fire right by
you but you healed you got to connect to
that you got to remember I healed in a
past lifetime you don't believe it you
don't believe it why are we here and
you're healing here in this
lifetime sounds like you might have done
it before you have this connection you
have this information it's there you may
have healed in another
lifetime that's how powerful the soul is
think about it now you're here in this
lifetime and you're healing now too
right do you want to say something to
everybody
yes so
I want like to thank everybody for fun
and like
for he
amazing is he
amazing anything else so thank you
everybody for like everything oh my God
oh my
God says it better than I could say it
by far I got to practice you know make
it better I appreciate you guys and he
did did it better he did it
better I got to tell you guys okay you
have to see your value okay you have to
see it on a soul
level you have to see it it's critical
it's
important everything changes when you
see
it because we just don't see that we're
so busy wrapped up with all the games
and all the different traps and all the
different you know trickery here on
planet Earth that's the that's the whole
game it's keep youall busy keep you busy
with all this bull crap and everything I
did bull crap instead of
bull you I just want to make it a little
bit more better you
know I can't swear
tonight it keeps us busy here is what
happens and then we lose touch with the
most important part of us which is our
soul and we don't just want to be in
touch with it when we leave here and be
like what what the heck we want to be in
touch with it now and that's what this
is tonight's light light blast think
about it hitting your soul too
strengthening it making it really bright
and strong because that matters too not
just our physical have it hit both cuz
it will
it'll hit your physical too and your
soul too the metaphysical it will it
will it
will you know what's amazing about Cafe
Gratitude and I just want to say this is
we can actually eat here without
worrying you know what it's like out
there you know I want to say this before
I
forget you know what it's like out there
water water everywhere not a drop to
drink
restaurants restaurants everywhere not a
bit of food to
eat okay you know how that works okay
and that's what's amazing you guys came
all this way to come here to eat the
food here it's healing food it's
incredible food to eat and it's a
beautiful thing it really is how did we
all get here together how did we do that
how did it happen just magically was it
a coincidence is that that what it was
it just a
coincidence have you guys been meeting
other people here that you would have
never
known right have you guys been talking
to each other at all are you guys
mingling you are getting to know each
other really you guys over there are you
guys friends
now and that happened because of
this oh my God that's
amazing that's amazing Two Souls meeting
right Two Souls meeting
here it's not a
coincidence there's a reason why
everybody's here it's a very special
moment in time and
history truly
is what's your favorite angels the
unknown Angels do you like Angel of
Mercy which which are your favorite
angels which one angel of Light angel of
Light amazing amazing any other angels
my god really that's a great
Angel do you know you guys are like a
rare Bunch not everybody talks to angels
not everybody do you talk to angels
which is your
favorite like spirit is my favorite
[Applause]
really when I'm complaining the spirit
later when I'm I'll remember that so I I
appreciate Spirit more spirit and I have
been sparring still you
know it's all good it's all good we get
along
enough Spirit has I know I'm all over
the place today Spirit has a strange
sound a strange voice strange language
it's the weirdest thing I think at some
point I'm going to try to document that
so you know what it sounds like and what
the words are
it's not normal I can tell you
that
do it's just it's it's the words are
very not not usual words and I have to
change the word to match the same word
it's kind of like an ancient language
you know where the word is different
than the word but they're the same the
same meaning and everything they're just
a little different it's an older
language it's taking too many years to
figure out but I have to tell you guys
it's not a mistake what we're all doing
here tonight it's not a mistake it's not
a
coincidence it's a soul experience all
our souls getting to know each other
okay do you believe that our souls knew
each other somewhere else or is this the
first
time what do you
think you knew each other really right I
mean come on right and that's the truth
that's the truth you guys okay you got
to remember that as well all
right you guys ready for a light
[Music]
blast all
right where's the light
going where is it
going your soul right yep strengthen it
also where in your physical body too
where's it going there okay pick the
spot that you think it's going or you
want it to go you know I think it's
going to hit my left knee that's where I
want to do who's got knee
problems right you got a knee problem
knee might want it to go there you too
send some light there I'm going to head
out I'm going to say head outside for a
second Christian all right you guys
doing okay you ready for the light blast
everybody in
ready all right all right all
right aha I caught you eating another
cookie good good we should we should we
should eat those cookies all
right guys everybody take a deep breath
then
release all right then release remember
it's not a
contest I say that all the time now it's
not yoga class in
La it's not yoga class in
Brentwood no disrespect or anything I'm
just saying it's not yoga class glass
and
Brentwood everybody take deep breath
then release you're you're laughing at
that
one all right good get ready for the
first one
okay not a not not a lot of blockages
with you guys tonight spirit is saying
not a lot guys are pretty clear tonight
I think a bunch of you had light blasts
all
week and and so this entirely different
situation I wonder if we did 10 more of
these in a row what would
happen all right get ready for the first
one okay count of three deep breath and
then hold it till I say release one 2 3
deep breath in hold it light light light
light light
release okay it's not so bad not so
bad amazing take a deep breath and
release you guys doesn't have to be a
big
one okay all right did you take a deep
breath okay ready release right okay
good good good good good get ready one 2
3 deep breath
in hold it light light light light
release it's amazing amazing it's going
through so many people how many of you
felt it go right through you felt it go
right through you do
wow you guys anybody here you filter
right through right through okay get
ready okay on the count of three all
right one two three deep breath in hold
it light light light light
release we're almost there it's getting
through
everybody all right remember this one
thing the light's coming from behind the
Stars okay from behind the Stars
Envision those stars go ahead light's
coming from behind it that's where it's
coming from it's coming fast get
ready where do you want it to hit your
soul your physical body your your aches
your pains maybe you're sending it to a
loved one I know a couple of people are
sending it to a loved one get ready one
2 3 deep breath
in hold it light light
Light
release we have like two people left in
here there's two
people somebody over here up at the bar
and there's somebody out here out here
get ready it's the last one one two 3
deep breath
in hold it light light light light light
light release everybody's clear you guys
you're good you're good
good you're
good amazing is Patrick still here is he
still here tonight
Patrick this guy right here and Chef
Drew he's not here right now but this
guy right here I mean seriously I just
wanted to give the mic to you you know
if you got
anything hi
guys thank you so much it's been such an
honor the last 3 days I just like
reflecting on some of the conversations
I've had and you know one of the
conversations really stood out to me
where you know it's been it was two
sisters and it was 10 years um that went
by that they haven't dined together in a
restaurant because of her sister and her
chronic illness um so yesterday was the
first time they were able to dine
together
um in a restaurant setting like this and
so it's stories like that that really
make me excited to participate and be
able to provide this type of Cuisine and
have you guys be able to be out in a
restaurant enjoy community so just super
grateful for you and we're glad we can
you know help the community so thank you
so
much thank
you thank you so much we love you guys
so much thank you unbelievable truly
honored seriously it's Patrick he makes
this happen here Drew too Drew is not
here for the moment but Patrick thank
you bottom of our hearts okay truly
medical medium team and everybody here
you know we love you
guys keep in mind when you pray the
angels and ask for help from the Angels
you know do it right before bed ask them
to sit by your
bedside every single night
okay very important get that connection
going if you haven't already something
in spirit of compassion always wants you
to do you guys know I care about you
truly you know and I'm trying to keep my
ego in
check all right I'm working on it okay
I'm working on it you know the story in
the medical medium book first
one the rake right I thought I was a hot
shot thought I was a hot shot I knew the
neighbor was you know po poisoned by the
water they were drinking couldn't she
couldn't walk she was in a wheelchair I
was in the garden was pulling out some
onions and
stuff neighbor came over he says I don't
know how you did it it's been to 30
doctors Been Everywhere best science
Medical Science could ever offer she
couldn't walk but you fixed it you fixed
it she got her life back and she's
walking in I said that's
right don't forget it and I
said I was in my late team
means I said don't forget it cuz I'm
always right never never never yeah I'm
always right and I'm always going to be
right knowing I had Spirit on my
shoulder I was like you know I'm good
I'm good I got up had some onions in my
hand I took a couple steps I stepped on
that damn rake that thing came up full
speed knocked me right out
I woke up with my neighbor hanging over
me and spirit said you listen to
me you get your act together okay cuz
I'm the one that's right meaning Spirit
not you you got to message this stuff
out there anyway I love you guys safe
trip home please safe trip okay
you guys out there safe trip home too
all
right and you know visit the restaurant
get a pizza if you'd like the food's
here they got it on the menu okay if you
live in the area stop in all right it's
a beautiful thing I'm going to do that
I'm going to be stopping in periodically
you never know you might be coming in
when I'm here I don't know sit down with
me in a booth and we'll talk okay all
right you
guys all right love you guys
good man good
man you
[Applause]
yes I was headed down the same path I
had
ALS and it was awful did you turn it
around yes you turn that ALS around
completely healed that's the way to do
it yes and so I just have to tell you it
was you know because I found the truth
you know the medical medium information
that helped me do that and I'm so
grateful and I have to tell you now I'm
actually helping other people healed so
I'm able to wake up every day and know
that I'm working for God and helping
others you have a you have a big story I
mean
ALS um that's a big deal and you yeah
and you conquered that and you're here
you're talking that's beautiful that's
just really
[Music]
special I want to just thank you for
doing God's work and I know that you are
touching the lives of so many people and
you touched my life and I had so many
moments where I cried and I prayed God
to give me healing and I found your
information and but you've been doing it
since 200 um 21 really oh that's that's
amazing been really amazing so I just
want to thank you I just want to say I
appreciate you coming seriously and and
being here and working on yourself and
healing your body okay I'm very very
proud of you that's a big deal means the
world to me
[Music]
thank you for saving my life I'm I don't
want to get too emotional but I'm so
grateful to you and for a while I
couldn't write and my passion was
writing you couldn't even write it was
just the brain fog wasn't coming to me
the way I thought it would so um I wrote
you something you're a writer you're a
of course you're a writer now I can
write again and I just wanted to thank
you for that so I this is for me you
wrote something yeah it's just a a
little thank you not a little thank you
note this is amazing what do you mean
hopefully you can read my handwriting
but I will okay Lauren I will thank you
you're working with everything you're
doing good stuff you're healing you're
already moving forward okay thank you so
much you really changed my life and I
was hospitalized for severe eczema and
Mera and um you totally changed my life
so thank you thank you for hanging in
there okay yeah it was really that's
brutal yeah it was like a lifelong thing
so yeah very special person thank you to
get through that and be on the other
side of that
yeah how hi hey what's going on nice to
meet you you been I'm I'm good and
better thanks to you so well I'm honored
you're here okay how long you been
working on the medical medium stuff now
you know what's crazy I got your book in
2016 but you didn't dig into it yet I
didn't dig into it and it kind of hit
later it hit later it was last year so
it's been about a year and once I
started diving in it made so much sense
clicked cuz I was so low carb and low
sugar before but no energy and my
adrenals were you know and then you knew
you were like okay this is working for
me and it clicked incredible so thank
you hey how are you I'm I'm speechless
but I'm I'm good I'm speechless too okay
I am too I'm so grateful for you and
spirit of compassion your information
and my commitment to doing this has
given me so much more strength than I
even knew and it's changed my life
completely it means the world to me okay
it does it means everything that's why I
get up in the morning and it's why when
I go to bed at night I say that's that's
what I want to do I want to help you and
get you out of bed get you going through
your day okay it's good reason to heal
and that's what you're doing I had some
brain uh mental issues with depression
anxiety and uh panic attacks and foggy
brain and I looked up celery juice I
look up the medical medium protocol but
there's so much more so much more and I
wasn't able to like Drive places by
myself I drove here tonight I originally
did the protocol from the medical medium
when I was 2 months pregnant uh I was
born with an enlarged heart and I've
been dealing with fibrous masses that
started at the stomach and spread over
to the lung my official due date for
giving birth was today uh but I gave
birth3 days ago this was my second baby
I noticed a huge Improvement in regards
to my heart and energy level my ability
to work out again I've been able to get
full workouts way quicker than before I
was connecting with these remedies
myself just on my own but having someone
that has been able
to listen more clearly and publish the
information in a way where it's
connected so many people that I got back
to me and ever since that day my heart
has felt stronger than ever I'm a
two-time heart attack Survivor so I'm
I'm so grateful yes I'm so grateful I
went hello oh a group hello
hello yes okay could you introduce
yourselves for everyone watching hi I'm
Claudia and I'm from Austria yes I'm R
from Austria did you fly all the way
here just for the event yeah wow what
was it that made you want to get on a
plane and come here to Cafe Gratitude in
Venice we just realize now that we are
here as for me it's amaz wow yeah it's
so amazing it's it's incredible so we
are just glad to be here and to have the
possibility uh to experience all this
and uh to talk to anony Anthony and uh
to enjoy the food at the Cafe Gratitude
for the first time so I'm really excited
yeah and to made all the community here
as well you having fun in line yeah
really we had a lot of fun and we met a
lot of people from the American
community and it was so interesting to
talk to them and to see how they are
working with the protocols and it's
really very interesting yeah yeah how
did you both discover the medical medium
information and how long have you been
doing the protocol for um um I'm in a
sixth year now and um I got the tip from
the hint from a colleague from a friend
and it takes two years and she always
told me in those two years Claudia this
is something for you this helps you with
your symptoms with all your a ages and
aches and pain I had a lot of pain and
uh you have to you have to try it and I
always said no I cannot um eat no gluten
no pizza I cannot live without without
that and yeah and then um was the point
um I had 24 hours seven uh days a week
pain and ages and it was really really
bad nobody could help me no doctor no
practitioner and I thought okay well
let's give it a try and it was amazing
yeah I the pain was gone and it was so
released and I was so yeah it's
amazing and nobody could believe that um
that you're really suffering and and and
they all the T us always Ah that's not
so that's not so bad and and and it got
it will be better and it's yeah it was
really it's lifechanging yeah I have I
Anthony and spirit of compassion they
gave me a life worth and and I'm so
gratitude for that and I'm so grateful
and so
yeah no word can express my what I what
it means to me because everybody says to
me me oh you cannot eat that you cannot
eat
that that's not the point because I have
a live a life now and and I enjoy it and
it's a quality life and it's so amazing
and
yeah and what about you what about your
healing journey I discovered the medical
medium information in
2017 and um and who did you find out
from one another or did you meet through
the community no uh we made a an
education for mm practitioners in in
Germany and there we met so yeah sorry
back to 2017 though absolutely okay um
and um I started uh right when I found
the book um and um it was no wonder that
I founded uh found it because um I was
suffering more than 35 years for more
than 35 years and I always was looking
for for information for help and nobody
could help me and uh I had this the
story as the most uh people in the mm
Community have have that um I tried
everything and um every every time I was
at the at the doctor's office they they
told me that my blood work is perfect
everything was perfect everything's fine
so it's just in your head and I knew
that it wasn't in my head and later on
when I was in my 40s then uh I started
getting really diagnosis uh but just
once with CA un know
so the same corner and
uh it went more and more bad and worse
and uh I had times uh when I really
didn't want to live anymore because uh I
was just in pain and uh stiffness and I
had more than uh 50 symptoms symptoms uh
I had
um I was a brain fall fatigue and I was
bad ridden part-time bad ridden I had
severe migraine severe constipation from
my youth uh beginning on and um so it
was really bad and uh when I found this
information and I started and I I didn't
jumped in with the whole information I
just started slowly with celery juice
and don't eating uh no Foods uh but not
really uh you know some people start
full power and with 20 day8 CLE cleanse
and such things I didn't uh do that um
but my migraine was and I had really SE
severe migraine I I was laying uh I
think every second weekend for three or
4 days I was in bed with my migraine and
uh this was gone after half a year and
my my muscle pain and my joint pain was
gone in 2 weeks and uh my stiffness uh
was gone in I think 3 months it was
amazing I mean I still have to work on
some um uh symptoms uh that's okay but
uh it's it's incredible uh how it worked
and I was so glad and um I had the same
like cludia that uh some people from our
friends they they cannot understand that
I'm doing that because that's what
Anthony always told us uh that you have
to to walk in their shoes you have to
experience this only then you can
understand it's the only way so yeah and
that's so what's so great about these
events is connecting with other people
who have gone through similar stories to
you and understand your healing Journey
yeah there is they understand and and
you don't it don't need any word you
don't need any word so you can and
you're not the alien you're not the
alien yes yes that's so true you you you
can um feel that the uh the the words
are so trueu you you feel the truth
with every with every word in this in
those books and in his lives and in
everything he tells us it's amazing and
there is only one thing I want to say
for all those women out there please
tell us it's it's all those women out
there who have endometriosis there is
really a great protocol and please
please please try it give him give it
really a shot and it's amazing and they
can change the life and they can have
probably children and they can have a
quality life yes yeah and
that's amazing yeah I know that's big
it's it's about quality of life right
and if you know it's incredible that you
guys you both have your life back you're
able to get on a plane you're able to
come here be at Cafe Gratitude yes
absolutely yeah I mean that's amazing I
mean I was I think I was uh on on my way
to come here for 24 hours because I had
no direct uh uh flight and uh this would
be
unimaginable I couldn't imagine this
years before Island
so no no there was no chance no idea and
we are here yeah what was some of the
protocols that really propelled your
healing Journey forward for people
watching
online I think um the liver uh liver
cleanse and there is um there's one um
live from uh
and he it's about
endometriosis and that's really with
very very important information and so
you can um you get all those things in
this in this life and it's really great
yeah because it's in it's very important
to leave some things out for the first
year and then you can tighten
it U uh be more calm yeah yeah you can
more calm you know so the first year is
really important yeah and do you have an
encouraging message you would like to
share with people watching who are going
through their health and healing Journey
M protocols do the mm protocols if
you're suffering any kind of symptom
it's uh so amazing it's the only way it
it it works and it's worth it and uh for
all those people who are afraid of
um that you will miss something this
feeling is gone that quickly you cannot
imagine I mean
I was a really cheese chunky I couldn't
imagine live without cheese and uh I
don't care about anymore so no way so
that's really great yeah that's great
and thank you so much for sharing your
story and opening up to us thank you my
first interview thank you so much oh wow
you did amazing that was
great thank you so much a enjoy your
evening thank you so
much hello everyone medical medium live
stream we are just having a fabulous
night and hope you're enjoying this live
stream as much as we're having fun here
wonderful we're having a blast right oh
it was perfect a perfect evening yes and
speaking of blast what was your
experience like with the light blast
tonight you know I felt it go through me
very quickly and he did it several times
and he said this was a very positive
atmosphere in the room and it it seemed
to flow it went easily and there's a
good vibe here and I think a lot of it
begins with the food at Cafe Gratitude
and it's good for your body it's healing
for your body it makes you feel better
and you know you're putting something
good into your body you don't have to
worry about preservatives or anything
like that it's soy free oil free
glutenfree and you know it contributes
to the positive vibing here and I think
the people come here with a good
attitude knowing they're going to be
taken care of physically mentally
emotionally and spiritually because
physically your body is going to feel
better mentally and emotionally you're
meeting people around you at your table
that are always in this well when you're
here you're in this kind of a good vibe
good feeling and spiritually medical
medium did a light blast and it's like
yay I feel better I feel like it's
it's oh well that's what you get when
it's live right yes we get it when it's
live I mean the atmosphere no one wants
to leave everyone's swapping numbers
we're connecting with each other right
exactly and I met this wonderful woman
here from the east coast and she's going
back tomorrow and I met someone else
from just a few miles away and oh when I
first first came I met this person from
Europe that came here in December and it
was cancelled and he came and so he
stayed in La for a little while and then
he came back and he was able to get
tickets for today so you know it's an
allaround good feeling even though he
had a disappointment in December cuz or
or it was in January but then we had the
LA fires but you had to get your tickets
in December it's like going along with
the flow of life you know and it seems
like when you're in here you're in a
safe place and out there is the rest of
the world so you feel protected you know
you're doing good for yourself you know
that people here are of like mind and
it's a good feeling yes do you think uh
having these medical medium friendly
meals on the menu here at Cafe Gratitude
and cleans options will make people's
healing Journey easier and more
enjoyable this is one place where you
can feel safe that you know you're are
putting something good into your body
it's not going to fight with you it's
not going to harm you it's not going to
give you like gurgling sounds or
whatever it's going to be healing and
the fact that medical medium now has
some things on the menu that are his
from the uh brain saver book he's got a
lot a lot of um offerings of uh menus
shakes and even pizza if you can believe
it or not you know so there's something
here for everybody there were children
here tonight you know and that is such a
blessing that they are getting this
information at such an early age and
there was this 11-year-old girl that sat
next to me and we chatted and I said you
know if I had known this at age 11 my
life would have been totally different
it has to be if you're introduced to
this as a child you know your outlook on
life is different you know you're always
supported you know there's something
more in life and not just the physical
of what you see and you tend to have
more of a forgiving nature you know
there is so much empathy and compassion
and kindness in this community you can
really feel it yes yes and of course
it's it's something you pick up from uh
certain Healing Foods or if you're
drinking celery juice and and for
medical medium too because he
communicates with Spirit of compassion
so if we could all learn to have just at
least a little bit more compassion for
other people I know some people have a
very sharp tongue and some people are
quick to anger and some people want to
get back at you and there's all kinds of
feelings out there and if you're a
sensitive person you can tune into that
and so you
realize that they are human beings
having their experience so you don't
take it that personally and you you you
seem to have more compassion for them
cuz you're not drowning your body in a
lot of one thing unhealthy food I mean
sometimes we like to have a little bit
of
indulgence you know especially in the
summer like a little ice cream or
something but you know dairyfree ice
cream so it just makes me appreciate
people a lot more because you see each
person more
as an individual having their own
journey and they make mistakes and they
have love and they get angry and they
try to be a better person and it's all
part of life yes yes so I want to ask
you a little bit about your journey with
medical medium information what have you
healed from using this information what
have I healed I wish I could say there's
one thing that's totally healed and it's
great but not for me I'm healing a
little bit here and a little bit there
and a little bit here and a little bit
there and that's part of my journey so
there's no one big miracle like you know
I've read testimonials I've seen you
know videos of people that one person
healed 49 symptoms I mean come on that's
a lot of work but I think most of my
work has been internal just
um trying to have more compassion for
people and understanding them in a
different light than I would have 10
years ago for example or 20 years ago
and realizing that each person has their
own Journey so I think most of my
healing has been internal so I don't
even really see it it's not so much you
know the physical ailments so that I
think it's brought me a greater
understanding of human
nature and I think that's important cuz
I think you know we could all get along
better if we had more insight into
people and and their Journey we don't
have to be you know
professional people that are trained in
this you just have to remember you have
a heart and other people have a heart
and we're all going through our same
journey and I think that that's the
biggest gift that medical medium has
given me just being able to see things
in a different light well that's a huge
gift thank you well thank you so much
for talking to us thank
you oh it's been beautiful thank you for
sharing your night thank you and I thank
everybody who came here tonight and
especially who you know was fortunate
enough to experience the light blast is
blessed you know because just being
around medical medium I mean he's got a
lot of energy but he has so much depth
but he's very human and talks on a level
that everybody understands and can
relate to he's very relatable you know
and so that to me is important so it was
great thank thank you so much that's so
true thank you so much enjoy the rest of
your evening thank you we're going to
talk to our next guest how are you I'm
Danielle I'm Daria nice to meet you yeah
lovely to see you are you having a great
evening I am oh it's wonderful yes what
was your favorite part of the night
definitely the light blast definitely
light blast I mean yeah people the
people and the light blast yeah what was
your experience like with the light
blast um it's always pretty strong um
this time around because I had a light
blast yesterday it actually felt it felt
so easeful um
and I just feel afterwards I feel so
happy and I feel so light for the lack
of better word um and I always feel like
an immediate shift in my emotional state
and then further on I think in the days
to come I usually start feeling things
in my body um maybe certain symptoms or
certain discomforts that I have they
just fade away and so I'm I'm a big fan
of light blasts um whether in person or
online and what was your experience like
tonight meeting aw
oh it was lovely I actually didn't meet
him tonight I met him yesterday last
night um he's honestly I think he's the
most kind man I've ever met he just he
just radiates kindness and care and it's
amazing to me how every single person
that comes up to him like he genuinely
cares about them and um it's it's such a
it's such an honor such a privilege and
yeah he was he was super sweet and it's
been just such an incredible evening
what did you think of the food would do
you have a favorite dish this evening
yes I um I my favorite was the the
Mexican Bowl the beans potato bowl with
guacamole I thought it was absolutely
delicious and then I also really loved
the Mediterranean pizza the one with
arugula and the olives and um the tahini
cookie was amazing love that yeah do you
think it's exciting that Cafe Gratitude
is going to continue to offer these
medical medium friendly meals and also
cleanse options here
absolutely I think it's it's phenomenal
honestly it feels like a dream come true
that there's a place there's a cafe you
can come to and you don't have to worry
about the food and you know you're
getting really good quality Healing
Foods um I think it's beautiful I know
they also deliver to other cities in
California I don't know if they will be
delivering medical medium things but
fingers
crossed uh do you enjoy connecting with
the community here absolutely it's um
it's so beautiful I was just talking to
someone about it that every single
person is so kind like every single
person is someone you're so happy to
meet and I think maybe because of the
healing Journeys this all the community
has been through they're just the
kindest bunch and I've made so many
friends here already and it's just a
it's it feels like the best party ever
yes yes and what's your favorite piece
of medical medum
information that's a very hard question
I think the one that I site most often
to other people um is the piece about
the autoimmune diseases that um he says
that the body never really attacks
itself it's just a virus that we can
detect and I think to me when I first
read it um that maybe made me fall in
love with medical medium information
because it's something I never thought
about in that way before and it really
clicked for me like I really felt it in
my body that like it's not attacking me
it's not attacking itself it wants me to
heal so um I'd say that one but there's
so many that it's hard to yes yes what
have you hailed using medical medium
information um I'm one of the lucky ones
that started without severe symptoms in
2017 and then uh I got very deep into
medical medium in 2021 when I had for
about a year year and a half I had this
mystery neurological rash all over my
body um which had intense both like you
know rash symptoms and neurology and I
went to the regular doctors I got
biopsies I got tests I went to TCM
doctor s nobody knew what it was and I
start tried taking some allopathic
medicine and I just felt worse and um
then I did a medical medium cleanse and
it went away finally and uh I think that
was my breaking point where I was like
okay yeah this is this is what works and
I'm not dabbling anymore I'm you know
fully fully committed was that the 369
cleanse you did or the morning cleanse I
did um I did a 28 day cleanse and the
yeah the symptoms went away and then un
fortunately I got a medical treatment um
and it the symptoms came back and then I
did the same cleanse again and it went
away for good and then since then I've
been doing all all the cleanses uh and I
try to do them regularly and um there's
just so many symptoms that I didn't pay
very close attention to but they
improved like my mental my mental health
my mental Clarity is incredible when I
do the cleanses uh my skin uh just the
way I feel my relationship with the food
and the body um has really healed uh the
deeper that I got into the medical
medium system so just I I appreciate it
so much amazing well thank you so much
for sharing your journey and uh and the
night with us and everyone watching
online thank you enjoy the rest of your
evening you too thank you Danielle thank
you I think we're going to talk to our
next person over here hello lovely to
see you both again yes so how was your
evening did you have fun tonight pretty
good
it was very nice what did you guys think
of the light blast what was that
experience like tonight with tonight's
light blast um pretty good I love the
light blast it just you feel so like you
get a blast from heaven and you feel
calm and at peace it's it's
amazing what was your experience like
meeting
aw it was really neat it was pretty cool
yeah he told Nicholas some really cool
things about his soul and so that was
pretty amazing to hear wow what a moment
yes do you like being around this
community did you have fun meeting new
people this evening absolutely it was
it's amazing it was pretty good yeah did
you enjoy the food did you have a
favorite dish um I say everything like
all the dishes were good yeah I liked
the Mediterranean pizza that was that
was so good that one's good do you know
tonight was the first night I tried the
time tea and I make that at home at on
the evening you know evening time just
before bed I love to relax and watch
some television have the time tea the
time tea is so much better here I don't
know what they were doing but there's
like extra love or something like you're
saying energy did you like the tea as
well it was so good we love time tea
yeah and it was extra it was
fantastic yeah I want to have some more
of that
actually do you have an encouraging
message you'd like to share with
everyone about the
evening I would just say to
you know look into the information if
you have not and I mean it's amazing
it's there for you if you need it and
just to stick to it if you don't get
what you if you don't see what you want
you see right away like just to keep
going and keep trying and dig deeper but
to not give up that you know healing is
meant for you and can
happen thank you so much I'm so glad you
had fun had an incredible light blast
and moment meeting a you what a night
what an evening yes thank you so much
thank you you too we're going to get our
next guest over here to see how they
enjoyed the night are you having a great
night yes what's your name my name's
Danielle yeah my name is nuia so lovely
to meet you where did you come from to
be here this evening from like a little
town called delhigh that's like 5 hours
away from La yeah what was it that made
you want to attend tonight um well you
you know Anthony of course because like
you know I just have so much
appreciation for him and you know just
being around him that's everything to me
and so yeah what was your experience
like meeting him um oh so um you
know it's just so special it's so
special to speak to him to be around him
and his presence um it just feels like
home in a way yeah that's a beautiful
way to put it yeah yeah and what did you
feel with tonight's light blast well
because I've had already many light
blast I feel like they just go right
through um but when I first got his
light blast in the beginning when he
first did the first one
um I could feel like it come and it's
stopped right here and then um when it
stopped right here I felt like I wanted
to throw something out of my
mouth and um and then you know he did it
again and then I kind of felt it stop
again and then after you know he did a
couple more and then it felt it go right
through um but that was my experience
with the first light blast definitely it
hit me right here in the chest and it
stopped and then cuz you know how he
says hold your breath so I was like like
something wanted to like come out and
then I was like that was my experience
with that so it was really interesting
yeah very interesting and what did you
think of the food this evening the food
was great amazing delicious everything
so good yeah did you have a favorite
bite um I like the noodles like the
papaya and yeah and yeah so good that
one so good I had those tonight with the
sushi oh they're so good it's kind of
refreshing a lot yes it is very light
very very good the flavors are really
good yeah so how did you discover
medical medium information how's it
helped you on your healing Journey so
with me I discovered it because I was
having
um
gastritis um I had like toenail fungus I
had like cold sores and then um nausea
for like a whole year
and I just was
looking for anything to help me I was
taking supplements I was wasting a lot
of
money and then I was looking into
holistic you
know doctor someone that could help me
and then I found someone and I went to
her and when I went to her she told me
about medical
medium and I started following him on
Instagram and then from from there I
wasn't paying much attention to the post
though I was just following him but she
kept telling me are you drinking celery
juice when I would see her because my
son and her son were in the same
classroom and then I'd be like uh yeah
yeah I'm I'm going get on it I'm going
to get on it and then um I finally got
on it and it was helping me and then I
kind of fell off and then I became
really sick again and then I started it
back
up and then after after that I she
tagged me on a healing
story because I had been diagnosed with
Barett esophagus and they had told me
there was no cure and so she tagged me
on a healing story that someone had
healed barit esophagus so then I started
following them and I started copying
everything they were doing on Instagram
and I started
recovering and but I hadn't read the
books I was just copying whatever this
girl did I was doing it and I started
healing and I told someone else about
medical medium and then they came back
to me and they were like oh I bought his
book and then I was like wait I need to
get the books myself and then I started
you know reading the information and it
started making so much sense and yeah
that's how it happened you know what's
interesting to me is the fact that uh
you heard this story of someone else who
was going through a similar dealing with
a similar condition or the same
condition and that inspired you you were
seeing their healing Journey it inspired
you with your healing Journey CU I I was
already dying and I needed like I just
saw that if she did it then it had to
help me I had nothing else I had nothing
else so by that person sharing the
healing Journey you were inspired and
it's just now taking me to this moment
where you're brave enough to open up and
share your healing Journey you don't
know who you might may be inspiring out
there as well it's really incredible
yeah so yeah it's incredible what
Instagram can do and what people share
as in what they do dayto day you know
how others can be looking at it and
applying it applying it in their life um
so it's powerful what people share in
their Instagrams and their stories and
their posts because people are looking
and people are doing it at home even if
they might not tell you or you might
know but you are are inspiring someone
out there to eat healthier yeah yeah so
true so how is your health now what
improvements have you noticed um okay so
when I started medical medium because
it's going to be 4 years now the first
thing that cleared up for me was my
toenail fungus like it was gone within
like months it was gone after I started
medical medium I never got another cold
sore which I would get like one or twice
every year and we know that that is like
in a lowered immune system and so I was
feeding my immune system with all those
foods and then I got rid of my
gastritis um and um just dry eyes I had
dry eyes burning eyes
[Music]
um strep too like I had some acne going
on um and there's probably things I'm
missing right now cuz I can't think of
everything but yeah there's been a lot
of healing happening and you know not
just with me but with my son um because
I also appli the information with my
son and there's been big improvements
with him as well yeah incredible that's
beautiful thank you so much for sharing
that thank you do you enjoy connecting
with this community tonight did you have
fun meeting new people yes I did I um I
met a friend that we were we were on
this group in Telegram so I've never
seen her in person and it's so funny
because we were staying in the same area
and the same place so I looked out the
window and I saw her and I'm like hey
that's her and I ran outside and I'm
like hey like we she's like noia and I'm
like yeah she recognized me and I
recognized her and then you know we were
also here we were talking and then I
also you know I met like two other
people and you know the conversations
are just so easy flowing like you know
these people they're good people people
so yeah it's it's just an incredible
community and for everyone watching
tonight just we want to share with you
how amazing the energy has felt here and
the community and it's just been awesome
connection you know yeah today went a
little different but I loved it I loved
it though I loved it like how you know
we went out there you know we got to
talk to Anthony I just loved how
everything worked out yeah it all worked
out the way it was supposed to be and
you know what tonight you're the last
guest on going to be interviewing and
thank you so much uh for sharing your
story we're going to wrap this 3-day
event do you want to do an outro with me
and say thank you to everyone out there
who's been tuning in watching watching
this live stream and should we should we
thank some people should we thank Cafe
Gratitude you know for putting this on
yeah we um Patrick I want to thank
Patrick because we all we got in contact
with him and said hey you know we have a
child with special needs we need like a
table and you know he was he got us our
table for this this is the second time
he you know gets us our table um so
definitely Patrick thank you to
Anthony for everything that he
does and also to Chef Drew for the
amazing food and thank you for all the
people that came out all the people that
are watching all the amazing people that
you know were here tonight the people
that I got to talk to and also to you
for your you know all the people you're
interviewing and the people that are
sharing their stories and everything
it's been an incredible night you know
like all of the staff here at Cafe
Gratitude did such an amazing job they
made it such a beautiful environment we
got all the camera crew the live stream
crew all the staff here the photographer
yes yes behind the camera aw his crew we
have just had an amazing time for this
three night pizza party the staff
actually um one of the staffs she took
my son and she was holding his hand when
he was going to go meet Anthony and that
was so sweet so caring yes that's
beautiful thank you so much to the staff
everyone for coming out aw we know how
hard he works it was just an incredible
three nights thank you everyone for
tuning in thank you to Anthony's wife
his family also for sharing him with us
yes the whole crew we have had a blast
thank you so much for tuning in until
next time stay healthy get that celery
heavy metal detox smoothie and if you're
in Los Angeles come to Cafe Gratitude
and check out the menu here it's amazing
thank you everyone Bye by
[Music]