e
e e
hello and welcome to the medical medium
live stream we are here at Cafe
Gratitude in beautiful Venice California
for the medical medium pizza party it is
a three-day event tonight is night one
and I'm your host for the live stream
I'm honored and excited to be back my
name is Danielle delate and we're going
to kick things off by starting with
talking to some of our guest if you'd
like to join us over
here what is your name for everyone
watching at home it's my name is Margie
majie Danielle nice to meet you nice to
meet you yes so where did you travel
from to be here today Maryland wow wow
what was it that made you want to come
to this
event I I wanted to meet Anthony in
person and to say thank you and to
just I'm just filled with so much
gratitude
and and I and I just want to express
that express that to him yes well this
event at Cafe Gratitude and this
collaboration between medical medium and
Cafe Gratitude is so exciting what are
you most excited
for meeting other people meeting the
other me members of the community
everybody is just so supportive and just
um and just full of stories and and the
stories are just amazing and and and it
just it just makes you want to continue
the journey they're so amazing and
inspiring do you have a story you would
like to share with us about how you came
across medical medium
information um I started um I I guess
about 5 years ago um I I had read I had
read a couple of his books but I wasn't
committed yet and and I was trying to
lose a little weight and um so I started
on the 28 day cleanse and I lost 20 lbs
and I was like Wow but not only did I
lose the weight I just started feeling
different and it's it was the feeling
that motivated me to continue doing what
I was doing and to um just well let me
just see where this journey
goes and um you know I'm I just turned
60 this year I have two grandbabies and
I feel better now than I did when I was
50 wow amazing so what are some of those
health benefits you've had from using
medical medium information
well I have more Vitality um just um my
hair has grown back thicker um the gray
hair seems to be
disappearing or it's not as um it's not
as thick and wiry um
just my skin is clearer um just
everything
just uh I I have a better attitude uh
towards life and and just just in
general yes well your skin is glowing
and your hair is so thick and gorgeous
I'm not sure if you can tell at home but
it's just so shiny and beautiful Under
The Lights here thank you and with the
community here have you met some great
people in line oh my gosh lots of great
people uh um okay so now I'm going to
draw a blank um I met some wonderful
women from uh
Austria and um Ro uh was it uh Germany
yes yeah from all around the world are
you excited to be sharing a meal inside
where you don't have to worry about any
of the ingredients oh yes that that is
like the most exciting thing is just I I
can sit down and not worry about what
I'm eating it's it's the greatest it's
it's just um I'm I'm fat free
gluten-free uh vegan and you you just
can't go to a
restaurant and and sit down and have a
meal without asking without being
concerned about is there canola oil in
it is there um you know what what
preservatives are are in it and now you
get to come here to Cafe Gratitude not
have to worry about that and be
surrounded by other people who
understand your healing Journey yes yes
it's wonderful absolutely wonderful it's
beautiful well thank you so much for
talking to us and sharing yes uh if you
want to make your way over there we're
going to talk to the next person
hello hi nice to meet you too my name's
Danielle what's your name I'm Vanessa
nice to meet you nice to meet you
Vanessa where did you travel from to be
here this evening I'm actually in Los
Angeles County in a place called San
Pedro so I'm about 40 minutes away from
here which I'm very blessed because I
know there's people from all over the
world so I'm just super blessed to be
here oh you're so lucky to have this in
your own backyard and to be able to come
to Cafe Gratitude to enjoy these menu
options all the time yeah I know I
actually haven't been to Cafe Gratitude
in a minute but when I found out mm was
coming here I was like need to be here
bought the ticket so it's just just a
huge blessing to be with to meet him
soon and to be with the mm Community oh
the community is so beautiful it's so
uplifting to be around the community
yeah there's like a high Vibe here you
know you feel a good energy around the
people yes for sure what is it about
this collaboration between medical
medium and Cafe Gratitude that you're
most excited for well I'm obviously
excited to have like a more intimate
gathering with mm I went to the event in
Culver City back in June and that was
enormous there was thousands of people
so I'm stoked that it's more intimate
with the food right because whenever I
go to a restaurant I'm like hi do you
cook with canola oil and I can't have
any eggs or dairy and they're like why
are you even here so when I'm you know
in Cafe Gratitude it's like I'm able to
actually eat the food and and know that
it's healing and it's also going to be
delicious yes healing delicious and
surrounded by such a beautiful Community
yes absolutely how did you discover the
medical medium information so uh in 2019
I was super sick of the acne that
covered my face I had like very painful
cystic acne and a lot of discoloration
on my skin and I tried everything and I
met with a you know like a medical
medium coach that I found off Instagram
and so she's like girlfriend you need to
get off eggs you need to get off Dairy
and gluten like that was my whole diet
and So within like the first night I
said let's do it and so on July 9th of
2019 I was like let's go and it was
celery juice morning cleanse and I never
looked back and my skin healed it took
some time um but the acne is gone the
discoloration gone so I'm very very
grateful to mm's Spirit of compassion
for the healing information that is put
out there apart from the skin uh glowing
like it is tonight uh what other health
benefits did you discover from using
medical medium information so there's
definitely been a shift in my mood I
mean I'm I still have my moments right
cuz I'm human but the heavy metal detox
smoothie really has helped alleviate
symptoms of depression and anxiety and
just like negative thoughts uh also
there's more of a feeling of being in my
skin like I'm at home in my body whereas
before there was a sense of like a
disassociation so it's been very helpful
mentally physically and it's also very
much elevated me spiritually because of
his focus on the angels and the
spiritual r
so it's like Mind Body Soul interesting
do you have any spiritual lessons that
you've learned uh through medical medium
information that you'd like to share
with us yes spirit is always with you
your angels are always with you and if
you're ever
feeling in a painful moment you can
always call upon the Angels you can call
upon Spirit you can call upon god and
goddess I'm very much about the divine
feminine a medical medium has helped me
really establish that relationship with
the spiritual realm yeah yeah beautiful
a lot of people talk about their healing
Journey also crossing over and being
quite spiritual as well yeah it's it's
I've always been a spiritual person but
the mm info definitely elevated that to
a different dimension so his information
about spirituality is very unique and
beautiful and pure and it definitely
serves the soul do you have a favorite
thing about medical medium information
that you would like to share with the
community watching online I do talk to
your angels and drink your celery juice
and eat your papaya honey because it's
the best for the skin yeah okay the
papaya I'll take that one too yeah yeah
so the papaya the Angels celery juice
and you'll be good to go what and what
profound lessons have you learned from
your journey uh healing chronic illness
discipline is freedom you know
discipline sometimes seems like just
such a buzzkill obviously because you
have to Institute guidelines for your
behaviors and your thoughts but the more
that you do it the Freer that you are
right because then you're you're warding
off all of the things that don't serve
you and creating space for what does but
it does require discipline you know but
that ultimately creates a sense of
freedom and peace in the body mind
beautiful thank you so much for talking
to us enjoy the rest of your evening so
nice to meet you too yes bye hi how are
you I'm very well thank you what is your
name my name is Lisa bck Lisa it's so
nice to meet you I'm Danielle where did
you travel from to be here from
Connecticut yeah wow what a journey so
did you fly here yes so we came in
January but you know with everything
that happened I was able to make it here
this time so grateful for that
opportunity yes beautiful did you come
here with anyone this evening um no my
family was going to come but I did meet
a lot of wonderful people so I'm having
a great time lots of beautiful friends
in the line here yes first time away
from children too so I don't even know
how to deal with this Freedom yeah so oh
you're going to have an incredible night
tonight yes thank you what was it that
made you want to come and attend this
event um I was back here in Culver City
in June and then I just wanted to come
to meet medical medium and express my
gratitude on more of a one-on-one level
yeah but um we started like seven over
seven years ago my whole family my
little one started when she was one and
a half and my other daughter started
when she was uh three and my
grandparents who are 88 and 94 have been
on the same Journey with us for 7 years
they uh they are actually reposted on
social media yesterday for wait I saw
that yeah that was from my grandparents
oh my gosh that's so beautiful that your
whole family is doing it together yes we
are y so it's been a wonderful Journey
um and one big thing that I healed was I
had really bad acne for almost 20 years
being called pizza face and like Ring of
Fire I mean you name it and you know
they have you on every drug every potion
every lotion try this try that and until
I found out the root cause you know I
was able to heal that and also help
myself and my family too you talk about
your family so uh have you or your
family healed any other symptoms or
conditions using medical medium
information yes so my mom had a really
bad stroke in 2017 which left her in the
ICU for almost 30 days which is
obviously a huge deal and she had the
top stroke doctor on the northeast but
they didn't even know the root cause and
I would ask all these questions and they
were actually annoyed of me but it
wasn't until mm information were like
wow there is a reason for strokes and
this is the root cause and this is what
we we need to do and obviously you know
she's not perfect with mm but she does
the morning routine she's on a bunch of
supplements and she couldn't be stronger
than ever we didn't know if she was
going to live it was literally minute by
minute 30 days in the ICU and she's like
thriving you wouldn't even know he
wouldn't even know yeah that's
incredible that's such an inspiring
story is your family tuning into the
live stream at the moment I hope so but
if not you know they'll watch it later
yeah hi everyone Hi Mom Dad yep hi yes
and what about your kids how do they
enjoy the medical Medan protocol
sometimes they'll give me problems but
you know you start off small so my
10-year-old now when she was three she
we gave her a little shot glass of it
and now she's up to you know like a
coffee cup size of you know um of the
celery but I can see their progress as
well like they're rarely sick and if
they're sick it's for like 2 days with a
little cough it's not anything bedridden
or anything crazy like so many kids have
these days so it's just a beautiful
process to live it and to feel it and
just to see it like right in front of
your face it's incredible thank you so
much for sharing your journey with us
yes so nice to meet you too enjoy yes
we're going to talk to our next guest
hello hi I'm Danielle I'm Pam so nice to
meet you so this is Pam everyone hi and
tell us why did you want to come and
attend this event tonight um when he did
the Culver City Event I couldn't make
that event and so I said to one of my
medical medium people I said well
wouldn't it be fun if he did something
more intimate and then he announced the
and so this was the first Cafe Gratitude
one that I was able to come to yeah
beautiful where did you travel from to
attend this event Orange County you're
very lucky I feel very lucky did you
come with anyone tonight or solo and
meeting friends here in the community
they're actually in line who I came with
who did you come with friends or family
friends and do they all do the medical
meeting protocol with you they do they
do they all helped save my life W
incredible do you mind if we talk a
little bit about that yeah be great um
in um January 12th of 2022 was my mom's
birthday I woke up and I couldn't my big
joints my shoulders and my hips and my
knees I just couldn't I couldn't move
and so I started going to doctors as you
know several several doctors and I was
finally at a cancer doctor on May 17th
and she said I can't test you for
anything else I don't know what's wrong
with you she said I can't find anything
I said well is it fibromyalgia we're
just guessing and she goes well if you
want to call it that we can just call it
that I said you know I said I think that
I need to find something else that was
in May and I weighed 97 lbs and in on
June 16th someone came up to me at my
job and she said you need to read the
medical medium I ordered it from Amazon
read it that weekend on the 17th started
the celer juice on the 22nd of June and
it will be three years this year that
I've been on the medical medium and it
literally saved my life and it was
really because for me what it was was
that they were just taking so much
blood they took 60 vials in one week so
they were just taking out my whole
immune system and I was so I was just
skin and bones at the time but super
super grateful yes very grateful that
you're here and able to feel well enough
to be here and celebrate and have this
enjoy this beautiful dinner I'm so
excited I'm so excited just to say thank
you really can you talk a little bit uh
more in depth about the symptoms and
conditions that that healed from using
medical medium information you know
what's interesting I said one time I was
telling some of my friends that I'm here
with that I should have written
everything down that healed because so
many things went away that I didn't even
realize were were I you know you get to
a certain age you don't you just think
that they're just part of getting old
but all of a sudden everything starts
going away and you're going oh my
goodness they're so my throat was
closing up at the time but there were
just and all the joint pain went away
and then there was just lots of small
symptoms that just continued to go away
um stomach issues and so many many
things I can't even tell you pain in my
foot pain in my side back pain
everything just disappeared the longer
that I've been on it well they may be
small but those things I feel like we
kind of tell ourselves oh that's it like
it's age or we just kind of live with it
but it's really that's incredible how
you able to lift those things and I
think you notice the difference when
it's gone you know oh it's amazing it's
amazing I feel better than I've ever
felt and so much better just emotionally
Happy Everything my it's changed my
whole life life it's incredible just
incredible wow and what about your
friends that are here as well how did
they discover did they discover it
through you or well I work at a school
so I happened to just reach out to see
if anybody knew anybody that was on the
medical medium and there happened to be
four people there so I reached out right
away to all of them to have all of them
help me with every tip trick whatever
they knew that would help was fantastic
what was some of the best tips and
tricks that they shared with you that
really propelled your healing Journey oh
she one of of them one time came into
where I was sitting eating some lunch
and I had a little tiny bowl of spinach
in there and she goes yeah she goes
that's not enough spinach and so she she
said you need to do a half a pound of
spinach a day so I just made it into a
smoothie in the afternoon that was
lifechanging it just catapulted me into
healing like I could not believe so many
things you know cut the bottom off the
cilantro and put it in water that keeps
it for the whole week just simple small
things that made it easier for me yeah
oh that's great what are you most
excited about tonight though just
telling Anthony thank you for saving my
life we're here at this collaboration
between Cafe Gratitude and medical
medium what is it about this
collaboration that also excites you it's
so funny you should say that so my
husband works out of the country two
weeks a month and so I take him to the
airport and then when I drop him off at
the airport I come over here so I can
eat I know it's so nice the
collaboration is so nice cuz we get
tired of you know our own cooking it's
nice to go have someone else's cooking
and the fact that you get to enjoy
healthy healing pizza tonight I'm so
excited for that well I am too cuz
that's something I don't make it's not
one of the things I make so it's
exciting and the cookies that oh I
didn't even hear yeah there's cookies
there's time tea oh oh it's on yeah it's
like four course meal family style
amazing amazing and the light blost as
well ex exactly that's always exciting
it's going to be great thank you so much
for your time beautiful enjoy your
evening okay we're going to talk to our
next guest hello oh a group hello hello
dou yes okay could you introduce
yourselves for everyone watching hi I'm
Claudia and I'm from Austria yes I'm
from Austria did you fly all the way
here just for the event yes yeah wow
what was it that made you want to get on
a plane and come here to Cafe Gratitude
in
Venice we just realize now that we are
here as for me it's it's it's so amazing
it's it's incredible so we are just glad
to be here and to have the possibility
uh to experience all this and uh to talk
to anony Anthony and uh to enjoy the
food at the Cafe Gratitude for the first
time so I'm really
excited and to made all the community
here as well you having fun in line yeah
we really we had a lot of fun and we met
a lot of people from the American
Community it was so interesting to talk
to them and to see how they are working
with the protocols and it's really very
interesting yeah how did you both
discover the medical medium information
and how long have you been doing the
protocol for um um I'm in the sixth year
now and um I got the tip from the hint
from a colleague from a friend and it
takes two years and she always told me
in those two years Claudia this is
something for you this helps you with
your symptoms with all your ACH aches
and aches and pain I had a lot of pain
and uh you have to you have to try it
and I always said no I cannot um eat no
gluten no pizza I cannot live without
without that and yeah and then um was
the point um I had 24 hours 7 uh days a
week pain and ages and it was really
really bad nobody could help me no
doctor no practitioner
and I thought okay well let's give it a
try and it was amazing yeah I the pain
was gone and it was so released and I
was so yeah it feel
amazing and nobody could believe that um
that you're really suffering and and and
they all the doctors over a that's not
so that's not so bad and and and it got
it will be better and and it's yeah it
was really it's lifechanging yeah I have
I Anthony and spirit of compassion they
gave me a life worth and and I'm so
gratitude for that and I'm so grateful
and so
yeah no word can express my what I what
it means to me because everybody says to
me oh you cannot eat that you cannot eat
that that's not the point because I have
a live a life now and and I enjoy it and
it's a quality life and it's it's so
amazing and
yeah and what about you what about your
healing journey I discovered the medical
medium information in
2017 and um and who did you find out
from one another or did you meet through
the community no uh we made a an
education for mm practitioners in in
Germany and there we met so yeah sorry
back to 2017 though absolutely okay um
and um I started uh right when I found
the book um and um it was no wonder that
I found it uh found it because um I was
suffering more than 35 years for more
than 35 years and I always was looking
for for information for help and nobody
could help me and uh I had this the
story as the most uh people in the mm
Community have have that um I tried
everything and um every every time I was
at the at the doctor's office they they
told me that my blood work is perfect
everything was perfect everything's fine
so it's just in your head and I knew
that it wasn't in my head and later on
when I was in my 40s then uh I started
getting really diagnosis uh but just
once with uh cause unknown so the same
corner and uh
it went more and more bad and worse and
uh I had times uh when I really didn't
want to live anymore because uh I was
just in pain and uh stiffness and I had
more than uh 50 symptoms
symptoms uh I had
um I was a brain FK fatigue uh and I was
bad ridden part-time bad ridden I had
the severe migrain severe constipation
from my youth uh beginning on and um so
it was really bad and uh when I found
this information and I started and I I
didn't jump in with the whole
information I just started slowly with
celery tues and don't eating uh no Foods
uh but not really you know some people
start full power and with 20 day8 CLE
cleanse and such things I didn't uh do
that
um but my migraine was and I had really
SE severe migraine I I was laying uh I
think every second weekend for three or
four days I was in bed with my migraine
and uh this was gone after half a year
and my my muscle pain and my joint pain
was gone in two weeks and uh my
stiffness uh was gone in I think three
months it was amazing I mean I still
have to work on some um uh symptoms uh
that's okay but uh it's it's incredible
uh how it worked and I was so glad and
um I had the same like laia that uh some
people from other friends they they
cannot understand that I'm doing that
because that's what Anthony always told
us uh that you have to to walk in their
shoes you have to experiences only then
you can understand it's the only way so
yeah what's so great about these events
is connecting with other people who have
gone through similar stories to you and
understand your healing Journey yeah
there is they understand and and you
don't it don't need any word it don't
need any word so you can and you're not
the alien you're not the alien yes yes
that's so true you you you can um feel
that the uh the words are so truth you
you feel the truth with every with every
word in this in this books and in his
lives and in everything he tells us it's
amazing and there is only one thing I
want to say for all those women out
there please tell us it's all those
women out there who have endometriosis
there is really a great protocol and
please please please try it give him
give it really a shot and it's amazing
and they can change the life and they
can have probably children and they can
have a quality life yes yeah and that's
amazing yeah know that's big it's it's
about quality of life right and if you
know it's incredible that you guys you
both have your life back you're able to
get on a plane you're able to come here
be at Cafe Gratitude yes absolutely I
mean that's amazing I
mean I was I think I was uh on on my way
to come here for 24 hours because I had
no direct uh uh flight and uh this would
be unimaginable
I couldn't imagine this years before met
Island
so no no there was no chance no idea
yeah
here what were some of the protocols
that really propelled your healing
Journey forward for people watching
online I think um the liver uh liver
cleanse and there is um there's one um
live from Anthony and he it's about
endometriosis and that's really with
very very important information and so
you can um you get all those things in
this in this life and it's really great
yeah because it's in it's very important
to leave some things out for the first
year and then you can tighten
it uh more calm yeah yeah you can more
calm you know so the first year is
really important yeah and do you have an
encouraging message you would like to
share with people watching who are going
through their health inhaling Journey mm
protocols do the mm protocols if you're
suffering any kind of symptom it's uh so
amazing it's the only way it it it works
and uh it's worth it and uh for all
those people who are afraid of
um that you will miss something this
feeling is gone that quickly you cannot
imagine I mean I was a really cheese
chunky I couldn't imagine live without
cheese
and uh I don't care about anymore so no
way so that's really great yeah great
and thank you so much for sharing your
story and opening up to us thank you my
first interview thank you so much oh wow
you did amazing that was
great thank you so much a enjoy your
evening thank you so much we'll talk to
our next guest hello how are you I'm
Danielle what's your name Caroline
Caroline so lovely to meet you where did
you travel from to be here this evening
from Berlin Germany wow what a journey
what was it that made you want to travel
all the way here to Los Angeles to be
here and attend this event I think it's
him medical medium It's s so it's it's
the spirit about it and the truth behind
it and I think it's the real truth and
it's like a banana you know how can you
describe somebody how a banana tastes if
you never have eaten one before so this
is medical medium try it and then you
know it yes and uh it takes time of
course it's not um an instant success
like a pill but um it's coming slowly
it's going slowly so um good things need
time and I think it's worth to to give
the time yes yes yeah well because we're
here at Cafe Gratitude for the medical
medium Cafe Gratitude collaboration what
are you most excited about for this
evening about seeing Anthony
life having the possibility to feel his
energy his vibration to to see all those
people here which are coming all over
the world and
so it's amazing yeah it's incredible
that so many people have come from all
over the world to be here what did it
feel like connecting with people in line
tonight without words because we are we
are sharing the same passion we are we
we are having the same goal and I think
um it's an it's an uplifting spirit all
over here and I wish this for the entire
world and uh this is all I can I can say
yeah yes and how long have you been
using medical medium information for oh
I stumbled over it I'm an Pilatus
instructor and client of mine just said
you don't know Anthony William I should
know and so I uh looked it up on YouTube
and I was thinking okay wild blueberries
uhhuh and if you keep it a little bit
Frozen in your fruit salad it tastes
better and it's even better I tasted and
it was so so convincing and this is why
I started it and I thought I don't need
it actually because I'm
healthy but as more I went into it I
understood that um having symptoms is
The New Normal exactly been talking
about that tonight that you know we get
told we have these aches and pains and
we think you know it's staging right
it's just or hormones or yeah you you
have to take it if you are older or yeah
not even older even the the the the
little girls and boys they are suffering
so much they are having um belly ache
they are having headache so much often
they are growing up they are not feeling
well
it's in a way totally clear but to the
others who are not in that spirit yet
and I wish it's coming soon and more and
more
bold it will take time so so you talk
about some of those things that you just
thought were normal uh aches and pains
and things like that can you talk a
little bit of more about them and what
things lifted for you as you as you
started using the medical medium
information what things healed for you
um I thought my digestion is perfect and
then I understood that the
digestion I had is not the normal for
example that you have much more action
in your body and that you can get rid of
things and you don't have to carry
things old things just like in life with
you so
sorry um but yeah you can you can get
rid of things which are not good for you
and so you you feel it you you feel
lighter you you feel more clarity you
you understand more things you get
deeper into the spirituality you can
talk better to people you understand but
for in every case uh in in any case is
it's good to to understand the
compassion behind it and so that you
understand we are connected and I think
this it's not a movement this truth is
just connecting us we are getting
rewired reconnected and I
think this is how we have to go for yes
reconnecting and I love that you say
compassion I feel that a lot in the air
this evening that everyone has that
compassion for one another yes yes I can
feel that too because you see you look
into the eyes and they are shining this
is there's a spark inside it's like a
Godly spark you see it finally because
if you I'm from Berlin here Berlin and
LA in a way you see the people are in a
way depressed they are walking like that
and since I'm teaching posture I can see
that as well in posture
and they are having so such a depressed
posture and if I see there are a in the
groceries only with chips this is not
okay today morning I was in the
groceries and a woman came and her
breakfast was just pulling on her chips
back to have this as breakfast so this
is for me in a way in former times I
thought okay why not it's not my way but
now I understand this is a big thing yes
yeah and what's your favorite thing
about medical medium information
H okay do I need to say one you can
share a couple okay um celery juice y I
hated it my friend was giving me a
juicer and the first thing what what was
coming out was I think a little short
glass from a big stock of of uh celery
and it was
disgusting and I was really
tempted to to give it up at the F in the
first day on the first day but I was
keeping I was I was go I was keeping
going and um the next is the heavy metal
detox the the morning routine I think
this is moving the needle yeah and then
if you are having if you are in this
state then it's getting by itself more
and more deeper MH yeah the morning
routine is great I feel like it doesn't
take that much time once you get into a
rhythm with it it's pretty good exactly
exactly so I I have to um commit that I
prepare for 2 days because I'm so busy I
I have really a lot things to do but
it's okay so at least I have one day
fresh and then I have
24-hour old celery juice heavy metal
however or a shot I think this is okay I
think this is okay yeah you're doing
amazing well thank you so much for
talking to us lovely to meet you yes
enjoy the rest of your evening yes yeah
yes and we're going to talk to one other
guest now hello hi welcome thank you you
look nice and cozy and warm I'm trying
to stay warm yes bit cooler than usual
here in Los Angeles this evening it is
it is and what's your name my name is
Tracy Tracy so nice to meet you I'm
Danielle thank you where did you travel
to be here tonight San Diego oh nice not
too far but no not too far but that's
great you're here what was it about this
event that made you want to
attend oh my gosh um of course meeting
Anthony and the food at Cafe Gratitude
is amazing and I'm really excited to
have medical medium approved food to eat
at a restaurant which I don't get to do
because I cook everything I make so it's
nice it's so exciting to be here this
evening around all these other
individuals that are on their healing
Journey as well and we're going to get
to your healing Journey but we just have
to cross because the uh meet and greet
is about to start so I'm going to
continue talking to you but we're on the
live stream we're going to head over to
the meet and greet right now with aw
it's about to start isn't that exciting
so exciting I can't wait yeah let's go
check it out all
right thank you so much
Journey for almost nine years in
2016 somebody gave remember I do I know
I know you don't have that that one
right now no a lot of extractors the
Advan it helps so much okay good good
good you're taking care of yourself good
yes I really want to thank you for when
you were done in Calabasas around 4:00
and you did the last Light blast and you
said goodbye but you came back and you
said spirit said there are a few more
people who just walked in and that's
when you felt and that's when you felt
it I just walked in I wasn't there for
the First on and so I wanted that light
to channel it to my mom and that's what
did at that that last one did and next
morning 5:00 a.m. I got a phone call
from my mom saying I have no pain oh my
God and that's what we needed she came
here spent 3 months in us we actually
booked ticket for January but she's gone
now she's not here anymore she had to go
back so that was for you see that that I
came on at the very end andal she needed
that she's healing she's I'm excited I'm
excited I'm excited well thank you for
coming tonight that's amazing want to
get a picture let's get a picture thank
you and I have one more question if you
can I would like to show
you wonderful show you this could you
please approach this problem in soon W
that been 30e Journey for this woman
whoa she's been with it for 30
years okay I'll start talking about that
okay thank you okay bless your
heart hi hi Hi how are you I'm good I'm
so happy to see you I met you in the
summer in June in oh my God but I wanted
so year ago I want I know I wanted to
thank you not only just for all the
healing that you've helped me with but
specifically after I lost my son about
10 months into my journey of medical
medium healing the medical medium tools
helped to give me my life back because
after I lost my 26-year-old son I just
felt like I was not how could I live how
could I live without him and I did I
felt that Soul stepping outside my body
that you talk
about above and I did like your soul
healing meditation every night and you
brought it back you every night for one
year I did it every night and then I did
special healing foods that you had in
the life for
emotional so you really committed
yourself and you were doing everything
you were doing yes you were doing
everything for the emotional that you
could yeah and I I had setbacks in my
physical healing that I had healed but
because of your tools I I heal you
brought yourself back you know you're
strong you're a strong person to get
through that the greatest loss that
could ever be is what you went through
and for you to survive that and fight
forward you know that's a incredible
inspiration for others yeah and I just
want to thank you so much I'm so so
grateful I I don't know where I would be
without medical medium information I
know you've dedicated your life to to
just being there for all of us and it's
just I'm sorry I feel like I'm going to
cry but I just it it's just really I'm
I'm just so so so grateful so thank you
for coming thank you for coming let's
get a picture over here for sure yes of
course of course thank you thank you so
sorry about everything you've gone
through
seriously right right here
thank you thank you for thank you for
the gift okay thank you so
much
Hi how are you how are you
doing so excited to see you thank you
for coming I saw you on cver City Kelsey
from YouTube yeah oh my God
Kelsey thank you for coming I read all
your comments I always do Kelsey Vach
there it is you heal 50
symptoms I tell everybody all the time I
know it's 50
symptoms I know thank you thank you for
hanging in there through all that and
all your healing process CU I think
about you a lot because of the 50
symptoms because it's people would never
know what what that's like to have that
many and they'll be like well how how
can you have that many symptoms but you
can it's so easy to have that many
symptoms but you're not functioning
you're not functioning so everything
just starts going wrong and you fought
your way back I was nonverbal I had no
energy I couldn't I remember I saw a
comment of one time you wrote about a
few things about it like you said you
had this and this yeah it was nonstop
I'm proud of now I'm here thank you for
being thank you for being here thank you
seriously I can't believe I'm meeting
you in person okay here step forward a
little bit that' be
great this is amazing you're going to
have some food tonight okay I'm excited
now when I see your comments and be like
oh my God I was just talking to
you hey hello Hi how are you hi I'm
cloria hi hi hi I'm good to see you hi
I'm so grateful to to meet you and to
say thank
you I cannot say I miss the words well
thank you for coming a small present for
you
okay wow it's a big present yeah that
those are letters from mattress illness
mattress Island yeah mattress Island
okay and they are from Germany and
Austria wow this is very special right
here okay I I okay I I truly truly see
this as just a a beautiful beautiful
gift okay with everybody's heart and
soul in here and it means the world to
me so okay so tell everybody okay how
much I appreciate this please that would
be wonderful watching us okay okay well
that's even that's better okay that's
good they're watching I want everybody
to know this is so beautiful thank you
small present for me and because all the
whole German speaking Community is
always praying for you and your family I
I need it the whole German community I
want them I want their their prayers of
course because I can use them and I did
some prayer cards for
you this is this is precious this is
precious we pray for your family and for
your beloved ones for your saf thank you
you so much for all those things you I
feel the same way I feel the same way
just so you know I do I do I do may I
can we get a picture together yeah thank
you incredible well I hope you enjoy the
food tonight too and everything thank
you hello hey hi how you doing I'm fine
thank you and you good good fine I
cannot believe that I'm here and I'm
where did you come from Austria Austria
with cloria oh together amazing I I I
came um one day later because it wasn't
posible for me but uh yes I mean I'm
just absolutely excited but Anthony may
I ask you one question can Spirit tell
me if the the dentist I have now is uh
okay for me I was looking for a dentist
more than 40 years and I what do you
like
them spirit says you like them enough
yeah I mean if he does good work that's
the main thing for me to s on this
things because my my teeth are
completely destroyed and I'm really
concerned about my teeth well you you
you
just just it it it it has to feel right
one thing at a time you can get you know
that you get done you know communication
with them is important and you have that
though like Spirit saying you have the
communication with them and that doesn't
that's not like that with all dentists
most dentists communication isn't there
they just want to get it done and then
move you out but spirit says you
actually have that communication with
them yes okay so that means something
okay do you want to get a picture Pa
thank
you thank you for coming yes yes thank
you thank you
what's going on
herey nice thank you nice to meet you
thank you for all this what you for all
us so amazing well it it's an honor okay
it's an honor to help in any way I can
it it truly
is I I WR you a letter you did you have
a letter there it's your present this is
a present made some
angels did you make those
the Angels
yes my God and she was at Med Med
meeting in my hometown there's a few
people around 40 people and they
are and now you have did you make
this oh my God that is amazing that is
amazing thank you thank you so much okay
this is a beautiful beautiful gift I
will treasure it okay
okay very special very special okay do
do you want to do you want to get a
picture together you guys
okay thank you for coming truly it means
the
[Music]
world hey you nice to meet you again hey
I have a honey from the Barian El for
you really I had to open it once though
I open please you opened it yes I thank
you that's okay you can open
it you can you can do that is there a
little there's a
little okay good I love honey I know I
know I love honey too yeah and when it's
really good when it's really good it's
another level so this is really good one
yes thank you for this thank you so I'm
glad you're here how how far did you
travel from Germany I travel with my
whole family my God to come here yes my
mom she's she has Alzheimer's I'm trying
to my own family is that Mom there
yes well let's get we'll get Mom over
here let's get Mom over
here hi she's on medic medum you're
doing medical medium things right now
usually very proud of you really is it
usually blue it's
usually heavy metal detox every day it's
good we got to get the metals out it's
important anything that I'm missing that
I could that's the most important with
this no matter what and then go through
the books and and you'll it it'll come
you know you open the pages and
sometimes you open the pages right in
the spot you need to be in that special
moment and and so yes can I know where
is it coming from we had Mercury mirrors
in the house is that it or really
Mercury
yes she was an antique how old were oh
Antiques and we had five Mercury they
used to put mercury in the back of the
glass yes yes removed it last this year
last year so okay okay well look you're
working on the healing process Mercury
comes out it does leave the body okay
here step forward here and I also have
my son here he has Metals his name is
Leo nice to meet you he was full on
medic medium for I don't know two three
and then he fell off the band
you got off the bandwagon you got
knocked off the bandwagon are you back
on yet no is tonight going to start is
this maybe okay okay I I that's all I
can I can't ask for more than that
that's fine that's
fine but I want to ask a question so how
do you I know it's true that you hear
Spirit how do I know yeah how does he
how can he know a lot of times he's
really
stubborn let's
go but in a good way though cuz you got
a good
heart
[Laughter]
he thank
you spirit says it's hard when you care
too much he cares too much but yet but
yet so you know he's hard on himself too
okay it's good to care but he's very
hard on himself okay I love you guys I
love you too I'm proud of you by the way
just to do any medical medium I'm proud
of you
okay hug hey look how are you you how
are you doing oh I just want to say
thank you so much and you changed my
life and I'm so eternally grateful for
you and I hope that god and goddess
always bless you and protect you thank
you I I'll I'll take any blessing any
prayer thank you um I found this in my
first yeah do You' like to have it and
if there's I could always use more
wisdom okay so this is beautiful all
right and if there's any message to
receive I would love to receive it well
just just remember this okay that that
you're moving forward okay it's not
about the past with you so you need to
kind of like set your own boundary about
how much you think about certain things
the past exactly okay you know what I'm
saying right I do I really and then it
just when that happens just say you know
what I'm moving forward okay okay okay
thank you
aess your heart
okay hi Anthony nice to meet you to meet
we were in Culver City um in June and
these are my girls they couldn't come so
if you could sign that my God sign us
she's you want me to sign the back no
just the picture the actual picture so
she's been doing mm since 3 and the baby
since a year and a half amazing yeah and
my grandparents have been doing it for
seven years they're the ones that were
on the social media I can't believe this
yeah this is unbelievable yeah so I just
want to express my gratitude to you tell
tell them I said hi okay are they
watching now or no um they're probably
sleeping but they're watch Sleeping okay
to watch it later maybe yeah but thanks
for being a gift to humanity yeah thank
you want to take a pict yes
please thank you it's so nice to have
you
here hey how are you I wanted you to
know that you inspire me to be
lighthearted that's important yeah and
it it's a powerful
word it is when it's put together just
lighten hearten and and put together
into one big word it's a very powerful
word it it it does something you know
when you even hear it it does something
and some words are that powerful and
it's important it it to keep that
light-hearted nature whenever you can
anytime you feel frustrated cuz spirit
says you do get frustrated and when you
get that way with rightfully so though
rightfully so spirit says you get a lot
of challenges okay right just just
remember to when that comes to be like
you know what stay lighthearted
regardless of what's Happening try to
stay lighthearted and you're doing that
yeah okay I'm proud of you I'm proud of
you thank you want to get a picture here
you can step forward a little bit
okay thank you for coming
tonight hey nice hat thank you it's
pleasure good to see you pleasure me I'm
brand new so I'm just learning that's
amazing you're just doing medical medium
stuff just I'm just getting kind of
introduced to all of you why I'm here
tonight with my friend to listen to what
you have you tried celer Juice yet I did
a little bit about a year ago but that's
amazing
okay I just found that I got a lot of
Pock ping from that and sometimes when
talks that's kind well it's it's pulling
a lot of stuff out that's why gets a lot
of stuff out but I'm glad you're
starting like into stuff yeah I've
really been on a spiritual PA too and oh
it's one and the same MH when you're
doing information from a above it
becomes just one and the same it's
spiritual and physical it's not just the
physical because the information comes
from a source that's spiritual so then
all these things happen spiritually
while you're doing it that's true I do
was just thinking that too because I was
really on hor PL lately as I've done a
lot of you know trying to kind of figure
out things as I was you know going
through different physical issues and
then I came back around to oh maybe I
should be going back into do that's more
physically cling and yeah that's amazing
well thank you for coming this is want
to get a picture question sure I was
wondering um Spirit of spirit of
compassion have anything to say
to it's okay to forget some certain
things that you forget like spirit says
you do forget certain things because you
have so much going on the memory lapse
is because you're trying to remember
everything it's it's you're
very in a good way you want a counting
of everything you know what I'm saying
so you have to it's okay to let some of
the things go and be like you know what
I don't have to have full control over
every little thing I could let some
things go a little bit and then free
myself up a littleit okay thank you so
much thank you
[Music]
thank you for
coming hey it's so good to see you again
I have a card for you oh thank you and I
have had the privilege of helping a
family member first of all thank you so
much for all the healing that I've been
able to receive and still am receiving
from you sharing this information that's
wonderful so grateful that's wonderful
and um I've helped a family member
similar to Cole your friend
um through an addiction with detoxing
with the protocols I was using for my
thyroid somehow addiction is really hard
and uh I'm I'm asking if I can I want to
I'm wondering if the supplements and the
protocols can be put together can they
be combined to create kind of a
something that can be put into rehab
centers and help people um yeah I mean
there maybe I could talk to some well
that's well that's the thing I would
just want to do it right if I do it well
well I mean you have to like see what
speaks to you too okay A little goes a
long way that's what Spirit does say
keep that in mind even with addiction it
doesn't have to be the kitchen sink do
have to be the whole doesn't have to be
the whole kitchen sink with addiction
that that's where we have to be careful
CU my thyroid protocol helped her
exactly exactly a little goes a long way
with addiction spirit is just remember
that so then you can pick and choose and
be like okay this is going to be okay
let's do this okay all right all right
thank you so much thank
you thank you
thank you for coming tomorrow I'll see
you start time just oh yeah
yeah hey how are you good to see you
good to see you oh I'm just so grateful
to be here so humbl thank you for coming
yes and I just want to say
just thank you I I don't think I'd be
here I don't take those words lightly I
don't you know I
I it's a lot because it has great
meaning okay cuz I know the path that
could be behind all that and it's no
joke so when I hear that from you it's
serious and there's a lot of depth and
there's a lot of story behind it and
experiences so just know I I I I
understand okay you want to get a
picture
sure where where am I
looking thank you for coming
tonight hello hey good to see you good
to see you too I just want to say thank
you so much for everything you've
done thank you for coming and thank you
for doing all the things that you've
done though you did the
work you're doing the
work well thank you I mean I'm glad I
can be a part of it you know and that
means the world to me that I could be a
part of it um it takes a hardworking
Soul though and you have that in you but
you've been like that your whole life
though that's not just about
this spirit says that you have always
worked hard all these years with
everything with everything and you keep
everything and lists and you
write things down and you're very
organized and that has that that's good
too because that is a gift that you're
using into your healing process so just
know that I'm proud of you okay thank
you thank you so much do you want to get
a picture yes want to St forward a
little
bit thank you for coming tonight have a
good
night oh my God so happy to be here
again thank you for coming you got a
little baby yes last time I was pregnant
when I came I know I know and then
there's the baby now the baby's here oh
my God adorable little baby medal medium
baby medical medium baby and I have my
son Noah last time we came with him and
my husband Noah he's also medical medium
kid yes yes I remember your letter
yeah well thank you for coming and thank
you for bringing your beautiful little
baby yes I didn't know if I would be
able to make it because it's only 6
weeks old well no I I I was going to say
that's that's why I'm surprised yeah
yeah but I'm glad you came it's
wonderful yes I'm very happy and
grateful to be here how far did you
travel I live in LA okay perfect that
made me
happy doesc have a message for me
tonight let's see
um this would be a little bit different
with you okay um spirit says you you
tend to find like relaxation later on at
night does that make sense a little
later in the night yeah okay and and
spirit says that
um um focus on a little bit more reading
when that happens when you're when
you're up in moments later on at night
it helps you with all kinds of different
things that are very important so
reading yes do a little reading when you
can like praying no reading reading a
little bit more reading okay it takes
your mind off of all these other things
and that keeps you stronger I don't know
why with you but that's what I'm hearing
yeah yeah so that's the advice for
tonight well that's for any night in the
future any night in the future yeah yes
yes okay want to get a picture yes thank
you so much let me move this another
picture
too thank you for coming amazing I'm so
honored you brought your little baby oh
my God
[Music]
hey Anthony hey how you doing how are
you fantastic how are you a few rapid
fire questions for you okay can Spirit
tell me what percent of my liver has
been cleaned up okay what percent of
toxic metals have been eliminated and
how much Karma I've eliminated Karma you
worried about Karma I want to make my
Ascension I mean you've already got the
karma beat that's a like like Spirit of
compassion sees it different than Karma
it's a different thing it it's not from
Spirit it's not called karma it's
something else that spirit always tells
me about but but let's just say karma
yes you got that taken care of okay yeah
so you have to now be like okay that's
done what's next you what I mean yes
don't hold on to that okay yeah cuz
you've already surpassed that you just
don't feel it
you're right I don't okay but you
already did okay and then everything
else you're moving up that percentage
every day just keep it going okay keep
you have any advice for me um you could
always do a little bit
more okay meaning meaning like
um all right well just remember this
okay you're already up there with
cleansing you've done a lot I have okay
so the little bit more now are things
like nature and stuff like that look in
the look in all that area okay look in
all like the nature tools and all that
like
ining like the first book go into all
those and see what speaks to you but
bring in more nature okay thank
[Music]
you thank you for
coming Hi H are you my God I just want
to thank you for saving my life you
saved my life you're going to get me
choked up here I don't want to get you
choked up oh my God I was so close to
godone I was within a couple months we
were just about to buy a wheelchair my
husband was my God and they had taken 60
vials of blood in oh my God and um
someone said to me you need to go get
the medical medium and I ordered it on
June 16th of 2022 I read it and started
the C reice on the 22nd and 24th hours I
was better I kid you not and I just
wanted to say thank you that was it oh
my God good for you seriously good for
you than you so that's
wonderful I'm very proud of you very
proud of I can't tell you how grateful I
am that you do what you do I mean for
all of us I hope you're taking care of
yourself I I I try okay okay I
try it's a good reminder thank you
though yeah please I need that reminder
yeah thank you for doing all yes I do
need one bad thank you for taking care
of yourself really good
okay hi hey how are you nice to see you
again good to see you I was just saying
it's crazy my first year in my healing I
sat outside and cry and I read your
books and I was saying I would just love
to meet him and then boom now it's been
like what four or five times that's
great it's amazing yeah I you know it it
look why not you know I'm I'm I'm able
to do this right now and not you know
distracted or working on so many things
that I can't be here in the moment so it
it's it's good that you're coming
grateful I mean who knows you know it's
it's I'm because it's been like years
before I was you know in person so it's
good that you're you're coming out yeah
does Spirit have any messages for
me I mean just always you can't beat
yourself up whatever you do okay so
always remember that um you do really
good really good about that really good
about that really good and then it hits
okay so when it comes to that point and
it hits remember what I just said okay
okay step over
here thank you so thank you for coming
so much andc thank you so much I'm so
happy that I finally can meet you thank
you for coming thank you for being here
and being such a great messenger oh I'm
honored I'm honored it it's it's the
least I can do because you know look how
hard you work on your health look how
hard you're working every day on on your
being and your soul and your spirit and
if I can be a part of it if I can help
in any way it means the world okay
you have any idea how I can be more
useful for
mankind I think look I think it come the
Angels do all kinds of things that we
just don't even see and then they do
things that we do see I think
something's coming your way where you're
going to have this feeling of this
purpose you already have the purpose
spirit says but then all of a sudden now
it's like oh no I'm going to do this now
it's coming it's coming I
feel thank you so much
two
more maybe one
without
[Music]
okay it's Michelle hey nice to see you
no way oh God I want to just thank you
and have so much gratitude for your
information and it's out on social it's
in the books all free for us and I
that's how I learned about you on social
in 2018 I saw a celery post and I
thought oh my gosh I'll try that for my
for my neurological limes disease and my
a depression and a chronic that's how it
started for you concussions I saw a post
so um oh I remember that the concussion
post you're right yes yes yes so without
you I wouldn't have healed these things
and in the interim I healed a lifelong
nickel allergy I've had W and so I've
come here tonight with my jewelry oh my
God and zippers is that gold is that yes
it's gold really me 14
18 I mean okay amazing
18K that's what you need to wear is 18
if you had the if you had these
allergies you got to wear the 18 I got
the 18 it it makes it so you don't get
triggered even when you heal it and
everything you just want to be sure oh
good good advice for everyone too well
all this thing I healed is a lifelong
allergy I've had and it's gone so
without your help and your free
information so lot much gratitude to you
that's wonderful what a blessing well
thank you thank you blessings to you
Anthony thank you you want to get a
picture
yeah yay enjoy your evening thank you
you
too hey Michelle I actually had yes I
had a session with you many years ago
like I was 23 at the time oh my God how
long ago was that like 10 years I feel
like it was like 10 years ago or
something that's crazy um and I was at
the Culver City Event and the Calas and
yeah and I love the community so much I
wanted to tell you I'm I'm a painter and
I love painting and um I was curious if
there was any like subject matter that
you like or something cuz I'd love to
paint something for you and your family
I mean do you do nature painting do
nature florals um animals all sorts of
stuff different color palettes or if
even Spirit had something to say about
animals nature squirrels squirrels okay
cool that's just great and bunny rabbit
in nature those are amazing
that's oh thank you for coming I can't
believe that let's get a picture
great amazing thank you so much thank
you for coming I hope you like the food
tonight hey you got a book I got a book
you got a C let me just sign the book
Thank you
thank you I'm going to frame that l oh
my God I might have messed up your your
binder for a quick second there thank
you my uh kids Kate and Kota they're
watching from Toronto they made you guys
are watching right now they're 4 and
seven they made that for you four and
seven wao to Medical
medium
W amazing we pray to the the unknown
angels we do your meditations before
bed really yeah they are Med medical
medium kids oh my God look at this it's
four that is so awesome it's going to
mean a lot to
him oh thank you so much it's an
absolute honor and you guys are doing
the meditations the meditations which
one which one's the
favorite Moon meditation or the fruit
picking the picking one yeah or they
like the soul light
that's the light one wonderful choose we
I have them all saved and they just
which one today and they're like Moon
fruit yeah well that's the best thing
I've ever heard okay I love that this
means a lot means a lot to me to be here
so thank you so much thank you
seriously can I ask um one brain shot
you recommend for ttis been doing your
protocols for 6 years going through some
neurological and adrenal fatigue right
now tonight believe it or not try try
the parsley shot the par the flat leaf
yeah yeah try the parle shot always
coagulates yeah yeah I know I know but
but but give that a go okay more parsley
thank you thank you for coming amazing
[Music]
amazing what's Happ no way got you the
video no way come on
video no way how are you you like the
jacket I love it okay cool I like yours
too thank you okay I do have a question
good to see I know good to see too how
much how much of a role does numerology
play with the cleanses cuz 36 to always
focus on it that always focus on it
because um even with numerology because
of Free Will with human beings with
angels okay and and um and even with
animals numbers shift it's not always
this this absolute perfect number
situation in the universe and and you
know in the galaxies and solar systems
and and Off the Grid on the grid so what
I'm saying is that um but yes the
numbers have meaning in the cleanses and
they're very important and they do have
meanings because there's when you go
days on a cleanse yeah um your body is
clocking those days and that number does
land on a uh important factor okay when
when cleansing so the numbers were for
the cleanses were given from Spirit of
compassion for a reason so yeah they are
important but at the same time we can't
get lost in all numerology because it
can be a rabbit hole you know for a lot
of people when it's shifting anyway
right in many ways just because like I
was thinking like do we have to
visualize like with the 369 like is it I
was trying to figure out like listening
to your older podcast cuz you were
talking about how there's three
quadrants in the liver and there's
another three another three so I was
like is it called three that's always
absolute that's always solid because the
liver runs on what the liver runs on and
those numbers really do hold true okay
so all right you're so awesome what
you're awesome too is there anything
that Spirit wants to tell
me I mean you know you're just always so
positive and you need just just stay
like you always stay on that posit
positive note because honestly you have
a big bright light and people like
people get help from you yeah so just
keep that light going keep it shining
because it matters because you know
you're helping people and all of that
and if you feel down sometimes cuz
spirit says you do feel down down
sometimes okay you do get you know just
um just remember though that like how
you are affects others because you're
such a light okay you got to remember
that so so keep that light strong
wherever you can okay thank you
good to see you again okay you're the
best thank you for all the support it
means the world
okay those vanished and so a lot of
great benefits so far and uh you know
we're on month nine now and so I just uh
want to keep going yeah for sure what
benefits did you know not to be TMI but
I use the bathroom all the time like
clockwork and it's all day long and so
it just shows that I'm cleansing really
heavily yeah a lot of people talk about
they didn't realize gut health was bad
and then they went on this and they were
like oh that's amazing this just changed
for me you know for sure and I just have
like family members like mentioning that
I have a different like light in my eyes
and it is very spiritual too so I
noticed this like the spiritual benefits
of just like being more centered in my
body and just like calmer so there's a
lot of really cool things happening have
you experienced any spiritual lessons
from the medical medium information man
it's just a an unwavering trust in
something greater than yourself in order
to get you
through um feeling like I've felt the
last few years and so you know being
able to read information and listen to
his voice notes I follow him on the
telegram chat too and he can connect so
well with with someone like me that's
going through these types of feelings
and and so he is just someone that
really I can connect with and that when
I read his his his writing and and it
just gives me more trust and faith in
this whole process and spiritually I
just feel clear and like it's the right
thing for me yeah do you have a favorite
healing food you've learned the benefits
of from medical medium information we
love making our potatoes they're just
delicious yeah the liys scene the
antiviral you know we do the gold
potatoes yeah so those are probably our
favorite meal yes what favorite recipes
do you have oh you got to do the healing
broth right always a healing broth I
like while I'm doing morning routine I'm
like cutting up vegetables and just
getting another pot um but I have
question and it's like I want to know
from Spirit if there's something that
I'm missing like with my acne like a
supplement a protocol a brain chop I
know like I'll do I'll do something
about acne soon it's long overdue and
then just you know make sure you catch
it when you can yeah no I will do
something for sure and like really like
outline some things for you to to just
you know be like okay that might be
something I could bring in but I'll
outline things okay I'll do something I
have to do something for AC decent okay
thank you for
coming I needed something a little more
but it's okay I appreciate your
guidance I'm not trying to be like I'm
going to have you in mind that really
yes okay so when when it happens keep
that yep keep that in mind all right
hello hey is this really love the
glasses thank you so much so cool good
to see you it's is this for real you
have the pizza party together with all
it is for Real a pizza party I can't
even believe it it's incredible oh wow I
I I have just a question I got something
in my mind um about languages um did you
think it's it's a good thing um to have
so many languages I was thinking because
I want to tell you something Jes or
maybe SOC and I was thinking which
language it's it's the best language and
and also struggling sometimes with
English or something and I was thinking
is this a good thing so much languages
on the world there there is it's a good
thing okay but even though there's all
these languages it's heart and soul
still speaks the same you know that's
that's all that's all tuned in on the
human soul you know regardless and the
human soul speaks through the person and
so regardless of language so the
barriers are broken by that so you want
to get a picture yeah of course yes
thank you so much
yeah right enjoy tonight okay good to
see
youy I'm Tiffany nice nice to meet you
I'm from the long far place of Palm
Springs oh my god really I know I know
that's crazy so it's I get to eat at
Cafe Gratitude at Le twice a week on the
menu
incredible my God are you do are you
going to do the medical medium menu well
yeah of course that's what I do thank
God I mean Hello that's why I'm here and
I'm I'm starting my garden I'm eating
from the garden I'm I'm getting the
elevated biotics from the garden all
those little microorganisms on the
garden food but I feel guilty cuz
honestly I feel too happy okay you feel
too happy yeah no no no no you stay
happy come here let's get a picture you
stay happy okay thank you so much
okay good to see you tonight thank you
so much I'm praying for you thank one
more here one more oh just kidding sorry
one
more okay thank you for coming I love
the fact that you're happy okay perfect
hi nice to see you again nice to see you
saw you on Saturday thank you oh my God
yes yeah you were coming in yeah yeah I
was a surprise I was like wow I know but
now we get to eat pizza tonight so how
great is that looking
forward well thanks for coming how how
far did you travel um not far not far
you around the area yeah yeah that's
what I thought cuz that's why you were
here okay here all the time good
good yeah I met you like three
times thank you for coming and thank you
for for eating the medical medium food
food and
everything you are my man I saw you the
other day yeah Saturday good to see you
thanks for coming again yeah absolutely
same you look good you look good yeah
same I love your beard we're keeping it
kind of similar yeah like I know I know
yours is nicer I like yours more you Mo
skin around the cheeks no I like yours
I'm going to dial in I got to dial in my
routine I'm watching your beard you're
watching mine
yeah thing is you're trying to get yours
to look mine I'm trying to get mine to
look like yours and then we're going to
mess them up and cut them wrong right
we're going to trim them wrong yeah it
happens nice to see you thanks for
coming you helped me with my thyroid
issue I V thyroidism 20 years on
medication and now I'm almost off oh my
God you weaned off we I've been going to
Dr Sher green
no that's wonderful it's wonderful what
a great doctor oh she's amazing and she
got me off my hormone um you know
estrogen all the hormone replacement I
was doing as well well following all
your protocols and I just so she's a
great doctor I'm so happy I met her like
just from hearing about when I met well
up your Culver City uh location then
that's how I knew I had to contact her
because I couldn't do it like without a
doctor I was feeling
about it but I'm so glad CU it's wor
happy though I'm happy your thyroid it's
it's recovering and you're doing some up
you know how far did you travel uh
Manhattan Beach oh my
God awesome all right well glad you're
here I'm glad you're here I am so
thrilled to be
here thank you for coming tonight
good to see you nice to meet you I'm
Fitness and training big Fitness
influencer and I've just been on the
couch for the last n months but no no we
got to get you off the couch off the
couch you got to get back into it are
you kidding this information has been
life changing so so many have gone away
you're already knocking them out yeah
I'm knocking them out right away I noce
relief the neurological symptoms take a
little longer hang in there some of the
neurological ones you know they'll
they'll you'll get there you know you'll
get there and then you'll be cuz it's
the only thing that could really hold
you back from doing your work is the
neurological ones mostly with Fitness so
just keep it up keep it up all right
just get back cuz I need you back in
shape and and doing it all right all
right you want to get a picture come on
let's get a picture it'd be
amazing like this way this way you got
it where are we looking
okay amazing thank you for coming
tonight I'm honored
oh beautiful soul lovely to meet you
that was just my partner so I'm just I
ended up with that's your guy that's my
guy oh my God that would have been that
would have been great to have you both
here that would have been fun well okay
but this is good this works he likes to
do things on I love that guy I love that
guy okay I let him do his thing I let
him he's my kind of guy all
right anyway thanks for coming yeah this
is stunning thanks for everything you're
doing for everyone well let's get a
picture let's get a picture course yeah
cheers thanks for keeping them on track
too okay abely I'm there for
zoee anony I'm back good to see you good
to see you my God how are you good you
put the big book out I'm so looking
forward to that you know so many people
didn't believe me when I told them about
demons you put the book out well we'll
see we'll see what they think yeah yeah
it's going to change things it's a huge
thing you're doing you know yeah I've
really I've been on a huge Journey with
them it's an intense audio it's an it's
a lot of intense information and uh and
um I'm curious to see how you how you
think about it I will tell you in my
Instagram and I was also going to ask
you if you could talk about artificial
energies Technologies entities cuz
that's where I've been on a massive
Journey it's get super multi-dimensional
and I've had this one attachment trying
to clear for two years it's pretty
gnarly I think you're gonna I think
you're gonna like what you hear then
okay I really do want a picture I think
you're gonna like what you
[Music]
hear than tonight you're the best you're
the
best whoa I like those those are good I
tried to match you I like them I haven't
worn the pink ones in a while darn it
you should right I should anthy good to
see you I've been doing this for a long
time and I feel like I'm not getting
very far what do you what encouragement
or advice do you have you know everybody
has a different you know batch of things
in them all right and so sometimes it
takes longer to get it out right that's
all it is you know uh everybody's a
little different with that but that's
okay that doesn't matter you just you
just stay on track and then you bring in
a little bit more and you shift it and
bring in a little bit more and then all
of a sudden you're going to be like okay
okay uh I'm actually getting there now
and the thing is you're already there in
a lot of ways it's just the nervous
system always kind of like lags while
you're trying to heal so you just got to
hang in there you just got to hang in
there okay all right I love your hat
thank you
I'm proud of you all right thank you for
coming thank
you hi oh my God how are you I love that
s what's going on how are you good to
see you too thank you for
coming uh thank you for writing the book
yeah we're so excited for the spirit
book we've been wanting that forever for
like our whole lives yeah yeah well well
we'll we'll see we'll see how you guys
feel when you hear it
okay you guys are come on you can you
can you're like he's just he's being
silly you know saying like Oh no just
got to look out here it's like you guys
are like don't worry it's going to be
all right yeah you want to get a picture
yes all right all right come on guys you
want to get on this side how are you
doing by the way I'm I'm hanging in
there I am I am it's good
oh amazing you guys going to enjoy the
pizzas tonight are you going to enjoy
the food good to see you okay
he hey look at that good to see you so
I'm looking forward to the book this
really good book and it's little bit
scary I'm working on all kinds of good
things I'm working hard I really am I am
can you tell him a little bit about my
traffic accident when I hit my head my
my head trauma and the Brain Hemes and
there was a man that looked with brown
hair brown eyes and brown beard and he
he looked into my eyes and then I woke
up and I saw the ambulance crew and
there was
a just a doctor that found me and I mean
I can tell you this you have you have a
lot of healing has happened you have a
miraculous ability to heal I can tell
you that okay because somebody else who
went through that did not have that
where you where they were they recovered
okay easy or over time all right so you
have a miraculous ability to heal that's
important to know so then the spiritual
aspects obviously they're going to be
there okay they're going to have
messages and you should write them down
all the time like you see this you saw
that you remember this write them down
take a sheet of paper put it under your
pillow sleep at night and see what
dreams happen Okay let's get let's get a
picture together a white cloud and in
the heart and
it's thank you for coming
good to see you carine nice to meet you
hi nice to meet you thanks for coming
thank you thank you for all you do um
I've been uh following uh your
information for 4 years now and four
years that's a long time yeah it is a
long time yeah I I had TMJ during the
pandemic EA all the no Foods floating
and um your information just really
helped me heal it after 6 months of
being on the supplements following your
protocols my TMJ just stopped all of a
sudden that is amazing that means
everything I mean people don't know
who's who have never had TMJ or any kind
of trigeminal issue so that I I love
hearing that yes thank you know you work
so hard and thank you for all your
sacrifice and um I used to not believe
in angels I was skeptical about God and
Jesus but after reading your books I
have I'm a firm believer I I call on the
Angels every single day thank you so
much for all the information that's
amazing not a lot of people ask angels
for help so that's important that you do
want to get a picture you
guys thank you for
coming yes of course of
course thank you for coming I hope you
have some fun
hey hi how you doing I'm nice to see you
excited to to meet you I'm excited to
meet you yeah I just have a question
about the
personalization um if people cannot
experience
emotions of Joy they're numb they numb
but how come they can experience the
fear and
anxiety how come they can experience the
because being numb can also be you can
be numb and have fear and anxiety we can
have all
three yeah and it's hard to get out of
that and takes time you know it takes
time it you are you you're going in the
books you're getting the information you
just keep on forging ahead okay and it
happen yes you healing the body wants to
heal do not forget that my body wants to
heal it does it wants to heal can I give
you a hug that's up oh my God thank you
let's get a picture yes
right
here thank you for coming okay thank you
so
much hey hi hi can I get a hug sure
sure thank you so much Anthony glad here
so so happy you've been so brave to help
us all of us well I and you are too
spirit says you're brave too okay okay
ask you could even be bra than me okay
oh I don't think so I think it's
possible can I ask about my eyes uh what
else I can do to help the cataracts the
glaucoma the vision issues F say there's
more you can do there's more you can do
and when you look at the information so
after tonight something might come as
you look okay and cuz things happen just
being here all right let's get a picture
thank you thank you let's get a picture
okay
thank you for coming thank you it's an
honor too for me for
me hi good to see you look at you if
your bik what did the cat drag in
here Anthony thank you very much for all
you're doing and would like to invite
you because I'm a beekeeper I I just
look after some bees come to England and
have some honey with that I when I get
out to England I'll look you guys up I I
would love to get out there I would it's
long overdue I have to get out there
someday so yeah please do come okay okay
I I is tea time still 3:00 or no is that
over that does really matter is that
done in England that's not that doesn't
happen new rollers new rollers no we we
are actually polished so we don't stick
to the okay I got you you don't stick to
all the rules no okay we break anywhere
any
let's get a picture let's get a picture
you
guys fantastic thank you thank
you hey how are you I get really nervous
every time I meet you but it's an honor
and a privilege to meet you you've
healed me a I feel the same way you
healed me of long and you're healing me
of 20 years of anorexia believe so oh my
God you're a fighter thank you for
everything I you have something inside
of you that wants to heal that's it you
want to move past that you want to heal
and I'm proud of you it's not easy so
thank you can I give you a hug yes of
course of course come over I don't want
to take too much oh of course my God
this is amazing that you're
[Music]
here and I'm so proud of you okay thank
you for
coming hey what's going on you got a
book I got a book do you want me to sign
it yes please let me see if I have a pen
here you got a a a a pen I will that's
yours right
there thank you and um I've been
following you since 2020
2020 yes when Co hit somewhere around oh
my God April when you got plans to heal
book but I bought your first book 2015
the first book the cleanse the heal book
but I was not convinced yet because I
had so many questions I had so many
questions and um but uh the Clans the
hill I was sold and I bought the liver
book nice yes that's wonderful yes and
uh done yeah it helped my family my son
gained two Ines from the really he grew
two Ines from doing everything yes he's
like my my husband is 6 foot my my son
is 6 fo taller than me 6'4 6' 6'4 oh my
God and he's a basketball player and is
a point guard and it help it helps him I
the smoothie two years he's been growing
like this oh my God yes okay music to my
ears music to my ears I want to ask you
something let's get a picture can I can
I
do I
we're miked up we're we're you're you're
you're going to be heard even when you
whisper yeah really yeah yes yes even if
you whisper to me everybody's going to
hear it problem you know I problem I
wonder how I get rid
of you know the answers are in the book
for that you can you can find something
it's not you have to look for something
different that may not be exactly what
that says but it's there just take your
time go through and something's going to
hit okay okay
[Music]
something's amazing thank you for coming
okay thank you okay
okay hey how are you good so nice to
meet you nice to meet you too 9 years
almost 9 years following you [__] doing
medical medium first book I cried
through the whole thing oh my God
knowing it was going to I just knew it
was going to heal me that I found my
answer and I'm still going strong oh I'm
proud of you okay I'm proud of you do
you want to get a picture together yes I
do come to San Diego that's where I'm
San
Diego I love San Diego thank you for
coming 9 years s know I'm proud of you
okay
that that Dem means everything
okay I try my best under all the
stress you're going to get a picture
together together yes they're together
all I try I
try hey how are you good to see you
thank you for coming oh my pleasure how
did you end up here huh you know what I
drove Tracy yep who has been one of your
people for a long time she just told me
9 years and I saw you on social media
about months ago and I thought this guy
is a
genius wow thank
you and it was a manifestation I drove
her up tonight has her driver she says
my daughter did you go you want to go in
and I said where are you going to oh I'm
Glad You Came I'm Glad You Came let's
get a picture let's get a quick picture
here it's
[Music]
amazing well enjoy your night enjoy your
night thank you so much I'm
sorry hey met your friend that's your
child friend you're just yes exactly I
love that exactly I said did he try to
give you advice and you didn't want to
hear it he like yeah all the time he
said would he say yes all the
time I'm so happy to be here with you
good to see you it's really good to see
thanks for coming you want to get a
picture I'm so grateful to you I'm
grateful that you're here okay I'm
grateful to be here I did uh 7 months of
potato mono last year
here we
go what happened last week I did seven
months of potato mono last year no way
and I've been doing a bunch of Advan 3
which one which one out of the mono
potatoes the potato one amazing and it
was really hard until I broke through
one day after like six or seven weeks
and then I started to enjoy them it
can't be hard just to eat potatoes come
on you know I'm kidding you know I'm
kiding I ask you just about injury can
nerves heal from injury cuz I had a very
bad head injury it's about it's about
healing them depend if they're severely
injured it all depends but you but but
they always heal to a degree so keep on
pushing forward okay they they always do
healing and then you get a little more
out of them over time okay okay thank
you
thanks hey look at how are you nice
necklace thank you nice to meet you nice
to meet you too how are you doing thank
you for coming I'm doing okay are you
are you doing okay some days some days
some days I'm better than I was 12 years
ago 12 years ago what happened I'm
better than I was 12 years ago okay that
matters yes that matters I'm here okay
you're not on mattress Island not
anymore you're here you know you already
know proba that's my husband's like what
are you going to say you your NOS
everything it's good to hear it though
it's good to hear it from you okay do
you want to get a picture yes okay thank
you thank thank you for coming thank you
thank is this the guy right here what
are you doing waiting over there come on
what's going on nice to meet you are
these the kids two of them no way look
at you already 6'2
easy 6' three hey look at you a strong
guy right there strong handshake yeah
how you guys doing good want to get a
picture all together yeah that'd be
great let's do it that would be amazing
how do you want to do this which way you
want to want me in the middle here come
over here you guys want to come forward
a little bit
yeah we just all got to move
forward the camera guy wants us forward
there okay in a little bit here okay
[Music]
amazing incredible thanks for coming you
guys thank you I'll see you
okay hey good to see you you I'm so
grateful to be here so today I have a
question about my walk so kind of
stressed out during the walk but I have
lack off the to make a because the
current uh marketing is not good so it
affect my wellbeing so I want to get
some suggestion from so or from you
would be really
appreciate um yeah you're staying
hydrated right yeah the spirit says you
do you do this the good stuff yeah
you're not
drinking I know that Dr Nesbit drinks
but that's another story we won't go
into that but um but no that's good okay
but um spirit says electrolytes are
critical
so when you are drinking things just
remember that okay just remember that
and and look through the books and look
through everything and think
electrolytes okay okay okay let get
a thank you for coming this is that's
from me yeah from China my God that's
the greatest St right there um Chinese
people doing the M medium protocol which
blows my mind which blows my mind this
is full of their uh love and gratitude
yeah thank you be really appreci you can
send them some information this is
special to me very special very
special hi hey good to see you nice to
meet you nice to meet you too yeah I'm
so happy to meet you yeah to drink
celery juice already for 2 and a half
years two and a half years of it is it
every day yes every day yeah I got a lot
of benefit from that yeah okay I'm proud
of you okay because I miss it some days
some days I don't even get it in you
know I'm doing this or I'm going here
doing this but when I'm out here I can
get it easy here but but that's amazing
2 and 1/2 years yeah it's really nice
and it's meaningful to me that my family
began to accept it that uh which made me
very very happy you know yeah being here
today I feel very beautiful now yeah
thank you thank you I'm proud of you
okay thank you for doing all you're
doing for yourself your healing okay
also have let's get a picture yeah get a
let's get a
photo I hope you enjoy the food today
thank you wish you all the best bye
thank you for
coming hey what's going on who's this
guy hi Anthony hi pleasure to meet you
pleasure to meet you you guys want we
felt like we'd speed it up for Star p
[Music]
don't worry you just got to keep on him
okay keep on him be like honey you got
to make sure you do this okay every day
oh I'm doing fine I don't I'm doing all
right I don't need to do that right now
I got my own thing going you know him
very yeah I do believe me I know him
more than you
think good to see you thank you for
seeing me and I'm so so glad that I find
that I could see you um I wanted to
really see you for one year I started
for one year yeah I
start like one year ago almost and I
started having like a third
time you went you went you know you went
around the Sun once with it all that's
that's powerful you know because 6
months is great and 3 months is great
but you went a full year it's like full
circle that's a beautiful thing to do
cuz then you can kind of see things
differently when you're doing your
healing that's
amazing I do you think I can get rid of
this Dan cancer
forever well look you're working with
your doctors right you're working with
your doctors you keep on bringing all
the good stuff in ask your doctor like
can I do this can I do this in the
medical medium and you show them all the
things you could do but customize it
okay look into it and really look cuz
those answers are there so keep on
looking okay and then you know and bring
that to them thank you for coming let's
get a picture than you so much take
picture oh my god oh that's that's
really
cool you got a pen you got a pen I do
well I got one right here thank you so
much enjoy the night thank you so
much hey
good to see you you too thank you for
coming yeah thanks for having me how are
you doing today I'm good I like that I
like hearing that you know I'm proud of
you yeah and spirit's proud of you oh
thank
you I appreciate that no that's good
that's good how far did you come from to
get here in the area yeah about an hour
yeah that's that that's remember yeah
well goodness see you yeah yeah I really
appreciate your INSP Spirits info um are
you doing the stuff in the books are you
looking through uh I I've just been
doing 369 oh just
only only just doing the 369 that's
that's a lot yeah yeah that's a
lot that's amazing yeah which 369 is
your
favorite none of them because it's it's
hard work yeah no no which one do the
advance
yeah you're doing the advance for how
long uh it's been about 3 months I'm
blown away I'm blown away let's get a
picture of her I'm actually blown
away and I'm proud of you thank you I
really try to enjoy your night I
will hey my friend l wants to say hello
to you she's on speaker pH right now L
just s I'm proud of you okay L you're
with Anthony s s I'm proud of
you thank you and thank you for
everything that you and SOC are doing
for all of us I'm honored it's great to
hear your voice just keep keep on keep
on keep on doing all the good stuff
okay okay all right bless your heart
let's get a picture
thank
you thank you so
much hey what's going on you guys nice
to meet you nice to meet you thank you
for coming I just want to say thank you
so much for everything that you've done
and I love all your content and I'm
obsessed with it and I love so's poems
at the end of your podcast they I'm glad
somebody likes those I love I God okay
now for him to drop more bombs about
everything thank you I know it's all
so's words you know it's crazy and him
or whatever the poems are are written in
just under I don't know 2 minutes 2 and
a half minutes oh wow yeah because
because I just have to listen so I just
have to listen so and I do them and and
I'm so I'm happy you like that no
they're
amazing thank you thank you guys thank
you for coming
okay nice to see you I'm Anastasia
Anastasia first spoke to you in March of
2015 exactly 10 years ago almost to the
day and my life let's go into the time
machine right now okay
2015 that's crazy that's 10 years ago I
have something important to share with
you but for privacy reasons I wrote it
down but if you're too snow blind maybe
you can I am pretty pretty snow blind SN
blind do I take this though or you take
it you can take it yes if you can't read
it please read it okay okay okay is that
all right okay if the words were this
big right now and right I might be able
to see uh behind the snow blind take it
and read
ity I wrote the poem for you okay and
it'll be a big honor for me to read it
it's very brief it started coming to me
when I was watching this event in
October okay can you read it quick yes
okay okay I don't want to keep everybody
with yes understand and now we rise
Straight From the Ashes a spirit is
strong we fight with light the darkness
shrieks and then it crashes as our souls
take sacred flight and I'll skip off all
the is in the world none will compare to
Soul's gold the healing path Now lies un
curled will let new story to unfold and
you can read the rest I just read you're
gifted okay um that had me already drawn
into it this line started coming to me
as I was watching your event okay that's
very special that's very special keep
this
one that's very that's very special and
you're very gifted so much bless your
heart
hi thank you so good to see you you to
you're such a blessing thank you so much
and um you also shared information about
that's helpful for people in the
entertainment industry about like
fillers veneers and things like that
like how do you feel about
veneers I mean look uh I I think
influencers get them every day right now
out there it's just everybody's
everybody's doing it it's just it all
depends if you're dentist and you feel
like it's right for you know you you
know and or it's the only thing you can
do because there's people that are in a
situation where that's that's what they
need to do because they're in a
situation so it it it all depends it
really does you know you want to get a
picture
together but a lot of people get them
and I mean you know I don't know how
many people are are upset or complaining
about it or anything but I hear people
are happy but it's all up to you in your
PST thank you so bless your
heart hey good to see you thank you
Frank Anthony I just want to know if I'm
an old soul I got 100 questions but am I
an old
soul you're an old soul yeah why you
don't think you are no not even with a
gray
hair not even with a gray hair but I'm
good thank you you're not a New Soul I
can tell you that okay let's get a let's
get a picture
I mean you got a thousand years on you
okay thank you I mean you got a thousand
on okay that came from above okay thank
you Anthony good to see you good to see
you too thanks for coming you're welcome
I'm really happy to be here I don't
usually goed this a big deal this is a
big deal then if you don't usually go
out this is a big deal and I want to
tell you I had some Communication email
with you about 3 years ago or maybe I
wasn't quite ready to make the
commitment and I committed it was an
email yeah we had some email
communication you told me about NX it
that 3 years ago yeah that's an
impostor that might have been an
impostor no no it was you did you pay
yeah it wasn't me that was an
impostor we didn't have contact 3 years
ago yeah there's there's a bunch of them
out there but but but I'm not an
impostor and I'm in person right now
with you okay let step forward a little
bit
up I'm so glad you're here okay for
bless your
heart hi hi good to see you to see you
thank you for coming I'm so happy to be
here thank you for
saying a of course I mean anything I can
do you know the information comes from
above and it it it's why I'm here I just
want to make sure that you get that
information and if it saved your life
then that is that's everything that's
what it's about okay but you worked hard
you worked hard okay and I know
that it wasn't just magically occurred
in a second you put work into it okay
and I'm proud of you let's see the
picture
[Music]
thank you for coming can I ask a
question I'm struggling with my
relationship with my longtime
significant others and I've done a lot
of healing and I was just wondering if
you have any input about if what I
should do with that
relationship I have some I have some
information coming out pretty soon and
it and just keep on listening out to
things that are coming okay I I think
it's going to be helpful thank you
see if you can sign
this that one didn't thank you you mean
so much to me thank you for me want to
get a picture Yes except
[Music]
for amazing thank you for coming to
thank
you hey how are you thank you so much
for another amazing event good to see
you good to see you um I had a little
question um about uh birth marks in
Mongolian spot my daughter has a pretty
large birth mark and I was wondering if
has any meaning or if it's due to toxic
heavy model solo Le birth marks can be
spiritual too okay spiritual meanings
behind them and for centuries people
have gotten them and you know and yes
I've talked about Metals right like in
the information but sometimes it could
be both so we're keep that in mind it
could be both I was wondering sorry if
Spirits has a message for me I just quit
my job and I'm kind of like U if Spirits
has a little message or a little
something well I mean you're very
creative you're also you're also very
smart Okay meaning like you can do a lot
of different things it's not just one
thing or something you do a lot of
different things so just know that you
have like all kinds of purposes and that
you may be able to go in a different
direction okay okay okay thank you so
much
proud of
you hi seeing you again nice to see you
happy to be here happy you're here um I
just had a question for you I will be
moving to Japan for a year um coming
soon and I will have access to my usual
kitchen appliances and my my tools to
heal um I just wanted to know if you
would have an advice for me on what I
can Implement when over there there
there you can still get a lot of things
depending where you are in Japan but
there's still there's still a lot of
things you can get okay to and and piece
it together okay it's going to be good
it's going to be okay if you go to Japan
okay here step forward a little
bit thank you for
coming uh we have a book here
yeah cleanse the heel
appreciate everything you done Anthony
I'm honored seriously we we just started
3 months ago um on so we're early on our
healing Journey so there's some
questions like know so you guys are
together yeah yeah where did you find
them we used to work together that's
where we used to work together you used
to work together uhhuh yeah he annoyed
you at first that's what happened he
annoyed you at first and then you were
like possibly maybe yeah yeah you're
like no he'll do it'll work I got her on
this it's the other way around I got her
no no it's the other way around you just
don't know it all right all right all
[Laughter]
right all right
let's want to step forward you
guys I love you guys thank you for
coming seriously enjoy the night for
real for real thank
you hiy good to see you good to see you
again thank you um last time I saw you
and you encouraged me to do the Advan
369 did did you do it I'm doing it
you're brave it's uh lifting the veil
and I don't even have words for the
Gratitude I have towards
you thank you for coming it's amazing I
am a filmmaker from Canada and I'm
working on a film that I think will help
a lot people and I just wanted to tell
you about it if you're interested okay
thank you this is super okay also the
community in Vancouver I love Canada
that's amazing we love you it's a
beautiful community that follows medical
medium and I promise them that I would
get a hug of course can you tell them
that I I appreciate all that they do
okay and all the support I it it matters
to me okay it really does thank you
thanks for coming thank
you hey what's going on my goodness so
we got the June uh was it last June June
and then September and next year I am
thank you for coming thank you for
everything you did I love you so much
well I appreciate you changed my life my
friends's life my family's life I'm
honored do you want to get a picture an
I have a question okay little quick I'm
going to have a to me in 10 days is
there anything I can do to help myself
what I would do is get all the books out
and then open them up okay close your
eyes just open them up and just read
okay okay and because you're very
connected so okay do that thank
you this way all right this way
okay all right
thank you for
coming hey good good to see you yes good
to see you thanks for coming yes I'm so
happy to be here and um I've had trouble
with my
eyes Okay my eyes are and I've been
seeing shadows from it and I didn't know
I'm and that help some I didn't know if
there was anything more are you bring
are you going into the protocols a
little bit Yeah and then bring bring
those protocols to your eye doctor but
go go into the protocols yeah there's
there's there's stuff in there okay
there is okay for that okay and then you
look at the cause of it right you know
in that one book yeah I know you go in
there and it says it was in cleansing H
I think and it said right yeah I know
the the TV confirmation yep it was there
and you see glaucoma yeah yes
yes where do you want me forward okay
thank you for coming
tonight good to see you good to see you
again is this your guy yes hi good to
see you I love the hat thank you all
right I'm glad you guys are here yeah I
was here last uh October and I was like
overwhelmed but I wasn't able to do um
say what I came here to tell you okay
yeah I just wanted to tell you how
grateful I am and thank you for
everything that you did and um I
appreciate it I'm honored I'm honored
I'm honored I see you got a nice good
smile yeah are you having fun tonight
already oh yeah just happy she to
express time that's amazing it's amazing
thank you let's get a
picture that is wonderful by the way
[Music]
thank you guys I'm honored okay I'm
honored have have a good time
tonight hey good to see you good to see
you too I'm from South Africa really and
you made the trip from South Africa yeah
okay that's that's amazing almost 3
hours how many hours it's about 28 hours
oh my God I couldn't do that I couldn't
I couldn't fly 28 hours yeah no it
wasn't easy no no but was worth it I'm
so glad to meet you thank you for coming
thanks so much that is amazing I hope
you enjoy the food and everything and
it's an honor how long have you been
doing medical medium 6 years 6 years yes
uh that's a long time yes I'm proud of
you do you have any messages for me do
you have any messages for me spirit says
you know what you're doing really how
come how come spirit says that that you
know what you're doing you know with
your health and stuff that you're
working on it like you always do some
times it goes so you you go like little
bit yep yep yep but then you go back to
it I'm proud of you okay let's get a
picture thank you so
much hey how are you look at you nice to
see you to see you thanks for everything
that you do thank you so much so okay I
prepared a little Spiel okay
I've healed myself and I'm so grateful I
want to help other people so I have some
ideas what do you think about it like a
Haven for autistic kids um a healing
place for them do you think it's the
time to try we try and start that I mean
if there's ever a good time it's it's
these you know these years we're in now
it's a good time for that I mean
definitely better
than always obstacles but probably less
obstacles as years ago okay okay let's
get a phot thank
you thank you so much bless you
too what is that there I want to bring
you that oh my God where did you find
this I painted that really she painted
this when but when I was in college I
was just there and I painted it and his
mom had it on her wall until she died
and then I got it back this is heirloom
it's old that's what this is this is
heirloom so okay it's for you and I put
it a a a note on the back okay I taped
it okay okay I'll watch that and make
sure it doesn't pop off or something
that's good to know okay I did so I
taped it with packing tape and your
friend has a box and and good to see you
you too it's an honor thank you you H
ours our honor what what what do I need
to work on you
she
knows she knows worry worry yeah yeah
you got to listen to her okay that's
tough that's your message that's your
message all right all right sip up for
here a little
bit I would love you oh I I'll do it
this
way amazing you guys enjoy the food
tonight good to see you than you good to
see hey you got a
book oh you got something in there no no
I just you got you got a
pen thank you so much Anthony thank
you you're welcome thank you for coming
you guys 5 years now and I have here my
TMJ uh vertigo o and also and vertigo oh
vertigo that's awful when people suffer
with that who's this guy my husband the
husband really amazing I got a question
for you as well but okay okay you got a
question if the husband has a
question yes well see I'm not 56 right
really you're not 36 I'm not 36 I wish I
was here's the here's the problem you
look 36 well thank
you uh I I'm now starting to get blood
pressure and his blood pressure pretty
high like6 you got to get his liver in
shape okay you going to work on it all
right let's get a picture okay here move
forward a little
[Music]
bit
sorry thank you guys thank you enjoy
tonight okay I I I'm doing my birthday
cleansing uh 9e uh uh cycle and I have
done five so far it's uh uh Advanced and
one more to go when I see the results
I'm getting lot of symptoms
uh like I want to see the results and
Improvement and healing right now all
the symptoms I'm getting well you got
make sure you always keep track of those
symptoms look in the books and try to
match them okay very important very
important hey yes of course of course I
love you oh bless your heart I wanted to
ask you a quick question about Erp shots
cuz I know you've said about in the past
if you inject something in the body that
it sees it as foreign so if you're
injecting your own blood in is your body
going to recognize blood is forign is it
safe to do is there something more
effective for Osteo thritis in
KN well you know it it it all depends
like how like how long have you been
doing it um I didn't do it I wanted to
see what you said about it I'm just
investigating PP
shots I think look I mean you got to
find a good doctor first of all for one
and then you need to tell that doctor
those those things and see what your
doctor says like tell them well I heard
this and this and this what do you think
you know challenge challenge your doctor
to get your doctor to think okay okay
they had said no it's safe it's no I
know I know but say those things though
and see and then go to another one and
then ask the same thing and you it's
always good to have a couple of doctors
is there anything else you recommend
better for osteoarthritis let's get
a thank you well keep keep up all the
good stuff get the assets out you know
look look at the books okay
hey how you doing how are you good to
see you long night huh how you real me
oh it's it's a breeze it's a breeze I'm
just going to throw this over
you thank you thanks for coming yes um
so I I've been uh I'm trying to get off
ssris for 12 months I tried I I weaned
myself off successfully but crashed with
panic attacks depression crying anger
and I just 12 months later I I went back
on and I'm trying to get off uh what do
I do well I axle specific are you doing
all these other things to counter it I I
was seeing uh a nutritionist I was
trying supplements and it wasn't working
you're looking at the medical meeting
books and dig in there and and look at
things to counter okay you like things
that you wouldn't expect uh but but but
that's what you have to do you have to
counter it so when you come off you're
in a better place right okay there
there's information in there okay okay
all right let's get a picture all right
yeah and it doesn't mean it's in the SSR
I think you just just other brain brain
there's so much brain information so
many brain protocols just look at what
you want to do in there see what comes
natural but counter okay that's how you
have to do you can't just go off that
and then you're not countering it yeah
yeah get some good Fe thank you thank
you
hi thank you so much for everything see
oh thank you and um just really quickly
I have tomias and I didn't know if
garlic Mullen oil I've been doing the
protocol for8 years but would Mullen oil
also help the drops or do you stay away
from drops for tontis I mean I look ask
your doctor but I like Mullen gar garlic
oil sure I like it for a lot of things
um you know get a good one um you know
if you do something like that the one on
your site I have but I didn't know for
tonight a specific well well you you
might have been doing things all these
years but but there might be something
you're missing that you're not that
you're not doing it
there okay all right I'm I'm giving you
a hint cuz there's more you can do to
actually improve that
369 there it's in there so here's what I
would do remember the viral thing so you
go in there and take a look okay okay
we'll do
thank you thank
you hey nice to see you are good to see
you good good I'm good too thank you so
much for everything you do for us you're
welcome where are you from I'm from
Chicago really amazing you made it here
from Chicago that that's that's a big
deal it's it's warmer here even though
it's cold sorry it's so cold here when
you just came from cold weather pretty
much the same it's very much of course
thank you we appreciate it more than you
know I'm honored I'm honored thank you
so much want to get a picture sure
amazing thank you for coming enjoy the
food hi good to see you good to see you
yes oh I'm so excited to meet you
Anthony um I just want to say thank you
so much for all that you're doing for
all that you do for us for the work you
do the time you put in I'm just I'm
floored and inspired by your
perseverance the spirit that you have
and the love you have for all of us it's
just it's overwhelming honestly I don't
want to
cry but thank you well I'm honored
seriously okay it means the world to me
okay so yeah and I do care I do care I
know you do I do I do I do here let's
take a picture take pict I really do you
know and I'm proud of you
more I hope I didn't
BL no way we probably got a good picture
I hope
so thanks so much thanks so
much hey what are you doing how are you
good to see you good to see
you thanks for
coming answers are coming I can't wait
can't wait for the book can't wait yeah
that's yep the new the new stuff is
coming new audio and and everything and
I hope you enjoy it I do I do do you
like the spiritual part of of of
everything I feel like it's going to be
the missing piece I feel like it's going
to be the missing piece for
me well
um you work on a lot of good things so
you're working on all kinds of stuff
you're very spiritual person so thank
you for coming where did you come from
uh San Diego nice you didn't have that
far to go do you ever come here ever if
I'm here I'm always I always stop by oh
that's amazing that's amazing well
thanks for coming today here
on okay amaz you want to get a picture
yes please thank
you you're looking Gangsta
today oh you're the best thank you for
coming thank
[Laughter]
you hi how's it going good
Jason nice to see you nice to see you
can I sign your book yeah it's for my
wife it's her favorite book it is she
couldn't make it this time so yeah I
don't know if you remember we were the
guys who came here in December yes and
me and my wife stayed until January
until the crap happened you know yes no
I know I
know thank you thank you for coming
though yeah can I ask you one thing for
my wife is if she has a a message from s
so for her
she gets she gets
sadness and when when it hits okay she
think about she has to think about
how um how she's a very really good
person cuz she doesn't think that when
the sadness comes she thinks she was
supposed to do something no she's a good
person she has to remember that okay
okay let's get a picture yeah
sure yeah of course
[Music]
thank you for coming yeah of course of
course see you tomorrow I'll see you
yeah it's good to finally meet you wait
for this moment for so long I can't
believe it yeah um so how long you been
doing medical medium stuff I've been
doing it for 6 years almost 6 years 6
years yeah 6 years and I'm so grateful
for your information but I'm still
severely depressed and have a lot of
brain fog so is there anything Spirit of
compassion can tell me what I can focus
on are you doing are you doing um have
you been customizing it for yourself
I've been doing everything everything
there something specific I can focus on
just a hint that's all I need no you're
you're you're still missing some things
okay
um you focus on
exposure cuz you're getting continual
exposure okay focus focus on exposure is
this environmental home yes just focus
on exposure something is is there so
you're not only cleaning things up from
the past but you're cleaning things up
in the moment too so take a look in the
books and focus on exposure is from the
get a from the home or is it from from
the
environment this
same here step forward thank you
environment environment environment home
environment hell Anthony such an honor
to meet you I can't believe I'm
here wow good to see I've been doing
I've been doing your protocols for seven
years seven years yes amazing yeah is it
keeping you going yeah it is but it's
still hard but I'm
trying can I a your question
yes still
pain very severe abdominal pain
sometimes what causes this what can I do
about it and you been to all the doctors
no not to
all but you've been to doctors and they
they've looked and everything and they
can't find
nothing uh no no but I I had
appointments but they were
canc are you doing are you have you um
have you looked and cleanse to heal okay
cleanse to heal that book look into that
book okay okay and and read that book
okay okay let's get a
picture
okay good to see you hi nice to see
you thank you for coming
I can honor to be well I'm honored I am
I am do you want to get a picture
together want to get a
picture did I want to do what do you
want to get a picture together yeah okay
why
not want to step forward a little bit
all
right I'm excited about the food did you
try it
yet thank you good to see you
hey everybody what are you doing all
right so we talked in
2015 on the phone I I haven't
forgotten can't forget yeah yeah you you
you remember everything so well um so
I've come a long way I've basically
healed my colitis
toally I mean I think so and then but my
nervous system is still healing my my
central nervous system is still healing
when it's been injured it can take some
time yeah it just does it does but
you're a young guy but it can take some
time yeah 43 aot no you just keep on
keep on working on it okay okay okay
very proud of you I'm taking more
vitamin C a lot
more that's actually
[Music]
good now for the acid when you when you
heal there's a lot of nerves on the
intestinal tract a lot of nerves and
when they get injured in the past they
still they take time to heal but they're
a lot fir along than you know a lot
further along than you know Hi how are
you good to see
you good to see you too how are you
doing you hanging in there yes okay
that's good that's good you're not being
hard on yourself are
you maybe maybe
maybe can can you read the
Press you trying to keep a light heart
mhm try keep a light heart yeah I
do
remember can you read the
question can I read a question question
I won't be able to read
it can I say a
question can Spirit help me to decide
whether I keep my wisdom teas or not and
if my body would hand a root canal in
one of
them um did you ever hear all the
different oral shows that I've done and
all that did you listen to those I think
there's a few of them I think I think
many times okay okay there's information
about the r canals on those and the
other thing is about
V do you have a dentist you like what do
you have a dentist you like or you
yeah that's important half of them done
they saying it has to come
out they're saying it has to come out
the dentist
yes different dentists say different
things yeah it's very
difficult let's get a picture let's get
a
picture listen this is your body and you
know how you feel about it okay and how
you felt with power past dental
things right with past dental things you
know how you felt
so you know always use that as as a
benchmark you know like a
benchmark what you went through in your
past dental things that's a spirit says
use that as a benchmark when you're
talking to your dentist about that okay
you had very bad
experiences you you got to use that to
to weigh that out okay
hey how are you how are you good I am so
grateful that you keep doing all these
events because it's like getting
together with all the old as long as I'm
not annoying everybody you annoy anybody
no okay thank you for coming yeah thanks
so it's it's like a big family reunion
and it just it feels that way and it's a
wonderful thing it truly is I I love I
love being here I love being here and
helping in any way and it's also the
fact that you made it possible to have
like a global community and have to be
able to meet all these friends from all
around the world fre Global Community
yeah so just a quick question does
Spirit have a personal message for me
does Spirit of compassion have a message
for me you know you you're you're a half
glass you know you're you're not the
half glass empty kind of person okay and
you already know that though I mean
that's one thing but
um but you have to always remember okay
spirit's
saying that every time you get stopped
from doing something cuz that's your
greatest Nemesis spirit says like when
you get stopped from doing something
realize you can alter and go another
direction to go around it okay okay
let's get a
picture thank you so much for coming
thank hey good to see you good to see
you again thanks for coming yeah thank
you so much for doing this adone no of
course it's it's an honor to be here and
do this you kidding I love being here
you're amazing um I have a really s
question for you okay silly is
fine why do the angels have
gender why don't they or why do they
yeah cuz you said there's like female
and male yes yes they don't really it's
it's um
I should say this when you're going to
find a lot of answers coming up in the
audio you're going to find a lot of
answers you're they're going to be there
for you
excit because they do but they kind of
don't as well so it's it's got thank
you what's going on you guys together
my daughter Tori nice to meet you Tori
I'm a big fan well thank you for coming
L people my God cool tattoo oh thank you
they're probably
toxic oh all you got to do with tattoos
is you got to do the hmd you know you
got to do the heavy metal detox here and
there and you can have you know tattoos
you know so yeah so lie heart I mean I
talk about tattoos and stuff and I'm
always like oh Metals Metals you know
the tattoo ink the T but but I also say
you getting you just got to make sure
you're being a little proactive so you
clean anything out that's fair that's
all so what a well thank you thank you
for your time but don't get don't get
into the addiction of it where you get
so many of them yeah no I did that in
high school so good
now you get too many you guys want a
picture amazing
amazing well let's go forward camera guy
is saying go forward
first CA this one
[Music]
here thank you for coming you guys it's
an honor seriously I'm proud of both of
you can I give you yeah sure
sure and who's this guy right here this
is my husband we decided to come
together this really really yeah we saw
you one really how'd she convince you
well we I here last time oh okay but how
did she convince you to get here again
well I've been doing it for you know I
fig okay good good I figur he'd be like
I'm going to pass with this one no get
him here we've both been 100% for six
years the whole whole way I know I know
I know you guys are you guys are Die
Hard you guys are in it you know and and
and I know I could feel it I know I know
I just like razing I like razing the
guys I can't help it I can't help it
well I'm glad you guys are here do you
want to get a picture can I ask you a
couple questions sure you got one
question maybe one question okay can
animals reincarnate and especially our
pets can they reincarnate and can they
come back animals can reincarnate if God
says so okay and can they come back
it's
family yeah they
can and animals can reincar into other
animals you have a pet and then now your
pet passes
away the soul can
enter the womb of a
hawk
owl so it's it's it's it's complicated
it's it's more than that I think I'm
going to probably just talk more about
it but it's really it's really
interesting information that always
blows my mind when I hear it from Spirit
let's all right I got lost there I got
to wake up now I'm
here thank you guys thank you thank
[Music]
you hi hey good to see you I brought you
something okay is it a riddle is it you
want a riddle okay
so it almost is a riddle it almost is
this is what I used to have used to
have what and this is what I have now
that's insane that's unbelievable so
thanks to you well okay okay right now
this is helping me because of the snow
blindness I just said to somebody before
it should be bright big and and
bright so this a this takes care of it
yeah yeah you don't have to do anything
I just told you what I have here it is
it's amazing amazing
thank you so much you don't have to keep
this but I just wanted to like show you
no it it's more than just paper to me
okay it's it's I understand the journey
so yeah bless you're awesome bless your
heart we love you so much you're just
absolutely amazing God bless you yeah
yeah here you want to hold these
sure thank you so much you're
awesome hey yeah oh you're wearing black
watching our jacket oh I love that I
love that it's an honor to meet you oh
honor to meet you too can I have you yes
thank you so much you you I'm on the
right track I know I'm on the right
track now I'm healing there's there's
yeah and you know remember three steps
up two steps back sometimes right you
can get triggered two steps back but
you're going up up up up and um and
remember that okay that's important
because when we're healing we sometimes
can feel like we get kicked down a
little bit and then we're swimming in
that for a little bit but just to
knowing it move we move further even
more than before okay cuz that's what
just happened I did my first 369 advance
two of them and then I got an ear where
am I looking we're coming here we okay
looking at this friendly guy right
here thank thank you for coming I'm glad
you're doing that that's amazing did too
then I got your section that was steps
back yeah but that was coming anyway and
good thing you were doing that because
that'll make it less problematic okay
thank you thank you thank
you to see you hey who's this guy wait a
minute this is my husband
Steve does this always happen when
you're in the grocery store you're kind
of like over here and your you got the
cart you're putting stuff in he's
like all right good to see you it's an
honor it's an honor thank you for
everything you do thanks for what you do
good to see you guys you want to get a
picture yes I do amazing here step
forward a little bit Steve over here
amazing I'm proud of you guys enjoy the
food tonight and and I'm honored I'm
honored nice to meet
you uh yeah I've been a chef for a long
time but I got out and spped there
stuff like but you understand the
trade good to see you nice to meet you
nice to meet you too thank you for
coming my pleasure thanks for having us
amazing amazing have you been here
before never no really it's the first
time yeah that's incredible yeah thank
you for coming do you want to get a
picture yeah sure okay let's do it all
right amazing we'll look forward right
here
okay more
I hope you enjoyed the food thank you
very much me
too
hello hey we're in a lot of gold jewelry
cool how are you
doing what's going on nice to meet
you so I have a question for you I have
only one kidney and um I wanted to make
sure that I'm not doing anything with my
morning sometime I have to drink all my
morning stuff really fast and I just
don't know if I'm doing a little too
much sometimes I want to make sure my
kidney the one is taken care of because
I don't want to take my
husband remember I mean I talked about
this before with kidneys way too much
protein is the bigger problem no no I
know but you know that and that's good
okay that alone is critical always
remember that that alone is critical so
um and then always always keep things on
the Lighter Side that's all always you
know always um don't overfill the
tank okay cuz I do that sometimes you do
that sometimes just don't overfill the
tank it's hard it's hard to not and if
you do you do if you do you do don't
beat yourself up I'm just saying just
keep that in mind okay let's get a
picture thank you are you want to get in
this picture we go over here amazing yep
right here this fell here we go
guys may thank you thank
you thanks for coming you
guys what's going
on you guys came together yes doing a
we'll do a hand J okay good to see you
guys good to see you thank you for
putting on this event oh you're welcome
you're welcome I hope you enjoy the food
yes we stopped in last night to try it
out really thank you for doing that
that's amazing what did you try last
night your kelp noodles oh I like f dish
so clean I just had it yeah yeah and
it's light it feels light I had that
today because I didn't want to be like
you know I wanted to feel real light for
tonight right so I ate one of those
amazing we brought some home a I not
home but to the hotel hotel I mean where
you guys from Kentucky Kentucky Kentucky
oh thanks for coming you guys thank you
for the support thanks we won keep wait
oh no let's get a picture we have to
okay you guys are tooo kind step forward
here
okay amazing proud of you guys thank you
seriously I appreciate
your oh okay my phone thank you thank
you good to see you what you how are you
I'm doing well thank you thank you you
know I was doing a 369 a couple weeks
ago which one uh simplified nice I like
that I had a fever I had this cold
symptoms like just feeling terrible and
I've done that four or five times before
but haven't felt like that I so you so
you got yourself a bug cuz there's a
billion of them going around right now
not a billion but there's like four or
five bad ones going around you get
yourself Day N I felt amazing you
knocked it out you knocked it out
instead of ever yeah instead of being
sick for a month coughing coughing
coughing coughing I'm proud of you thank
you that's the way it should be that's
the way it should be really appreciate
it let's get a
[Music]
picture I'm proud of you by the way
thank
[Music]
you amazing thanks Anthony take
care hey hi what's going on how's it
going how you doing I just want to say
thank you so much I went to the K coner
or the K conference and you did a
personal white glass AUD and yeah
no way it was amazing and you said you
know you're not a bad person and I was
so emotional during that time and I just
felt like you help me get through a lot
of emotional struggles was just dealing
with a lot during that time you did get
a personal light blast oh my God
unbelievable let's get a picture can I'm
proud well well thank you to SLC by the
way but can I askc to
is there any message for mess you can
provide you know look you're a fighter
you're stronger than you know a lot of
times you don't believe that but you
have to know that you really are okay
seriously okay don't let anybody tell
you different right andc is amazing
too thank you for
coming hey how are you I'm good I'm good
good to see you good I congratulations
on enlarging Your Vessel it's like a
spiritual concept like you're reaching
more and more people a thank you I'm
really grateful but it's hard to do it's
like you know you being an example it's
it's really hard and you're doing a
great job I just want to make sure you
know that that means a lot okay it does
it does it means a lot to me more than
more than you know it does okay good I I
feel hard thank you cuz I try my best
and I keep on trying I keep on trying
and then you know I feel like like some
days and then I just get back and just
go go go go
go thank you so much I hope you enjoy
the food
tonight what's going on everything I'm
good how are you so nice to meet you
nice to meet you too um I just want to
ask you a question I've regressed a
little bit I was doing really well the
first couple years and now I'm
struggling any advice on how to you
regressed on doing the information just
the I mean I get cravings for things I
didn't get before and so now I'm I just
want am I doing wrong you're getting
enough you're getting enough of like the
balance like the potassium the sodium
the glucose you're getting like you know
what I mean mbly not okay okay okay
spirit says you like think a lot you
think a lot you know what I'm getting at
like you know this right like you you
there's people who think and there's
people who like and you're you're like
way over here that means your brain's
going to require more so just remember
that when you're going into everything
okay okay I will thank
you
okay proud of you okay so much get some
good food tonight thank you so
much what's going on here hello how are
you I'm Samara and this nice to meet you
I'm Z look at you Zach Zach SX thank you
for coming yes thank you seriously I'm
honored oh we're honored to be here we
have a quick
question with Perkinson okay and the
protocols and he's working which of the
protocols would you say are the most
important it's on both sides huh you got
a little bit in both sides of the brain
um he's got a lot of copper what why
were you around a lot of copper when was
that that was when I
was 39 years younger than I am 39 a
child maybe cuz he lived in New York and
Manhattan and you got exposed to a lot
of copper okay so so we we it's about
getting not Mercury but getting copper
out okay that's good to know all right
so um
he's doing the hmd right yes we're we're
doing the medical medium protocols for
stay stay strong on that I'm 89 years of
age and
looks you look good though even with
everything and the symptoms you look
good I'm proud of you okay I love you
guys let's get a picture is that okay
yes
two
more he's a keeper yes he he's a keeper
had him for 33 years yep thank you for
the
comer thank you so much love you much
love you
much what's going on here hi I'm
Kim a little step a little B good to see
you guys you want to get a picture get a
let's get a
picture you
ready yeah
thank
you
okay thank you amazing thank you guys
for coming all you do and all your
information you're
welcome I'm proud of you guys I'm proud
of you guys get some good food tonight
thank you
so nice to see you nice to see you
amazing as always uh oh thank you you're
too kind you're too kind no I'm not um
question for you is there anything
Spirit wants me to know that is
directly um you know with you like all
the little things matter and that's
important the little meaningful things
right so just don't stop with that don't
lose track of that it's very important
for you okay like all the little
meaningful things they are very
important to your soul so you know go go
through your things and find those and
be like okay I remember this this means
a lot to me just keep on connecting to
all of that for you that
matters a let's get a picture how long
before I have to leave
California you know you know
you're
up let's get a picture ready we'll come
over
here thank you you don't have to run I
don't have to run do I have like at
least 3 years three years I think so
okay good okay for as far as right now
where it stands okay it could shift
because there's crazy things that happen
I would let everybody know okay good hi
Anthony so nice to see you again good to
see you oh you've made such a difference
in my life life and thank you for
everything that you do and I really
appreciate it it's it's an honor I'm
glad you're here thank you oh thank you
I was wonder if I could actually a quick
question I know last time I was here you
mentioned that our pets are the first to
GRE Us in heaven they are and do they
ever well they they are the first okay
and I in fact I I answer that question
even more thoroughly coming up in the
audio okay so I was wondering if they
reincarnate In Our Lifetime and I'm
going to even do more over time but I
can't wait for you to
[Music]
listen welcome thank you for
coming hey how are you nice to see you
ni see you good to see you I preordered
your spiritual book I'm really excited
about it I'm I'm honored seriously I I
I'm excited too I am I am I've been
doing mm few years I just got interested
in growing my own food I wanted to know
if growing it in the ground in a in
above in a pot you know I got grow bags
I have a place in the ground I'm just
curious are you going to do some kind of
gardening tip yes I'll do more want to
know what type of soil to use I've seen
peite vermiculite pus like all types of
stuff but yeah I want to know some more
I'll do a thing about it soon 10 years
overdue yes all right okay thank
you well thank you so much it's an
honor all right what's going on here hi
nice to meet you amazing amazing to meet
you thank you it's an honor thanks for
coming guys thank you for having us you
are changing slowly our lives and our
diet and I have psoriasis and it's
getting better know about you unless it
was for her so thank you for everything
oh so you listen to
Mom you're a good kid you're a
good we can set up uh right
[Music]
here I'm proud of you guys enjoy the
food tonight
nice to see you hello hey I have a quick
question for you a strong guy right
there um sometimes when I wake up in the
mornings I have a very discomfort and
then it need me to have a seizure and
sometimes I get to control it and
sometimes I'm not able to and uh it's
really affecting my life and I've been
following how long you been how long
have you been doing the hmd and all that
for 3 years I've been doing that and I
see Improvement and I'm going to keep on
doing the 369
and I want to know if it's ever going to
go away because it's really affecting my
life your body wants to heal it does
okay and um I don't don't overthink
don't over stress even though things are
stressful I understand but but don't let
it say say look I I the stress is here
I'm not going to be a part of it in the
moment okay cuz stress does that's a
whole another Factor even if it's a
little bit and I do your uh lemon balm
therapy and then the B12 whatever is
this everything count count everything
counts everything counts some difference
but um it's anything else I can do
there's a lot of things that happened
where over the years it it could have
been the on the flip side it could have
been getting worse and you stopped that
you see how it
works so but but your body wants to heal
and we want you know and and it's going
to want to work with you just keep on
fighting forward yes okay get a pH get a
picture for
me thank you so much good to see you
good to see
you got a book oo the wa look at this
one right and it's highlights and so oh
my
God what's highlighted in here it's oh
my gosh oh my God look at this
whoa
wa thank you so much um thank you for
message from Spirit of compassion for me
I've been having such a terrible week
and this this is just I need to this so
much look remember I always say this I
know I sound like a broken record three
steps up two steps back yes okay just
don't your body's healing you just keep
on moving up moving up okay you're
working hard on all keep a late heart
see the cover that's
great oh nice to see you nice to see you
too thank you so much for all your
healing and for Spirit of compassion for
such deep gratitude you're welcome thank
you so much for coming I really
appreciate it you want to get a picture
we'd love it thank you so much we see a
book cover oh sure yeah all right here
we go
y
more thank you I hope you enjoy the food
oh I'm GL too thank you any words of
guidance and spirit of compassion for me
you shine a very bright light okay you
do all right and um but don't be hard on
yourself you know you're trying to do
things for other people you care about
other people you care about everything
and then you're hard on yourself at the
same time you just deserve to not be
hard okay thank
you hey how are you how are you nice to
see you good to see you too it's the
third time oh my God it's three yes yes
okay I'm so lucky I'm lucky I'm lucky I
adore you thank you so much every night
I'm saying thank you Anthony thank you I
will receive I will receive all the
positive positive thoughts and prayers I
feel so blessed that I got to know you
your books I'm listening to the podcast
everything I'm following you and
Instagram I'm trying to absorb every
word that you are saying I'll try to
keep you so much for all the effort you
put I'll try to keep it going I'll try
to keep on doing you want to get a
picture let's get a
picture here step forward a little bit
here more
thank you for coming thank you bless
you look at you I recognize you come on
apprciate what is going on how are you
doing huh how are you guys time huh
first time really yeah oh my God good to
see you guys thank you for coming our
dog has really B like skin allergies do
you have the doctor just been giving him
like antibiotic and shots do you have
anything speci speciic you recommend are
you
um are you you're looking in the books
and everything are you doing this the
celery juice and all that you're
bringing in different things you can
always bring in a little bit more just
just keep there's there's good stuff in
there for that
um you know look into pathogen things in
the books okay pathogen
things not just allergy but pathogen
and then just look through and see what
you and then ask the doctor and just
look okay okay good to see you guys here
want to get a picture want to come up
forward up up forward
more okay there we go well that's the
guy right there okay there we go how's
that we want to get a good picture okay
now we got
everybody thank you guys enjoy the food
good to see
you is this
Augustine the second oh my
God we're matching I know I know I love
the look oh look at this little baby huh
she's a little baby cute little ears
good to see you guys okay your question
if that's okay um I've been dealing with
like a professional and spiritual kind
of conf and I'm not sure how to move
forward at this point exactly if you
have any feelings or
anything well I mean look you're doing
all the right things you just it's
timing for you now remember that it's
timing you think it's the right time but
it's not and then when it finally comes
you're like now I know why it's this so
just hanging there thank you so you guys
I love your little doggy I can't believe
it I was so excited for you to meet her
yeah want to get a photo yeah of course
all right you want to step forward
more by the way it's really good to see
you to see you're a good man and I know
that thank you thank you I love you guys
yeah of course are you kidding I love
you so much of course you have a great
you're a good
kidy what do you got there that's a
letter for you really thank you oh my
name's Iselle by the way hm my name is
jelle ohelle yeah I never tell you I
like the mask oh thank you but I told
you this time there's a lot of bugs
going around right now oh look at
this there you are thank you Anthony oh
thank you Uncle a you're the best do you
want to get a picture yeah okay here's
the guy right here we'll go have you
move forward
[Music]
okay amazing than thank you for coming
okay you going to enjoy the food tonight
uh yeah also I just want to say thank
you for the book that's coming up oh
thank you for the what the book that's
coming up oh yes yes I'm really looking
forward to that all right just I hope I
hope you still like medical medium after
that I think I'm ready okay
okay nice to see
you wow nice coat good to see you nice
to meet you look at you thank you for
coming you're a beautiful human being I
feel the same about you for coming then
you came here and everything where' you
come from the area or I'm I'm from Ohio
okay amazing good good I have many
friends who just love well that that is
mindblowing to me okay it makes me very
happy I can't even tell you do you want
to get a picture
together let's do
[Music]
it amazing tell your friends I said hi
okay I see these pictures yes yes you
will you actually will I
promise God bless you
okay nice to meet you Tyrone pleas to
it's such a pleasure um thank you for
everything and for thank you for than
Spirit compassion for helping me heal
with so many addictions and uh mental
health stuff and I'm just I'm forever
grateful but you're doing the work you
put the work into it you're still doing
it I'm proud of you any suggestions or
advice just just you know try to try to
not come try not to fall off the wagon
like you know just stay just stay
straight go along you know okay okay yes
sir consistency is important for you and
and you do that but I don't want you
stopping okay yes sir sir thank you so
much let's get let's get a picture let
that would be amazing that would be
amazing here I'll have you step forward
a little step it
up thank you thank you for the life
good night amazing
I good job
okay
okay we are having so much fun here
tonight the meet and greet with aw just
finished so you know what it is now time
to head inside come inside with us
because the medical medium pizza party
is about to begin
don't
for
[Music]
for e
better
should
[Applause]
I
I e
[Music]
it's
[Applause]
really
[Music]
for e
[Applause]
care
for e
[Music]
little e
spe
C
[Music]
Sweden
spe
can't now
[Applause]
a
take
[Applause]
to e
you're
as
[Applause]
the third person that told me
[Music]
my
all e
start
[Applause]
should e
a
spe
one
e for
[Applause]
w
pizza
[Applause]
[Music]
party how's the food going all
right all right good I want to make sure
this mic's on you guys hear me all all
right um what an exciting night come on
Pizza like that's just unbelievable
[Applause]
right I know Cafe Gratitude is famous
for their
pizzas really famous because they are
best pizzas out there I don't care where
how when doesn't matter I mean you can
go to Italy and sit down and have a
great pizza but I swear these taste
better here and I'm not kidding that's
how I feel
anyway
[Music]
so and it's a great honor and I just
want to say it's a great honor to know
that they collaborate orated with
medical medium for pizzas with pizzas I
mean I'm still Blown Away some people
are blown away by other things you know
what I mean like a like a big moon in
the sky or something I'm blown away by
this because this is a big deal and um
it really is has a lot of meaning so
how's everybody feeling
tonight and you don't mind the cold
weather do you
guys I just want to see how everybody's
doing out here in the
back
amazing what's going on out here you
guys all right I didn't forget about
you I wouldn't forget this time no way
no way good to see you everybody's
comfortable tonight comfortable good
good you know this this isn't just
dinner this is like a
spiritual aw spiritual Gathering you
guys ready for light blast
later I was hoping I was
hoping I never you know I never know if
I'm going to be able to do one and I
kind of for the message from above to
say we're doing one to happen so it is
it's going to happen
tonight I have to knock on any wood no I
think we're going to do it don't
worry all right you guys are enjoying
yourselves out here I could see
Fant and the food is amazing right right
it's amazing good to see you again all
you guys wow
incredible so yeah back in here for a
little
bit just want to say to everybody thank
you people who traveled from far away
thank you seriously it's a great honor
to know you guys came down here all
right and uh I just want to say that
it's going to be fun tonight it's just
it's just getting started start it it's
just getting started so I'll be
back I'll be back enjoy the food relax
we're going to do a light blast like I
said
yep and and we're going to have a little
talk we'll see what s so says we'll see
what comes out of my mouth and
uh hopefully it's it's all good it's all
good
[Music]
great to see you guys I'll see you soon
I'll be out here don't
[Music]
worry for
[Applause]
[Music]
in
[Applause]
e
e e
are
[Music]
cathic High School cathol no
prob
need
[Applause]
B time
[Music]
know
e
for
e e
spe
you for
[Music]
[Applause]
real
e for
[Applause]
every
[Music]
no
e e
SA
[Applause]
for e
no
only
for e
[Music]
me
[Applause]
better
on e
[Applause]
understand
spe
like for
[Applause]
the
for for
[Applause]
[Music]
so we're inside Cafe Gratitude for
everyone watching at home the pizzas are
just coming out of the oven and they
smell amazing now we're going to come
back up this way and start talking to
some of the guests to see how they're
enjoying their delicious medical medium
pizzas hello
everyone hi I'm Danielle hello do you
mind if we join you while you're taking
a big bite do you mind if we join you
here at the table can I sit it next to
you do you
mind okay thank you
so this all looks delicious would you
mind showing me and everyone joining us
on the live stream what you're
eating you're still you're still eating
but we can start over here we're eating
the veggie medley
Pizza it has spinach red and yellow
peppers creami mushrooms Red Onion
broccolini pizza sauce cheesy potato
sauce herbed M seeds hemp seeds and grol
and I don't know what grandma Lada
is good question we might have to talk
to Chef Drew about that but how does it
taste how what is the flavor profile
like um the herbs are definitely
reminiscent of like pizza I used to eat
so that's on point uh the veg are good
um the tomato sauce yeah the flavors all
work together it it it tastes like a
pizza tastes like a pizza but healthy
and healing
absolutely which pizza has been the best
bite of the night so far so we just
started so we I don't think we've had
the second pizza unless this is the
second pizza too I don't know but I
would honestly I would say good oh is it
okay so she likes that one I would say
everything else has been
amazing I'm more of like a salad person
to the green papaya and kelp noodle Thai
salad all oh my gosh I came uh 2 months
ago for the last event and it's still
just as good that vegetable Sushi oh
that's really good really really good
and the spicy burrit amazing absolutely
amazing those just like kicking out of
the park the pizza's good but those
other ones are like way better for me
interesting but I feel like from the
whole menu though as a whole there's so
many different flavor profiles right
yeah it's a little bit of a a little bit
of like Flavor Whiplash but I'm taking
it all and it's each one is really
delicious if you can like switch gears
you know yes just cleanse your palette
in between with with a little glass of
water exactly mhm and then you got to
get ready because there's cookies coming
out and there's timey tea there's more
to
go you can get the cookie to go yeah yes
will like the time tea will hit the spot
to digest the food yeah but really
amazing Chef did a really amazing do job
putting it together do how does it feel
to come out and be at a restaurant and
enjoy a meal that fully supports your
healing Journey it feels good to like
eat yummy food that doesn't make you
feel like
horrible
yeah well said and to be surrounded by
such an amazing Community as well yeah I
mean that's my favorite part like coming
here and hanging out with my friends and
meeting new people like the mm Community
is my home so it's just amazing yeah not
you don't have to worry about any of the
ingredients in here didn't have to ask
the waiters any questions about what's
in it you know oils and things like that
everything has been C to help you heal
cuz usually at restaurants I don't go
very often but I get stressed out I get
worried what's in this can I eat this
will I feel bad but this like I don't
have to worry and I'm sitting with
friends we're laughing the whole time
people are stopping by to say hi it's
just such a happy with spirit and you
digest better when you're happy
obviously yeah yeah can you talk a
little bit more about the atmosphere for
everyone watching at home the energy in
here the Vibes The Vibes are good
they're really good you know it's it's
refreshing to be around people who kind
of understand um why you live your life
the way you do I have a lot of people
around me that kind of think I'm weird
and question why I eat the way I do and
everybody I'm normal to all these
[Laughter]
people it's beautiful and such an
uplifting Community I feel like there's
compassion that you can feel with the
energy and then just the smell of this
food as well is delicious yeah yes yeah
it's really good can you talk a little
bit about the pizza and the crust what
did you think of the crust of the pizza
I think I'm getting used to it because
this is the first time I've had
something like a pizza since I before I
got got sick and was eating like real
pizza so the adjustment you know I'm
having to switch gears a little bit but
it's you know for being so clean and
made of the ingredients it's made from
they did a really good job yes well
enjoy the rest of the evening enjoy the
lecture from aw the light blast the
cookies and time tea what an what an
awesome night right yeah thank you thank
you so much for talking to us thank you
we're going to move on to the next table
here and see how there there evening is
going hello everyone I'm Danielle nice
to meet you uh can I sit down a little
bit if with you join your
table so can you take us through all of
this yummy food that you have here
sitting on the table for those who are
watching
online yeah can I talk uh can we talk
about the one the the first one the
first dish which is a sushi the rice
sushi you can talk about whatever dish
you like yeah that was my favorite it
has a sesame just because it was so
fresh and you can eat the tons of
that and then the amino the amino soy
sauce is very good it tastes better she
was saying it's uh more sweeter it
tastes better than the one that you
normally get right I wonder if the
kitchen made it we wonder if the kitchen
made it themselves or some brand bought
it have to find that out and the Wasabi
was really spicy and really good real
masabi maybe with hor R you hat you so
far with what you've tried if you had to
give one dish some love for tonight and
a shout out would it be
that I personally yes the sushi yeah the
roll yes the roll the roll for me is
salad yeah yeah very fresh yeah Pap
salad I think I think the roll the nor
roll is the best yeah sushi sushi for me
yeah and what are some of these that you
have in front of you
so this one the pizza pizza thatat bread
and um yeah it's little bit sweeten and
um with some cheese spicy potato burrito
bowl
yeah sweet naturally
sweet yeah I can taste the sweet and the
is very
spicy I mean it's good spice it's a good
spice it's a good spice
yeah so can you take me through which
pizzas we have here and the
toppings oh the toppings oh they have
broccolini right broccolini and then the
cherry
tomato and uh chickpea oh chickp cheese
that was really good Capers basil Pasto
camata olives preserved lemon arugula
herb herb hemp seed oh there's hemp seed
in here I didn't know oh yeah it's right
yeah I think this one yeah it tastes
good I mean I think we would enjoy it
more if we weren't so full right like we
had we had a lot they can exchange this
this order
this comes first no one can eat more yes
and it's a lot of healing foods and
ingredient in there that's that's really
good heing yeah you mentioned this is
the only food that I mean you you don't
feel bad eating this like you don't
there's no guilt you know that's what
you were saying right like something
that you can eat and enjoy without looks
like cheese but no cheese it's really
awesome plus that you're not worrying
about oh is it any MSG or is it any
stuffff canola oil or the bad stuff that
great to be able to go out to a
restaurant with your friends and not
have to worry about all of that and to
have this beautiful menu that's been
catered towards your healing yeah yeah
we wish many restaurants has this kind
of option we wish that other restaurant
has these options too you know having a
healthier and better better quality
ingredients and fresh ingredients
definitely a demand for it and these
pizzas just look so beautiful you're
saying about the crust that it had a
sweetness to it what's it like is it
crunchy what's the texture like when you
um take buite yeah it's the this side is
the side is very crunchy and sweet it's
very uh chewy chewy yeah yeah in the
middle it is chewy and then the the
Tomato make it is very uh watery yeah so
combine them together is yeah enjoyable
yeah well thank you so much for talking
to us we're going to head over to the
next table and see see what dishes
they're enjoying this
evening hello
everyone hello
hello it's nice to see you all enjoying
your
food and you're into the pizzas can I
join you for a for a moment yeah we'll
sit down next to
you okay so it looks like you've already
gotten through the first few courses of
the food you're up to the pizzas what
has been the highlight for you so far
foodwise I love all of it it's really
really hard to choose I don't eat grains
so it's a big deal for me to have the
crust and I picked the rice off the
sushi but um I had the sushi last year
and it did the grain St sit well with me
I loved it so I'm enjoying all of them I
don't I don't know I'm having trouble
picking a favorite so that tells you
everything I think yeah it's hard to
pick a favorite when there's so much
amazing food here what do you think so
far what has been your best bite of the
night I would say definitely the pizza
how could it not be come on I'm never
going back never going back take me
through what dish we have here what
pizza dish we have here what are some of
the ingredients for people who are
watching at home well it's funny you
should
ask what we have here is a Mediterranean
putanesca pizza with cherry tomato
sundried tomato chickpea cheese which
was outstanding papers basil pesto
calamada olives preserved lemon arugula
and herbed hemp seeds that was my
favorite I have to say it had it all in
there lots of flavor and good crunch too
on the crust yeah it was surprising but
sometimes for some people the pizzza
it's all about the crust so if it passed
your test that's amazing really did it's
outstanding yes I highly recommend it to
you at home very very good and how how
are you going over this side of the
table which which pizza are you enjoying
the most oh which pizza they're both so
good it's I I don't think I could pick a
faig between the two they're just
delicious really really
delicious uh I didn't get to try this
this pizza but the highlight of my the
whole dinner was the
salad I I ate the whole thing I just
couldn't stop and Sushi was very good
too uh Pizza is very tasty but uh the
sell it was just beyond
yeah well what an amazing meal this
evening so much food so much healing
food how does it be feel to be in an
environment eating this beautiful
healing food not having to worry about
the ingredients in it and to be
surrounded by other individuals that
understand your healing Journey it's
absolute freedom it's amazing it's
really feels like you're being spoiled
because when you prep all the food
yourself which I do all the time this is
such a break to just come out and have
it done for you but know that you're
eating something that's really clean
really healthy and actually healing food
it's wonderful what about you one word
Guiltless
loved it yeah and there's more to come
as well we've got some cookies to come
out we've got timey tea I mean oh my
gosh so much food you've already got
some to-go boxes too oh yeah we're not
going to miss it yeah we're saving room
we don't want to miss any of the
courses well I can't wait to try the
pizza I haven't tried it yet and the
cookies I'm looking so I'm so looking
forward to that cuz I love a good cookie
and the time tea oh I make the time tea
at home so to have that out tonight is
going to be so much fun yes thank you so
much for talking to us thank you it's
been a pleasure thank you guys we're
going to move to the next table and see
what their dining experience is like
hello hi just wanted to check in say
hello and see if you're enjoying the
evening have a look at some of this
yummy food you've got here as well how
are you going so far uh we're doing
great no we're here my family my my
lovely son my wife we're enjoying the
food and uh we having a great time well
this is a big moment I mean you're here
at Cafe Gratitude having this pizza
party with your family are you enjoying
this
yes you're eating lots of yummy
food yes I see you've eaten all the
toppings off your pizza right yes do you
have a favorite bite of the night what
was your favorite thing you eaten so far
cookies you haven't eat you haven't
eaten the cookies yet but I I can tell
they going to be his
favorite chocolate there's no chocolate
no chocolate in these cookies but
they're going to be amazing we got some
I think we got a ginger cookie coming up
too favorite
Noah which of these your
favorite sauce and pepperoni there's no
pepperoni where do you eat pepperoni
what we ate tonight the pesto this one
right yeah
if it's as good as a regular pizza for
him I think we've won he held out all
night for these and he just like he we
were so full he's eating all of them
these were going to take home he's going
to get them packed for lunch tomorrow so
incredible what has been your favorite
bite of the night my favorite these are
incredible I'm I love the sushi and I
love the potato bowl those are my
favorite Sushi is still I mean I feel
like that's a bit of like a work of art
to create that the amount of uh work
that goes into it and love that goes
into the sushi it's a lot of preparation
yes yes absolutely it's I remember the
first time my husband and I had it we
were like oh my goodness this really
tastes like sushi
so for my son who pizza's always been
his favorite food we've been mm for a
little over a year now so I mean he
doesn't even ask for pepperoni pizza
anymore he
just I make him you know pizza at home
with the potato crust so it's but it's
like very laborous to make so it's so
nice that I can just you know order it
to go from Cafe Gratitude now is that
great do you think that having these uh
options on the menu and also the cleanse
available will help your healing journey
and continue to be more enjoyable oh
absolutely yes 100% yes now you have the
option to go out and eat and you know
have a night off in the kitchen we
brought him out for Valentine's Day we
came here we had a really nice family
dinner together and that wouldn't have
really been possible before so he just
he's
thrilled yeah we continue enjoying the
night it's been so nice talking to you
all enjoy the cookies I know you're
looking forward to the cookies did you
enjoy the pza
too yeah it was really good especially
the um I think the pestl yeah yeah cuz
it's a little bit salty so it's really
good yeah yeah but I'm a little bit full
right now so that's what everyone's
saying they've been saying that there's
been so much food coming out that
they've been getting so full yeah for
sure but I'm excited for the the cookies
oh yeah yeah I'm excited for the cookies
too cookies to come time tea we've got
aw's lecture an interview with aw as
well and of course the light FL so make
sure you stick around that's all from
the dining room tonight but we'll back
tomorrow with more
you
e for
time
all e
my
me
I
[Applause]
to
think
[Music]
hey guys we are back here with aw now
we're back at Cafe Gratitude again this
time for the medical medium pizza party
how does it feel oh you think about it
pizzas that's a big deal what I'm just
so excited because cathic gratitude's
known for their pizzas I mean around the
world seriously they're Incredible
Pizzas anybody in La they get their
pizzas and Cafe Gratitude they wanted to
collaborate medical medium on a pizza I
mean on pizzas it just doesn't get any
better than that it's so exciting and
they taste amazing so I'm just really
excited about it because it it's it's
like think about it like when someone's
trying to heal and they're sick and
they're not well they know not to eat
pizzas out there and but if you can get
a medical me and pizza that's really
clean really pure really healthy that's
a big deal deal I mean especially if
you're somebody that you know has been
through hell and back with your healing
process you've eliminated so many foods
you've been to you've done every
modality every diet belief system and
you know that pizzas aren't on that list
but pizzas are on the list now that's
the thing people should be coming here
to get these pizzas they're unbelievable
oh this is so exciting and it's been a
while since we last talked what have you
been up to lately what projects have you
got going on angs demons and spiritual
tools it's it's going to be mindblowing
when people actually hear the
information from above Spirit of
compassion answered a lot of questions
about afterlife after death it's a big
deal Angels Fallen
Angels uh something called Falling
Angels that's a big deal all on its own
like the information about the soul even
some stuff about ghosts like how you
know how does that even work but really
just powerful
information uh it it's an incredible
audio book audio original audio that
that's being released um it's going to
be out March 18th I hope people get a
chance to actually hear it it's it's a
big
deal tremendous amounts of
information about angels and demons but
you got to be ready for it you got to be
ready for it
because the information is is
mindblowing Awakening it answers a lot
of questions all around that people have
like what is a demon what is an angel is
an Angel Real so many people don't even
believe in angels so many people don't
believe in so many different things but
that's the project and it's a spiritual
one but but you got to be ready for it
the information is is it's a lot to take
in a lot to digest and it comes from
above basically what I did was I just I
asked a lot of questions and a lot of
questions and
the information came through and just
like you know medical medium fashion
it's it's a lot of
information and uh and doesn't just make
sense it's like it is unbelievable so
yeah yeah you know I was listening to a
snippet of that last night that you have
on Instagram and I went as soon as you
finished I was like wait I need to hear
more so I went on Spotify and hit the
pre save yeah okay cool cool yeah I I
hope I hope a lot of people you got to
sit down when hear it you got to
actually be sitting down when you hear
this information yeah and um I mean the
medical meme information or the medical
books but that's what that's what it is
and it's mixed in with some spiritual
information about the soul because when
you're healing the physical body you
also want to heal the soul there's a
combination of both and all that but the
medical medium books they are medical
books to get people you know out of the
woods get them into the light of healing
but this book book this
audio is a whole another thing this
isn't just about tools with nature and
you know and spiritual information about
the soul it's way beyond that and I
think people when they hear this they're
going to be like oh my God and it's
going to answer a lot of questions yeah
wow I can't wait how is it possible that
so many people have healed from
devastating chronic diseases through
medical medium most people most people
around the world there's no modality
there's no belief system in health
there's no any of that that can beat
medical medium information healing the
most people in the world it just is it
is just a fact it's just what it is and
and that's what's so incredible about it
I I think that also makes it challenging
because there's jealousy out there and
there's people out there in the health
movement that they don't like seeing
that nobody wants to see something heal
so many people like meaning people that
are actually out there in the industry
people in the industry don't want to see
millions of people healing from this
information because it just it just
really gets under the skin of so many
people in the industry but it's the most
people healed hands down around the
world it's a very special thing it's
it's it's truly a miracle what has
happened the information from above and
people getting their lives back people
getting getting out of wheelchairs
people I mean neurological problems
everything from aches and pains and
ticks and spasms and ringing of the
years in Vertigo and all kinds of
different conditions eczema psoriasis
and brain fog devastating brain fog and
depression and anxiety more people
healed than anywhere no matter what that
is just the way it is and you know it's
something to be proud of it's something
for the people who work so hard and
their healing process and found their
way to this information to be proud of
them and proud of the information and
proud of the record the street cred the
the the record of healing so many people
in the world and it's not me healing
them I'm a messenger it's the
information from above you know since I
was a child and getting that information
and that's what's healing people I'm
trying to message it the best I can and
get that information out there the best
I can regardless of obstacles and oppos
position and Sinister crap that's out
there in the world and all that that
doesn't want to see this information you
know heal everybody but either way it
still holds the record hands down
there's no I mean it just is what it is
there's no podcast doctors that have
that many people better there's no
influencers in the world that have that
many people better it's just it just is
what it is people getting out of
wheelchairs people getting their lives
back and I say this anyone out there
that's struggling with any kind of
symptom and mystery chronic illness and
autoimmune and neurological problems
whether they know it or not if they have
a neurological problem that there are
answers there is a way to heal this
information has proven that the medical
medium books have proven that and it
it's just a it's it's a great time to be
alive it's a great time to be here yeah
it's it's so incredible and I just love
talking to people and he and hearing
their healing journey and now the heavy
metal detox smoothie is available at
Cafe Gratitude yeah no think about that
the the hmds heavy metal detox movie is
here and that has a track record that is
the number one heavy metal
detox hands down and that has a track
record people got their lives back from
getting Metals out of their brain
getting Metals out of their liver out of
their body out of their bloodstream out
of their organs their pancreas they
spleen their kidneys getting Metals out
moves people forward and when it's
something that works it's an it's just
it's a whole another thing you know
everybody wants a Magic Bullet everybody
wants a Magic Bullet right now out there
and you see it in the health world and
they're all looking for a bioh hack
everybody's trying to get the latest
Trend the latest biohack and everything
like that if you're not so sick fine you
can play in that world man you get real
sick where you wake up in morning you're
like oh my God I'm sick I'm like really
sick and you wake up that you know that
morning that it hits you finally you you
are now Rock Bottom you need something
that works and now it's you can't play
games enough of that the [__] is
over you can't play games you have to be
successful in your healing now and so
it's not just go try this bioh hack and
go try that and this trendy thing and
here's this commercial and here's this
ad you need something that works you
need something with a track record and
the hmds the heavy metal detox medical
medium that has the track record and
people can't waste time when they're too
long when you finally get to that stage
and you're like wait a minute I'm losing
my life that's what I'm doing it has to
work no more games and that's medical
medium that's the heavy metal detox yeah
the heavy metal detox and it's in Cafe
Gratitude yeah so now people can get it
here they don't have to make it at home
they can come to Cafe Gratitude exactly
exactly you know what I am so excited
for these events because people are
going to be getting another light Blast
from you tonight but for those who are
watching who are unfamiliar with it how
does a light blast work and can you tell
us about it light blast is something
that you know it's one of these things
where I wasn't sure if I could ever
really live up to what Spirit of
compassion you know wanted me to do with
this so I was trained really young and I
fought for it you know so if there'd be
a wounded baby bird that I would find
spirit of compassion would help me get
light to that bird and and we would
practice and and try to infuse you know
turtles that are injured birds that are
injured with broken wings the light
blast started really early on right and
but when I was you know 5 6 7 years old
8 years old I never dreamed or thought
of me doing being here today and doing
the light blast in here right now like
at 5 years old like that wouldn't have
really computed so it's been it's been
in kind of an elev thing where it
started where where I was really little
giving the light blast and then getting
a little bit older and and offering that
light blast to people not just animals
getting really good at what Spirit of
compassion wants me to do and wanted me
to do with that light blast and now all
the you know what it's developed into
and the decade after decade of doing the
light Blast for people and to be here
right now it's very special honestly it
really is and I never know if I can
actually you know do it that day or not
Spirit of compassion can I got to be I
got to be at a point in order to do it
it's it's intense um and yeah and I and
I talk about I've talked about this
before it takes a lot out of me but it's
it's worth it to see people move forward
and heal I mean the Miracles that
happened from the light blast people
like like getting rid of pain getting
rid of problems it's gone the next day
some sometimes gone in that minute when
they get the light blast that makes it
worth it that makes me want to keep on
doing it no matter what it takes and the
energy and the output but um we're going
to do it tonight for sure wow I'm so
excited and thank you for that thank you
for doing that uh it's amazing what an
amazing talk we had tonight we're going
to be back tomorrow night for another
chat and we've got the lecture coming up
the light blast so much more to go we're
going to go check that out now great all
right thank you thank you so much thank
you that was great
[Applause]
[Music]
want
[Applause]
St e
know
somebody
[Music]
somebody for
[Applause]
everybody
eating whoa look at those cookies did
you try the cookies try the cookies good
how was the pizza all right it was was
good oh my God those are insane are so
good good to see you guys out here
everybody's
[Applause]
full you know you know what I say when I
when I've just eaten a whole bunch I'm
like I'm
stuffed I'm
stuffed that's what I like to
say um when I think about
it when I think about like where you
guys have come
from and where you are
today it's it's pretty
mind-blowing how many of you were on
madress
island yep so you know what you know
what it's like you know what it's like
and you guys outside too right madress
Island yeah I
think it it's almost impossible for
somebody to understand what that is
unless they've experienced it themselves
unless they lived it
themselves it's really difficult to be
on matress Island and see the world go
by around you watch the world go by
around
you and people not understand really
what it's like unless they've been in
your shoes so when I think about anybody
who's been on mattress Island which
means you've just been in bed a long
time bed in bed a lot more you know what
I mean even if it's just a couple hours
during the day it's still a lot when you
see everybody else what they don't need
to take a nap right you see other people
out there well they don't need to slow
down they're up there they're outside
they're moving and grooving they're
doing things and then you watch that and
it's really hard when you've been
struggling and you've been sick for a
long long time it makes it really
difficult makes you feel kind of
alienated right makes you feel kind of
like whoa why am I not better how come
I'm struggling how come I'm
sick and so mattress isent is is
something
that is important to me because it's
about understanding chronic illness and
mystery chronic illness and when I think
about how many of you would not believe
you would be here today is there a few
of you guys that wouldn't believe you'd
be here today
but you are right you're here right now
in this moment pressing forward into the
future you know right on that edge of
time and you didn't think you'd be here
but you are and that alone is a big deal
all on its
own it's inspiring Beyond
inspiring I think it's difficult in the
health World these days and you see it
out there okay there's a lot going on in
the health world and I still think till
this day that chronically ill people
people with chronic illness people who
are sick with mysterious symptoms
conditions are swept under the carpet I
still believe it's happening I do they
don't get the respect they need I still
see that too the respect isn't there and
it's really really sad we got a world
where we just don't have some sick
people we got a world where we have a
lot of sick people now and they're
getting sicker and sicker I don't know
if you guys are seeing that out there
are you is everybody just healed in the
world or do you see people getting
sicker yeah no I know it's it's it's
crazy when you really think about
it all the organic food in the world all
the great stuff going on all the health
conscious stuff all the meditation
everything but you see people getting
sicker out there interesting
right I think what happens is with
medical medum information is once you
find it you realize you're home you know
what I mean did you guys get to that
point
[Music]
once you
right
y once you find the medical meme
information you're like home you you
know it makes sense you know it's the
real thing you just know it cuz you
tried everything you've been there You'
done that you're seasoned you know and
that's the other thing the medical medum
community is the most seasoned Community
there is it's the most seasoned you know
group of people that have been there and
done that and tried everything and what
I've noticed about people in the medical
medium Community is they're seers they
see the broken glass out there they see
right the live wires hanging off the
telephone poles that you're not supposed
to touch they see all the potholes now
you know what I mean you stepped in
enough of them throughout your life
right and now you become this like Wise
Wise soul that sees things and you see
it clear that's the difference with the
medical M Community is you eyes become
spiritually empowered and can see things
and that is mind-blowing all on its own
I've watched that all through the years
through the decades really I've seen it
myself where now you guys are seers
that's what it comes down to you see the
trouble you see what's going on in the
health movement you see all of it I know
everybody wants a Magic Bullet I just
mentioned it out there for a minute when
I was talking people want a Magic Bullet
but does it work like that is there just
one trendy Magic Bullet that fixes
everything right people are looking for
it out there they want that one magic
pill they want that collagen powder did
you guys try collagen powder did you
guys do the collagen thing or is it my
imagination did you try that years ago
did you guys get sucked into all the
fish oil stuff what was that did you do
the fish oil stuff right you you just
thought you were supposed you needed to
shove all that fish oil capsule stuff
down right what about the charcoal did
you guys try the charcoal stuff you did
that oh I got to do this charcoal let me
shove this down it's got to be the
charcoal that's next
right it's unbelievable and there's a
lot there's a lot more stuff out there
I'm sure you guys Tred did you try the
ionizer water that that would be the fix
it
all the alkaline water that would be the
fix it all
it just doesn't work like that you need
you need things your body really needs
to heal and it takes me to the next
thing I want to say is our bodies want
to heal they do they want to
heal they just need to get what they
need to do
so even if your mind's not there yet
here's the thing about the medical meme
Community too many of you guys who've
been through hell and
back your spirits were broken at some
point right were your spirits broken at
some point
and
then you needed to see the healing first
a little bit right before you were real
you started realizing wait a minute here
something inside of you said let me do
this medical medium information
something inside of you was like I'm
going to do this I heard about this one
person I heard what happened maybe you
know this book fell in my lap I'm going
to do some medical medium stuff but you
were already kind of busted up you had a
rough go rough road many people in the
medical medium Community have had that
but then you see a little bit of healing
and that's when all of a sudden you're
like whoa what is this I'm actually
starting to move the needle something is
starting to move the needle for me
something is happening here and then
then something just lights up inside
your soul gets boom a boost and it
starts to awaken and you're like you
know what I'm on the right path I'm on
the right path and then you run into all
this
crap all this crap for it you're doing
your juicing you're taking care of
yourself you're doing your mono eating
you're doing your 369 you're doing your
28 day cleanse you're doing the things
you need and you're getting like what
confrontation many people have gotten
confrontation oh you're doing that again
you're doing this again just go to the
doctor I've been to the doctor
how many you guys been to
doctors and I think that's a massive
misconception all on its own it's like
people think a sick person just didn't
get to the doctor yet a person who isn't
sick yet just thinks the sick person
just didn't get to the doctor
yet and that's something I've seen over
the years it's like get to a doctor you
should just go to a doctor get fixed
come on we need doctors there's some
great doctors out there but you know the
world just doesn't always work like that
it's not black and white when you got
symptoms and conditions and you haven't
been
well there's all these different gray
areas and gray zones and nuances and
details and that's another thing too
being heard with your symptoms when you
have a lot of symptoms how many of you
have had more than one symptom how many
of you guys had more than one symptom
more than
one I think pretty much all of you guys
had more than one symptom right about
more than two more than two symptoms oh
that's an easy one right that's an easy
one you're like that's an easy one I've
had 50 I've had
60 how many of you guys have had like 20
symptoms plague you yeah yeah the
nuances the details it matters these
symptoms each one of them
matters and we go to the doctor we go to
two doctors three doctors have you been
to a specialist who's been to a
specialist been to a specialist right
specialist you guys out there too B to
the
specialist well you got to see a
specialist now you got to see a
neurologist now you got to see a
pulmonologist now you got to see this
other doctor it's not an easy Road it's
not and so something has to kind of
like take
over our Free Will has to now take over
and has be I need to heal I need to get
better I need to do something about it
it has to change for
me and then you wake up one morning and
you're like I'm done it's time to heal
it's time to get better and then you
think about that thing somebody told you
about with medical medium and then you
think about someone said something about
medical medium how did you guys find
medical medium was it just a social
media post did somebody tell you what
was it
right and
then you're like I'm going to do this
I'm going to do
this I'm going to take control over my
life I'm going to take control over my
health my free
will I'm going to use it it's not going
to be locked up anymore controlled by
somebody else I want my free will to
work for me I want to heal I want to get
better I don't want to be sick anymore
and then you rise out of the ash es and
you work on your healing process and one
day at a time how many people know about
three steps up two steps back have you
experienced it triggers
exposures all of
it you guys have become really really
wise beyond your years you already were
to begin with then even more so than
ever now the amount of wisdom you have
and experience with your healing process
is unmatched it's unmeasured
it's got to be respected you got to have
respect for it you know about how the
healing process works you guys are
experts you know the three steps up two
steps back and then you move up again
and you go back a little bit move up
again and you go back a little bit you
guys know about
that all of these things matter they
just do how seasoned you are what you
went through your symptoms the nuances
the details how many symptoms you've had
what you went through your darkest hours
at night when you lay awake and you're
like what am I going to do how am I
going to take care of myself how am I
going to take care of the people I care
about all of that matters and guess what
it's not just seen by someone maybe you
know here or you've talked to it's seen
from above every little thing you guys
have been through and what you've done
and every symptom you've had has been
seen from above this entire
time and I promise you one thing you're
not alone there's a lot of people in
this world sick with chronic illness and
there's a lot of people in the medical
mem
community and I really say communities
actually all around the world all over
the
place I think the one thing you guys all
need to know when this is critical
okay is you have a life experience
a life experience that needs to be
valued in the highest degree the highest
degree the thing is I know you guys are
all humble every one of you I met every
one of you guys tonight you guys are the
most humble people I've ever met I
humble way more humble than what I might
be I can tell you okay sometimes my head
gets
big and then it's got to be like popped
my head gets big again Anthony like you
saved my life I'm like hey that's
amazing that's
amazing but you guys seriously truly
humble Integrity is really there and
your old souls the thing is not one of
you guys walking in was a young Soul
just
weren't you ever talk to somebody in the
spiritual World maybe a medium maybe a
psychic or something like that like
you're a young Soul you just got here
did you guys ever run into that anybody
ever run into that ever talk to a
psychic they're like no you're a young
Soul you just rolled
in you got a lot to
learn the thing is is people in the
medical medium Community they're not
young
Souls I mean they're not just just
here there might be
one but everybody here really old souls
though for real like a thous th years
old 1500 years old 2,000 years old 4,000
years old yeah 4,000 years old souls
here I mean I heard from Moc tonight
like this person's like 4,000 years
old and I'm like well what about me what
about
me what I'm just 300 years now
what oh why did you pick me then because
you can handle it I can
I don't know about that but seriously
really really old souls here for real
though that is no joke and that's true
and that says a lot all on its own so
that means that your souls contain and
harbor life experiences from every
lifetime it's in there it's locked in
there and this is another one
now and it's locking in there now but
this one's a little different this one's
about chronic illness this is about
having to fight your way
back having to heal after everything
you've been
through this one's
different this is about that emotional
struggle this is about really really
perfecting your soul in a different way
than ever before because sickness
changes everything it is by far the most
spiritual Soul growth that could ever
happen is through sickness and chronic
mystery illness there's nothing more
that can be any more powerful for
perfecting a soul for growing a soul for
spiritual growth and movement forward
it's chronic illness it's those symptoms
that's the big challenge it's different
when you're getting older and you're
getting older and then you have a heart
attack that
sucks that
sucks you're getting older you're
getting older you're getting older you
get type two diabetes and you you know
and that sucks it does you're 20 years
old and you're on mattress Island and
you're like what the is going on I'm on
mattress Island I'm 20 years old I'm 22
years old whoa there a whole different
thing going on there same thing if
you're 30 or 32 or 39 it's like whoa
wait a minute I'm supposed to be living
my life man I'm supposed to be at the
best I've ever been I'm supposed to be
like at the top of my
game I'm not saying heart attacks are no
big
deal like I said they're they're no
fun but it's different with chronic
mystery illness and getting it young I'm
looking at a lot of young people here a
lot of young people here so think about
the spiritual growth and the level of
that spiritual growth and that has to be
respected and
appreciated first by you you you're not
going to like have an ego just because
you appreciate your spiritual growth
like it is at this point you're not
going to be like like egoed out just
because you appreciate where you are
with your healing and what you've been
through you have every right to hold and
wave that flag that you've been through
hell and back and healed or you're in
your healing process too with your
chronic illness you should be proud of
that you should be able to wave that
flag you should never ever think that
that's not a big deal it is it's
special I think this world just beats
people down that's what it does it does
beats people
down that's the way it's designed uh on
a bummer note that's the way it's
designed it's just is I mean sure
sure but man you
guys it's whole another level and that's
the thing okay as you're coming back
from your illnesses as you're actually
healing and you come back from your
illnesses you guys possess more power
than you realize you possess an energy
force more than you
realize more than somebody who's never
been hit by anything never had a
struggle yet in their life maybe they'll
die of a heart attack when they're 65 or
something but before then they're just
skating by skating by and they think
they got it all down they think they got
it all down right they do and you feel
I'm sick I feel weak I I'm not strong I
feel I'm not I can't do what that
person's doing right there I'm not
successful I feel just not right all
that no it's the opposite it you're the
strong one you're the one that possesses
that light and that life force and the
energy force and that spiritual growth
like I said you're the one that
possesses all that not the person who's
skating through life all fine and
everything's great you know and all of a
sudden yeah they get a heart attack at
some point and they get a surgery and
that's what they do no no no no no you
guys whole different lot whole different
lot of people a whole different breed of
people on this planet people with real
experience people with real real Soul
real Soul because you know what happens
when you get sick you got to get in
touch with the with compassion you have
to if you've been through hell you have
to get in touch with compassion and then
what happens when you hear somebody else
is sick you guys care right you care if
somebody else is struggling oh man you
got tingles and numbness and aches and
pains and your back hurts and you got
something wrong with your jaw and your
tongue is just like buzzing and you're
vibrating through your body and you
can't you can't even get out of bed and
your legs feel like sandbags and your
arms feel like dead
weight you feel bad for them right you
feel bad for
them even if you're not even 100% better
yet you just got yourself 50% better
thank God and you still feel bad for
them and you still care about them
that's the kind of things you guys have
real compassion not fake [__]
compassion and there's people in the
spiritual and and there's people in the
health Realm
where you know they act like they got
compassion they're doing their thing
they're out there they never had a
challenge with their health not
yet and are they really compassionate I
don't think so maybe some are but not
the majority of them but you guys are
real compassionate you guys hold
compassion that's a big deal you
care you guys can go back in your
database of I've been through hell and
back I've had that symptom times 100 I
know when I was on my hands and knees
praying to God and I was like God I'm
either going to live or die so we got to
make something happen right now
right you guys just have to understand
and I know you do you're very
special and I'm not blowing smoke
here that's not what I'm
doing I know it I know it that's why I'm
even here and doing this
my
God I have to somehow rise to some
degree or rise to some you know aspect
or just rise up to try to like match you
guys do you understand that that's what
I have to do I know a lot of you guys
look up to me and you say like Anthony
you're a great guy aw you know all this
great stuff but I still have to I have
to fight my way up to try to get to your
level do you guys understand that that's
the truth I have to like
I do I
do it's
legit
because I haven't laid in bed with 150
symptoms for the last 20
years I mean I don't have it totally
easy I don't have it totally easy all
right the [__] I'm up against every now
and then is ridicul
but but honestly I got to dig deep and
dig deep and be like crap I got some
work to do I got to bring myself to
their
level their level of experience and
understanding what they've been through
I got to bring myself up to their level
of what they're they're with coming from
hell and back rising out of the ashes
all of it I have to kind of like get in
touch with that I have to be I have to
be one with that I do I have to be it's
critical for me to understand that so I
have to fight for it to get to your
level you guys are already there you're
already
there you guys up for a light blast
[Applause]
or I know that some of you guys have had
a life Blast how many people here who
have who hasn't had a light blast that's
what I'm curious to you haven't had one
you haven't had one whoa whoa whoa whoa
what what really you come on couple
there couple people out you're right
there you haven't had one yet whoa
whoa couple more out there all right
we'll get ready you too huh okay I just
wanted to check out and see check things
out and see who didn't get one
before in person in person in person how
do you like
that so since I was a
child Spirit of compassion
taught me how to do a light blast and I
started with baby birds with broken
wings I started
with you know injured bunny rabbit that
got hit by a
car and getting in touch with people
suffering and struggling through animal
suffering and struggling too and then
learning how to do the light
blast being a part of it part of spirit
of compassion's ability to get some
light down on
everybody and I always tell people this
in the past too you know just you may
not even believe in so does it matter
you're going to get hit with
light I mean I I want you to believe in
s so sure but you don't have to it's
fine because I know you're still going
to get that light right on top of the
head it's going to run right through you
and it's going to happen no matter what
where do you want that light to hit do
you want it to hit your heart do you
want it to hit your brain do you want it
where do you want it to go I want
everybody everybody to think about where
it's going okay where is it
going I I'll give you a couple seconds
is it going to somebody else doesn't
always work that way but tonight we can
make it happen where you can direct it
if you have to direct it okay
we can do that we can do
that I'm at your service
tonight it's it's the least I can do for
all the hard work you guys put into
yourselves it's the least I can do the
least where do you want the light to
hit it's going to hit the top of your
heads but it's going to go someplace
it's supposed to run all the way through
you and it's going to but you can Center
it to certain areas in your body is
there a symptom you want it to hit and
that may not be exactly where in the
sense where well I have a symptom but I
don't know what that symptoms where it's
coming from is it coming from the brain
then let it hit your brain if you don't
really know how to put that together
then let it hit your symptom and just
call it
that I got a skin WRA CR I want it to
hit
there I got an achy hip I want it to hit
there so what we're going to do is we're
going to do like a count of three I'm
going to have have you guys hold your
breath just for a few seconds spirit's
going to send the light down and then
you're going to release but we're going
to take a deep breath first before we
even do that everybody take a deep
breath and then
release this isn't like breath work or
anything you don't have to take a big
deep breath
you don't have to sit there killing
yourself to get you know all this air
in and there's no contests here you're
not going to win if you take a bigger
breath than somebody else this isn't a
yoga studio where everybody's trying to
out breathe everybody that's not what
this
is I don't know if you ever seen that
before maybe that one's my imagination
and that's not what's happening in yoga
studio but I have a feeling that's
what's happening everybody's trying to
out breathe them
like right you know showing off like I
got this after that like where's my
matcha tea
right all
right get uh count of three take a deep
breath and just release one 2 3 deep
breath
in and then
release nice we're almost there we're
almost there I'm waiting for my my
signal which comes on this side here
sorry I got to shove my left ear into
everybody's face over there on the red
carpet all right count of three deep
breath one more time release one 2 3
deep breath
in
release all right ready for the first
one we're going to hold our breath for a
couple of seconds okay guys if that's
okay if you can't hold your breath for a
couple seconds don't don't it's okay you
don't have to but if you can do it on a
count of
three take the deep breath we're going
to hold it and spirit of compassion is
going to send light
down one two three deep breath in hold
it light light light
release that was the first
one take deep breath release 1 2 3 deep
breath
release all right get ready for this one
it's going to be a little bit more
intense and to count of
three one 2 3 deep breath in hold it
light light light
release we got some blockages tonight
just hang in there everybody take a deep
breath release one two 3 deep breath in
and then
release we got a few blockages I noticed
there's been some increased stress in a
few people's lives in that are in this
room so is saying that there's stress
going on in a few people but they made
it here but they're up against some
extra
stress on the count of three this is a
bigger one one 2 three deep breath in
hold it light light light light
release all right we're moving forward
now all right everybody take a deep
breath and release one two 3 deep breath
in and then
release I'm watching Everybody outside
too okay this is going to be a big one
right
here there's been a bunch of people
where it went all the way through who
felt it go through them already all the
way through you got it all the way
through you you got it all the way
through you nice still going to go
through you
again get ready count of three 1 2 3
deep breath in hold it light light light
light light
release I'd say
about 40 more people roughly it went
through
them all right we got a few
stragglers which is great
we want people that it hasn't gone all
all the way through it hit their chest
it's stuck we want it stuck somewhere in
them because it's only going to make it
better for everybody else who had
already went through and they're going
to get a whole another clear one right
through
them get ready there a big one one two
three deep breath in hold it light light
light light light
release we only have one more is all we
need one more okay everybody think about
where you want that light to go this is
going to be the last one where do you
want this one what's eating away at you
what is it is it somebody that's up your
ass somewhere and you know whatever
because they're just giving you
confrontation is it in the workplace is
it somebody that's just you know on you
the wrong way because they're just
giving you trouble and causing all kinds
of flack what is it is it somebody or or
is it just something it's an
institution what happened you couldn't
register your car the other day what is
it where do you want this last one going
to or is it just directly to your organs
your bloodstream your bones how about
your bone marrow where do you want it
going
okay all right count of three one two
three deep breath in hold it light light
light light light light light
release two people left and the last one
we're going to do right now get ready
one two three deep breath in hold it
light light light
release that's it you guys you guys are
cleared for tonight you guys are
cleared I'm going to I'm going to need a
pizza I'm going to need a pizza that's
what I'm going to do after
this a healthy good pizza you know
what's crazy what's crazy is
right is you guys know that pizzas
aren't that great for you out there in
the world how many frozen pizzas are you
eating that you just got from the store
right now huh are you guys eating pizza
every single night this is unbelievable
what happened tonight to be able to
actually eat pizza in like the most
amazing
restaurant it's really incredible I just
want to thank everybody at Cafe
Gratitude seriously all their hard work
Patrick over there the
COO Chef Drew of course who's helped us
with all the collaborations honestly
he's made me look
good yep he's made me look
good he's like no no we put this in here
this is the I'm like yeah that's
incredible I'm I'm I'm I'm so
good and I really appreciate everybody
your hard work seriously and um thank
you guys for coming out
tonight and honestly truly truly truly
just warms my heart all of you guys so
proud of you so proud of you okay
I'll see you guys I'm and I'm Crystal
where are we coming from today from
Germany so this means that this is very
important to you guys extremely
important okay so tell me why tell me
why because of Anthony we own our lives
to him actually because we were severely
sick and he helped us heal I was very
Hill I had a lot of dizziness I couldn't
um stand actually most of the time I had
a lot of infections and I went from
Doctor to doctor and they were like we
don't know what's happening with you
maybe you're crazy or you're making this
up I had aggressive brain fog since I
was 14 nobody could help me I had
serious problems I was always tired uh
and no one understands it I didn't know
the uh the word brain frog I learned it
from Medical meet him anything
specifically we excited about for
tonight yeah meeting Anthony we are so
excited just thank him for everything
that he does for us he thank you for the
organization thank you an thank you for
everything I was an alcoholic for a long
time because our people were in the
residential school system I'm PR I'm pre
First Nations from northern what they
call Canada and um there was a lot of
trauma and I have been an alcoholic all
my life and with the medical medium
information it actually helped me to get
rid of the Cravings which was profound
to me because I didn't know you can
actually cure yourself which it feels
amazing like I don't have to suffer
every day wanting that alcohol I've
worked so hard to try to find joy in my
life and there's days where I have it
and days that I don't but there's more
days that do have it now then before it
was also always so hopeless it's just
incredible very very incredible and so
powerful I hope that you have a really
good rest of your night can I give you a
hug
yes if I were to pinpoint when I became
sick it was when I was in seventh grade
and it was a pretty emotional time in my
life for the next 20 25 years I went to
so many different doctors from
conventional doctors to Natural doctors
I was kind of like I will try anything I
heard heard about celery juice and I
gave it a whirl and I could I felt an
immediate difference after even like a
day or two and then after two weeks I
kept on feeling better and just kept on
implementing more and more of his
protocols into my life and 7 years later
I've been drinking the celery juice in
the heavy metal detox smoothie I have
definitely noticed differences in my
brain and I've reversed about 95% of all
my chronic illnesses it's made a huge
difference in my life just in how I show
up in the world in general
and it's because I feel better for me
medical medium information is really
about empowerment it's about giving you
the sense of control with your own
health and healing when I was really
sick I went to doctors they all told me
I was fine my blood tests were normal
they was just like yeah you're just a
little stressed and in the meantime I
was like riddled with fatigue and pain
in my body it's obviously super
unconventional there's no formal you
know institutional thing that really
recognizes medical medium but if you
want to really heal from something that
people tell you you can't heal from
chances are you can and the chances are
you'll find that information through the
medical medium and you'll get your life
back I had um alterative colitis it's an
inflammation in the gut and you can't do
anything you don't have energy to do
things and you can take part in life
right you cannot do the things you love
and it's hard I've been plant-based
before but then I would still get sick
you know so I when I found Anthony's
information and his books I realized
there's so much more specific
information so many specific tools like
juices specific smoothies right celery
juice heavy metal detox smoothie using
these tools on a daily basis being
consistent
and that just yeah made a huge progress
uh for
me I had s thus I could barely walk I
could only walk like two to four steps
at a time where i' would have to stop it
was excruciating it would sometimes take
10 minutes to get out of bed um I I was
suicidal now I'm going to get weepy and
I don't want to but I was cuz the pain
was was unbearable so anyway I went
online and I looked up natural ways to
heal because I refused Pharmaceuticals I
refused a wheelchair and I stumbled
across the medical medium I I never
heard of him before so I now have all
his books I still eat the way he eats I
I I took out the oil I haven't gone back
to oil in 5 years now I'm great I mean
look at me I walked here and no pain so
for my journey I'm was really sick as
Anthony likes to stay on mattress Island
I was really suffering in a lot of pain
I had been to 30 plus Specialists with
what was Ms Crohn's neurological lime I
can't even tell you I just felt like I
was trying so many things and I wasn't
getting the relief that I needed and one
night I prayed to God and I said God I
can't I I really can't do this anymore
take this away from me and he gave me
like you know a thought he said celery I
said why does that sound familiar and I
watched a documentary with lovely
Anthony and it was heel and I remember
seeing his face and I thought I wonder
if he does consultations I didn't need a
consultations because he wrote those
lovely books him and so took that time
to write those Bibles for us so we can
be our own doctors and bring back you
know our own Sovereign right as human
being to be able to be healthy and to be
able to know and have the answer when I
first started I kind of Dove right into
it and did the 28 day cleanse and that
was amazing you know I had like lupus
rashes on my face that I used to have to
spend $300 on creams to try to get rid
of that went away I think two months
later was off all the thyroid medication
had thyroid disease I was off all
allergy medications I was off all
medications even the hormones um and
when I met with the doctors after the
pandemic there like you're off all your
medications and you know I was supposed
to have hysterectomies during that
period of time I canceled three
hysterectomies all of that healed and
they did the blood work and they're
Blown Away they couldn't believe that my
blood work was better than when I was
actually on the medication and they're
like hey you know how are you doing this
so it's amazing how much was turned
around in such a short period of time I
have a whole list of symptoms I'm still
working on and everything's getting
better but I think the main thing that
heal right away for me was addiction I I
was heavy on drugs and alcohol and
smoker and within the first month maybe
two months I completely all my Cravings
were gone after I started the protocol
so I've been able to go back to school
and now I'm on the path of becoming a
chemical independency counselor so I
could help others so it's also helped me
find purpose and yeah it's
amazing I was trying to go to the
previous events I couldn't because I was
bedridden at the time time I was
hospitalized again I fell for the fourth
time it is normal to feel discouraged
but for the first time I felt a little
bit more at ease because I had this
truth in me having this peace in your
heart is what'll allow you to heal
freedom from knowing the truth and
knowing that I wasn't crazy right
because unfortunately Society has
brainwashed us to not even know we're
deceived right and it's like how can you
heal if you don't know you're in the
position to be able to heal so it gave
me such a sense of relief it validated
all my questions all my Agony and I was
like you know what for the first time I
feel heard and I knew it was going to be
okay from that moment
[Music]
on when I first came across his first
book in July of
2016 uh I had already been searching for
answers for health issues for me and my
family for almost three decades so when
I came across that book it was just
another step in my research to try to
find answers and so when I opened it up
I noticed okay there's no bibliography
there's no footnotes there's no letters
after his name I read the first chapter
and saw where he got his information and
said okay and then read the book it was
the best medical book I'd ever read and
it actually gave answers and I just put
my hands up and said I finally found it
and now I can stop searching and start
learning healing and that's what I did
I've been using the medical medium
information since about 2019 into of
2019 I got the book as a gift for my
birthday and I read the first page and
that was it I was sold I knew this is
truth and I went with it
and everything has helped me in my life
physically mentally spiritually the the
whole thing a lot of depression anxiety
loss um betrayal stuff like that really
took me down for a long time and that's
where all the physcal things started to
happen gained a lot of weight and uh
everything just started to fall apart
when I came across Anthony's information
that's when it's slowly starting to get
my health back and everything just start
to fall into place you know so I've just
been doing more and more and uh you know
when you get the freedom freedom in
health and freedom of your mind you want
more what have you healed personally
from the medical Med
information how much time do you have
um I struggled with a lot of um chronic
illness autoimmune disease in my early
20s I had developed pots and chronic
fatigue and sibo and eczema and the list
can go on I had a lot of neurological
symptoms and I tried so many different
things to heal and in 2018 I found
medical medium information and within 6
months I was medication free and of
course my healing Journey has been
really messy with ups and downs but my
health has been very good thank God and
now um I'm pregnant and you know I get
to do all these things I didn't think my
body was capable of doing so
congratulations thank you I had thyroid
cancer I had my entire thyroid
removed and have been on thyroid
medication for a long time and since I
started medical medium I learned I could
heal that and I've been regrowing my
thyroid and slowly lowering my
medication which my doctors don't
understand and they keep testing me and
they're not they don't believe that it's
happening but it's happening and so
that's just the beginning right and
right now I'm healing even deeper parts
of me and healing my soul
I started when I was nine and I had
something called complex regional pain
syndrome and I couldn't walk and um that
went on for a long time in my life and I
would go in and out a remission and it
was chronic chronic pain deep chronic
pain I have been on mattress Island a
few times in my life but here I am I
feel better than I when I ever did like
in my 20s I mean this is phenomenal I
have been to pain clinics and and I've
been up and down the road with doctors
and needles in my spine and all kinds of
everything nothing nothing nothing
worked till I found this information
medical medium information and as soon
as I read the first paragraph I knew
that this was the
[Music]
answer I found uh Anthony's work about 8
and 1 half years ago I had a long list
of symptoms and things I've been dealing
with for over 30 years I'm a healthcare
practitioner I've been doing so many
things that it either helped me to a
certain degree or not helped at all as
soon as I found this work and delved
into it and started applying it I
haven't looked back I'm 100% in been
doing it all of it um for the eight half
years and uh it's literally changed my
life I know in my heart if I had kept
going the way I was going which was I'm
a chiropractor and a nature path so I
was kind of like a functional medicine
people now but I've been doing it way
before it was called functional medicine
and I just kept hitting a lot of dead
ends and so not only have I seen
Miracles with myself I've seen Miracles
with my patience and to be able to share
this with so many other people and see
them heal and see them change wow it's
that's why I'm here to just say thank
you to him because he's sacrificed a lot
to give us this information and it's
changed my
life so we're back here for the live
stream how are you enjoying this evening
tonight it's been really nice um I
enjoyed all the food and socializing
with everyone yes it's been a really
nice evening meeting Anthony William MH
it's been amazing what was your favorite
part of the evening uh the life blast
yes yes what was that experience like
what did you feel from tonight's light
blast I felt like um like the tingling
in my feet but not after the first one I
think like around the fourth or so I
started feeling like almost like someone
is tapping under my feet yes and then it
went up through my whole body wow wow do
you still feel any of that now or um yes
I still feel a little bit of my
feet yeah incredible what was your
favorite dish this
evening H that's difficult that's a
difficult one
[Music]
um I would say the Pizza the pizza yes
there were two different types of pizza
so which one okay the yeah the one with
the broccoli on so I can't remember what
the name is what is the name of that one
oh my gosh I have I don't know the name
but we can grab a menu behind
us which one is
that let's have a look here it's the
veggie medley vegie ve medley yes yeah I
can't wait to try I'm going to try it
soon yes but I do love the sushi as well
M it's always been my favorite Sushi and
the the tofu the um what the pumpkin
seed tofu inside that's amazing yeah
that one is so good I love that dish did
you like the cookies tonight and the
time tea yes yeah the time tea is my
favorite yeah the cookies was really
tasty as well yeah was there anything
that stood out to you tonight in aw's
lecture
um I like the part about the old souls
where says our our souls are so old and
yeah I feel that just resonated and yes
and did you enjoy being here with the
medical medium Community I loved it yeah
it's been really nice it's been a very
nice evening you make some new friends I
did I did I met someone that was sitting
next to me um from Canada now we chatted
nicely met Amber
so is it great to be in a restaurant
where you don't have to worry about any
of the ingredients and you can just
enjoy this incredibly healing full
course meal I know it's so amazing it's
so amazing to just like sit down and you
can just trust everything you eat
instead of like having to worry you know
like is there something going to be
triggering me or upset my stomach you
know it's really good and how do you
feel after eating all of that yummy food
my stomach feels great I mean it was a
lot of food I couldn't finish everything
it's a lot of food but yeah it's no it
was very good my stomach feels 100% yeah
still feel lightened yes yes well
beautiful thank you so much for talking
to us and sharing your experience I
think we're going to talk to the next
guest here who's ready yes thank you so
much we're going to get the next guest
oh my gosh that pizza looked incredible
tonight now I've eaten the sushi many
times since the menu was launched back
in no and um October and it's just one
of my favorite foods it's great to just
grab on the go and we're so lucky here
in Los Angeles to have these options
here at Cafe Gratitude and the fact that
the heavy metal detox smoothie is on the
menu as well oh my God that's just
amazing we are so so lucky everyone has
just been having the most incredible
night here The Vibes the energy is just
it's off the charts it's it's incredible
and I just love hearing all of these
healing Journeys we're going to talk to
this lady over here hi would you like to
share your experience this evening
you're having fun you're welcome to
stand over here oh no I'm good here
you're good here okay here join us here
in front of the in front of the camera
how's your evening going so far it's
been really fun yeah what was your
favorite part of the
evening I think the entire dinner it was
just really fun you know talking to
Anthony again seeing him and then just
having fun with everyone at my table was
there anything that stood out to you in
aw's lecture this evening
I mean everything like every everyone
can resonate with what he said you know
like everyone went through it and you
know you I kind of got emotional at
times but I was like no I don't want to
get emotional tonight you know because
it just kind of it brings you back to
like what you went through but we move
past it so and then if we encounter any
challenges like we know we have the
tools and we know what to do we have the
resources and how was your experience
with tonight's light
blast it was good it was I definitely
felt it a lot more so yeah I definitely
felt it
like especially like my extremities so
it was good interesting and how has your
journey been with using medical medium
information how have you
hailed it has been interesting because
you definitely take two steps forward
three steps back or the Matrix just
throws things at you too like you know
to try to hold you back in some way or
go after you in some way but I mean
thankfully I have the tools and I've
been able to recover like whatever you
know was thrown at me so but yeah I'm
happy to be here and I thank God every
day I found his information honestly
because I was literally on my hands and
knees like praying like please like help
me like figure something out so like the
right way to heal would you mind and do
you feel comfortable opening up about
some of those symptoms and conditions
you were dealing with yeah a lot of it
was from black mold exposure so I moved
into an apartment that was highly highly
toxic with black mold and it completely
changed just changed everything about
like how my immune system was how my
skin was so it was like eczema really
bad eczema just like weird skin
conditions bad brain fog memory loss
chronic sinusitis so and it just I've
never felt that way this it wasn't
normal
and I just went on a
journey you know to figure out how to
heal naturally cuz I wasn't going to pop
pills that wasn't in my nature and I
spent a lot of money put in a lot of
time and effort and nothing worked until
I found him and I was like this has to
work and I and it did everything made
sense so I just dove in yeah do you have
an encouraging message you would like to
share with the community that's watching
online oh man
I would like to share I mean this is
like a loaded question but I would
say just don't give up I mean every s
really cliche but just don't give up
and just dive deeper into the
information like listen to his older
podcasts they're extremely extremely
powerful and I tell that to people that
I know and that you know they're really
trying to heal and maybe they hadn't
been doing it that long and I tell them
listen to his older podcast literally
just scroll through all the way down he
shares so much information like if you
don't have the energy to like mentally
focus and read just and to just listen
listen to the older ones he shares so
many gems because I found him when we
didn't have all the books out there like
The Liver Rescue and you know the what
um the brain saer one and stuff I'm
trying to think of the other ones oh
yeah cleanse to heal like all we really
had was his first book the uh thyroid
healing celery juice one and then the
living foods but there's so much
information in the older podcast like
literally go through so that's what I
would say and you'll come out on the
other end like I prayed that I would too
like I would see the light and I did
like thank goodness so well thank you so
much for that sharing that opening up
and sharing your healing journey and
also that encouraging message it's been
lovely talking to you this evening yeah
enjoy the rest of the night thank you it
was good talking to you too yeah thank
you so much we're going to talk to our
next guest about their healing Journey
would you like to come over and have a
talk to us how are you enjoying the
evening it was good so far yeah really
cool like interacting with a lot of like
high vibrational people you know yeah
yeah and how did your experience go with
tonight's light blast it was really
interesting you know I this was my first
time doing it so it was very cool just
to like be in the presence of everyone
here you know but yeah it was really
nice was there anything that stood out
to you this evening with aw's
lecture
um I would
say trying to think of like a specific
moment I just feel like a lot of
different things that he said resonated
with me and so I think I just took like
different parts and aspects of what he
said and just took it into my own my own
being yeah how long have you been using
the medical medium information for well
I I learned about it through my mom
actually and so um I've been using like
a lot of wild blueberries like that kind
of stuff um no Dairy I've been cutting
Dairy out which helped my acne a ton um
and obviously that could be hormonal
fluctuations too but I think it just
helped on top of that yeah that's
incredible could you talk a little bit
more about the health issues you were
dealing with prior to using medical
medium information um I would just say I
was a lot more tired more like brain fog
for sure M yeah um acne mood swings
really like bad as well but other than
that that was you know it really helped
a lot yeah and a lot of that's lifted
for you you're saying yeah and I feel
like my energy has vibrated upwards too
so that's really helpful but yeah yeah a
lot of people talk about it being a
healing Journey but also a spiritual one
did you find that the case as well I
think it's all together it's like a
spiritual physical emotional
everything is just completely worldwind
upwards you know yeah do you love coming
to these events and connecting with the
community well this is my first time so
it's been really cool to like connect
again with like more higher vibrational
people and just like feeling out
different energies and all that kind of
stuff yeah you make some friends over
dinner tonight yeah for sure it's really
interesting to see how everyone's passed
and how we all come together from our
past experiences yeah so yeah do you
have any encouraging message you'd like
to share with the people watching at
home um I would just
say your
determination um is really what's going
to get you through it and um yeah just
keep just keep going just keep pushing
you know yeah yeah it's beautiful keep
going yes thank you so much for talking
to us tonight we're going to talk to our
next guest thank you so much and our
next next guest is going to come in
yes we ready
yeah hello are we going to do it
together okay come over this side
here yes
yeah you're good yeah how is your
evening going so
far wow it's amazing yeah I had a really
nice time and the food was great and
everyone is really kind and I just love
the community so much did you have a
favorite dish from this evening oh my
God so the pizza it's extremely
delicious and then the cookies I really
want to have like 20 or 30 cookies
cookies laying down dipping them them in
the th tea and eating them oh my God
they are really good right yeah they
were really amazing I will say
definitely they worked hard yeah they
worked hard to put this together I mean
it's so incredible to be coming to a
pizza party that's healing right yeah
yeah definitely so we eat a lot and but
then we wake up tomorrow and we get more
healed and feel feel feeling better yeah
and uh it's it's it's really cool to see
um yeah we was not able normally to go
to restaurant and all the stuff and now
people they Chronicle sick they have
have the ability to socialize and eat
well and going out yeah they have
ability to come here to Cafe Gratitude
and to also do the cleansers now that
are available here to do at home thank
you so much for the reminder we maybe
tomorrow we have to have to start with
the cleanse yes and what is some of your
favorite highlights from this evening
um I think hearing Anthony speak it like
speaks to my heart and speaks to my soul
because I've just been through so much
and so I think that was definitely one
of the highlights to the night just like
being validated and knowing that you're
not alone and knowing that
like
um people in the community have
experienced the same thing and yeah it's
just a really nice
feeling it's such an incredible
Community do you enjoy connecting with
the community at these events yes the
people are amazing and we had really
nice conversations learn a lot doing uh
sometimes uh notes in my my phone
because uh yeah you learn always
something when you when you communicate
with the cool people um yeah and it's
it's it's such an a really nice pizza
party I was looking here to to close
more of this because it's it's so full
my my stomach right you have to take
care yeah so how was your experience
tonight with the light
blast amazing what what did you
experience what did you feel so I get
like this Goosebumps and uh it Felts it
it goes through so um it's definitely
it's it definitely work the light plus
it's something special especially when
you when you feel it um here uh when you
are here life but I think it's also good
when you when you see it online yeah I
felt like at the very end there was just
this like relief that like released from
my body and it was really really nice to
just feel like completely at
peace yeah that's beautiful do you have
an encouraging message you would like to
share with the community that's watching
[Music]
online um you go first so um what I want
to share so there's always always hope
so it's it doesn't matter in which
position you are right now or your
friend you know um and it's doesn't
matter when the doctors say bad stuff or
or friends say oh it's not getting
better it's that's always a point where
it gets better and where you can heal
and yeah this is what what I what I want
to say it's it's a lot of Hope for for
everyone
here um I think that's great yeah no
it's great um I don't know I think uh I
think you should definitely just
keep reading the books and um keep
reading the living words because um I
think it's easy to Stray From the Path
and think you are healing all the things
that you're healing but there's so much
information to learn and there's so much
information to know and you can never
stop growing from from healing and yeah
I don't know I feel like there's just so
much to learn so just keep learning
and I feel like when you go back and
relist to things people were saying that
they learn or they get a different
message from that say podcast when they
relisten and hear it again a different
message or you know interpret it a
different way and I love that like
you're saying you keep learning and you
keep growing on this journey yeah
definitely definitely there's so much
there's so much and you definitely do
hear something different every time and
even Anthony says like keep listening to
this relisten to it the healing path
like relist to it listen to it again
again there's so many gems and um yeah
you can never you can never stop
learning so it's really nice what are
some of the things that you've healed on
your journey with medical medium
information um I'm still working on
healing a lot of things but I would say
that I've healed um a lot of my
OCD um chronic
fatigue I was like basically living in
on the couch and like in my room for a
really long time so I have like so much
more energy now and I can actually hold
a conversation with people and yeah I've
healed I healed a lot of emotional
trauma things that like I didn't even
think were possible to heal or work
through um so yeah I'm really really
grateful for that and excited to see
like how far I can go with healing yeah
what's next in your healing journey and
Tobias you talk a lot about your recipes
that you like online what are some of
your favorite medical medium recipes and
what is this medical medium glow oh the
so so I think um there's a lot of good
recipes I have to figure it out how how
to make the cookies uh the medical
medium cookies and what is about the
glow so I think when when you when you
get on the morning cleanse that means um
in the morning you start with the lemon
ginger or honey water then after that
you get the celery juice and then a
fresh heavy metal detox smoothie for
sure for sure you get the glow it it's
coming it's it's it's it's shining out
of you so can you give them a famous did
you now did you so yeah the famous did
you know that's how you start your
Instagram videos right yes yes I say
always like did you know you can change
from this to this with this and then I
say maybe with the mm glow routine or
something like this this the way how I
describe the stuff to um get people a
little bit curious and and maybe when
the people get curious try it and then
they think oh wait a wait a second I get
a little bit glow in my face or
somewhere else and uh but it's it's
really working and uh and I was trying
yeah to to to found a word for this and
I think a glow or glow up it's it's a
good expression right for for this what
you experience yeah no I love all your
videos and they are definitely
um what's the word I would say they're
giving enlightening to people but it's
like your videos are so compassionate
and like they're so silly and sweet and
they like make people smile so I love
that one day my English will getting
better and then I get more poetic and
and can explain a little bit more stuff
but yeah that's the way well you're
doing a great job right now you know so
I think you're doing amazing thank you
so we can experience right can um learn
right now with you English while while I
doing this here right so thank you so
much yeah oh well thank you both I'm
glad that you've had such a great great
evening tonight uh I love that you love
the cookies and you might recreate them
and thank you for sharing your medical
medium energy and glow with us yes yes
of course of course thank you we're
going to look for some other guests to
talk to but you know what I think that's
it for tonight I think that's chiao caka
yeah see you later alligator yeah we're
going to wrap up this live stream do you
want to do it with me we're going to
wrap up tonight it has been an
incredible night the energy tonight has
felt oh my gosh
inspiring
phenomenal and glowing glowing we're
going to wrap up this glowing medical
medium event here at Cafe Gratitude the
pizza party night one and we'll be back
tomorrow same time for night two we'll
see you then thanks for tuning in
everyone see you later guys bye bye bye
Chia Chow