How many people you know like pizza? Do
you like pizza? This is a collaboration
between Medical Medium Cafe Gratitude.
Medical Medium pizzas on the menu. The
first of its kind. They've never done a
collaboration with somebody with pizzas.
They're known for their pizzas around
the world. Their pizzas are
unbelievable. They're delicious. You
should come and try them. But also, when
you do, try the Medical Medium pizzas on
the menu because those are on another
level because of Chef Drew and me.
Medical Medium, we work together on the
crust. It's a chickpea crust with potato
and sweet potato. It is so delicious and
so pure and so clean. All of our years
of experience went into these crusts.
That alone is a whole another level. I
love pizzas. I'm all about pizzas. But
the problem is you can't get pizzas out
there in the world too easy that are
really good. There's a lot of oil.
There's a lot of salt. A lot of people
get salted out when they're eating
pizza. These are low sodium,
gluten-free, soyf free, nutree. You
could eat these pizzas every single day
and get that sensation and that
delicious pizza flavor with that
incredible crust and feel good.
What are you most excited about with
this collaboration between Cafe
Gratitude and Medical Medium? The pizza.
Yeah, it's really exciting. Like medical
medium pizza. Hello. I mean, I
personally haven't had pizza in I don't
know how many years. I've been like
dying for some pizza recently. Yes. She
knows. Yeah. Yeah. Are you excited to
try the pizza? Yes. Being on this
lifestyle, a lot of restaurants, like
the most mm friendly thing you can get
is a salad. And I'm like, how many times
can I eat a salad at a restaurant? You
kind of get tired of it. But now the
pizzas, we're going to have it here. And
so I'm so excited to try it out.
Oh my god, this pizza is like beyond.
The pizza was just delicious. The crust
was phenomenal. This pizza had more
flavor and more complex flavor. Like at
home, I can never make it that tasty or
that crunchy. This is really, really
nice. Restaurant quality. Yeah. You
know, the flavors all work together. It
tastes like a pizza.
I think the pizza is a nice treat cuz
it's something we don't get very often
and it's not anything that I can make
myself without a lot of effort. I love
them. I love them. So tasty and so
healthy. It's just with every bite I
feel like, oh, give me more. It's so
delicious. Prior to this, it's not like
I was ever able to order takeout or
anything. Um, so this is a really great
option to have for me to feel like I'm
like partaking in normal life. The pizza
was incredible. I haven't had pizza in
so long and sorry I ate both pieces, but
it was so good. This is the first time
in 9 years where I've gotten to go out
to eat with Lauren and she hasn't had to
bring her own food. That means the world
to see my sister sit down and eat a full
meal and be taken care of and not be
judged. So to me, the food's excellent,
but it's also someone created this
environment where you can feel included
and
seen. It makes me emotional, but it's
beautiful. She deserves that all the
time. But to get it like this is so
special.
How many people love pizza for their
comfort food, but they don't eat it
every single day? Because in the end,
it's not really comforting. But if you
can have pizza every night as a comfort
food and still stay in shape, do your
healing, get nutrients you need, if
that's something you want, you should
try it. And these pizzas taste decadent.
They're gourmet pizzas. here at Cafe
Gratitude. Come on down anytime you get
a chance. This is an amazing special
moment in my life to know that they
collaborated with me, Medical Medium,
two incredible legendary iconic pizzas
now because it's here at this legendary
iconic restaurant. I can't wait for you
guys to try them.
[Music]