we're talking about smells
we're talking about chemicals in the air
we're talking about how much really is
in the air by the way you guys i did an
amazon live check it out because i talk
about air cleaners
so i talk about air cleaners the whole
bit so take take a look at that when you
get a chance it's really cool so you can
see the link is in profile link is in
description the amazon live i just did
let's check it out
when you get a chance because i had all
these air cleaners out and everything
and i was talking about the air cleaners
i had the iq out i had the molecule out
i had the co the co-way out so i had all
these different air cleaners it was
really great so talking about air and
how much people don't realize
what's actually in the air outside and
this isn't about all living fear living
fear breathing living fear of what's in
the air that's not what this is about
this is about just knowing
what you're up against so you can
protect yourself and that's really what
it is so you can protect yourself you
know that's a big deal right there on
its own
you using things to actually support our
immune system right was really good when
you're dealing with things in the air so
i might get a couple of things out talk
about that in a second too good to see
you guys incredible you saw the iq air
thing that i was showing the iq air i've
been using that for 20 years the iq i
showed you guys right
and i showed you the molecule and all
that on the some of you guys just were
at amazon live and saw that yeah it was
a great show people should check it out
when they get a chance the link is in
the description right there amazon live
right
hilarious watching you're laughing
laughing fit i'm still
yeah i'm still trying to get over that
laughing fit
nicholas russell thanks for being there
seriously thanks for being it took over
and i was just paralyzed from it it was
crazy
um thank you for being there yeah on
youtube amazing nicholas on youtube you
guys on tick tock just so you know we're
talking about
what people are up against in the air
what they're dealing with different
smells
so it's not like you can you know if
people are near a beach and they go walk
on the beach
it's like you don't even smell the salt
air anymore people go into a park
and they're taking a walk in the park
they don't smell the fresh air anymore
so much people are completely
blitzed out their
senses are blitzed out
their cranial nerves are blitzed out
they can't smell
anymore
because they can't they don't know what
they're smelling because they're so
drenched in all kinds of toxic things
right
cold right spring says i can't believe
you you would be back laugh out loud i'm
back
i'm back
so
so what happens is that we get so much
scent like fragrances in our system
we're smelling it all the time they're
making sense last longer so there's
detergents that are like extra scented
like extra activated so what they're
doing is they're making
chemical fragrances
where they become activated when you go
near them practically i mean this is
like diabolical
chemical concoctions
where if you touch
whatever was on there like if you touch
that fragrance
if it was an air freshener and sprayed
on a couch and you touch that couch it
blows it up
it blows it up that's how highly toxic
toxic it is so chemical companies the
chemical industry they sit there and
they design all these dangerous
chemicals
and these things are just unchecked and
then they just dump them in products and
dump them in products right
and that's how it works so perfumes and
clones aren't what they used to be from
yesteryear and this is important to know
too right
[Music]
if you're somebody with chronic illness
okay you don't want you don't want to be
using perfumes and clones let's just
break that one so we just it's just a
continuation of the amazon live i just
did
yeah um
yeah so tori said bioplane
you check out that amazon live exactly i
talked about all kinds of stuff right
so
what happens is people don't realize
that perfumes and colognes aren't like
they were a hundred years ago 80 years
ago 60 years ago
they're a lot worse now they're really
dangerous chemical concoctions is what
they are
and people don't realize this and if
anybody's got chronic illness and
they're breathing this in every day
there's people on
instagram
there's people right on facebook
instagram on all the other platforms
that have chronic illness they got all
kinds of problems they got all kinds of
nervous system problems migraines all
these issues and then they're like okay
i'm heading out to go see my friends
right here i'm gonna head out and go see
them i just got that all over me just
now that's fantastic this is great
so
yeah
so um
oh my god
that perfume bottle just exploded
practically
so people don't realize
that when they get
when they get this perfume oh let me
just put some perfume on me here let me
just spray some perfume on me right now
and what they don't realize is is that's
lowering their immune system and
intoxicating them in a really
effective way where it affects their
lives so they can get the migraines
worse worse headaches it can bring on
neurological symptoms if someone has
depression perfume and cologne won't
help that depression it worsens the
depression can help worsen the
depression right
these are things that we have in control
we could be like okay i can stop my
perfumes and clones
i can stop my aftershaves right i can
stop my really bad hair care products
i can pull my air fresheners out of the
wall we have control over those
dangerous chemicals going into us every
day knocking down our immune system
knocking down our immune system
so
there's yeah and look i know you guys
are going to come up with essential oil
thing this is where the whole essential
oil thing comes out like essential oils
essential oil essential oil essential
oils but
check out on rumble i did an essential
oil episode on rumble when you get a
chance we're live on rumble right now
too but
check out on rumble the essential oil
episode i did so you know about that too
because that's not all
just perf you know all fine and dandy
and nothing to worry about there either
so that's an important episode so if you
guys just came on
tick-tock right now we're talking about
we're talking about fragrances we're
talking about chemicals we're talking
about how much chemical scent and smell
that we're breathing in and i talk about
that and cleanse the heel too
right i talk about chemical
sensitivities in cleansing heals there's
a chemical sensitivity section here
check it out when you get a chance
that's in cleanse the heel
i talk about that i talk about like
fragrances
send the candles and all that stuff so
send a candle santa candles is another
one
to be really concerned about
is the scented candles they come in all
shapes and sizes
and
that's something that's really
interesting too so people think they're
health experts of course and they're
like well and you may be a health expert
absolutely but what happens is there's a
lot of people though they're like you
know lighting their scented candles but
they're also into natural health
and they're literally intoxicating the
people around them they're poisoning
their family they're poisoning
themselves with the said the candles
because we're talking about a
compilation of a
thousand chemicals and more
yeah incense is bad too totally crucial
on youtube incense is really bad as well
we're talking about a lot
of chemical concoctions
that are
irritating and damaging to the central
nervous system chemicals are a big one
right now so we're heading to a place
where no one
10 years from now
is going to be able to really smell what
nature smells like anymore those days
are over
because people are going to be coated in
all this stuff they're going to be
coated in fabric softeners detergents
that have scents and fragrances right
they're going to be coated in all of
this
okay so michael h says poisons are
everywhere and we must live in constant
fear aw
we don't we we don't that's not it at
all what it is it's about chronic
illness so if you're somebody with no
chronic illness
okay and you're not struggling with any
kind of symptoms and conditions
and you want to douse yourself in
chemicals until someday those chemicals
take you out
be that person
so if you're not sick with anything and
you want to use all the fabric softeners
and you want to use the detergents with
the fragrances you want to dump perfumes
and clones on you and you want to burn
scented candles and you want to stick
plug-ins in the wall and you want to
cook yourself with all this stuff right
if you want to do that and live your
life fine eventually it'll get you in
the end and you'll be like walking
around dementia and be like this later
on you'll be like
you'll just be that person that walked
out of their house
in their underwear
and you're walking down the street
and all of a sudden a family member has
to call the police
and they have to say my aunt just walked
out of the house she's got dementia we
don't know where she went
and that's what happens you know so that
will happen later on fine you might be
that person you get nothing going on but
when it comes down to chronic illness
when it comes down to neurological
symptoms when it comes down to aches and
pains ticks and spasms chronic fatigue
burning skin
jaw pain neck pain back pain eczema
psoriasis you want to know
about these chemicals and these
fragrances you want to know about them
all
that's really important because it's
it's not about being in fear
it's about protecting yourself so does
it make sense to you where
okay because
i know somebody right
that
they use cologne
lots of it right
lots of it okay
their child
and their pets
have all these problems
and the clone is just like saturating
the house because every time you use it
every day it gets on everything it rubs
on the walls it gets on the furniture it
gets in everything right
right
and so
the the children were getting sick baby
was getting sick
pets were getting sick
right
and
this person got rid of the clone
and everybody started getting better
it's that toxic that toxic and it all
depends on what's happening in your life
you can be that person it doesn't affect
but eventually it will right so
when it comes down to all of these
chemicals it's not like it used to be
these chemicals are a lot more dangerous
because they go deep into your cells
they go deep into your organs and
there's a difference here
it's not like it was years ago okay
we're in a time
cornelius says i lost smell since
december don't don't smell a thing but
get headaches around cleaning products
or perfumes
or perfumes because the reason why is
even though you can't smell the perfume
right perfume perfumes you can't smell
them
they're causing
a problem with your central nervous
system so they cause a problem with your
health it's a prime example but when you
can smell them too you'll even correlate
it that way too
okay
yeah
so
christy i was struggling with chemical
sensitivities before knowing from
anthony its origins thank god i know now
how to protect myself with this
information kristy why don't you just
plug in air fresheners
light some scented candles start get
some new perfumes right no you no way
cause exactly you're so smart
because it's important once you know you
can protect yourself and not have all
that exactly so here's what happens with
the chemicals today and i want to just
i just want to run this by you guys this
is serious stuff
what's in scented candles and
ever since the whole plague started
the scent scenic candle world has
exploded every single person practically
in the united states
and other places around the world almost
every single person decided to buy a
candle or start burning the candles they
had and buy more candles
and so every home and apartment around
the world basically especially in the
u.s they're scented candles now burning
so ever since everybody was kind of like
locked down
in that plague situation
they were just burning scented candles
it was like rituals everybody had them
on their coffee tables they had them in
their bedrooms it just it's the candles
right
they got highly highly intoxicated we've
come to a point where
it's really out of control so what what
is in here what's a chemical what's a
dangerous chemical it's a synthesized
it's synthesized material that was
synthesized off of another material off
of another material off another material
chemicals aren't just they create a
chemical and that's the chemical they
use and that's it they create a chemical
then they mix it with another chemical
create a new chemical mix it with
another chemical create a pneumochemical
and what they do is they create
like a bloodline
of chemicals
that are destructive in nature more
stronger than the last chemical and
stronger than the last chemical and then
that's one of the reasons why it's so
devastating on the system and everything
we're live right now on rumble youtube
facebook getter
twitch
tick tock telegram we're even live on
twitch like twitch
we're live on twitch we're live on
twitch you guys
that's a really cool twitch so i'm
excited about that i'm excited with all
this all
right yep our local hairdresser sprayed
many chemicals on my hair so next time
no what you do is when you get your hair
done
get your hair done you don't have to get
the chemical say look can i not get all
the
all the chemicals can you not spray all
those chemicals on me afterwards like
that's a nice hairstyle we just gave you
let me just
spray all this chemical on you right
it's like when it comes out as chemicals
they're not much different than this
right here it's like basically
look i'm just gonna spray this insects
killer on your on your head okay so let
me just spray this on your head
afterwards
there isn't much different a difference
at all
from pesticides herbicides fungicides
because pesticides are in hair care
products they're in perfumes i'm not
talking about a trace of pesticide i'm
talking about
pesticide
like a certain level of it a certain
amount of it used as an ingredient
purposely that's the difference like
they're like okay we're going to make
this perfume
and we're going to add the ingredients
into this perfume since nobody knows
what they are and we're going to add
actual pesticide and they actually put
real pesticides and that's the whole
point that's why pesticides smell like
perfume people don't realize it
pesticides insecticides lawn chemicals
okay if you've ever
if you ever live near a conventional
farm
where they're spraying everything
they're spraying tomatoes they're
spraying you know whatever it is
zucchini they're spraying whatever it is
if you ever been next to a conventional
farmer they're spraying cabbage
it's perfume
the insecticides are using on all of the
crops are straight perfume you literally
you litter there's no difference between
the person walking by in the street with
the perfume the wind blowing the perfume
off of them and what's in the field
they're one and the same people don't
realize that that's how crazy it is yes
there's differences but they're actually
still connected
check out chuckie elle says i was hoping
he'd be here on twitch
incredible
on twitch awesome yeah no i love twitch
trying to come up with a new new like
dance
with that one it's incredible um kimmer
cool that you have a twitch too
hey awesome twitch
i love it
twitch
all right
every time i say twitch it's like i want
to start twitching
all right okay all right
you guys this is incredible so we're
here we're talking about the damaging
effects of these chemicals so we're
breathing in more toxins than we know
and they're around us every day so the
regular ones are like your fabrics
offenders your detergents right your
household cleaners right your insect
killers right that's the whole thing
your insect killers
right you want to like kill your insects
right
and everything's got a roach right here
everybody's trying to kill everything
that crawls into their house
and they're breathing all that up
breathing it in it's getting in their
organs so where does all the stuff go
it goes inside the liver
that's one place it goes it goes inside
every single organ it goes inside the
lungs it stays in the lungs forever it
goes inside the heart stays in the heart
stays in the nervous system
i mean it's just it it travels all
through the body
and it stays in the body stays in the
brain that's the other place it goes
that's a big deal right there so any
chemicals we're breathing in
stays in the brain forever
it just does
stays in the brain forever unless we get
it out and it's hard to get it out
unless you do the right things
so soph 743 says hey anthony
on twitch again twitch
i gotta get the twitch thing down
which isn't funny because i know people
that suffer from a lot of twitches they
get tons of twitches and spasms but this
is a different twitch i'm doing this is
a twitch dance
so that's different
michelle l
good to see you
michelle you're on twitch
this show you're actually on twitch it's
amazing
oh hey melon says elaine melons on
twitch
games really need that b12 for the
gamers really need that b12 for their
brain yeah let me get that b12 it's so
true they do
they do need to be 12.
exactly
so yeah we're just trying to find that
wall really quick
yep can't find it this is some week man
all right
yeah i'll get in a little bit because
it's true with the b12 which is actually
important though another twitch they're
they're mingo
so you really are on twitch yeah i'm on
twitch bam twitch
i'm on twitch
i actually really like twitch right now
i'm not kidding i'm excited i'm going to
come up with a new twitch dance
it's kind of kind of different than the
robot though
all right
these chemicals get stuck
karen says not funny it's not funny with
the twitching i know i know i got i know
there's a lot of people with a lot of
twitching and spasming and i'm always
worried about them i want them to get
better this medical meme information can
help them
so
but that's not the kind of twitching i'm
doing i'm doing the dance all right you
guys we're live right now
so it's critical for b12
so that's important to know right there
if you guys listen i got a newsletter
video coming out it's about the pancreas
or sundays i mean sundays was about the
pancreas so i'm letting you know so sign
up to the newsletter so you can get
those exclusive videos right
tick tock i got exclusive videos on tick
tock you got to check out when you can
right i posted uh exclusive video on
tick tock about roving body pain that's
moving body pain right
so yeah that's moving body pain
exactly it's vega serve related so i
talk about that on snapchat
i did an exclusive video on snapchat on
colitis you gotta check that one out
when you can on telegram doing exclusive
audio messages and in amazon live today
i talked about air cleaners we're
talking about air quality right now
so make sure you check out the amazon
live i just did because i was showing
everybody air cleaners it was really
cool link is in the description just so
you know
it's a b12 right here when it comes down
to the central nervous system it's
critical
critical to have the b12 you need now
b12 testing
doesn't cut the mustard it doesn't
because they can't tell in a b12 test if
the b12 is entered the nervous system so
i always keep people that i've ever
known like friends and family i keep
them on a lot of b12
and i keep staying like i personally
take a lot of b12 every single day
that's what i do this is the vimergy b12
it's v is in victor
i
am is in mary ergy dot com so
vimergy.com
i'm not sponsored this is the
methylcobalamin in adenosil cobalamin
b12
this is the b12 to use
okay
i don't own the b12 company and i'm not
sponsored but this is the one that i use
and i give friends and family right
so it's one of the defenses
use
against like the chemical world because
if you're gonna be
if your central nervous system is gonna
be under
fire
from all the chemicals from the
fragrances from the scented candles from
the plug-in
fresheners
right from the perfumes colognes from
the mosquito spray falling out of the
sky
you want your your nervous system to
have enough b12 ticks spasms right
twitches burning skin
pain pain in the neck pain in the jaw
trigeminal neuralgia back pain neuron
neuralgia neuropathy right
all these different things people go
through
brain fog
central nervous system issues all of
that like b12 is critical
for all of that
dementia alzheimer's brain fog
anxiety depression depersonalization
in in the problem is people don't have
enough b12 in their system they just
don't it's one of the key things you
have to have
it's really important
suzanne lund says peterson says i'm
taking all the energy supplements that
you recommend and felt that feel great
on youtube
suzanne thank you for being here
incredible you guys just i'm just
showing you like the vimorji as i fall
off the table here just showing you the
bimmer gb12
and i'm not sponsored but that's the
vimergy b12 it's really a great one so
anyway so look
and that's that's the book with the
supplement protocols recommendations in
here supplement dosages for over 200
symptoms conditions that's cleansed to
heal you guys
so what i do when i take b12 every day
i'll just show you right now since we're
talking about the b12 since somebody
brought it up right
so what i do
is i do two dropper fulls
right
i do it twice a day
if i'm under a lot of stress if i'm not
sleeping because i'm working too many
hours if i'm doing 18 hour days 20 hour
days
what i'll do is i'll take a lot more so
when i'm doing 20 hour days
i do four dropper holes twice a day
i'll do six dropper fulls twice a day if
i'm really up against a lot of stress
lots going on in my life
personal life
and professional life right
where i'm working 20 hours a day at the
same time getting kicked in the stomach
i walk around with a kick me sign on my
back just so you know i do
it comes with the territory of hearing a
voice that's age four so walk around
with the kick me sign in the back it's
just what happens you know so when
things are happening in life
b12 is critical for protecting yourself
critical for protecting your nervous
system because it's about the nervous
system
that's a big deal and so whenever so
we're talking about like chemical
fragrances perfumes perfumes fragrance
means
you're not allowed to know what's in
there the reason why
that fragrance
whether it's an air freshener a plug-in
one whether it's a spray one whether
it's a spray bottle one whether it's out
of a can the reason why you're not so
allowed to know what's in in that
fragrance
is because it's highly toxic
if
someone was to fill
a giant
container of that fragrance in there
and you were to dive in there
and take a bath in it
you would die
but when it's in small amounts
you don't die
fast spray it on you
breathe it in
you don't die quick right you breathe it
in
get the laundry going oh i got the
laundry with the extra fragrance scent
in there let me get my laundry out of
there
you know fabric softeners you don't die
quick
right it's a slow death really slow
death right
now if they took all those chemicals
from your fabric softener from your
detergents
from your perfumes from all this stuff
and they put they put it into a big
swimming pool and they pushed you in it
and you decided to take a bath for an
hour in it you would die
you would die
that would be it you would die in the
hole you would die in that in that in
that chemical bath
so but what they do is just put a little
in all these things
and they they kill you that way
right
death by a thousand cuts that's right
jeanette exactly spot on
so and you brought up the beach somebody
brought up the b12 earlier so it's
talking about how that protects the
nervous system and it's one of those
great things
that i use for friends and family it's
like are you on your b12 you guys should
hear because like all the time it's like
this it's like
yeah
you on your b12
good good how much you taking
aunt margaret yeah maggie
you took four dropper holes today good
good
you didn't take it yesterday no you have
to take it every day
you have to okay how's your pain
it's a little better okay good good all
right buy it maggie
it's like that all day long
so it's always like did you take your
b12 are you taking your b12
anyway that's the vimergy just letting
you guys know
just so you know it's a v v is victor i
m e r g dot com it's vmrg.com i'm not
sponsored
not the owner of the company
um okay
so we're we're talking about chemical
chemical products chemical sense and
then there's stuff that is it's out of
our control they drop it out of the sky
so there's all the chemicals are
dropping out of the sky in us all the
time mosquito spray right so that's just
happening all the time they're just
dropping mosquito spray out there they
put billions and trillions and trillions
of genetically modified mosquitoes out
there
and then they drop mosquito spray which
doesn't kill them
because they're still there
they can helicopter all that mosquito
spray over us all the time in every
state in the united states all around
the globe they drop it on everybody
every year
every month
every other week in your town in your
village
whether anybody likes it or not they
drop it
so they're doing is they're like just
doing that
because they're trying to exterminate
mosquitoes
but they never get rid of them
exactly and then we're breathing that in
all the time okay
so yeah when it comes down to b12 levels
it works like this even if your b12
levels show up good
it doesn't mean they're testing your b12
levels in your central nervous system
they can't
check how much b12 is in your vagus
nerves
so let's talk about that for a little
bit
okay
so your brain stem back here okay
this is important to know your brain
stem
all right
okay your brain stem that comes down
right comes down through here
your vagus nerves that come off your
brain stem they can't do a b12 test on
your vagus nerves they can't check your
brain stem to see how much b12 is in
your brain stem they can't check
your
brain
to see how much b12 is in your brain
right but if you're still chronically
sick
and you've got anxiety
depression bipolar ocd depersonalization
right schizophrenia
body pain
burning skin
tingles numbness twitches
by the way we're on twitch you guys now
spasms
okay
right
and
ticks
right
dizziness
vertigo
ringing in the ears tinnitus if you got
all of that or any of it
your central nervous system
needs that b12 so they'll say your b12
levels are fine
but if you got all these conditions or
symptoms
your b12 levels aren't fine it's
critical
to actually
to actually fix things it really is
all right so
you guys we're just covering some
different stuff on chemicals chemical
toxins all the stuff we breathe in
everywhere this doesn't even include
like exhaust and other stuff like that
this doesn't include all the different
things that we're up against all the
time
but we're also up against things that we
can control like perfumes like care care
products like body lotions with all this
stuff in it right hand creams that have
all this chemical in it we can't see
fragrant stuff fragrance laundry
detergent all those different things and
that breaks us down and beats us down
over time
and and really does a number of us on us
you guys i'm gonna head off to ig i'm
going to put telegram on back on and
tick tock back on and i'm going to
instagram
yeah and uh yeah chuck else says heavy
metals can be passed down absolutely
generation to generation to generation
to generation
for sure
check out the amazon live i just did
talking about air cleaners check out my
check out telegram for personal uh
audio messages exclusive audio messages
check out tick tock for exclusive videos
i'm putting out there snapchat i'm on
there now too right check out the video
i just did today on that one you guys
incredible so i'm heading off to ig
turning telegram back on and turning
tick tock back on i'll see you guys in
what a few minutes so just a few minutes
be ready we're going