[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 20 30 years to
wait for answers on PCOS polycystic
ovarian syndrome or anything just
waiting for answers on anything PCOS is
the topic today it's a great one because
it really showcases how research and
science doesn't really know anything and
I say that because they really don't
when it comes down to PCOS they might
know something about how you know a
rocket ship can get into outer space
okay so a space shuttle and a space
station you know we got that kind of
technology and and quite honestly that
technology is probably way behind
compared to it where it would be
actually at this point I mean to the
bottom line or where it's supposed to be
going when it comes down to chronic
illness though research and science fall
short I mean really flat really flat I
mean don't get me wrong research and
science is in in fact amazing in so many
different areas especially especially in
medical
technology as far as medical technolog
is getting better and better and better
and it's still still far far behind in
so many ways but but yet it's Advanced
too and I respect that I mean you break
your leg you break your leg they're
putting bones together better than they
ever did I mean you know you get into a
car accident something happens you get
hurt and there's really some some good
medical technology today it's way better
they just don't take two boards and slap
it on your leg and tyro rope around it
and hope you live or who knows dies so
you know it's not
1850 but you know so we're in a better
place there without a doubt and and you
got to have a lot of respect for that
and there's some incredible surgeons too
incredible surgeons seriously that save
lives save lives all the time um there's
some great internists some great MDS out
there great medical doctors great
functional medical doctors too there's
there's a lot of great great great great
doctor and you know great er er doctors
everything and and don't don't forget
about the nurses actually because um
there's just so many we're blessed to
have the nurses that we have in the
industries and all this is incredible I
I don't want anybody to think I lose
sight of any of that so if you're new to
the show but look we have to be honest
and we can't be in denial we have to be
honest we have to be truthful we have to
be we have to be straight up truthful I
mean this is no joke people suffering is
no joke and and where we are with PCOS
is really really sad frightening sad
chronic and Ill chronic illness in in
science and research with chronic
illness is disastrous including any
chronic illness any chronic illness
science and research is disastrous just
anything pick anything pick Alzheimer's
pick dementia pick anything you can just
randomly go ahead and pick something
it's
disastrous just just so you know just so
you know you can pick lupus pick
anything all right it's just all of it
not only not only do research and
science even doesn't even know what
causes anything out there really doesn't
cause anything and then they and they
throw it into genes and you know which
is what we're going to talk about
PCOS and they throw it into the body
attacking itself theories and just just
to distract us because they don't know
what's going on because it's
embarrassing it's embarrassing at this
point because you have to understand
there's a tremendous amount of
prestige and money
and money and Prestige I'll say it over
and over again and that money and that
Prestige and that schooling and that
that arrogance doesn't want to actually
be mocked mocked because it doesn't have
a true answer for PCOS it doesn't want
to be mocked the industries don't want
to be mocked and the people in the
industries don't want to be mocked they
don't want to be mocked when they don't
have an answer for Lupus they don't have
any real answers for anything you know
I'm just picking random random illnesses
but the point is they don't want to be
mocked that's serious I'm talking I'm
I'm I'm serious about this you have to
understand this it's all about oh how
many studies and oh I've been involved
in peer reviews and no I've graduated to
the best top my class and the best
medical universities I've gotten
everything else and oh no no uh PCOS oh
it's it's it's it's jeans it's jeans no
but luis's body attacking itself it's
autoimmune uh uh ra us autoimmune genes
and it's genetic too
because if you don't have an answer you
don't want all that you did all that you
worked for all that you have all that
entitlement all that whole thing with
bureaucracy in the medical world you
don't want all that mocked and laughed
at so it's better to just throw it on
you it's your fault you got faulty genes
and that's just the way it's going to be
guess what that's not the way it's going
to be because it's not the way it is and
that's not the truth and it's not about
genes it's about not knowing what's
wrong with someone is what the truth is
of what's happening in chronic illness
and everything else so you have to
understand something got tremendous
respect for science and research which
by the way is is all theories because
that's how it works they they they have
a theory they have a theory they base
the theory it's not about math it's not
like ACC counting where the numbers come
out right and that's it it's concrete
you got the numbers and the numbers
that's not science that's not
science so science science is just a
theory you work off the theory and you
hope and outcome goes your way so then
you can publish that outcome and make
the investors happy really important to
understand this because we we walk
around we walk around blind to how it
really works and what's happening and
then we shoot our mouths off like oh oh
you know hey uh those medical medium
books they got no science in them oh no
no no s it's all science if you read the
medical medium books it's all science
it's undiscovered science and it's truth
about what's causing illness and that's
what it is and it gets people really
heated up out there too I noticed it
gets some people heated up when you're
healing tens of thousands of people
through the words from Spirit hundreds
of thousands of people and millions
globally through these books that Spirit
puts out there and people are getting
better and their lives are turning
around it really pisses people off out
there it pisses them off like you don't
even know because the truth is no one's
really supposed to get better that's why
the world is getting sicker and sicker
and sicker because it keeps keeps the
industry going and it keeps the dollars
going it keeps the wheel going around
and you have to know that that's the
where they where they really want it
actually and science and research
doesn't really want to go in the right
direction with chronic illness with
chronic illness the doctors do they want
to but they don't have control over it a
lot of the doctors and lab technicians
don't have control over it I know I talk
to them I talk to them I talk to lab
technicians I talk to doctors I talked
to a lot of people I talked to a lot of
high-profile people all across the globe
I've worked with a lot of extremely
extremely high-profile people globally
and I know how the industries work and
so when it comes down to PCOS this is a
prime example this is a real prime
example of ignorance arrogance
entitlement all put together and then
women suffering with no answers and the
answers they have are are absurd and
insulting and not only insulting
ridiculous and utterly wrong and that's
how it works so you know hey man I just
I can't say enough about all this it's
really frightening it's
disappointing and it's disheartening and
sad and so we're talking about PCOS
today so if you just tuned in or
something like that and and uh if you
just tuned in listen to the show on a
replay and just listen to the beginning
of the show it's important everybody
needs to know how it works they need to
know how it works and as far as about
this show and how it works this the only
show there is in the medical field
alternative and conventional that
doesn't have repackaged or recycled
Theory made to sound like a new
understanding of PCOS or any illness or
disease in this show the information
here doesn't come from medical interest
groups the information here isn't
contaminated with medical funding with
strings attached botched research
investors investing in a guy to have an
outcome to make the investors happy so
they better come up so the thumb gets
pushed on the scale so that we all get
cheated and chronic illness goes nowhere
that's why we're getting sicker and
sicker lobbyist medical lobbyist that's
right it's all just just you wouldn't
believe what goes on internal Kickbacks
persuaded belief systems belief systems
like for instance that hey Croc you know
chalk it up to all to genetics that
belief system will stop the hands of
time from getting anybody better I don't
know if that made sense stop the hands
of time you know what I mean
literally that belief system that it's
all genes halts it's going to halt any
any any movement in chronic illness and
autoimmune disease it's going to Halt it
for a century a century you need to know
this because when you have a belief
system like its genes you will never
look for the truth you'll just it just
money will funnel into jeans and they'll
just be worried about cloning because
they they have sinister sinister
sinister things they're doing with genes
and that's where money is piling in and
piling in piling in and they just say
leave the chronic illness people just
let them die let them die just tell them
its genes and just give them the
steroids and just give them whatever and
just let them suffer and then it can
suffer and if they die they die if they
live they live who cares that's how it
works just so you know up at the top at
the top at the top bar that's how it
works and I feel bad for doctors to have
to be even you know and you know just
just go into the system and they're just
like I didn't and they go in and they
didn't realize their hands are tied and
they're kept busy with all kinds of
jargon
private panels of influencers you
wouldn't believe how that works health
field payoffs or trendy traps none of
that is in the information in the show
it's the only show there is in existence
on the planet and globally that actually
has information it comes from an
untampered Source a clean Source Advance
source and I know what you're thinking
you're thinking wait a minute there's
other Alternative Health show shows out
there what do you mean that
information's not good that information
like I said has all that stuff attached
to it it has the private panel of
influencers in the way back it has the
trendy traps it has all of that both
alternative and conventional medicine
it's the only show that doesn't so this
information is pure gift I was given at
age 4 whether anybody likes it or not I
noticed that people are getting a little
jealous about that it's strange back
when I was younger they weren't jealous
about it they used to line up at the
door at my family's house on Sunday to
get readings when I was 8 n 10 11 12
years old and no one was jealous about
it but I noticed in this internet age
and the way things work right now and I
know how it all goes people are jealous
they're jealous when you have a real
gift just like you have a real gift in
your life I'm I know I know somebody
who's an incredible painter they're
incredible painter maybe you know some
people don't like what they're painting
and think that they're not gifted but
they are there's no question credible
credible painter and and and this person
was telling me person was telling me
that when they were painting years and
years ago there wasn't any jealousy
towards this person's gift and now
there's just like jealousy you know with
with with what this per how great this
person's painting and all that there's a
jealousy there's jealousy the internet
age and everything else this person
can't believe it so whatever gift you
harness or possess because everybody has
a gift you're you know you're going
start seeing jealousy creep up out there
and this is what happens with the
medical field and everything providing
real answers really gets people pissed
off out there and you know Spirit
forewarned me my own family for warned
me when I was a child you know I
remember my father and my mother telling
me look you know uh it's probably not
going to get easier and easier with this
gift out there and I'm just doing the
best I can to get you the information
pick up the medical medium books if you
haven't thyroid healing yes thyroid
healing that book is really really
really cool because every time I open it
and I even just go in there and read
what Spirit had me put in there I just
my head explodes it's like the the Emoji
with the head that blows up it's amazing
and I say that because it's amazing to
help you I talk about PCOS in that book
that's why I'm even bringing it up I got
a little little part in that book PCOS
but we're going into PCOS we're going
into it big time right now so fasten
your seat belts this is no joke this is
a serious serious serious talk about
PCOS and so let's get into it a little
bit let's start
now all
right so symptoms of PCOS or theoretic
symptoms of
PCOS this is how it works let's go into
those a little bit high blood pressure
that's a symptom of PCOS that they look
for high A1C so you know insulin
resistance type two diabeties depression
anxiety acne that's something they look
for
too okay hair growth in strange places
or you know more hair growth than usual
weight gain regular periods hair
loss all these symptoms are these
symptoms of
PCOS are these symptoms of PCOS I mean
this is how ridiculous this is this is
really going to be an eye openening show
so these are the things they look for so
they look for insulin levels they test
you for Diabetes Type 2 diabetes
pre-diabetes that's what they're
concerned about that because they're
thinking people with you know women with
PCOS more prone to
diabetes diabetic issues and are they
are they or is PCOS just something that
they have too and if they didn't have it
would have bet all the women that are
pre-diabetic that don't have PCOS what
about all the women that are
pre-diabetic
that um what about all the women that
are actually diabetic that don't type 2
diabetes and have hair loss and even a
regular periods that don't don't have
PCOS what about all the women that have
we weight gain what about all the women
that have acne there's so much confusion
tied up and wrapped up in here it's
insane okay and that's what I mean it's
like if they really cared about women
the industries really cared about women
they would organize this they would get
people on this they would dump money in
this stuff they would dump money into
helping women and figuring out symptoms
and conditions with women but they don't
because the industries don't care
doctors do doctors care they care about
their own their own women they care
about their wives they care about their
daughters they care about their patients
they do of course they do I'm talking
about above the doctors the doctors
always have their hands tied most of
them anyway um so the deal is is that
there's a theory theory is more more
Androgen hormone levels rising or
increasing that's a a theory so the
theory is that the O the ovaries are
being stimulated to produce a more of a
male hormone so that's a theory that
they have that they look for and then
there's a symptom of O ovaries
collecting pockets of fluid so fluid
filled
cysts fluid filled cysts so follicles
are are forcing fluid to build and grow
and then they got these fluid filed
cysts is that's something they look for
too that's an identification of PCOS so
if a woman has the fluid the fluid
building around the
ovaries and then she has type 22
diabetes and she has something else
going on or she has you know insulin
resistance they package it all together
that these are the symptoms here but
what about the woman who doesn't have
the fluid around the cyst but has
everything else it's just there's a lot
of confusion great
confusion so so science and research
have locked on to one thing they've
locked onto one thing that's interesting
that we're going to cover so it it's
like they touched upon one thing but
it's that it's like you're almost it's
like you're almost there you're almost
there and oh no no you're not you're not
you're not like you're almost there it's
like you know you're going to you're
about to get there and then no it just
not going to
happen it's like it's the let down thing
it's like you know you know talking
about it's non-stop like that the
medical world so science of research
locked down to one Discovery and there's
low grade
inflammation they don't know why they
don't know where of course not cuz who
cares who cares
seriously because research and science
doesn't care if they did all they have
to do is just dig a little deeper and
look a little harder and then you
wouldn't even need me anymore you
wouldn't even need me anymore and maybe
you know what maybe maybe hey that would
be a great thing they had all the
answers for every single illness and
they had all the answers for chronic
illness if I didn't have to constantly
beat out science and research my whole
life 24/7 since I was age four that
probably would be great for me maybe I
could just you know do something with my
life for
once and so anyway the bottom line is
they locked on to lowgrade
inflammation low grade influ so that's
that's important that's important to
understand in the reproductive system so
mystery has
it Eureka low grade inflammation we
don't know what it is spirit and I know
what it is but we don't know what it is
science and research that's how they
look at it but it's there and the theory
is the theory is too that you can get
this other other thing happening liver
inflammation randomly occur occurring
another
Discovery another another discovery that
they're kind of putting together the
dots so they got all these symptoms all
these
conditions okay all these symptoms and
all these conditions and then they
have with that a couple of other things
thrown in there but if if they knew what
the cause was for all these symptoms and
conditions they would have have this
down they would know what's going on
they would know what to do they would
know what it is but the problem is they
don't even know what causes type 2
diabetes they don't even know what
causes type two
diabetes okay that's number one that's
number one they don't know what causes
high blood pressure science and research
doesn't know what causes high blood
pressure meaning someone without a heart
problem they don't know what causes it
they don't know what causes depression
they don't know what causes anxiety so
think about this all the symptoms and
conditions listed as as being part of
PCOS they don't have the cause in
science and research for someone with or
without PCOS someone with or
without um fluid around the ovaries
someone with or without Androgen levels
being uh increasing from the
ovary okay so what I'm saying regardless
or not they don't have answers for high
blood pressure they don't have answers
for high A1C they don't have um science
research doesn't understand depression
have a single answer for depression not
one that makes sense and is real and
legit or anxiety science research has no
idea what causes anxiety and probably
will never no matter what even I could
do a million shows on anxiety I can put
out books on anxiety I probably just
ignore it why thousands and thousands
and tens of thousands recover from their
anxiety and get the right
information okay and the reason why
there's no there's no money in it when
the answer is given to you there's no
money in it there's no there's no all
that stuff that happens I talk about the
beginning of the show acne they don't
know what causes acne science and
research doesn't know what causes acne
just for the record they don't we've
explored it on the show if you're if
you're if you're listener to the show or
if you you know if youve you know you
know the stuff that I put out there then
you know okay they know the cause of
hair growth so so hair growth in random
places or excessive hair growth and
women hurt to its them or you know just
just hair popping up in places they got
an idea and that's the Androgen hormone
so they got that one weight gain they
still don't know I mean they'll just
think it's you know a bad diet and no
exercise or they'll think someone's just
eating too much they'll think someone's
eating too much something blamed on
women
forever ever women aren't allowed to eat
they're not allowed to eat they're still
not allowed to eat because if a if a
woman's eating too much whether it's a
fancy dinner somewhere at a gathering or
whether it's home if if a woman's eating
too much all eyes are on that in this in
this day and age still in this day and
age it's it's unbelievable it's
unbelievable um so hair loss they still
don't know what causes hair loss science
of research has no idea no idea and I
don't care who the doctor is they have
no idea unless they have the right
information that that we've been putting
out spirit and
I okay they don't know what causes the
level of insulin Rising they think it's
sugar they think it's sugar that causes
insulin to
rise that's not true it's not sugar
sugar is not the cause I talked about
that in medical medium book one science
of research um oh face it science of
research doesn't even know what causes
regular heart
disease so this is just and there's
other symptoms too that can be chocked
up to PC there's other symptoms too that
can that can be blamed on
PCOS but science of research doesn't
know what any of symptoms are so I love
when they package them up and they throw
it into a PCOS
bag and meanwhile women all have those
symptoms without any signs of any kind
of ovary
problems without any of that depression
anxiety elevated blood sugar high1 see
you know the whole bit hair loss weight
gain all of that a regular period
periods too including acne all of that
even hair growth without an increase of
Androgen levels without the increase of
Androgen
levels hair growth yeah then what's
causing that what's causing hair hair
growth someone that's not when you're
not detecting Androgen
levels it's a mess it's a hot mess in
the industries it's so bad it's so bad
it's frightening look I have have to
tell you because if I don't tell you
you're just going to walk around and
you're just going to be not know and
they can get sucked into stuff and
that's what happens you can get sucked
into stuff you can get sucked into
stuff and it's frightening I've seen
even the best practitioners the best
doctors in the alternative movement
offering things to people people have
had to come to me they're being offered
things that are entirely opposite of
what they need and what their condition
really is I still see it every single
day it's
unbelievable so in so when it comes down
to PCOS what are they closest to
understanding to anything about PCOS the
lowgrade inflammation that occurs in the
reproductive system now they think
science of research will be just thought
it's a body attacking
itself that's genes and the body
attacking
itself but that's not how it
works at all and that's not right on any
level so they got the low grade
inflammation tag going on and so they're
you're they're on to something they're
actually on to something but it's never
going to go anywhere ever ever ever so
you know 50 years go by the Next
Generation generation Generation
generation three four generations
whatever 60 years goes by three four
generations of women entering puberty or
just in their their young adulthood
developing or getting diagnosed with
PCOS with no answers to come is what's
going to occur and this is a prime
example
so so what do we do what what's going on
with PCS what's happening PCOS has
everything to do with the liver with the
liver so a woman's liver and what's
inside the liver and this is this is
another thing too they see the
inflammation in livers too with women
with PCOS do see that as well so that
occurs so it has everything to do with
the liver it's a big part of it it's
actually a big part of it but it has
everything to do with the reproductive
system too to some degree as far as the
fluid filled the fluid around the O
ovaries the fluid in the fluid around
the ovaries is a virus called the
Epstein bar the Epstein bar is the
common virus for PCOS it is the cause of
PCOS it's what I put in the thyroid book
I had a a thyroid book in front of me
right now I I could read the PCOS
section um so but you should when you
get a chance you
should and Epstein bar is a virus that
enters into the liver very early on it
could it could be passed down from the
family um literally right from birth you
you could get it anywhere you can get it
in
preschool you can get it in daycare you
can get it anywhere a child a baby can
get it it's pretty easy to pick up the
Epstein bar
virus almost everybody has
it as far as in the US also globally
it's not it's it's everywhere so but it
has the potential of of of going after
the ovaries attacking the ovaries that's
the that's what it does it has the
potential of doing that and when it does
that the fluid will will build up around
the ovaries this is from a viral
infection that viral infection prompts
your immune system to be elevated on the
lookout for this virus the immune system
doesn't
attack the
ovaries so your white blood cells can't
attack your
ovaries but they're Mindful and they're
out and about looking for viral material
now there are
antibodies
undiscovered for this ovarian
syndrome okay so so just hear this out
for a second here okay with with
Hashimoto's
thyroiditis which by the
way women with PCOS all get thyroid
problems they all get thyroid problems
because they have the Epstein bar and
the Epstein bars be is is is causes low
thyroid and hyperthyroid it causes low
thyroid hyperthyroid talk about all that
and thyroid healing the epine bar goes
into the thyroid and causes all this so
women with PCOS whether at the very
beginning around puberty or even earlier
or anytime anytime the epine bars in
their system could eventually go after
the thyroid at some point so you you
have to know how that works so with PCOS
I mean the ovarian fluid that going on
there
that's from the virus now you you can't
put all those other symptoms in a PCOS
bag it's wrong to do that they all have
some they have similarities there's
reasons for them all but you can't just
throw them all together and say well
that's what a PCOS person goes through
that's why that's why the PC PCOS a
someone with
PCOS can be skinny and thin someone with
PCOS can be
overweight it depends how much Epstein
bar is inside the
liver and of course Foods matter but the
foods that you're feeding the epine bar
with inside the liver matter so when you
take away certain
foods there could be a big difference to
your weight loss because you're not
feeding the virus so we're going to go
into this a little deeper I mean it's
it's it's little complicated that's but
simple but simple simple simple simple
so what they recommend out there is low
calorie diets meaning low calorie from
carbohydrates so they want you on no
carbohydrates so what they do is they
put women on the same old high-fat diet
they put them on high fat the trendy
high fat diets out there to try to lose
weight they get them exercising some
women lose weight some women gain more
weight some women really just they tire
out they get sick because they got no
sugar at all to run their body they got
no sugar to run their cells they got no
sugar to run their organs their adrenals
collapse and then they run into that
where the high trendy fat diet just
literally destroys them and that happens
all the time with women especially with
low-grade Epstein bar because when
you're dealing with PCOS and you're
dealing with the fluid around the the
fluid filled cysts or the fluid that
actually impacts the ovary when you're
dealing with that you have a viral
infection you have a low grade
inflammation that's causing caused by a
virus now antibodies there's an antibod
that they've discovered that has
something to do with Hashimoto they
haven't discovered all the antibodies
with Hashimoto they've only discovered
one they haven't discovered all the
antibodies there's all kinds of
antibodies running through the body that
the immune system creates that your
white blood cells create the white blood
cells happen to be adjacent and they
happen to be revved up and they happen
to be around the reproductive system
because they're releasing an antibody
that hasn't been discovered by research
and science yet that antibody is
released not to harm the body but to go
after the Epstein bar virus to go after
the Epstein bar virus the science of
researcher discovering you know lab
technicians science of research
discovering there's some inflammation
going on some chronic lowgrade
inflammation but they're not connecting
the dots they have no way of knowing no
way of whatever because we're 100 years
from even knowing anything maybe 20
years from now they'll discover the
antibody and they'll be like okay wait a
minute there an antibody to PCOS but
chances are they might not because
they're passing everything off to
genetic to such a degree that they're
dropping chronic illness like never
before on their agenda so they're just
putting it in the back seat like they've
never done before in history we had this
time in the 80s when when genes didn't
take over as far as as the theory as the
as the Fall Guy and in the 80s they were
moving forward with some research and
science towards chronic illness the
minute they started getting close and
closer and closer started really in the
60s they started getting closer and
closer it was all shut down and pushed
back and genes then then are taking over
and The Chronic and then autoimmune the
body attacking itself took over because
the closer they got to real answers for
women with chronic illness and Men it
was too frightening for the industries
because it meant a tremendous amount of
money
lost tremendous amount of gains lost so
this is serious stuff so on the chronic
illness in the reproductive system it's
the Epstein bar it's a variety of
Epstein bar that tends to go to the
reproductive system a lot of times in wh
with women Epstein bar heads the
reproductive system goes into the uterus
it goes in it it it attacks the ovaries
it heads into different places in the in
the reproductive system this is this
also creates mystery pregnancy problems
miscarriages it's not the thyroid that
causes
miscarriages it's not the ovarian
syndrome PCOS that causes
miscarriages and pregnancy problems it's
the viral infection causing pregnancy
problems Mis miscarriages inability to
become
pregnant and the dysfunction that's
happening with the ovary it's the virus
causing that it's not a mystery it's a
mystery to research and science but it's
not a mystery over
here so it's a virus and just so you
know I've known this since I was a kid
kid because spirit's always known
Advanced information it's not like
Spirit learned this information
yesterday and now hey by the way Anthony
uh I I'm getting information now on PCOS
right here in 200 and whatever we're
in No 7 eight years old someone walked
in front of me with fluid filled cysts
in their ovaries spirit said this is
what it is nothing's changed at all
with the advanced information you're
hearing today than if I was talking to
somebody when I was 9 years
old that's how it's always been so just
so you know what's going on I've never
put that in the book either I should
actually talk about that in the book
because it's a whole thing behind that
you would be just blown away I think I
mean it blows me away when I stand back
and I look and I say spirit I don't know
how you do this
amazing because spirit's amazing now me
I'm just a big pain in the butt okay so
the bottom line is this here we go
understand this so you got an antibody
that's not discovered by science and
research the antibody is trying to go
after the virus so it's trying to do its
job that's what's happening there nobody
knows about it whatever fine you got a
virus that's attacking the ovary causing
fluid the fluid is a weapon is the
ovar resistance it's the resist
resistance that's what the fluid is the
fluid is to try to stop the virus it's
released as if you had the flu in your
throat and mucus was forming to be
released to try to stop the flu virus
the ovaries
releasing mucus the ovaries releasing
mucus that fluid is in
water it's
mucus so the ovar is bleeding
mucus leeching mucus and and and and
around the ovary to stop the virus to
trap the virus to try to shut it down to
try to tangle it up and then they become
cystic sometimes with some women where
it's not just the these bubbly pockets
of mucus instead it's it's more than
that becomes in sometimes the you be you
get the cyst involved
too and Epstein bar creates ovarian
cysts that are not fluid filled to too
it also does that a lot of times with
women they have PCOS they got the fluid
filled stuff and then they get the
ovarian hard cysts later on down the
road too that's always optional with
Epstein
bar so the the the ovies are trying to
protect itself to protect themselves
that's a defense
mechanism at the same time you got an
antibody that has been discovered
floating around trying to get to the
virus to stop it and you got white blood
cells trying to look for the virus to to
tag it it's a lot going on what does
science and research say uh just some
chronic low grade inflammation you eat
too much you better lose weight better
go on a high fat no carb diet um you
know this is
genetic uh you're you know whatever on
and on it goes stupidity stupidity at
the best clinics at the best medical
clinics there are the best conventional
medical clinics there are you would
think they have Godly Godly information
for women to heal with real real
information but no no it's just Earth
Earthly stupid human crap bureaucracy
crap paid for bought just just just you
know thrown on women just just that's
the way it is and it's sad so and and I
I get I get passionate I get emotional
about this for a reason because women
suffer with this like emotionally
mentally not just physically it's all of
it and you know and and and then the
people around them the their family and
you know their spouses and their
partners and just all of it it's it's
there's nothing easy about it so it's
insulting to where we are and how they
treat women with this and how it's done
sure doctors are nice it their hands are
tied it's the industry above them I talk
about always know that
always know that I'm sure there's a some
doctors out there with some bedside man
bad bedside man or sure whatever but I'm
just saying overall it's the industry
the bottom line here is that we have to
do something better so let's cover some
of these other we got to cover some of
these other symptoms too that's what we
need to do acne first of all acne when
you have Epstein bar you also have strep
strep acacus acne is caused by strep
that's what causes acne it gets it's in
the liver goes up through the lymphatic
system then it goes up underneath the
Derma and it sits there sits there and
sits there and it works its way up acne
is what it it acne is Strep women with
PCOS meaning an ovary problem because
they're fighting Epstein
bar have acne because they're going to
have strep too research and science is
so far from that it's unbelievable to
this deg to this degree um irregular
periods of course it can be irregular
periods when you have Epstein bar
reproductive systems go irregular
happens all the time W gain that's the
liver that's the liver causing that
because what happens is for the
reproductive system to be like this
because of the fact that Epstein bar was
present it means you had it your whole
life all the way since childhood the
sluggish liver occurs that sluggish
liver occurs in a lot of women they'll
have one or two varieties of Epstein bar
inside the liver and they'll also have
other gunk in the liver too and the
high-fat diets really burden the liver
too cuz everybody's on a high-fat diet
all the way from bird on all the way
from birth on I mean not birth sorry
after the breast milk which is lowfat
it's high we we we all push high-fat
diet the the human nature does that or
whatever the industries it's all high
fat high fat under the hidden gu of high
protein by the way so the weight gain is
the sluggish stagnant liver that's a
liver problem hence why you can even
have inflammation discovered by science
and research where they discovered
inflammation in the liver and they've
Associated that with PCOS cases because
duh it's the Epstein bar inside the
liver causing the liver to be stagnant
sluggish and
toxic and what happens then is the
weight gain occurs because of the liver
condition this is just some symptoms
same thing with the diabetes that's a
liver condition the diabetes insulin
resistance because your liver runs out
of glucose so it can't protect you
anymore it can't release GL GL the
glucose into your bloodstream to protect
you anymore and then and then when
you're dumping all this high fat into
your body and high fat into your
bloodstream you get insulin resistance
and then when you even eat a piece of
sugar the insulin the insulin resistance
shows itself it shows itself I talked
about this on the diabetes show it's not
the sugar that does it it's all the high
fat and the sluggish liver and the liver
dysfunction same thing with cholesterol
problems it's the liver dysfunction all
because of Epstein
bar that's how it works um I'm just
going over some of these some of these
so the whole bit and then you know
what's really disturbing about the whole
thing with PCOS is the diets that they
recommend for it first of all treatment
birth control that's the treatment oh
birth control there's the treatment
great progestin there's the treatment
great um diabetic drugs there's the
treatment great um you know that that
that's the treatment right there that's
what we have here we are right now what
year we're in where are we and that's
the treatment right there that's the big
big
Discovery that's where science and
research is here's birth control a
steroid to try to suppress your viral
symptoms they don't know that they don't
know that that's trying to suppress
viral symptoms because it's what it is
now I'm not making fun of birth control
I mean I'm not razin on it it's what it
is birth control is it's it's a it's a
variety of steroids it's a certain batch
of steroids it's a certain combination
it's a certain chemical balance of
hormones which are
steroids and the reason why they even
see some results with that is because
when you have a viral infection and a
chronic viral infection steroids tend to
numb it out meaning reduce the
inflammation calm things down so that
everything's not going chaotic and crazy
but research and science doesn't even
acknowledge they don't even know that
that's what they're using it for that's
how backwards we
are and so treatment is really now just
okay you get these trendy clinics
conventional medical clinics with
doctors in there and like okay you got
to go high fat you got to go no carb you
can't get sugar in you we got to get you
exercising here's here's birth control
and this is you're going to have this
the rest of your life you're never going
to you know have babies and you know and
you're going to have to get used to it
we have a counselor here at the clinic
talk to the counselor make appointments
you're spending thousands and thousands
of dollars you didn't even get a real
answer to what the illness is and then
when you try to ask the doctor what is
this doctor says well you know we just
think it's it's
genetic and maybe maybe it even could be
the body attacking itself but probably
just all genetic in this situation and
then you go to your counselor you're
spending all this money all this money
not everybody has health insurance not
everybody has good health insurance some
people have terrible terrible health
insurance some people they can't even
use their health insurance a lot of
people can't because they can't even
meet the the required whatever so it's
like the bottom line is is then you're
just you're just that's it that's it
there you are where we are today with
womenkind I mean come on it's
unbelievable when you think about it
okay so what do we need to do we need to
go after the virus 100% we need to
attack and kill the virus can it work
yes it can work can you get rid of PCOS
yes you can meaning you can get rid of
the ovarian syndrome part of it and you
can get rid of most all other symptoms
too you do all the right stuff one of
the most disastrous things you can do
with PCOS or anybody diagnosed the PCOS
or with diabetes or with any of the
symptoms I talked about
before is eating high fat is eating that
all it does is B bog your liver down
make it worse and worse and worse make
things worse eventually switch your
weight to not losing it anymore because
it's kind of like the ketogenic method
where you take all your sugar away you
eat all this high fat you start losing
weight you exercise and then guess what
you blow up and you gain the most weight
you've ever done in history 5 years
later 3 years later with still having
PCOS still having symptoms still having
to be on everything else so what can you
do you can do something I promise you
you can first thing is first you got to
go on an antiviral protocol you have to
you have to go on an antiviral protocol
talk to your practitioner get somebody
to help you with this okay and you want
to do some cats claw very helpful with
with this because cats claw will go and
start to seek out the cats claws
photochemicals that are poison to
viruses like Epstein bar and quite
frankly poison to strep which causes
acne and and so you know it's the
confusion they don't even understand
because all people with bcos end up with
thyroid problems too it's all kind of in
the it's all part of the Epstein bar and
all these different symptoms occur from
the liver the Epstein bar and the liver
all these different symptoms occur and
everything they just don't even
understand any of this it's amazing so
what comes down to the diet we'll talk
about more about supplements in a minute
too when it comes down to the diet you
want to be lowfat and you want fruit in
your diet they keep fruit away from
women the very thing that heals the
reproductive system the very thing that
can actually give a woman a chance to
have a healthy baby is fruit for the
reproductive system a baby is a fruit is
a fruit of the reproductive system
that's what that it's every flower the
reproductive system is this flower is
what it is and then it gets
pollinated
right and so that's the whole point
that's the whole point and and you have
to eat fruit you need the antioxid since
you need the sugars to feed the
reproductive system but starve out the
virus the Epstein bar virus because
that's what it does the fruit also
restores the glucose glycogen res um
storage banks of the liver so the
adrenals get stronger so the weight
drops that's critical but you got to
keep the fats down low here's the great
disaster about PCOS eggs they tell women
to eat more eggs lots of eggs eggs are
disastrous they feed the epine bar they
make PCOS worse so worse so bad it's
unbelievable it's it's the most
frightening frightening recommendation
is eggs for a woman with PCOS dairy
products cheese they'll leave they'll
leave their the you know they'll leave
the doctor's office going to buy cheese
and the doctor might be like oh no get
hard cheeses though quality hard cheeses
unbelievable and oh be on eggs y be on
high protein make sure lots of chicken
chicken's the worst thing the worst
thing for p PCOS I would consider going
even plant-based with
PCOS at least for a time in your life
for a little while and then or and if
you can't do that you can do a little
chicken but a little bit or a little
because you're not going to make room
for the foods that actually knock out
the Epstein bar and heal the liver so
you can get rid of your your your your
high blood pressure get rid of your high
A1C get rid of your pre-diabetes get rid
of your type 2 diabetes get rid of your
PCOS get rid of your acting get rid of
all of it I would consider you
plant-based for a while it has nothing
to do with my belie system here or there
whatever cuz I don't buy into any belief
system there is it's what's right for
the person what's wrong with them and
what you need to do and what's happening
and with the Epstein bar getting into
the ovary and doing that in the
reproductive system you want to starve
it out and in order to starve it out you
need all the good stuff you want the
heavy metal detox smoothie because he
got the the vimergy barley grass in
there it's got the spirulina it's got
all these the Hawaii spirina it's got
the Atlantic Sea dolls it's got the wild
blueberries it's it's got the cilantro
you pull Metals out of the reproductive
system cuz Metals feed also feed the
Epstein bar and cause it to get stronger
you pull that out of your system you get
that the spirina feeds feeds the ovaries
so they can get stronger so they can
actually fight the virus itself that's
incredibly important you get the cats
claw in you you're going you're going
against Epstein bar so you need the
Eline you need some zinc all you can get
this off the directory meaning the right
cons you know where where to go is the
medical medium website for the directory
I don't sell these but they're there so
you can go and you can know which ones
you get the lysine you get that you get
the vitamin C vitamin C is incredible
for PCOS you get that one there too
that's amazing raspberry Leaf's
incredible for PCOS lots and lots of
nettle Leaf tons and tons of nettle Leaf
is great for PCOS lemon bomb's great for
PCOS these are all great um it's it this
is some of the focus you don't have to
be no fat you can have a little avocado
you can have some hemp seeds you can
have some pumpkin seeds you can have a
few walnuts you can can do things like
that but you have to have enough fruits
and vegetables to help heal the problem
so that means you got to lower the
chicken you got to lower the turkey you
got to lower the red meat whether it's
grass-fed or free range or whatever you
got to lower them because the high fat
content fills up the blood clogs up the
liver the the virus thrives in the liver
when the virus thrives in the liver it's
going to thrive in the reprodu
reproductive system it's going to thrive
in the ovaries and when you have that
you can't even go after it so when the
chronic inflammation that they're
detecting is viral caused your body's
your body is trying to go after this
virus and if you clog up the blood and
everything else in the reproductive
system with high fats and your liver
gets sluggish and it's clogged up with
high fats you can't even go after it and
when you lower your fat and you bring in
more fruits and more salads and more
spinach and lots of cilantro and parsley
and you bring all this in and tomatoes
lots of fresh tomatoes tomatoes are so
incredibly important for the
reproductive system for PCOS you can not
only reduce the fluid levels around the
ovary and drop the cysts and reduce
cysts around the ovaries not only can
you do that but you can also do more
than that you can get rid of diabetes
you can get rid of high blood pressure
cholesterol that could come in the
future high cholesterol you can get rid
of all of that you can get rid of your
acne you can get rid of your hair loss
you can stop the growth of hair in the
wrong places that are happening to women
with that are worried about PCOS and
hair growth you can even turn that
around and you get what you get the
apples in you every day apples you get
peaches when they're out nectarines you
get the the kiwis you get the plums you
get anything like that you get the the
the mangoes you get the the melons you
get the celery juice every single day
which really helps ovaries and
reproductive system the mineral salt
strip down viruses such as EBV kill it
and destroy it you get the celery juice
you get the cucumber juice you get all
of that and in you every day you have
cucumber tomato avocado salads you make
some guacamole you throw some hemp seeds
on your salads you do that you have
cucumbers you have tomatoes you have
celery sticks on your salads throw some
mushrooms if you like mushrooms get some
baby Bellas chop them up throw it on the
salad if you're worried about fungus
mushrooms kill bad fungus in the
intestinal tract it's like versus like
when it comes down to mushrooms get
chaga that's amazing for Epstein bar in
the liver get the vimer chaga mushroom I
love that I use it all the time the
vimer chaga mushroom get that in you it
actually cleans out the liver cleans out
the upsteam bar of the liver and out of
the thyroid and it helps the
reproductive system so you go on the
chaga every single day do a couple
teaspoons of that make a chaga tea make
a you know pour hot water and make a
chaga tea all that's incredible I would
go on some turmeric too and do turmeric
in your juice do the turmeric ginger
shot incredible for
PCOS and then when you got all the
butterleaf lettuce and red leaf lettuce
and you put all your tomatoes on top and
you make this beautiful salad and you
throw your avocado on there and don't
throw eggs on there because that will
feed the virus and make PCOS so much
worse and you don't want to do that if
all this is scary listen to the show
over and over again and get the kind of
like you know stop it and start it again
and try to get the information write it
down if all this is scary and you don't
want to reduce your animal proteins to
once a day cuz I would if you're a big
animal protein person I would reduce it
to once a day if you love chicken and
chicken's all you eat do it once a day
do avocados and salad on the other time
you're supposed to eat and do snacks in
between a handful of nuts your celery
sticks apple slices all the time if you
want some dried fruit you could do a few
raisins or something or whatever and you
can you can do this you can do dates I
would do smoothies banana blueberry
smoothies on top of your wild blue I
would do your wild blueberry smoothie
then later on the day have a banana
blueberry smoothie and you can get rid
of PCOS meaning you can kill off and
start killing off your Epstein bar virus
go get the thyroid healing book and
check out all the supplements right
there all the supplements in the thyroid
healing book and start incorporating
them bring that to your doctor and
practitioner get some answer meaning get
get some help I mean from your doctor to
take those supplements if you want and
start bringing them in because it'll
start killing the Epstein bar behind
PCOS and you know what you do all this
and you're doing a little walking or
you're doing a little light exercise and
you've increased your fruits and
vegetables and you lowered your fat
you're going to get rid of pre-diabetes
you're going to get rid of the ovarian
swelling you're going to get rid of
things and you're going to be able to
have a baby and move forward and start
healing healing healing healing
and it's really critical and having
these answers is so
important and so we're towards the end
of the show now I hope we got some
information um spirit and I got some
information to you so you'll understand
PCOS the best you can and and uh we take
one day at a time I'm always going to do
more shows and more shows about the same
topics as time goes on because you know
it it's good to remind people but we're
going to do new shows too but whatever
listen I stand behind you I love you
guys I love everybody out there that's
listening just know that my heart's with
you you know you're just you're you're
so amazing every one of you and thank
you for all that you've done all that
you struggled with all that you're doing
all that you're learning take one day at
a time I got your back love you dearly
bye