matter if you don't have any symptoms or
conditions you have nothing wrong with
you at least in the moment maybe down
the road you'll have something wrong
with you because everybody's going to
have something wrong with them
regardless of what's going on but
it could be a trigger that you're
sensitive to because there's lots of
triggers out there all over the place
everywhere one of the triggers that's
happening right now for people that's
not good for their health because of
what they're struggling with and
everything else is environmental
disaster air quality stuff going on
fires
fires right
fires that have been saying for years
are not just naturally caused
so and that's a whole other story but
regardless
fires that are happening is a big
problem and it isn't just the smoke
itself
it's the Smoke Plus
so many other things burning within that
fire so it's not just the wood smoke of
the trees and the leaves and the woods
it's more than that it's much more it's
when junk in the woods gets lit up with
it it's when houses get lit up with it
with all that treated lumber
and then it's all of the fire flame
retardants that are dropped over and
over and over again from the sky onto
the fires and that stuff travels
hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of
miles and it's in the air and it's just
white powder that's floating in the air
and it floats endlessly endlessly
endlessly and then we breathe it in so
I'm talking about air quality tools but
I'm going to talk about some other stuff
too because there's lots of triggers
that bring people down and bring their
health down and brings them to such you
know a susceptible place and we don't
want to be so susceptible
we want to be empowered no matter what
we're up against no matter what we're
breathing in no matter what we're seeing
no matter what's going on in our life we
want to be empowered and strengthened
and that's really a critical part of it
anyway you guys
I want to talk a little bit about all of
it I have a PDF
and it's not 99 and it's not 250 dollars
and it's not 39.99 the PDF is free
it costs money to make I had to have a
whole team working on it
it's an incredible PDF
and it's free
free free
because it's not always about the money
it's about making sure you can provide
whatever you can for people so they got
every fighting chance so I wanted to
make sure I do another free pdf
environmental disaster air quality tools
by Anthony William
the medical medium
it's a free download
medicalmedium.com
environmental disaster air quality tools
environmental disasters happen all the
time on this planet
purposely
or not on purpose
causing the air to become polluted and
toxic often from smoke burning and fires
it's not just the smoke itself that
causes harm to our health but also the
chemicals in other toxins that are in
the air
the link is in the profile and the link
is in the description you can download
it free right there right in the link in
the profile description how cool is that
it's not just the smoke itself that
causes harm to our health but also the
chemicals and other toxins that are in
the air
for example when a building Burns there
are countless chemicals that burn and
get into the air or when fire retardants
are sprayed dumped on the fires
endlessly their chemicals in that float
around forever toxic heavy metals are
one of the thing that's in those Flame
retardants
and they become a part of the dust and
smoke that people and animals are all
breathing in all the time you may be
somebody that's like well you know what
I don't need to watch this right now
because I'm not dealing with any kind of
fire stuff but I'm going to talk about
other triggers I'm going to talk about
sensitivities
things that break down our immune system
and make us susceptible
aside from causing a more obvious
breathing and lung issues poor air
quality can lower the immune system what
poor air quality can lower the immune
system and be a trigger to all kinds of
chronic illnesses symptoms and
conditions both in the short term and
long after the environmental disaster or
exposure has occurred so here's the
thing you might be out of the woods by
now maybe you don't smell anything
anymore but then something kind of
develops later
Aftershock it's kind of like that car
accident
that you were in
everything felt fine
you open your car door you got out
you're like wait a minute I think I'm
okay I think I'm all right okay let me
just go find out this person's insurance
information maybe we'll call the police
and have a you know traffic cop out here
and everything's good you go home you
don't need to go to a hospital you go
home and then it hits you as the night
goes on or the next day or two weeks
later
so our immune system can be lowered
triggering chronic illness symptoms
conditions both in the short term and
long after the environmental disaster or
exposure has occurred guys are wondering
what I'm reading reading the free pdf
you can download link is in a profile
link is in the description good to see
you guys by the way
One Way pollutants in the air can be
problematic is because they not only
lower the immune system
yeah
lower the immune system they also
provide food for viruses
that then release neurotoxins and
dermatoxins
mm info has been all about viruses for
years and years and years decades and
now everybody they're a virus genius now
symptoms and conditions such as
headaches and migraines fatigue eczema
psoriasis aches and pain sleep problems
autoimmune disorders brain fog and so
much more a flare-up and worsening of
symptoms and conditions you already have
struggled with or currently struggle
with or the onset of new symptoms and
conditions can occur especially after
heavier prolonged exposure to poor air
quality or if your immune system is
already struggling sounds like a drug
commercial almost like
right look out for side effects
your side effects may be bleeding your
side effects may be
what happens is that people don't
realize what they're dealing with
they're dealing with a lot of different
viruses inside their body low grade
viral issues
bacterial like streptococcus those
things amp up when your immune system
drops so we walk around with our immune
system hopefully intact and strong and
then as our immune system drops and it
gets triggered by chemicals and
pollutants in the air and all that then
viral issues rise up
Dr Fawn says it's true nowadays when you
Google autoimmune disease plus EBV there
are so many articles one to two years
ago it wasn't there four years ago
definitely wasn't there five years ago
no MM info putting it out there
yep
we don't need to be fearful of these
kinds of events out there that happen
and their impact on our health they're
outside of our control
we can't control we can think of fire to
not happen we can try to stop a fire
with our mind
we can stand there on the edge of the
woods and just say fire die down
and we can use every single thing we
have we can use our psychic of power
that powerful psychic abilities we can
try to stop that fire but it doesn't
mean you're going to be able to stop it
that way
some things are going to be out of our
control
and these fires that are started by
evildoers or just started because two
bunny rabbits in the woods
we're rubbing two sticks together and
started a fire
I think this
natural fire disaster that's taken over
thousands upon thousands of countless
Acres was started with two bunny rabbits
that were trying to start the fire by
whittling together two pieces of wood
because they were cold because you
believe everything right
just put it on the news two bunny
rabbits
were chilly that night and they were and
they were rubbing sticks together and
they started the fire that's what our
research has shown
we don't need to be fearful of these
kinds of events
and other events too that happened you
remember Fukushima
yeah what was it 2011 Fukushima all that
radiation heading to the West Coast
heading to California
oh all that radiation particle just
heading to California coast in Hawaii
people in Hawaii would glow in the dark
after that
I just it's unbelievable really when you
think about it
that's why it's critical to do some of
the medical medium tools because to work
on like radiation exposure
I have a friend that lives in Hawaii
and they're still doing my friend is
still in their family are still doing
medical medium tools for anti-radiation
and everything else
because of that whole Fukushima thing
there and it's not like anybody told
everybody in Hawaii like you might want
to leave Hawaii for a little while but
no that's not how it works
we're off the beaten path right now so
hang on we'll get back on the path
we need to be equipped and empowered for
those times when we do have to live with
poor air quality and toxic exposures and
give our bodies the extra care they need
you guys if you just got on here reading
this incredible PDF I printed it out you
can print it out download it for free
it's not 39.99 or anything else it's for
free and it's a killer one it's packed
I'll talk a little bit about what it has
in it but it's jammed jam-packed
I miss you guys so great to be here this
guy gives you
a range of simple and actionable tools
tools you can use when you need them you
can Implement them or choose what
resonates with you and what you can
manage times are tough for many people
on this planet
and we need tools like this which is
great which is great
so I want to make one of the tools if
you guys don't mind
and I might read a little bit more too
if I'm not boring you hopefully I'm not
boring you
I'm at your service I am at your
disposal
today
okay
all right so check this out right honey
lemon ginger water so simple simple easy
like so easy I don't have a grater
so by the way you guys I'm back on tick
tock
it's not my old account it's a new
account
not gonna tell you what happened there
but many of you know
I was the only one that was permanently
banned on there
for no reason
all right but I'm back on Tick Tock so
check me out when you get a chance
because I'm going to be putting some
exclusive content
somebody's gonna say he's not the only
one no no I was the only one
maybe one of the only ones
that
in health the only one in health about
all right so I'm chopping up a little
bit of ginger
supposed to grate it but I'm gonna
finely chop it
tells you when you're doing something
right
you just get so many people upset
everywhere
the more people that get healed
the more you get
all right
enough about me
so I got some chopped up Ginger right
there what I'm gonna do is put it in
here
I'm gonna put it on top of here so let
me just get it into my little strainer
don't use hot water just you know just
regular temperature water
and I will definitely not
and I repeat not
spill it on my PDF I just print it out
so I'm going to let that sleep for 15
minutes that's what you do this is so
simple
but it's powerful
don't underestimate ever
lemon ginger and honey
in water don't underestimate it it's
powerful makes a difference big
difference all right
I want to show you this little trick too
before we talk about that as well first
of all I got my celery juice right here
it's been sitting for a little while
made it earlier you know how it settled
sometimes right we can shake it up
before you drink it celery juice that's
another powerful tool for when you're
dealing with immune system antagonizers
because that's what I call it so not
just air quality issues or immune system
antagonizers but so many other things
are too
and um I love that celery juice for that
it's about keeping our immune system
strong why why even bother keeping our
immune system strong what's the what's
the reason who cares who cares if
everybody's immune system gets dropped
or gets tackled
or starts to break down who cares
we should all care so when our immune
system starts to break down
hits the fan and we have to be
careful we want our immune system nice
and strong we want it to do its job
wanted to conquer Invaders so I'm
letting this steep for a little bit I
want to show you this little trick right
here
now I know there's a lot of people out
there just freaking out about masks
right there's a massive mask War out
there Mass need Master mask right don't
wear masks ever they're killing you
master good Master bad Master's doing
bad bad good bad bad everyone wants to
kill each other
over masks
this is not a freaking mask
so I just want to make that clear
because someone's going to think this is
a mask
and then they're going to want to cancel
aw over that
this is a wet cloth right
so
see doesn't even ring out oh it rings
out a little bit
so it's nice and
nice and good
so what am I doing with this
this is an incredible tool right here
when you're dealing with smoke and smoke
pollutants all that inhalants all that
stuff all the toxins that are in the air
from the fires
right here now somebody
who's really really smart
they believe they're really smart
they're going to say how is this going
to filter smoke
it's thin it's a dish cloth washed towel
whatever washcloth
how is it going to do it what happens is
when you wet it
it swells the cotton
it swells the fabric
and it swells it together like it
spreads it out
so this is important to know
and then when it's wet
the moisture is what captures the flame
retardants the dust the pollution the
sea trails
the whatever
now it's not perfect
by any means some will escape but it
brings it down greatly if you're in a
serious
situation especially if you're running
from the house to the car especially if
you're you know if you're out somewhere
whatever it is and you're stuck in it if
you have a bottle of water and you have
a piece of cloth even a t-shirt in your
car whatever and you wet that it's
really powerful
and so what you can do with this
is you can put it just like this
now what you're doing is you're giving
yourself lots of room in there so you're
making a pocket in there
and those pollutants that smoke that Ash
those flame retardants those chemicals
all of it
start getting trapped
in here
because the moisture is what does it
if this was dry it wouldn't do it
it just would not work the fabric
wouldn't swell
because that's what it does it like
swells itself shut when it's wet
and so as you're breathing you're
pulling in all that stuff through the
water
in the fabric the water is what captures
everything so it has to be moist like
that don't
run towards a fire in the smoke and be
like it doesn't matter I have I have my
wet towel I'm gonna go find some fire
I'm gonna go find somebody's fire pit
then go look over the fire pit and just
like don't do that whatever you do
but
Death By A Thousand Cuts
quiet Roseman says
IG
Death By A Thousand Cuts medical medium
term
used in health regard regarding to our
health
breaking down our immune system breaking
down our body breaking down our organs
all the different cuts out there I can
name so many in a row really quick too
it's not even just stuff like that or
triggers but stuff that's out there that
people are using every day
there's so many triggers out there that
don't help us there's so many different
things that are not that are not helpful
right let's finish making this right
here if you guys don't mind
straining this
okay
210 15 minutes I like 15 minutes
that should be pretty good right there
get a lemon in here I'm gonna squeeze
some lemon in here it's like this
of course I got lemon juice on my PBF
all right and then we're gonna get some
honey in here too
I like doing things live
cut cut gotta edit that we got to do an
edit you guys we gotta edit this
I don't want that on there for everybody
to see
I want it to be perfect
lemon honey ginger water
honey is antimicrobial antibacterial
but it's more than that it's glucose
glucose protects the brain when you're
in fear
it's a glucose it's so easy to get to
the brain
honey goes right to the brain and then
you got all the trace minerals
phytochemical compounds
and the liver too mm info the glucose
that's preserved in the liver
all of that right
the liver helps flush out toxins too
that's what it does the liver helps to
flush out toxins
and then more glucose is used out of
your liver the body needs the glucose
the honey is a great source of glucose
regenerator
storm okay
I like trying to use some different
words right sometimes they're not so
great but they're good enough I think
all right so that's this can I sip this
if you guys don't mind
that's so good ah I love it
love that very much
all right
so I want to go through this PDF a
little bit for a couple of minutes
before I read a little bit more
so what I really like about this PDF is
you got the seven top supplements right
there
and you'll see them I have them out here
seven top supplements four air quality
problems immune system building all of
it you got the propolis right there you
got the B12 you got the zinc you got the
micro C you got the glutathione it's
incredible for detoxification right
there
helps the body to naturally detox bodies
that are sick and filled with garbage
and filled with junk livers that are
sick and filled with garbage and filled
with junk for years decades
and then on top of that we get problems
where all of a sudden we're breathing in
all the fire smoke or breathing in Sea
Trails that's another one all on its own
all the sea trails that were inhaling
and breathing in dumping on us we live
in it it's being you know dropped on us
every day
so I love things like the glutathione
that's the Imaging one you guys know I
endorse these guys the best stuff out
there
and that's the micro C doesn't burn a
hole in your stomach
when someone says vitamin C to me I'm
always just like
vitamin C really yeah yeah I'm on
vitamin C really I hope you're not
burning a hole in your gut
with that ascorbic acid and so I love
about the vermergy micro C it's not all
that ascorbic acid so hard on the
stomach so hard on the intestinal
Linings you know to worry about that
with people
when they're doing vitamin C out there
and they think they got a good vitamin C
and it's just like eek eek so we got the
zinc liquid zinc sulfate where we got
that one we got the B12 we got the
propolis so good all of those immune
system Builders keeping our immune
system strong
and it matters because what happens
after we breathe in toxins and poisons
and environmental junk and garbage and
everything else and sea trails and Flame
retardants and that's just some things
and pesticides herbicides whatever it is
that we're breathing in or taking in
especially if it's burning
whatever it is it drops the immune
system why because our immune cells have
to gobble it up
and that's something people don't
realize that our immune cells have to
eat all the garbage and junk so if
you're breathing in smoke all of the
immune cells in the body are now just
eating smoke that's all it's doing and
then the ball is dropped
that's how it goes wrong it's one thing
to say oh yeah immune system yeah I
learned something the other day you know
the immune system is uh it weakens when
you breathe in fire
I heard some guy talking
um when you breathe in bad stuff your
immune system has a problem right it's
one thing to look at it that way it's
another to know why it's because your
immune cells are eating all of that crap
that was in that smoke that smoke enters
into your body
it's like you know go to a barbecue or
go to a barbecue restaurant and they're
smoking or like yeah we use oak wood to
smoke our pigs and look let's open up
this big old thing
there it is right there we got a whole
half a pig here we got a whole brisket
here we got a whole another half a pig
we got two turkeys here we've got four
chickens down here and we're smoking
this stuff and we got the oak we're
doing the oak logs that's what we do in
our our you know bar at our Grill at our
barbecue
and that smoke enters into every pore
and every single cell in that Pig's body
and in that brisket
in that cow's body
and in those chickens body it enters in
it goes Cuts right through it like no
tomorrow that's what it does
and when we get it on our skin it cuts
through in in us and we get it in our
lungs it cuts through in US
it's like we're feet where it's like
we're smoked pigs you know ready for a
barbecue and
then our immune system has to gobble up
every single bit of it every little
particle it can possibly gobble up every
toxin it can gobble up and that's what
happens is our immune system has to
clean up the mess and then our immune
cells get filled up
and they die
it's not like
they can restore their
their actually ending their life cycle
because of this stuff
so when we get exposure our immune cells
have to eat it all up
and then our immune cells are spent
they're spent it's not like they
recharge many of them eat all that
garbage up
and they die with that stuff
and you can see it and then it leaves
your body inside those dead immune cells
which is really interesting
so
but then we're lowered immune system two
reasons why we have the lowered immune
system one is because our immune system
is working so hard eating all the junk
and garbage that we're breathing in or
getting exposed to
and the other
is
because it's just in the end takes time
to restore immune cells we stay low for
a while when that happens so when we're
exposed to something it could be a week
later two weeks later and we start
getting symptoms and then we're like
wondering why are we getting symptoms
like why am I getting symptoms what did
I do to two weeks ago what happened or
what did I do today is what it is so
people are like what did I do today what
did I do wrong
how come I'm kicked back a couple of
steps how come I don't feel good how
come I feel like I'm three steps back
four steps back what am I doing wrong
right now oh I had a celery juice this
morning maybe it was the celery juice
that did it no it was the fire and the
smoke and the stuff from a month ago
from three weeks ago it was an emotional
experience from a month ago it was from
that breakup from a month ago let's hit
other different let's triggers let's hit
a lot of different triggers let's go
there
here's some common triggers right here
lowers the immune system greatly mold is
one right there all on its own
you're exposed to mold extensive blood
draw I talk about that all the time you
guys right you have a blood test a month
ago and you're and you're literally
feeling that effect a month later talk
about that I'm not against blood tests
you guys know the whole blood draw
information for medical medium it's
really
comprehensive
hey W how important are supplements
while healing
well
let's cover that a little bit
I take supplements I'm under stress
I burn the Midnight Oil I've burned the
candle at both ends I mean that's what I
do
so I use supplements for sure if I was
somebody that was sick
if I had symptoms I would use
supplements
if somebody in my family was sick I
would have them doing supplements but it
depends on what supplements you're
talking about because there's a lot of
supplements out there that are not a
great thing not helpful they have all
those natural flavors in it all that
citric acid in it all the junk and
garbage into really low quality if
that's the case I mean I'm not thrilled
about taking stuff like that I don't
take stuff like that I'm very fortunate
lucky that there's a company out there
that puts the greatest stuff I've ever
seen out there for for people
but overall
if your suffering is struggling you've
got chronic fatigue syndrome you've got
aches and pains you've got brain fog you
got dizziness you've got ringing in the
ear you've got tinnitus you got vertigo
you got skin problems and everything
else
supplements are critical they are
and it all depends like when I say that
I'm not saying that just like hey you
know one size fits all out there just go
find supplements in the world I'm
talking about medical medium protocols
ask your doctor if the right for human
medical needing Protocols are critical
for people who are sick and struggling
for many years and that's why people use
medical meeting information they tried
everything they did that they tried
supplements out there they've tried
diets out there they've tried everything
and they still were sick so it's not
just about the loose term supplements
it's about the right tools The Details
Matter and that's critical supplements
that don't have alcohol in them
supplements that aren't toxic
supplements that aren't hiding
ingredients in them that you shouldn't
be consuming all of that matter so it's
a question that takes a lot of
information a lot of details to answer
it
but straightforward
if you're somebody who's really sick
you've been through hell and back
it's good to know where to start maybe
one or two supplements maybe something
that can be really helpful
and so yeah
The Details Matter David
so let's move through here a little bit
celery juice
that's a detail that matters
um something you know about celery juice
if you mix it with stuff if you're
putting lemon in it you're killing a
part of its power if you're adding water
to it ice you're killing a part of its
power don't add things to your celery
juice
celery juice is anti-viral antibacterial
restores your HCL makes your HCL Rock
Solid over time so you can digest those
proteins break them down kill off
pathogens that's mm info about HCL
killing off pathogens and bacteria and
all of that and
so celery juice if it's used right can
be so helpful for people
there's people out there that only do
celery juice and that's it they do that
one medical medium tool and it's
critical for them
so you guys this is a free pdf
medicalmedium.com I'm going through it a
little bit if you can see this it's not
99 it's not 39 it is free it would cost
money to make worked hard on it I want
you guys to have it for free the link is
in the profile link is in the
description
cucumber juice another great option if
you don't happen to have celery cucumber
juice is another fantastic
healing tool
lemon honey ginger water which I have
right here if you guys don't mind
so good I just couldn't help it heavy
metal detox smoothie
now the lemon honey ginger water when
you drink this healing tonic when you
first wake up it will help your liver
flush out toxins
because when we're breathing in poor air
quality like most of us on the planet
are breathing in poor air quality first
of all all of us on the planet breathe
in poor air quality
all of us I don't care where you are on
this planet
the air is circulating
you're not somewhere where the air
hasn't been somewhere else there's no
such thing
you're not in a dome or a bubble
somewhere where the only area breathing
is in that Dome or bubble
wherever you are on this planet you can
be on a crisp clean fresh Mountain Top
far away from civilization and you can
still be breathing in every single Sea
Trail and dust and garbage and junk and
everything else
easily and not realize it sure it's not
maybe cleaner than being up against that
junk in those pollutants and everything
but still there's nowhere on the planet
right now where you're you are free
from breathing in toxins poor air
quality everywhere on planet Earth I'm
so sorry that I deliver bad news about
that
I can't help it I'm not gonna lie to you
and be like oh
the air quality is only poor here not
here oh where do you live you live out
there oh no air quality is perfect there
not bad
your quality is only bad here that would
be actually ridiculous it's bad
everywhere
heavy metal detox smoothie why heavy
metal detox movie because of the heavy
metals that are in the air sea trails
traveling pesticides DBT
right DBT also poor air quality from
fires remember the two bunny rabbits
that Lit the fire because they were cold
actually the real story is a deer was
playing with a pack of matches
so the deer had little deer hoofs and
was trying to
actually strike a match found a pack of
matches in the woods
you know and then it went up okay
extractor smoothie so back to the heavy
metal smoothie sorry about this it's
there to bring heavy metals out of the
body and other pollutants and toxins out
of the body so the scale gets tipped the
more goes in and doesn't leave us the
dirtier we get inside internally that's
liver included all of it our brain
included
and then the scale is tipped and then
something goes wrong and now we're like
visiting doctors visiting therapists
visiting psychiatrists because no one
really understands about our
neurological symptoms how we got Tremors
at night and our body feels like it's
vibrating and our tongue Wiggles and our
eyeballs feel like they're vibrating and
we have a shooting pain in the back of
the head no matter how many MRIs and we
did all these things right you have all
the stuff next thing you know if you're
at the psychiatrist and you're telling
them that you got all the stuff
and they're like well
take all these drugs
um
but do do what you're got you know
what's right by you and your doctor of
course that's your doctor what's right
for you extractor smoothie I'm very
happy about extractors smoothie is
helping a lot of people out there in the
world right now and that's also in this
PDF this free PDF
extractor smoothie
should never be underestimated it's very
powerful very potent
that's a great one there
um
so then there's the exposure shots also
in here too the toxic heavy metals
exposure shot
the Chemtrails exposure shot the
pesticide herbicide and fungicide
exposure shots
and so much more a couple of tips also I
want to say to you guys is extra leafy
greens that's a great one right there
so extra leafy greens is important
cilantro use it as a leafy green parsley
use it as a leafy green so those are
herbs that I love to use as leafy greens
spinach is a great one right there easy
one two you can do the medical medium
spinach soup you can use spinach in your
salads more spinach is better okay so
lettuces are great too but try to go
with those darker leafy greens and leafy
green herbs arugula parsley cilantro
incredible for detoxifying the body for
grabbing onto pollutants all kinds of
other things that help to carry that out
of the body as well guys free PDF
just wanted to drop that on you guys
so you can download it anytime link is
on the profile link is in the
description
so
medicalmedium.com you can find it there
as well too
so
keep that in mind when you get a chance
it's a great tool has so many great
Tools in it
it's really incredible
so I want to make sure you guys have
these options empowerment is about
having information
and information that can help you heal
strengthen you help power you through
so it's not about fear or anything like
that we don't want to walk into
a storm
because we just don't fear it it's not
that if we have to walk into a storm we
want to know what we can do to support
our body and strengthen it as we're
walking into a storm and that's
important right there all of it
so here's a question right now how long
should we expect to feel detox symptoms
so keep in mind with a lot of people
okay
everybody's different in so many ways
somebody
could think they're having a detox
symptom
but they're dealing with a symptom
so that's important to know right there
somebody could be thinking they're doing
something that's making them detox but
they're not doing something that's
making them detox
keep that in mind too I've seen people
out there in the world right they've
seen people on social media saying
they're detoxing and then they talk
about what they're eating and doing in
them and looking at them like I don't
think you're doing some detoxing with
that right there
they're eating cheese or whatever it is
that they're eating
so there's so much misinformation about
detox I'm gonna do a podcast episode
just letting you know it's a word that's
way overused all the time by everybody
okay and it's way overused by people
outside of the medical medium
information so a lot of people be like
all medical medium does is talk about
detox that's kind of strange because
that's not what medical medium only
talks about so that's kind of a term
that's used out there in the world
throughout the years when someone
doesn't know why someone is sick and
what's happening to them medical name
info cleared the air with that by giving
people
their information that allowed them to
find out why they were sick and why they
were struggling what these symptoms were
and what was happening with their health
that information was critical for people
to heal but detox is thrown into
everything now out there it's also a
term that's used to sell products now so
all you're going to do is hear the word
detox out there
because detox they're just they're
basically aligning detox with products
so everybody you know becomes like a
sales pitch out there with the detox
word so keep that in mind too
but a lot of people don't realize it if
they have a flare up with something or
they were sick with something anyway
they don't realize what's detox or not
that's important to know I'm going to go
into deep Hill on the whole process
about detox a lot of people blame real
symptoms on detox
which is wrong it's not detox it's a
symptom that was already there
that's critical to know too so I'm just
giving you little tidbits about detox
but I see it all the time on social
media I see people saying they're
detoxing and then you're seeing what
they're eating and
then you're like okay
um with what you're eating I don't know
what kind of real detox you're doing
because it's impossible to detox when
you're on nuts and seeds it's impossible
to detox when you're on nut Butters it's
impossible to detox when you're on olive
oil I'm not saying anything these things
are good or bad so don't don't get
scared I'm not saying that also people
blame detox when really they are
emotional because they are not drowning
their emotions out
so a lot of people have emotions that
are surfacing
because they're not suppressing those
emotions with food
so it's it's a tricky situation we can
get into when we're doing Comfort Foods
including vegan Comfort Foods out there
I've seen a lot of intense vegan Comfort
Foods
we can suppress our emotions with eating
no judgment It's Hard Out Here on planet
Earth it's not an easy place to live
and so we can easily suppress our
emotions with food
and that happens a lot with so many
people so once you're taking some of
those Foods away the emotions are just
gonna pour out
and it's like as they're starting to
surface and pour out it's like we've got
to get that food in us we gotta get that
emotional food to suppress it that
comfort food to suppress it
program
understandably so and rightfully so
a lot of people have it really hard they
lean on food completely understand I've
seen this out there it's a normal human
experience and a difficult one for so
many people
but
that alone can create an emotional detox
and that's really intense all on its own
so detoxing is you can't patch it all in
one word like it's detox it's detox it's
detox there's a lot of there's a lot of
people in health that don't know what's
happening with there's a lot of people
that work in the health space they have
clients
and there's a lot of health coaches that
have clients and they don't know why no
disrespect but they don't know why
their client is having a symptom or
their client is having something happen
and so it's so easy just to say you're
detoxing
that's what it is you're detoxing that's
what it is
so
it's kind of easy to do that
I'm not and I'm not judging any health
coach or anybody around that
it's not what I'm doing I'm just saying
it's an easy word
to throw around
and toss about
one that's tossed about way too much in
too many ways too many
too many times so
so is detoxification
you know a real thing yes it is
but it's such
a mixed bag of nuts and there are people
who don't know
what's happening with their body or
inside their body because they haven't
been taught why they're sick and what
their symptoms are and so they'll come
across somebody that just tells them
they're detoxing and it's like uh no
I've seen this with friends I've seen
this people I've known out there
they did not know why they were sick and
somebody told them it's detox it's like
uh no
um
she's dealing with a viral infection
so there's so many different levels of
how it works so I'm just giving you a
couple of tidbits but honestly it's it
takes a podcast episode and we're just
gonna have to jam pack that episode like
to the Tilt because there's so many
details around detox you're critical to
know and critical to understand
basically it's overused
most of the time it's used for the wrong
reasons most of the time it's just a
word to paper over and blanket
something someone doesn't understand
and we have to be careful with that word
detox and it's being used with selling
products right now big time skin
products facial products internal
products body products
hair products
it's just a great term being thrown out
it's being
weaponized so it's another thing too is
the word detox was being weaponized
against kind of infiltrated into the
medical meeting community
it's not that I ever said detox isn't
real or I never talked about detox
before that's not true but it filtered
into the medical mean community and
became like a weapon
and has confused a lot of people
and so that's something that happens too
A lot of times somebody might go through
a serious emotional experience
it lowered their immune system
they had a flare-up
and then someone said it's detox
that's really common
but really you went through an emotional
experience a month ago
and that emotional experience lowered
your immune system now it's time to
actually build that immune system up and
do the right things but someone will say
no it's detox stop everything you're
doing
that's something I've seen a lot and
it's saddening I've seen people move
forward move forward and then they get
exposure to something or an emotional
experience and exposure to something
your immune system drops
they get a little bit of a flare up and
then someone who thinks it knows
everything they'll say oh it's detox
stuff everything and now they're getting
worse because they stopped everything
that was healing them to begin with
because a lot of times when you're going
through something you drown your
people are drowning their feelings and
body with adrenaline and comfort foods
to override it so when we're up against
stress and emotional abuse and emotional
struggles
all of that we drown our bodies with
either adrenaline or adrenaline and food
and we're pumped up with this and we get
really toxic
from all of that and so
a lot of people don't realize and so
detoxing yeah it's a real thing but like
I said it's overused
you know
and you could feel good doing it too you
can you can feel like whoa
um I'm eating all this food and I feel
good and everything else and we're we're
suppressing everything that we're
drowning ourselves with adrenaline from
the comfort food so I just wanna
let me put a little Clarity on that too
when you eat a food that you've reframed
from for a while
because you know the food that food is
probably not helping you you know that
food is probably not that great but you
refrain from that food for a while and
then you eat that food you get an
adrenaline rush
an adrenaline Surge and you get euphoric
from having that food
and so
then you think whoa I just stopped my
detox but really
you just got jacked up on a tremendous
amount of adrenaline
happens all the time I've seen people
with chocolate the war of chocolate they
have like a war with themselves the
chocolate they have a chocolate drawer
saying I like all their chocolate in
here and they know not to have too much
of it because they know they can get so
jacked up from it but they stay away
from that chocolate for a little while
and then they go and they have that
piece of chocolate
they get euphoric and adrenaline floods
them and they're like whoa I just broke
a detox no you didn't break a detox
you're saturated with adrenaline the
cocoa butter the cacao butter any kind
of fat can also saturate our bodies with
adrenaline too that's another thing that
happens chocolate will surge adrenaline
and that gives you the feeling the
euphoric a feeling right between the
caffeine and the adrenaline both
combined and you feel high and you're
like
I don't know why you know that feels so
good I slowed down my detox I stopped my
detox
and then there's chemicals in food and
natural flavors and food the MSG gives
us a feeling too of like a euphoric
addictive feeling that ends up surging
or adrenaline too so when we stay away
from those Foods
we're really feeling
how sick we really are and then when you
bring some of these Foods back in you're
like you get high for a moment you're
like wait a minute I've seen people go
on a massive
a massive Indulgence
where they're just they're just like oh
my God I could eat everything I want now
and I feel good but what you don't see a
month later is they won't post on social
media that they have tanked and they are
feeling crappy again and their food took
them down
you won't see that
coffee and matcha tea same thing a lot
of times you'll see people where they're
actually staying they're they're keeping
to something they're keeping to a
routine they're actually eating good
they're keeping something maybe they're
doing a medical medium 369 for a while
maybe they're taking care of themselves
and they're keeping out the garbage in
the junk right they're keeping out the
trigger foods they're keeping out the
the brain rotting Foods the
troublemakers and they're keeping all
that out and then
they start eating something they're back
to eating a lot of cacao and they're
back to eating something else they're
back to eating pizza whatever it is and
they feel you bork and high and they're
on adrenaline and they feel amazing and
they feel so good and they're like I
should have been eating anything I ever
wanted this is all I needed to do was
just eat what I wanted and all my
problems would be fine I don't know what
I was doing I was detoxing all that time
always detoxing I'm sick of detoxing and
now I'm eating so good I'm eating sorry
eating anything I want
that medical medium was wrong or that
medical medium person was wrong whatever
it is and then like they're shooting out
their posts like I feel good I just
needed to do this I just needed this
meditation and I could eat whatever I
wanted I can just I just need this neuro
realignment tool and I could just eat
what I want
and then what you don't see after you
see all those posts you don't see a
couple months later someone who's back
on all of the medical medium stuff a
morning cleanses the mono cleanses the
heavy metal detox smoothies the 369s
they're back on their celery juice
they're back on all that but they're not
going to go and correct everything
because they're going to look like a
so they're not going to go and and bite
the bullet and go into a post saying you
know what I actually had it wrong and
now I'm back on MM stuff no one corrects
it they never do it they just you never
know what happens to them two months
later
and many people heal and then they go
eat what they want and they get high on
it
and when you get high on it you think
you're just like whoa
and they end up just on what
what they what got them better
they end up on what got them
better we're doing a little detox talk
right now how about what's the chance of
that didn't expect that today
I'm at your disposal that's why and
that's your service
did not expect to be talking so much
about detox
so many people heal with the medical
medium information then go run around
eat what they want
and
end up on everything that got
them better in the first place I had to
say it again because I just like the way
it sounds for some reason
anyway
I want you guys to take care of
yourselves
okay it's all about taking care of
yourselves free pdf it's free no strings
attached
there's no firewall
no pun intended no paywall
nothing you guys it's packed with
information Paco tools do one tool do do
maybe two
ask your doctor what's right for you if
your doctor will let you do any of the
tools in here
ask your doctor what's right for you and
take care of yourself
I
I held back my celery drinking for the
day because I wanted to have a celery
juice
here for today for this for the moment
so that's my celery juice I'm going to
drink this
and you guys I'm proud of all of you
just know that and a shout out to
Germany right now we're doing
a festival and uh proud of everybody
there
truly you guys
um check out my telegram message I'm
doing some more telegram messages coming
up check out my telegram audio messages
when you get a chance I just did one
recently
go to medicalmean.com constantly doing
some incredible stuff with the website
so people have more information and
follow medical medium on Tick Tock if
you can
because we're gonna try it again
we're gonna try it again and maybe I'll
do some of that
comedy stuff on Tick Tock you know if
you guys like that not sure if you guys
like that maybe I'll do a little bit of
that and some other things too but I'm
going to make sure real informational
stuff like everywhere if I put
informational stuff but I'll do some
exclusive stuff for fun
um yeah
right on
and check out the medical meeting
podcast when you get a chance
not sure if you guys have listened to
the medical medium podcast lately
two
get a newsletter because the light blast
will be coming up Spirit of compassion
will provide a light blast
I'm actually really excited about that
to be honest
so get on the newsletter light blasts
will be coming up go to
medicalmedium.com so you can get on that
light blast newsletter
but you got me signed up she got to know
when that light blast is happening and
you got to get on there
last time we had 20 plus thousand people
is all our machine can handle technology
whatever can handle and we had to shut
down the sign ups after one hour less
than one hour
um and we had twenty thousand signed
twenty one thousand signups
for um the weight loss medical medium
white blast I think if we open we're
trying to set up the technology so we
can open The Floodgate and not just have
to shut it down to one hour we can open
up The Floodgate for the light Blast for
multiple hours and we'll probably get 60
or 80 000 people and so forth and that's
what we want to be able to have the
machine ready for a lot of people to get
the light glass
machine meaning technology so that
everybody could be there live and we
could actually pull it off it takes a
lot you guys Moon meditation yep
medical meme podcast at Apple podcast I
see that Moon meditation I have done the
moon meditation recently Lorraine L yes
comedy gold
you got it coming right up does that
match your service I'm excited I want to
do some fun stuff I want to do some
funny stuff but I also want to do some
serious stuff as well
yep all right you guys
God bless you
and see you soon