we're live clubhouse facebook
youtube we are live we're talking about
plant-based versus
animal based the ultimate battle
out there it's what gets in the way of
people healing
are you plant-based if you're
plant-based hey you know don't you're
going to worry about all the
animal-based people if you're
animal-based you're going to worry about
all the plant-based people right
meaning hey look all the plant-based
mamas
they're all starving their little
children they're starving their babies
they're feeding them lettuce
feeding them tomato and lettuce feeding
them a little piece of fruit and they're
starving a protein
they get no protein right all the
plant-based mommies are starving their
children
no protein no nutrition malabsorption
all that bs that was told to
so many plant-based moms right
and then hey the vegans in the
plant-based you know they're not
innocent either okay you're killing all
the animals
you're killing you're destroying the
animals the animals got souls which they
do
you're destroying the animals you're
you're harming the environment
you're you're you're creating the
situation where
you're knocking down the amazon to just
raise cattle
so we're losing our amazon we're losing
our
natural the natural preserves of the
planet right the forests
um the jungles right we're losing all
that
because you guys want to knock it all
down and you guys want to grow
you know you want to raise cattle and
hamburger meat right
so that's the other thing too so there's
this war out there right
which one's right which one's wrong me i
don't care
i don't care who's right or wrong i
don't i don't
i don't i don't care for the fight the
battle because
that's uncool i believe that i believe
that people shouldn't be throwing stones
at each other and yeah they shouldn't be
and they shouldn't be saying all these
terrible things or whatever they're
saying right
because it's a bigger picture than that
right good to see you guys
we're live on facebook live on youtube
live on clubhouse we're live on all
three right now
and but what people don't realize
is that the vegans the plant-based
people
the animal be the animal-based people
all get sick
they all get sick you get sick as a
plant-based person man you go running
for
the hills you go running for the hills
it's like
you're running by the way you guys i'm
making these killer potato
uh wraps and i'm gonna i got lettuce
here
i got all kinds of great stuff so it's
out in the medical medium book
the new addition it's the pizza potato
wrap in salad right right there can you
guys see that there you go
how's that is the lighting a little
leading a little better
right it's a salad wrap today that's
what we're doing it's out of the new
edition an incredible recipe i'm excited
i'm gonna cook with the oven so which
are you guys which one are you guys you
guys plant-based
you guys vegan
are you pescetarian are you vegetarian
no one really cares about them anymore
it's crazy right
no one cares it's i've seen that out
there too they've been phased out are
you
you macrobiotic like what are you right
and
it's all been phased out like it's crazy
how it works but it's true
really it's just animal protein it's
just keto or plant-based
or vegan right plant-based are vegan and
the vegans in the plant-based they
separated
so they separated like everybody wants
to belong i guess
in some place right they want this
belief system right
they want a belief system you know the
vegans are mad at the plant-based people
i didn't even go there
right but it's true because the
plant-based people are still wearing
leather
right they're still they're still
wearing leather shoes
okay so then you got that little war
going on too people like wait a minute
are you vegan
are you plant-based right we're totally
censored today by the way
right across right across the board
we're really censored today
um we can't even get anybody on today
we're so censored
so do you have this whole war that's
happening with vegan and plant-based
the plant-based vegan movement with each
other right and then you got the
animal-based movement
the animal protein movement where the
keto people they get all mad at the
other people who are eating animal
protein so the keto people get all mad
at the other
animal protein people you guys right on
clubhouse you guys
never notice that you guys and and
youtube facebook
and because there's a little bit of a
war going on there
okay the food wars right
the plant versus animal wars right
good to see you dr fong glad you're
coming on yeah sorry about the sensory
yeah no totally it's just been
unbelievable lately it's just getting
worse and worse
so we got we got and who gets hurt the
chronic leo
i don't care about me but who gets hurt
is the chronically ill getting
information and everything else
so but we got the keto people they're
upset at the animal
protein people because the animal
protein people aren't
adhering by the law by the law
of the keto people law right
because wait a minute you're either keto
or you're just eating you know regular
animal protein and then they
start saying maybe you're on a standard
american diet and people like no i'm not
it's not a standard american
diet i'm not doing processed foods i'm
not doing you know
processed foods i'm not doing fast foods
i'm not doing fried greasy foods
but i'm i i guess i'm not all the way
keto
so what am i so but i'm eating clean
right
so the keto people are yelling at the
people who are eating clean people that
are eating like clean diets or yelling
at the keto people
and you've got the vegans yelling at the
plant-based and plant-based yelling at
the vegans and then the pescetarians
they're just kind of like out there like
you know they're sitting out there
somewhere on some island right
pescetarians
you think about that or the vegetarians
who even talks about vegetarians anymore
i mean it's like it's that's a whole
nother thing all in its own it's
you know uh be open-hearted hey good
glad you're on
good to see you um so glad you guys are
coming on and
this is an important talk because you
take your eye off the ball
when you're fighting for something
that isn't really got your back
you're taking your eye off the ball i'm
so busy fighting
i'm so busy being a staunch plant-based
person nothing wrong with that if your
plant-based stay plant-based
if your animal protein staple animal
protein it's fine right
lunelle good to see it's so but but what
happens is we get wrapped up into the
battle
it's the battle right so i'm plant-based
i'm gonna follow all the plant-based
people right
i'm gonna follow the plant-based people
if i'm animal-based i'm gonna follow all
the animal-based people right
but everyone gets sick everyone gets
sick michelle l says we have to keep the
eye on the ball our eye on the ball
right
yeah um so we're vegan saying we cannot
be vegan because we consume
honey uh it is called healing
people right that's another thing too
with the honey yeah first of all
honey is vegan honey is plant-based
right
a bee is an insect really important to
know right there
a bee is not an animal so someone missed
the memo on that whole thing okay
so and and the b doesn't get hurt
so the b doesn't get hurt through that
process okay so that's important to know
right there
right and these bees have been here for
forever on this planet thousands of
years
right providing a source
for animals and humankind you know
but you know i if someone says well what
does anthony williams think
can you be vegan and still have honey
yeah i do i know that's gonna get people
mad
because then all of a sudden the vegans
are gonna be mad at me now oh he's he
doesn't know he's not
he's not woke on that whole thing like
aws not woke about that you know he's
off the mark and if he's off the mark on
the honey thing
i'm not gonna listen to anything the guy
has to talk about i'm not gonna listen
to anything meanwhile
you know they're doing medical medium
information tidbits that got into
all the different diet beliefs out there
right
that because the keto belief system is
now
surviving because it's it's adhering to
medical medium stuff that's how it's
even surviving
because in the old days you went keto
you got sick
real sick keto now was in keto by the
way i want to cover that for a second
before i make these potato wraps these
killer potato wrap salad wraps
um but keto is in keto anymore
that's it okay you eat a tomato
you eat a tomato okay on a keto diet you
can't go into ketosis
there's too much sugar in it there's
sugar in the tomato you there's glucose
in tomato you can't go into keto
you can't go into ketosis you can't go
your body
can't evolve to that process it can't
make that process happen
you eat an avocado as somebody on a keto
diet
and you can't go into ketosis it's not a
keto diet anymore
i mean when you really think about how
much confusion is in the diet world it's
unbelievable
minis are good to see it tonight you
know it's when you think about that
how does that work if you're eating an
avocado which is filled with sugar
should you guys know that you know that
avocado has glucose in it it's a fruit
it's not 100 fat fruit
avocados not it's got some sugar in it
it's got glucose in it
you can't go into ketosis so i'm on a
keto diet i'm doing my avocados no
you're not on a keto diet you're on
what people think is a keto diet but
it's not
it's not because it's got the sugar in
it i'm on a keto diet i'm doing
i'm doing uh almond butter there's sugar
in nuts and seeds
you can't go into ketosis because
there's sugar in nuts and seeds you guys
this is powerful information this is how
you empower yourself
by knowing where you're being tricked
and duped your whole life
you know what you know what if you guys
want
look i'm not against it if you guys want
to be tricked your whole life
if you want to live your life in some
weird
phantom world of misinformation but just
living by misinformation your whole life
i thought our lives are really important
where missing why would you want
to be stopped up and soaked with
misinformation your whole life
and not have the truth and the answers
isn't your life important don't you live
by your truth you live by your truth
right yeah but that's that's where they
trick you in alternative medicine
conventional medicine you get tricked
right because it's someone should just
all of a sudden be like uh
hey um everybody um it's not the keto
diet
it's just now a clean diet
you can be plant-based keto you can be
animal-based keto
but they're not keto the word doesn't
even apply anymore
that's how it works the only way to go
into ketosis
is literally just maybe doing animal
protein by itself and never
having any glucose no lemon no avocado
no tomato no starchy vegetable
not nothing right you just you're doing
just animal protein so you end up
and there's still glucose in meat but
you have a better
chance of heading into you know
ketogenic
state right you have a better chance of
of
reaching that keto ketogenic state right
especially if you're not eating a lot of
meat so
say you don't eat a lot of meat like say
you're a carnivore person
and you're not eating dairy and you're
not you're and you're just eating some
meat
you can go into ketosis if it's not a
lot of meat because if you're starting
to do a lot of meat there's sugar in the
blood
the blood of the animal their sugar it
caramelizes
it's in the it's in the meat it
caramelizes right so what happens is you
guys
when you eat a little bit of meat and
only a little bit of meat that's when
you go and take
you know into ketosis that's when you
can do it
but why doesn't anybody straighten out
all this misinformation
why is the world it's like the matrix or
something right
just everybody living this phantom
misinformation
place and nothing gets fixed and nothing
gets corrected
you can have all these fancy tv shows
you can have all this information on the
internet you can have all these articles
on the internet
you can have all these interviews all
these podcast doctors and nothing is
correct
nothing gets fixed it's almost like
it's it's yeah it's the matrix that's
what it is
in in natural health and conventional
health right
so um so paula torres says this is
nonsense i was vegetarian for 20 years
and it was
the worst thing for my body try am i
telling you to be vegetarian
i'm confused tried medical medium 2 it's
nonsense
at the bottom what affects everything is
genetics
read gene keys so okay so paula
so you just think our genes went all bad
in the last 20 years
our jeans went all bad in the last 25
years
so everything was going fine and now we
got the worst chronic illness ever
before in the history of humankind right
now
and i guess your genes all went bad in
the last 20 years so that's what you're
chalking it off to be
just so you know the whole it's your
genes comes from a theory that it's your
body attacking itself did you know that
like it's cause unknown do you know why
they came up with the word genes
do you know why the gene theory now
paula remember this it's called the gene
theory it's inconclusive
there's no facts there's no study that
proves it's your genes it's inconclusive
so
here you are already you're sitting here
you're
you're spouting out inconclusive stuff
like cause
unknown so they just say it's genes
right
but you might not be able to handle this
truth so paula
you might not be able to handle this
truth and i'm kind of wondering what mm
did you try
because there's a thousand different
protocols to customize for everybody's
problems
for people who are animal protein people
who are plant-based
people who are anything it's there for
you to heal
so i'm starting to scratch my head right
now paul and i'm wondering
what were you doing because huh um
yeah well the phone's ringing too so i
mean
all i know is
hello yeah i'm a fly uh-huh
guy buzz
annoying yeah i know yeah i'm on the
wall right now yeah there's paula
you see paula uh-huh uh-huh
yeah what's she doing now uh-huh um
yeah i know i see you're eating it yeah
i don't know what medical medium
protocol paul is on
because uh i didn't know caffeine was in
the protocol
uh-huh yeah i didn't know chocolate bars
were in the
protocol do you see the chocolate bar
uh-huh i'm gonna leave i'm gonna i'm
gonna
i'm gonna okay i can't you know what
there's so many things i'm seeing
there's a lot of different things yeah
no definitely not medical medium
protocol
uh-huh lots of fat too yeah
apple cider vinegar uh-huh yeah on
yep on the salad some eggs too
yeah if you want to get better us
flies know that medical medium says you
got to take out the eggs
yeah i know vegetarian always eat eggs
they do
yep okay this is huh
yeah i'm gonna fly i'm gonna fly away
this is
i gotta get out of this house uh-huh
yeah i gotta get out of this house it's
a mad house
[Music]
what happens is that what people don't
realize is what are
what are what what's when someone says i
did mm doesn't work
it's all jeans right what do you mean
did you take out all the fats is your
perfumes colognes is the air fresheners
gone
are you lighting scented candles you can
be doing medical medium stuff and you
got scented candles burning and you
ain't getting better
because you might be that one person
that's chemical sensitive and there's a
different protocol for that
right chris good to see you and so
and that what people don't realize right
how long did someone try medical medium
were they doing 32 ounces of celery
juice
every morning or not were they doing the
spinach soup every day were they keeping
it fat were they
keeping the fat free were they doing 28
day cleanse were they doing the 369
cleanse advance for someone who's really
sick
were they mono eating because they have
all kinds of digestive problems and
chemical sensitivities
and food sensitivities were they mono
eating which is
medical medium protocols right and did
they do the 369 cleanse over and over
again to get out of that place of health
so they can heal
and did they do 64 ounces of celery
juice because they needed that to heal
like what where did they go and what
about supplement protocols
were they doing vimergy stuff
or another or traditional medicinals
were they doing a company that doesn't
have the alcohol natural flavors the msg
what were they doing were they doing
somebody else's supplements out in the
world where there's alcohol in there and
other company supplements out there it's
alcohol i'm not sponsored by
them it's the best stuff right were they
doing nutritional yeast
was that in the works right were they
having a glass of wine once in a while
with their friends
how what was happening and what is wrong
how do you heal how do you
heal right it's hard it's hard to hear
this i know for a lot of people the
truth is really hard
and you know sometimes you and what new
medical treatments is the person doing
they're doing a lot of antibiotics are
they doing a new antibiotic a medical
treatment a new
heavy duty antibiotic medical treatment
right
are they doing that okay so what else is
happening
all these things matter and they add up
they add up how much cacao how much
nutritional yeast how much acv
right did they do the bentonite clay did
they do some kind of zeolite did they do
what are they doing that isn't helping
it's not beneficial are they doing
corella
and you got to think about this i want
you guys to be your own detectives
own detectives i really really got to a
point
in the la the last 30 years especially
with social media recently when someone
says i tried on them and it didn't work
because that i'm scratching my head
really you tried mm because did you do
all the different dosages and
supplements in the book like all the
doses
did you use the stuff that was all
friendly instead of stuff that's toxic
right how long did you do it what also
what else are you doing and mixing in in
there
what foods are you doing are you doing
pizza on friday nights is anybody doing
pizza on friday nights right
are you doing that because that's
another one right there that's a head
scratch roll on its own
is the pizza happening on friday night
is it happening on saturday night
what about eggs you didn't have any eggs
in there huh right
dairy products at all i'm not shaming
anybody
it's just that if you want to go all the
way
don't throw mmm under the bus
because you didn't do your homework
don't throw a medical medium under the
bus
so that 10 other people say oh that
person tried mm i better not ever try it
so let me just stay sick the rest of my
life
because you'll send somebody else
packing and that person packing
up their belongings and going on the
road going on the road to musical chairs
and guessing games
you'll send them on that road for the
next five years
because they got thrown because they
believed
you were doing a real medical medium
protocol
doing it right doing it the way you
needed to do it
and then you just sent somebody on their
way
see you later alligator you've been sick
for another four five
six seven years before you learn what
viruses are causing your problems with
bacteria
causing your problems about the toxic
heavy metals about all the things to
avoid
and then you learn i should have been
doing the heavy metal detox smoothie
long enough i should have been doing the
celery juice a little bit long enough i
should have been doing spinach soups
i should have done the anti-radiation
tea i should have done the things that i
needed to do
i should have done use the right
ingredients and not
hpp i should have picked a celery juice
that was freshly juiced and not
high pressure pasteurization because you
can't get batter from that
right so i'm i'm just giving you the low
down
of how it works so i actually giving
good to see
i'm scratching my head when i hear that
one that's a funny one to me
so um you guys we're making food we
gotta do this
we're talking about plant-based versus
animal-based
this is a really incredibly important
topic because you can get wrapped
up in the belief systems and lose your
chance to heal
i believe in plant-based i believe in
vegan
i believe in animal protein if someone
wants to be on animal protein okay
because i've come i've come from a place
where spirit of compassion
has told me that it's not the person's
fault wherever they are spiritually
right
it's not the person's fault if they make
mistakes
right it's not the person's fault
of why they're even sick we have to not
pull the blame game on the person
we instead have to give the people the
tools and the truth
and then when they have that in their
hands they have a chance to heal and
move forward let's start making this
i'm excited you guys so
and basically it's about having a choice
i mean don't you guys want a choice
it's about having a choice you want to
be able to
be able to make that choice to
make a decision so listen if you're
animal protein you got to do it right
to why you're sick if you're plant based
if you're vegan you've got to do it
right to why you're sick
knowing why you're sick is part of you
guys on clubhouse knowing why you're
sick
is part of it it's a big part of it then
knowing what to do
the tools and how to do it is the other
part of it right
same thing you guys on facebook and uh
youtube you guys i got some steamed
potatoes right here
in this bowl i don't know if you can see
that is the lighting any better
i know that someone's like the lighting
i thought lighting was good today i was
checking it out it's like you know what
this
this lighting looks good for today i
think we might be able to see
better um i'm putting some potatoes in
here
so i'm making these potato like um
wraps right and let's see if i can do a
good job at it i really don't know
you know you guys know
how it works we're live this isn't a
studio
performance pre-recorded where
everything's perfect and you clip and
edit and then you redo it if something
didn't go right
i slap the stuff together and we just
pray
we just pray it's gonna go it's gonna go
good
um good to see you guys coming on
so i'm actually i got some potatoes in
here
i'm gonna put some maple syrup two
teaspoons of maple syrup in here
okay there we go
got two teaspoons of maple syrup which
is fun
right you have a little bit of garlic
powder in here too
can you guys see this yet
and a little bit of onion powder in here
as well
right
okay i'm gonna
give this a whirl
so let's do that all right i think i got
it
this is like making batter it's like
making a batter you know
i'm going to give it a pulse
one thing that we have whether you're
vegan or your animal protein there's a
serious emotional attachment to food
we have emotional attachments to food
this is something we all
battle and if you've ever heard somebody
say i don't think about food i don't
have any emotional attachments to food
i live my life i'm i'm all about living
life
not living for eating you know i live
for living
i don't live to eat right there's people
out there they'll say that and
um just so you know they're really just
they're really they're really not
totally honest or they're completely
unaware
of really what's happening because
everybody thinks about food
if you took away the food they like to
eat they would freak out like you never
would believe
right so there's people that are like
you know i eat when i'm hungry
i don't think about it it doesn't matter
i'm not thinking i'm not
thinking about um i'm not thinking about
what i'm eating i'm not it doesn't
matter i just live my life you guys all
you suckers just worry about your food
okay
all you all you losers just worry about
your food you're worried about what
you're eating you're worried about what
you're putting in your mouth
you're worried about how like every
minute is about food right
they'll make you feel that way they'll
make you feel that way they'll make you
feel
like you're just all consumed you got
the eating disorder
you guys got the eating disorder it's
you guys
all you guys that care about your food
right you're orthorexic you got eating
disorders you're worried about food
every second
we're living our life we ain't worried
about food one bit no one's worried
about food
we're living our life we're doing what
we want to do i'm just moving this
around it's almost done just give it one
quick whirl
and the casino don't buy into that
that's a trick
to trick on social media too that's an
actual trick
that's to make someone that's to make
someone this is done that's
to make someone feel like they got
something over you
right you're out of control you're not
in control they're in control they're in
control of their emotions they're in
control of what they're eating
they're just living their life right you
know that's the vibe they put out right
you're the one that's a mess
you have to go to the health food store
you have to get the right food you got
to get the right everything
you're worried about your healing you're
worried about all this and
that's a game being played and you'll
play you'll see that out there
so you see some people they act like
they got it all together on youtube or
somewhere else and it's like this is how
this is what i eat and um and i really
don't care what i eat i just eat when i
feel like it and they pull that thing
and
that's a trick right there just letting
you guys know and it's a good trick too
because it can get you it can get you
believing that for some reason you're
you know you're the one that is like
worried about your food every minute
whether you're keto or your or your
plant-based
that's another trick that's happening
out there
so i'm gonna make a couple of these this
is like a batter right this is the maple
syrup
and the potato the steamed potato but i
gave it a blend
um and so i'm going to throw this in the
oven in a little bit but first i'm going
to prepare a couple of them
we've got lots to talk about while we're
doing this so
just bear with me let's get some of this
batter out
and the batter is just steamed potato so
we're not using a batter right
now why do i like recipes like this you
guys
because first of all there's no gluten
in here
right gluten feeds the bugs inside of us
you're sick
you're sick right and
if you're sick with anything there's
some buggies going on
there's some buggies at hand yep there's
some buggies at work
okay just giving you the 4-1-1 right
there if you're if you got a problem you
got a complaint you're at the doctor's
office
there's some buggies going on right
keep that in mind that's how it works
so first of all i'm just going to make
this tortilla right here
um let's see how that works here so what
i'm going to do is
i'm going to make a wrap and this wrap
is going to be
this wrap is going to be um
you got to keep the spoon kind of moist
so i'm going to just do this a little
bit and i'm making a potato
apparently potato pizza you can call it
a potato wrap you can call it a potato
pizza right
that's what i'm doing here and i'm just
gonna flatten this out a little bit
i'm going to try to get some shape to it
if i can
god willing there we go
kind of can shape it a little bit right
and then flatten it out more
you don't want it so thick
right you don't want it so thick but you
don't want it
so thin so there's this there's this you
know way you can have this right
i got the oven preset it's preheating
right now roughly around
400 i got a little lump right there
it's 200 celsius right
i think
all right there we go so this is one
wrap that's coming together nice
let's make another one
i want i don't want anybody left out of
the whole keto thing i wasn't ranking on
keto that's not what i'm doing i'm just
telling people you guys aren't on keto
you're not going into ketosis it's not
possible you guys got carbs in there and
you don't know it
but no one's fixing that like no one
corrects anything
right details matter and hey hey
maybe the details don't matter so much
if you're not sick
right maybe it doesn't matter so much
just live your life right
you're not sick but when you're sick
if you're sick those details mean
everything
that's make or break that's you're gonna
that's gonna be the point of like are
you gonna heal or not
do or die right
thrive or or not thrive
that's what matters the details make a
difference on
all of that think about that a little
bit right
every little bit counts when it comes
down to healing
so i'm going to add a little bit more
i'm making another shell
or another potato crust for this right
put a couple teaspoons of maple syrup in
here this is going to be really good
put a little garlic powder a little
onion powder in here right
so it's not that i'm ranking on the
ketos that's not it
i'm just letting you know it's not the
keto diet keto diet is
very little food uh-huh
and it has to be just meat and then you
go into a glucose deficit
and then you go into ketosis is that
good for you
horrible okay now carnivore
doesn't even go into ketosis really it
doesn't i'll tell you why
carnivore you're eating a lot of meat
you're also eating other things too
right but you're eating a lot of meat
so if you want to be a carnivore person
making another
crust on the shelf
pickle says anthony are you saying real
ketosis is okay no it's terrible it
killed a lot of people back in the
um early 80s
killed a lot of people with neurological
problems what's neurological problems
aches pains tingles numbness ringing the
ears dizziness vertigo
burning skin uh body pain aches fever
not fever sorry um uh fatigue that's it
fatigue
killed a lot of people darcy lee i love
this information so much i am healing so
much
incredible tara appleman tara thank you
for bringing fruit back
into my life incredible because the
fruit fear we broke fruit fear down and
then they just
the demons out there fight for it they
want to take down fruit they don't want
fruit to exist
um soul seeker i have healed with this
medical medium information
incredible
doing a little bit more of this pulsing
on this right now you guys deborah i'm
eating more fruits thanks to you anthony
incredible
proud of you the real keto diet of the
80s which i
watched has been around a long time
you know which i watched ended a lot of
lives
the keto diet you see now is not
keto it's just a clean animal protein
diet
right an ant clean animal protein diet
without the processed foods
but there still is carbohydrates it's in
the avocado it's in the nuts and seed
butters it's in the seeds the nuts
there's sugar in there there's sugar you
can't go into ketosis
you see how important this information
is but we walk around
i mean you can you smart people don't
know this
doctors on magazine that talk about keto
don't even know this
think about this right like and they're
smart
people that's how tricky it all is smart
people don't know this think about that
um what they're really on it's just a
clean animal protein diet and they got
plenty of not plenty but they got
some glucose enough glucose to stop the
ketosis
process ketosis p strips
um i'm sorry but they just don't work
no one can really detect truly what's
coming out
in our urine because we don't understand
our detoxification processes we don't
understand
how our kidneys work we don't understand
what's in our bloodstream how that works
heck they can't even figure anything out
with blood tests
i mean we still don't have a real window
into why
first of all we don't have a window into
why anybody's sick
so all of a sudden what the ketosis p
strip is going to have all
it's going to be like think about that
right nobody knows why everybody's sick
nobody knows why 20 year olds are sick
in bed a mattress island with fatigue
nobody knows why people have eczema
psoriasis nobody knows why anybody has
debilitating depression anxiety
but the ketosis p strips are just right
on they're just
they're infallible right they're just
perfect right like
we can't doubt a ketosis p strip god
forbid
even though no one knows why anyone is
sick
one thing about medical medium
information is it makes
sense and if you say well yeah of course
you're going to say that you're the
medical medium
you're going to say it makes sense
because you're the medical media nice
try buddy that's what you're going to
say to me like nice try anthony william
it makes sense because you're the
medical media well that's funny because
i don't have this information it comes
from above
okay i had to learn it just like you
guys i had to learn it just like you
guys okay
i'm making another one here this one's a
little thicker so i might kind of remove
some but i'm going to see where it goes
as we go along
um i might take some of it back
right so this one's actually perfect
because you don't want it to fall apart
and tear
and this one here is just a lot
a lot thicker so we're gonna make one
big one here which i'm actually
kind of excited about that so
yeah of course you're gonna think your
information anthony
is is perfect it makes sense because
you're anthony and you're you're
actually
talking about it's like well that's
funny because i had a question spirit of
compassion my whole life as a
as as somebody who is learning because
it's
it's technically not my information
it's from above right i'm the messenger
right i'm the messenger it's no one
else's information
it's spirit of compassion's information
right and then yeah
of course i'm the one talking about it
and putting it out there so yeah i guess
it makes it
medical medium information my
information of course right and then
science takes from it and they take what
they want from
it and they don't cite me and they and
they plagiarize it which
they are not allowed legally allowed to
do that by the way
but i still have this thing in me that
wants people to learn
so i don't like come down on
on on that whole thing too hard but the
point is is
medical meme information published first
you know is then taken and used other
places without citing medical medium
information so other people can find
their way back and feel completely
but either way it makes sense
it just it's info that makes sense right
now i know you guys are smart so
when you learn this information you guys
are like okay
yeah well there is in order to hit
ketosis
you can't have sugars you can't have
glucose or sugars
nuts and seeds have a large percentage a
large percentage of nuts and seeds
they're sweet they actually have a
sweetness to it peanut butter is sweet
right there's a sweetness to these nuts
and seeds and butters right there's also
the fat too
but there's a sweetness can't go into
that ketosis with with all that there
right but you can go in it if you're on
a little piece of chicken
right a little piece of meat you keep
your calories down
and that's all you eat each day and then
guess what you're gonna hit that
ketogenic state and guess what
if you're somebody who's sick and not
well or somebody who's not even
sick you're gonna go downhill downhill
downhill downhill because guess what
your brain
needs glucose it dies without it
you guys on clubhouse i'm going to tell
you right now without your without
glucose in your brain
in five seconds your brain starts to die
your brain's made out of sugar
now the reason why carnivore people can
survive and
i'll tell you why they survive because
they're eating larger amounts of food
they're eating larger
larger amounts of meat and there's
enough blood sugar in that animal's
blood
when it was killed to give them enough
glucose to stop the ketosis process
so even a carnivore person doesn't go
into ketosis
right and plus they're eating some
cheese which is sugar it's lactose
plus you're eating some other stuff too
you know i mean and plus they
they put in the chocolate with with some
they bring in their sweet
i can't tell you how many how many
carnivore people are still having their
chocolate bar
and they got the cane sugar in the
chocolate bar and you know they got
you know i mean the whole bit all right
guys i'm gonna throw this in the oven
i think we're good it's gonna be a thick
wrap but you know what
it's gonna come out good so i'm showing
you what i got going on here you see
this
basically we have two pizzas right two
potato pizzas
but what i'm going to do is fill these
babies up i got tomatoes i got cucumbers
i got all i got some sprouts
i'm excited about this let me get this
in the oven
how much can you guys see over here can
you see the oven over here i'm not even
sure if you guys can see this
okay we're in the oven now
we're in there let's cook that puppy up
while that's going there i might do a
little chopping if you guys are okay
we'll see we'll see we'll give it a
minute um
chop some stuff up in a few seconds
right so
i'm not against i'm not against animal
protein diets i'm not against eating
animal protein if you want to do that
i just want to help you do it right i
want to make sure you can have it in
your life if that's what you want and
still
heal so mm info is about making sure
whether you're animal or plant-based
which side of the aisle are you on it it
still means you can heal
but you need the tools to heal and
that's why the animal protein people and
the keto people and everybody else like
eating clean diets they still get sick
they're still sick
and they're still in the dentist chairs
the the plant-based people the vegan
people
still get sick but the thing is i feel
bad about the plant-based people
the minute they get sick they are
running
running for the eggs running for the
eggs
they get scared their doctor tells them
they need their protein you shouldn't
have been vegan you shouldn't have been
plant-based
and you go running for not everyone but
you run
for the eggs it's why the plant-based
people
never really attacked the eggs they
never hit the eggs hard they kept them
like
coveted eggs are coveted by everybody on
the planet right
medical medium is the only is the only
place where it was
like you know the eggs are bad the eggs
are bad all these years going like 30
years now the eggs are bad it's all
medical medium eggs are bad right what
happens is
man the plant-based people they kind of
keep that like a dark secret
i'm not making fun of them i get it it's
a comfort food you keep it as a dark
secret you always know
somewhere somehow you can always fall
back on those eggs
you see your family members eating eggs
you see your friends eating eggs
see your friends get drunk at a party
and now they're in a diner eating eggs
right
at two o'clock in the morning you see
everybody eating eggs
okay grandfather's eating eggs
grandmother's making the eggs
like you just this is all about eggs
right the whole bit
but if you want to heal you got to take
out the eggs with the plant-based people
man they get sick they run for the eggs
that's where they go you know and you
know they not just run for the eggs
they live off of the chocolate and the
vegan cookies
so they live off of the chocolate the
chocolate bars right
that's right they live off of the
different
vegan cookies right plant-based people
are always running for a vegan cookie
i get it i get it i i i'm not it's not
about
harping on anybody right and then the
plant-based people
run for the butter next right they'll
run for the butter next
maybe maybe they'll even run for the
vegan grilled cheese sandwich
the vegan grilled cheese sandwich with
the vegan cheese and the gluten-free
bread
right they'll run for that so you know
it's worth
the vegans and the plant-based they get
their comfort zone they're running for
all the cheese the vegan cheese or the
real
cheese when they get sick because then
they're like whoa i think i need my
protein i heard there's
this you know this raw cheese diet i
could be on and
raw butter and stuff like that and you
know the real stuff you know and you see
somebody else
on the internet or youtube channel and
they're raising their own
um you know raising their own cattle
they're dude they're cows they're doing
the bug their own
butter and i'm not harping on any of it
i'm not harping on any of it
you guys i want you to be able to do
what you want be free
but i got this thing where the chains of
the chronically ill like the chains
of chronic illness the chains that
keep people down right and sick right
and the industry's behind them right
so when you're sick and you can't get
out of it
there's a way there's a way you might
have to let go of your eggs
but there's a way okay you might have to
let go of the butter but there's a way
you might have to let go of the cacao
but there's a way
the caffeine you might have to let
something go but you know what
spirit of compassion is going to make
sure you're able to eat more things than
you ever could imagine
more so than the other diet belief
systems believe it or not
because they're all anti-fruit pretty
much and if the plant-based ones aren't
it came from medical medium
because they always were going all the
way back you know what you know what
you know what the vegans did back 30
years ago can i tell you
it was dried fruit was the only thing
they eat fresh fruit wasn't even in the
equation
it was dried fruit it was dried fruit
so that's where it was it was like
people it was raisins it was like people
you know and here's the thing mm info
can give you guys fruits apples cherries
berries melons right peaches nectarines
mangoes papayas said the bananas right
and then the other part is leafy greens
getting all these leafy greens in there
and then the wild
foods right the wild fruits like you
know the wild the blueberries right
that's the wild blueberry juice but it's
all about
it's all about the wild foods too and
the aloe
in all of this it's about not having
fear it's not having it's not having
fruit fear
so it's about knowing how like i'm sick
why am i sick
what can i do and then not not fearing
anything
because you got answers and and foods
too
this is going to be an amazing dish so
let me chop up some stuff right here
um i got that cooking right now in the
oven right now
soul seeker az says so true i've never
had such a variety of foods
flavors tastes life is beautiful
soul seeker that's a whole thing it's
like the other diet belief systems all
through the years were anti-tomato i got
these beautiful tomatoes in front of me
isn't this like
it's saying look at these tomatoes so
many other belief systems
right were anti-onions and anti-garlic
right if you like onions garlic you can
have them okay
right so all the different a lot of
other belief systems were anti-sprouts
you got
all the different sprouts a lot of other
belief systems were anti-potatoes
and you got all the potatoes you want
including anti-sweet potatoes out there
too
sweet potatoes right and then people
didn't know about
winter squash and how awesome that is
too
and then the melons everybody feared the
melons
watermelon honeydew melon people didn't
even know they could even eat a honeydew
melon right
and so it's all the different things
that we can eat
and the figs and the apples
i heard for years you guys from doctors
that would contact me over the years and
they would say
did you tell my patient that they can
have
apples i said yeah and not the green
apple
i'm like what do you mean not the green
apple and be like yeah the green apple
they're only my patients are only
allowed green apples
it's like why because apples have too
much sugar it's fruit
so it's only green apple and i'm like
okay well it's your patient that's what
you can do but then don't don't send
your patients to me
because i'm gonna actually you know make
sure they can have
other things too and it's like it's like
like
real apples not just the green granny
smith apple
that you can't taste really any kind of
sugar or any kind of glucose
and people don't realize your brain dies
without the glucose
and if you don't keep the fats down low
you can't get sugar
to your brain cacao is high in fat
and caffeine right so two things are
wrong right there the caffeine damages
your adrenals
and the fat keeps glucose from going to
your brain
so then you get addicted because the
fats blocking everything so that's what
happens with chocolate you're eating
your chocolate
and you're eating your cookies and stuff
and you get addicted
you get addicted to that fat here's what
it is it's like
the sugar's not getting to your brain
because the fats blocking it it's called
insulin resistance everybody gets it
you have a chocolate bar then that
chocolate bar has honey in it or
or raw sugar or something right you know
like honey and raw sugar which is
which is fine right but then any kind of
sugar in your diet or any kind of sugar
in your chocolate like whatever it is
you can't get
the sugar to your brain um you seem fine
to me chris says pizza has more sugar
than fruit
oh yeah big time big time i'm checking
on my pizzas
right now you guys i'm gonna give a
little look here they're still cooking
i'm going to pump this up to uh
um i'm going to pump this up to 400 okay
so you guys with me here there you go
gonna go to 400.
all right
but you know what i was saying like you
know everybody talks about the matrix
that's what i've heard for years and i'm
like huh what
what never saw the movie never saw the
movie it was like ah it's like the
matrix everything's like the matrix out
there right i'm just
thinly slicing some tomato and
then you know i checked into it right
saw the movie
a friend said you got to see it you got
to see it you got to see it i said all
right i'll watch it
and meanwhile everybody's like yeah i
don't get tricked we're in the matrix
we're in the matrix everybody's like
that i heard that for years
i'm like dude you guys are all in the
matrix when it comes down to health
and wellness you guys are totally in it
there
totally in there keto is not keto
plant-based is too high in fat
right plant protein powders
are a menace you guys are in the matrix
apple cider vinegar for keto people
plant-based people animal protein diets
whatever it is i don't care what
name you stamp on the diet
right and then all the fats everybody's
doing
everybody's doing the apple cider
vinegar they're doing the fats you're in
the matrix
and that could be fine you can play in
the matrix you can be in the matrix all
you want
it could be fun when you're not sick
when you're not sick but when you're
sick
okay playing in the matrix isn't fun
anymore
how many doctors appointments do you
want how many times you want to see your
doctor how many blood draws do you guys
want right
how many different blood draws do you
guys want you know that's another thing
on its own
and because you'll keep on getting the
blood draws over and over and over again
um you get sicker they're going to take
more blood get sicker they're going to
take more blood
take more blood more blood and there's
your immune system see you later it goes
out
you lose your immune system your white
count your white count
goes away you lose it no more blood you
lose your weight count
that's how it's done out there right so
um
yeah you guys i'm doing uh you should
listen to the blood draw podcast
medical medium podcasted apple podcast
so i got some tomato slices
already for my let's do some from my
wraps my pizza wraps here
let's do some thinly sliced cucumber so
i'm gonna do that okay
so we'll do that some thinly sliced
cucumber right here so we'll do that
don't slice them so thick where you just
got these big wedges
in your way you kind you really want
everything sliced
kind of thin i mean that maybe you like
it differently
i saw a cucumber slice roll right off
and hit the floor just now it's pretty
funny
um let's get some nice thin cucumber
slices
you should listen to the podcast that i
have on fruit fear that's a great one to
get a lot of knowledge
you guys on clubhouse have you listened
to the fruit fear podcast
you guys on youtube facebook have you
listened to that one right the fruit
fear one it's that medical mean podcast
at apple podcast
you know that's a great one
so i'm just thinly slicing some
cucumbers slices
cucumbers right here okay there we go
if you ever get a new knife i just got a
new knife it's razor sharp right
and um if you ever get a new knife be
really careful
because you might be used to using your
old knife which is
dull and so you get more when you have a
dull knife people say you get cut more
with a dull knife that's not true
you get cut less with a dull knife right
i got to get an onion real quick you
guys
so
i'll be right there we have some damage
control disaster
relief i got to get an onion right here
you guys there's a lot of varieties of
potatoes i want to run that by you
there's the
you know the yukon gold potatoes right
the gold potatoes there's the purple
potatoes
there's the potatoes right
there's the russet potatoes and then
there's like the gold russets there's
different types
and there's different types of sweet
potatoes right so um
you know it's you have so many different
options when you think about how many
foods we have
but if you're afraid of potato you just
lost
out a whole group of foods think about
it right
there's so many different squashes out
there if you're not into squashes
there's delicata there's uh
kombocha there's delicata there's sweet
dumpling there's acorn
there's delicata i think i said that
already but yeah i'll be right back
gotta get an onion real quick you guys
so we're gonna chop we're gonna cut open
another onion
that's what we're gonna do thinly sliced
it
this one looks great
doing that right now
so i'm going to do some thin slices on
the onion here
i'm also going to check those potato
pizzas right now let's do that
hey you guys holding up wow these are
coming out great
whoa they're even like puffing up
incredible there's so many varieties of
apples
right you got the brae burns you got the
honey crisp you got the fuji i mean
those are just some but there's a lot of
different varieties you got the pink
lady
so many different varieties of apples
it's not just red delicious and
macintosh
there's a lot of varieties of foods
they're there
but if someone says no apples you just
lost like 10
easy 10 varieties of food when someone
says no potato
you just lost 10 varieties of potato
that's 20 that's 20 foods
you just lost 20 foods when someone says
no oranges
you just lost another extra 20. now
you're
40 foods in the hole think about that
there's different tangerines there's
different oranges you got the red navel
you got the
regular navel right that's two all on
its own
you got so many different varieties of
you got the pond cans
you got the robinson tangerines you got
the mercut honey tangerines
i could go all day on this you just lost
another 10 easy
okay stay away from citrus you just lost
lemons
oh there's there's easy 10 varieties of
lemons you just lost a couple variety of
limes
you just lost 10 easy 10 varieties of
oranges
that's coming up to 30. no grapes
you just lost 10 varieties of grapes
that's another you just
no cucumbers no onions look look what
you lose
you lose so okay if someone says stay
away from onions you're staying away
from now chives
scallions green onions you're staying
away from all these different onions
you're staying away from the vidalia
onions the sweet onions the yellow
onions
the white onions the red onions now
you're staying away from everything
okay so um the point i'm making is
medical medium information is about more
foods than anybody really knows but then
when someone says
stay away from those nightshades
whatever diet you guys have been on or
tried right
somebody says stay away from those night
shades okay
now your peppers all gone can't do any
peppers no bell peppers no
you know no red bell peppers orange
these are ripe peppers
ripe peppers red bell peppers orange
bell peppers yellow bell peppers
gone eggplant's gone right stay away
from those nightshades
nope no the tomatoes all the the variety
of tomatoes
alone easy ten varieties of tomatoes you
can get in the stores
gone so guess what we just lost 100
foods
we lost 100 foods um i'm we're losing 10
foods at a time
with all the different diet belief
systems 10 foods at a time
think about that checking these pizza
crusts because they're cooking they're
looking good
they're good they're they're they're
getting some air pockets in them they're
in the oven they're baking you guys in
clubhouse we're making
you know i don't know if you can see it
but you know if you look on youtube or
facebook right now
youtube's probably where to go facebook
they're just censoring and kicking
everybody off right
i'm not against animal protein if that's
what you guys want in your diet
i'm not but look how many foods there
are so you can actually lower your
animal proteins a little
bit because your animal proteins are
animal
fat that's the fact
fat stops us from healing you fat
yourself to death it stops you from
healing we're fatting ourselves to death
we're a society
that's fattening ourselves to death and
alter the alternative medicine
conventional medicine is all about high
fat right now
complete talking about the matrix again
we're back in the matrix again
it's misinformation everybody hops on
the trend train
and now everybody thinks it's good to
just just
bombard your system with fats kill when
you don't know it
you're killing your gallbladder you're
killing your liver when you've got that
gallbladder that wants to explode down
the road or you got that liver
that just wants to get sick down the
road you don't know
all that trendy information led you
there
it was it was one of those things that
led you there
and people are fatting themselves to
death and that's what they're doing
um okay so i got thinly sliced cucumbers
here thinly sliced tomatoes here
this is really coming out good okay
so um it's moving some of these out
what i like about if you want to do some
animal protein do it at the end of the
day
right don't do it in the middle of the
day don't do the breakfast morning time
and the whole intermittent fasting thing
that came about
has helped people to some degree it's
still not perfect at all on any level
because
when you intermittent fast you still you
still don't get the things you need so
you'll age you'll still age
quickly down the road right because
you're living off adrenaline and
adrenaline ages us
it ages us all that adrenaline so if we
stay
on the intermittent fasting train we're
eventually just going to get dried up
down the road we're going to just our
adrenaline is going to dry us
up we're going to be a plant that
eventually gets dried up
and then you know and we age quick and
the wrinkles come
and everything else but yeah
intermittent fasting actually helps
people temporarily
because it's giving them energy because
they're not doing steak and eggs in the
morning anymore
they're not doing bacon in the morning
they're not doing all that nut butter in
the morning they're not doing the fats
in the morning
they're not doing all that nut butter
and cheese in the morning
cheese and eggs they're not doing all
their eggs in the morning because when
you intermittent fast doesn't mean they
don't eat that at the end of the day
but when you intermittent fast you're
giving your liver a break
that's how it works and you're get
you're giving yourself a break you're
giving your liver a break when you
intermittent fast
right this is still cooking up it's
coming around i still want to get a
little bit more toastier
so serena says that food makes you sick
what about the fact you were already
sick well we're eating fats our whole
life
that's what's going on we eat fats our
whole life we're taught to just be on
fats our whole life
right our kids are eating hot dogs right
our kids are eating chicken or kids are
eating
peanut butter right it's not just about
animal protein it's plant
fat too okay so oils
all of it fried food or kids are eating
fried food
so what no kids ever have fried food no
no kids ever had hot dogs no kids ever
had
chicken fingers no kids ever had any of
that kind of thing right
you know and um
but what it is not just that and i know
that i'm heading there it's not just
that
it's like it's like
it's it's not just like our children
eating the chicken fingers and the
little
you know buffalo chicken wings right and
you know the hot dogs okay it's we're
trained
we're raised on fat and we're trained to
be on fat right
but it's not just this you can do this
and still not get sick for a while
but you end up getting a pathogen or you
end up getting
which everybody has in the end they'll
have their epsine bars they'll have
their streptococcus
and it's those pathogens that get away
from us
because we keep on bombarding ourselves
with cheese
and butter and we're dropping our immune
system with
all that fat and that's how it works and
then we're eating eggs and that feeds
the pathogens it's all important
information
i think these are just about ready here
i don't know maybe a couple more minutes
actually and we're good
so um
but the bottom line is you can be you
can be look you can still heal
and but it's about having those tools
lowering the fats is really a good way
to heal if you're sick
bringing them down a little bit so if
you're doing animal protein do it at the
end of the day
don't do a lot of it maybe do it every
other day but get ready for this if
you're vegan or plant-based you guys
right do the avocado at the end of the
day and do it every other day
right just bring in some steamed
potatoes okay bring in papaya bananas do
the smoothies bring in steamed potatoes
do the leafy greens keep the leafy
greens going in there
all of that do the spinach and leafy
greens do more fruit
and then keep your fats try to stay away
from the cacao and all the nut butters
and everything
look i know this information is annoying
in some way but
it's not annoying when you're sick
what's more annoying
is it just being sick all the different
aches and pains and
tingles and numbness and exorisis and
acne and
you're sluggish and you're just and
you're fatigued and
you're just you're hitting the doctor's
office you've got the functional
medicine doctor now your chinese
medicine doctor and you're
now you're at the dentist and now you're
back at the doctors and you're you know
back to functional
now you're back at your conventional
doctor and and
what's more annoying is it that or
having tools to actually
be able to rise out of that okay and
grains can be okay for people if they're
not dealing with pathogens and
other things or if they're not super
sick and fats can be okay for people if
they're not super sick with pathogens
right
but when everybody's sick and they're
getting all the symptoms then we've got
something we need to do
we need to do something all right these
are done i'm going to pull them out
so i'm going to do that now
and
this thing is really really hot so i'm
just letting you guys know
so i'm going to kind of pop this right
here okay
there we go i'm going to move this over
let me get these tomatoes out of the way
you guys are okay with that
all right i'm gonna move them out all
right
and so i got these pizza crusts
you guys seeing i mean
these are really awesome they really are
i'm gonna actually take this knife
and cut this one right here they
probably could have been in the oven a
little bit longer
but look at that peels right off
i needed the oven probably a touch more
and
but i'm going to let them cool a little
bit that's really going to help so let's
let them cool
and then we're almost there we're about
to plate this up and get it to get it
going
so i look at it this way every time
a doctor contacted me over the years and
said
i have a patient dealing with a lot of
mystery symptoms they got the tingles
the fatigue
they got numb toes they got back pain
neck pain
their teeth hurt they're highly
sensitive
they're brain fogged out how many of you
guys got brain fog
have had uh brain fog right um
uh nirashini good to see you i studied
medicine for two years and there was no
nutritional course in those years
amazing good to see you tonight um
you're on youtube right i see you may
comment sometimes
and um thank you for always being out
there you know
just helping people out like all you
guys like a lot of you guys are just
always looking out for people it's
incredible
and you guys care i know you guys
actually really truly care
you really do um let's have doctors over
the years ask me
you know look um can you work with
someone if they're eating animal protein
like yeah of course um can you work with
someone if they're
vegan or want to be vegan or plant-based
yeah of course
it's like how's that possible like how
is that possible i don't get it
how right how is that possible and it's
possible because
of knowing why someone's sick and either
side doesn't know
and that's why the vegans are
plant-based people get sick you guys and
that's why the animal protein people
keto people whatever you want to call it
get sick because they all do and then
they flip flop
and it's like flip-flop back flip-flop
back here flip-flop flip-flop and then
everybody's
looking for this sacred root somewhere
in the amazon everybody's looking for
this next trendy thing
they're looking like for maca powder to
save their life
they're looking for like deer antler to
they're looking for something to you
know
they're we're looking for psychedelics
now to save their life they're looking
for something that can save their life
right
because it's a guessing game and you go
on that journey of a guessing game
and and this is
important because that guessing game
journey can wear you
down and wear you down and break you
down and break you down over time
and that was you so yeah and and
totally get it so the bottom line is
i'll give you some takeaways right now
okay definitely let's do takeaways
before i plate this up and make this
into like a really nice meal
um the takeaways for this wherever
whatever aisle you're on you got to
bring down the fats that's the key
it's not you don't get an award
for plant-based keto when i
hear it i go oh my god that's somebody
that's going to get sick down the road
and they're gonna leave plant-based
they're gonna leave the plant-based
movement they're gonna get sick down the
road
good to see you emcee uh mc says people
are looking because you're in pain good
to see you tonight
so um i read your comments a lot
austin good to see you tonight right the
deal is you have to learn what's wrong
you have to learn why you are sick
that's the deal and then when you learn
that you know that plant-based
keto isn't the answer to heal high-fat
vegan and high-fat plant-based will keep
you sick
if you're sick enough if you haven't
gone there yet
if you haven't gone to that place of
being sick enough yet
then you can probably do okay on that
plant-based
keto that plant-based high-fat right
you can do okay long enough right
but if you do get sick or you do
get to a place where things are starting
to fall apart and happen it's because
the fats aren't
allowing the body to heal with what's
behind the problem which is
the pathogens the epstein bar the
shingles the cytomegalovirus you know
most people walking around they got all
these bugs in them they'll have two
varieties of shingles
three varieties of streptococcus two
varieties of epstein-barr
and they'll have that inside them and
that's how it works
so i'm letting this cool down it's
starting to come out
it's peeling it back a little bit more
from the paper from parchment paper
all right
still cooling down a little bit so
there you go but
i like making meals that are fat free
because i know
everybody's gonna eat the fat i can't
stop you i can't stop anybody
they're just gonna do it i got friends
where like i'll teach them how to heal
you know and then they're still having
their vegan pizza or something else
and that's what they'll do elena said i
had ocd
and after medical medium protocol i
don't really have it anymore
and i had it for four years that's
incredible
i remember i put an ocd post out and i
got slammed
slammed by the ocd community
and they were all upset that there was
an answer
they were mad that there was an answer
toxic heavy metals
and they were angry that there was
an answer you know the ocd community
it was like they were just it was
unbelievable what happened and i'm like
wait a minute are you really suffering
from ocd because if you're really
suffering from ocd you're going to want
an answer and you're going to want to
heal
so now i'm starting to wonder wait a
minute are the is the ocd community that
was attacking me
were they really those people with ocd
because
i've known a lot of people over the
years at ocd they're just like what do
we need to do because this ocd is so
brutal i'll be like great let's get out
the toxic heavy metals
and let's heal and then they heal and
it's such a nice thing to see
you know such a nice thing to see when
people heal with ocd because that's a
tough one for so many people
it really is so i'm gonna get this
plated now we're just about ready
right here
um i'm gonna put
some tomatoes in here
let's do that see i'm putting these
beautiful tomatoes
let me put some lettuce first actually
that's the best way to do it
get some lettuce that's the whole point
got the leafy greens
what kind of lettuce do you guys like
shaking a few water drops out of here
okay
this this can actually take a decent
amount of lettuce
he's right here
guys i just do the books if anybody i
know people say look do you do
consultations i don't do consultations
stop that many years ago before um
before writing the books right the books
have the
details the information that is healing
people worldwide
so you guys i just put a whole bunch of
lettuce in here do you see that i'm
gonna show you too i'm gonna put some
tomatoes across
the top right here look at this
incredible
um
how do you get out of the matrix of
health how do you how do you escape it
right jenny my fat craving finally
calmed after my most recent 28-day
cleanse that
that just wrapped up a few days ago for
the first time i'm actually
preferring my food without avocado
incredible
and i want you guys to know it's not
that i'm anti-fats
it's reducing them getting some control
over them
is critical to healing it really is
and if you can bring down that avocado
yeah you can do some healing
how special is that it's not because
avocados bad
it's just that we got bad stuff in us we
got bad things in us that are causing
our sickness and problems look at this
i'm putting these cucumber slices in
there this is amazing
and you in order to for your body to go
after a pathogen you guys
you can't have your blood filled with
fat if your blood is filled with fat
you can't your body's immune system gets
tangled up in the fat
so it can't go after your epstein bar it
can't go after your shingles it can't go
after
the bug that's keeping you down you got
chronic sinusitis and chronic utis and
bladder infections
got kidney infections that's all
streptococcus to go after streptococcus
you can't do it by eating a steak dinner
and you can't do it by eating a nut
butter dinner
too much fat ernia says potatoes do not
cause migraines
correct they don't but people will be
told that
it's a lot of
wolves dressed up like sheep out there
and they're usually also always selling
all these trendy products and
it's the same old same old and there's a
migraine chapter in
the medical medium new edition if you
guys have the book um get it free at the
library all medical medium information
is
free you're welcome to purchase it at a
local bookstore or amazon
but it's free at the library and i love
saying that because
i so many people get it at the library
that's the new
new revised new addition revised and
expanded edition
so i'm going to put a little bit of
sprouts on top of this
here we go and i'm going to put a little
bit of basil here
now i'm not going to chop up the basil
i'm just going to just pull apart a
little bit of basil some of the leaves
right i like you know i also like the
basil leaves whole
too check this out you guys incredible
right
there we go
i might put a little bit more basil if
you guys like basil
i do a little bit more
okay now here's the wrap right here
you can put it fresh on some more
parchment if you want
here's this one right here which is just
delicious incredible
some reason an onion was just caught on
me
there we go this is an amazing pizza
but really like pizza burrito kind of
thing it's just incredible
just wrap this up a little bit
there's this one love that right there
so there it is
so i'm gonna put it right on this plate
that's one
get another one
i like doing this little parchment paper
thing throw it down like that
get this on here
there we go that's it can you guys see
that
does that look good it's huge david
scott
right you guys check out medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast right the fruit
fear episode
always a good one to listen to the the
egg episode another one
the blood draw episode that's critical
the neurological episode the five
meditations the moon meditation which i
still do even in between the full moon i
still do it because
every time the moon changes there's
still a power it has
apple cider vinegar episode the whole
bit medical meeting podcast podcast but
check that out
in that incredible look at these babies
there you go
that's it right there and guess what
there's no oil in here no avocado no nut
butters in here no chicken
no cheese in here right no eggs in here
and i'm not trying to shame any of that
right there are some healthy fats out
there
absolutely if i was going to eat a fat
i'd be eating hemp seeds
coconut a little bit of coconut meat
some hemp seeds some avocado that's what
i would
do some pumpkin seeds right that's what
i would do if i was eating some fats
the point is is none of that has to be
in here and when you have meals
that don't have the fat your blood thins
out so you can get rid of the toxic
heavy metals the medical medium
protocols
you can get rid of the pathogens with
the medical meaning protocols
they can leave the body there's no such
thing as detoxing
when you have your fats all piling up in
your blood when you're high in blood fat
there's no such thing as being able to
detox when your blood
is thick with fat keep that in mind
healing recipes in the book medical
medium new edition
um i'm heading off to instagram
and i'm gonna be also bringing clubhouse
back too so i'm gonna be on clubhouse
and
instagram in just a little while you
guys i can't wait i'll see you then
love you guys