comedian we're live right here live
streaming
as i'm sitting here um potatoes
episode 16 okay
potato the nightshade healer is out
so medical medium podcast at apple
podcast if you want to hear the episode
you're going to want to hear this
episode because if you have doubts about
the potato
you know i'm going to talk all about it
in that episode it's in there i have
talked all about it in that episode it's
really powerful lots of information
there
and i'm going to talk a little bit about
the potato in this
here live so we're live streaming right
here
um these are russets i got in my hand
so i'm excited about them these are
really good potatoes right here so
i know a lot of people they love
potatoes a lot of people
love to hate potatoes a lot of people
don't care about them
a lot of people you know it's just
everybody's got their own thing about it
i totally get it but i'm going to talk
about why this is a healing food and why
this
actually turns lives around all the way
from food poisoning
to you know when you're when you're
trying to recover from a really bad case
of food poisoning and your guts not
right
or if someone thinks hey they got a
parasite or something like that and
they're dealing with some kind of
parasitical infection
because they're sick in their guts for a
long time and having problems
and why potatoes incredible for any kind
of digestive system issue and the whole
bit so i'm going to talk about that is
this really
exciting yeah i mean they heal the
nervous system
i just saw that right now i think uh
jennifer was saying something about the
nervous system as
the comments were going up um but
they're powerful
tools right here these potatoes so i'm
going to talk about that
so episode 16 you don't want to miss it
episode 16
make sure you catch it if you can
there's ichota
um oh wow this episode blew me away the
poem at the end
alexander alexander is here you love the
title of this podcast
the nightshade healer awesome awesome
incredible
and you know i know that a lot of people
are afraid of them because they have
misinformation
about potatoes and what they can do
and the power they have as a healer and
how we can't underestimate them and how
we take them for granted
it's unbelievable so um look
i'll tell you right now when it comes
down to potatoes
it's vast as far as what they can do for
our body
and there's a lot of confusion about
potato like what to eat them with and
that's a big problem all its own because
you might somebody that might be
somebody that puts oil on them
you might be somebody that puts sour
cream cheese on them
butter in them and that's where the
problem lies
it's right there it's one of the
problems because that's a big deal i'm
going to talk about also the sabotage
the sabotage on the potato okay we'll
talk a little bit about that too
about how the nightshade fear kicked
into gear
and when it did it really basically
stopped people from healing stopped a
lot of people from being able to heal
because then they get afraid and they're
often whoa it's this nightshade right
here
this is what's wrong this is what's
bothering me like you know and
so i've got so much to cover um
catherine says and the kids love
potatoes yeah of course incredible so
glad that's amazing
um and you know it look the bottom line
is
this episode is so packed there's
michelle michelle's there michelle said
the end is amazing
michelle did you hear that hidden
message in the ending and so i'm not
sure
if you're picking anything off in there
and that the ending of
the potato show but there's some
powerful messages in there in that
ending
um you know somewhere like three
quarters in
three quarters in on that ending
somewhere around there
this is real powerful messages uh kaylee
i have hashimoto's and i heard
nightshades are bad for autoimmune
diseases is this true it's not true
now kaylee here's how it works okay well
no one knows
how autoimmune disease even starts or
even occurs or what causes it so
and all they think is your body's
attacking itself which is actually a
theory
so here we go we have this autoimmune
theory autoimmunity as far as symptoms
are real and hashimoto's
is real i have books written about that
and there's a book behind me cleansed to
heal with packed information about
hashimoto's
hyperthyroidism and everything so but
what you need to understand is that um
when it comes down to
people saying well a nightshade's bad or
a potato is bad if you have hashimoto's
well that's interesting because
they don't know the cause of hashimoto's
so okay so
how do they know what's bad for
hashimoto's how do they know what caught
like
what can if you don't know what causes
the thyroid problem or hypothyroid
or hyperthyroidism or nodules or cysts
and you don't know the cause of those
then why is everybody such an expert as
saying no stay away from potatoes if you
got hashimoto's
well the funny thing is is that the
medical medium information
allows for potatoes with hashimoto's
and guess what more people healed their
hashimoto's thyroiditis
with medical medium information all
around the world
proven proven results than anybody else
so it's like okay
all right well hey potatoes are bad for
your thyroid potatoes are bad for you
for hashimoto's okay that's interesting
because
thousands and thousands and thousands of
people have healed oh my god
thyroid healing book i wish i had it in
front of me right now millions of people
have have gotten that book all around
the world and healed and reversed their
thyroid conditions with thyroid healing
that book
and potatoes are a healing food that's
incorporated into the recipes that's
incorporated
as far as the healing food so i just
want to make sure you know that so
you're not cheated out of
healing try to listen to the podcast if
you can
it's episode 16. it's called the
nightshade healer it's called potatoes
so it's potato the nightshade healer
that's the episode medical medium
podcast at apple podcast that's where
you have to hear the episode
um sherry said diabetics can't eat much
though because of a starch so what
do you have to say about this issue
really good question
and i talk about the diabetic issue in
this episode so when you hear this
episode
link is in the description you really
got to hear the episode
it's so worth it it's so worth it and i
talk about how
it's not the potato that's the
troublemaker for diabetics
it's not the potato it's what you put on
the potato
so what happens with potatoes you can
reverse
type 2 diabetes using potatoes so you
could be eating potatoes every day
um you know i have a stack of potatoes
right here with me
it's them right there so you can you can
be
do eating potatoes every single day
and a lot of them and reverse type 2
diabetes
and put it behind you if you know some
of the tools
too like for instance it's what you have
with your potato
and that's the key so listen to the
episode so you can know and that's
misinformation
so here you are you know if you're
dealing with diabetes
and you want to heal but yet someone's
keeping you from a healing food
how are we gonna heal and that's the
whole point so i talk about guessing
games you know that whole thing
right um krisha says i love potatoes but
i'm obese and told to stay away from
carbs anthony please please do a podcast
on losing weight
and what to eat i pray that spirit of
compassion will let you see this comment
and help all the suffering people like
me i have medical issues and i'm trying
but i can't trying but i can't gain
weight i'm so confused
so um definitely i want to be able to
help so i
am going to do a wait episode okay so i
will do one and i'll try to do one
sooner
and i'm so sorry you're struggling and
i'm gonna try to do one sooner for sure
and and pack it with information like
i'm doing
lots of it and i talk about i talk about
weight loss in the
the the podcast too in different
episodes and
potatoes you could still do potatoes and
lose weight it's just
so much information to learn about how
and which way and all of that
so but i want you guys to have every
every opportunity to heal
so i will focus on that i'll focus on
starting to work on
an episode that's around weight and
around losing weight and and and all of
that so it's really important
emma says thank you for confirming
potatoes are good for us i grew up on
potatoes and i'm so relieved
can enjoy this okay so
here's the thing potatoes are really
good for us
and i'm just going to mention a couple
of tidbits right here there's zinc in
the skin
so zinc is critical for our immune
system it's critical for
our survival here and
so in zinc there's trace mineral zinc
inside the skins of potatoes so
if you're going to eat potatoes and
there's all kinds of nutrients and trace
minerals inside the potato too
so lots of nutrients and trace minerals
inside the potato
but in the skin itself it's got a high
amount of zinc and that's a critical
mineral
that we need too and i'll talk about
some other stuff as well
um i know you a lot of you guys are
afraid of nightshades you're told to
stay away from a nightshade you're told
to stay away from potatoes and that
a potato and that's where we get in
trouble that's where we lose an
opportunity to heal
that's when we can't fix things i talk
about in the episode so just so you know
if you just got here
i'm live right now live streaming so i
want you to know if you just got on here
um and i'm talking about episode 16
of the medical medium podcast so the
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
really you guys should catch the episode
it's it's a mind blower it really is and
um it's packed with information about
the potato and
it's something you don't want to miss
because if you have anything with your
digestive system bloating
cramping sibo ibs crohn's colitis
gastroparesis whatever you're doing with
intestinal tract disorders
acid reflux ulcers all of this stuff
it's important to know that potato can
be brought in and how helpful it really
is
it's a free resource i don't know what
else to say i just try to do free free
free free free and you're going to
notice something
there's no ads there's no commercials
there's no infomercials
it's just free listening and you're not
being bombarded by
silly ads and stupid ads and stuff like
that okay
lorraine else here awesome glad to see
you glad to see you
um um she's a meditation expert i mean
she's
she's tried everything done everything
all through the years incredible
incredible
uh sharon the potato skins make my mouth
burn
like i ate pepper or spice if i don't
eat the skins do i
do i not get sick you still get zing
from it sharon you still do
but you get the normal amount of zinc
and maybe that other
fruits and vegetables and different
things have so
and herbs and wild foods so you get the
normal amount but there's a little bit
more on the skin it's okay you don't
need to eat the skin you can peel the
potatoes without a doubt
you can easily do that and what you'll
notice that
if you try different potatoes maybe you
might not get that sensation with
another one because the skins are grippy
and when the skins are grippy
because that's what they are they're
grippy skins sometimes what they do
is if you're sensitive um you know
what happens is the grippy skin it you
can kind of just
it it's kind of one of those things
where it rubs a little bit and that's
how it gets rid of the bad bacteria too
so when you're eating these potatoes bad
bacteria that's in our gut
that causes sibo that causes all kinds
of gastritis
cramping and bloating the potato grabs
onto it and starts to pull it all out of
the intestinal tract
it's like it's it's a really powerful
healing and cleansing food for the
digestive tract
and the inside of the potato there's
these little
stringy things inside the potato you
can't really see them but stringy fibers
and when they go into you
they bind on to bacteria and roll it up
and pull it out of the body so
if you hear out there i don't eat
potatoes and you know they're not good
that's ridiculous they're one of the
most important foods
i mean if you want to eat them you don't
have to you don't have to
christine said potatoes are high in
potassium i'm at a dangerous level of
potassium
if you have a potassium level where
you're at some kind of dangerous level
potassium your doctor feels like you're
at a dangerous level of potassium then
you got to watch
everything you eat so just every single
foods you eat
you have to look out because potatoes
not the highest in potassium
um and there's lots of foods that are
higher in potassium
so you have to look out so christine
definitely keep an eye on out you know
don't do a potato if your doctor doesn't
want you because of potassium but look
out for of course your potassium levels
on all foods
it's it's something that's really smart
to do i'm glad you're on that um
so but potatoes very important food you
guys
really is um so for the nervous system
so i want to go into that a little bit
um
margie says i can't afford potatoes are
you okay you can't afford potatoes sorry
i didn't
you can hey we're live what am i gonna
say what can i say
we're live streaming right um yeah
that's incredible yeah
they're affordable and they're healing
and they're a powerful healing food
incredible really is what's the name of
the book
um well cleanse the heel is right behind
me i'm going to try to get a cup reach
over and grab a copy in a second too
and clench the heel is an incredible
resource for healing there's 75 recipes
in there i'll show you in a minute
but the episode i'm talking about is
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
check that out it's the potato episode
you guys
and i'm gonna talk a little bit more we
got more to cover haven't even scratched
the surface right here of these babies
and but the the episode is potato the
nightshade healer
why would i call it the nightshade
healer
why would i call it that you know so i'm
going to have the book right here
that's cleanse the heel um this is a
medical textbook
amazon.com us has a sale on this book
right here 51
off 16.99 if you don't have it you're
missing out
it's already healing 1000 actually right
now it's healing millions of people
around the world globally this book
um and so it's the most powerful
resource in comprehensive resource
there is in and basically in medicine
that's what doctors tell me all the time
so
lots of doctors are using them in their
practices now because they've used
medical media books in their practices
for years going now
so this is the books over 200 symptoms
of conditions i talk about things like
supplements in it like that's the b12
that i take that's the vimergy b12 i'm
not sponsored by the way
all right just like my episodes on
medical beam podcasts
don't have any advertisements on there i
don't work like that
so anyway but that's the b12 i take it's
an important key factor into healing
the vimergy company these invictor
i-m-e-r-g-y
so check that out um but yeah
that's the cleanse the heel book
different cleanses in there over 200
symptoms and conditions
75 recipes so that's there right there
uh uranus says i eat my potatoes with
acv
to slow down the release of insulin so
you know the thing is well that's a
that's a theory it slows down the
release of
insulin um you know that's that's that's
a good theory there's lots of theories
out there as far as far as what happens
and what doesn't but
the key is with potatoes is any kind of
insulin problems
that can happen with any kind of food is
you have to make sure you're not dousing
it with
oil you're not dumping lots of oil on
your potatoes or
any food really and you got to make sure
you're not having potatoes with
another fat like too much fat you don't
want potatoes with
turkey fat you don't want potatoes with
beef fat you don't want potatoes with
chicken
fat so that's where the insulin stuff
happens and that's one of the keys you
need to know but that's like that with
everything you don't want to have bread
with chicken so if you have a chicken
sandwich you're having your
chicken fat with your carbohydrate your
bread
even if it's a gluten-free bread even if
it's a whole grain bread
even if it's a wholesome grain in
gluten-free grain if you have it
with your chicken grease or you have it
with your turkey grease or turkey fat
if you have it with you know if you have
a steak sandwich
or something you're having fat with a
carb
that's how the insulin goes off the
charts
that's how the a1c goes up see so that's
how it works with the whole
insulin diabetes but we don't have it's
like that information
is just for some reason just it's not
out there so people just struggle and
they
keep their their insulins all over the
place their numbers are all over the
place
they're up and down they're a1c they got
insulin resistance no one's teaching
them how it works no one's saying
don't have a carb of any kind with
a fat no one's saying don't have sweet
potatoes
with turkey at the same time no one's
saying don't have sweet potatoes
with i'm just talking about anything
like sweet potatoes is
right there i mean so many people eat
them but they eat them with all that oil
and all that grease or whatever they're
eating them with um
so let's go into this part by the way
i'm taught i'm live right now i'm
talking about potatoes
i got a sack of potatoes right here i'm
talking about healing benefits i'm
talking about
how you shouldn't run from potatoes
because of hearing it's a nightshade
misinformation as far as how that works
out there okay it can stop you from
healing i talked a little bit about food
poisoning i think i still will where
potatoes are
a saving grace for post-food poisoning
for recovery
i don't know if you've ever had food
poisoning but let me tell you there's
people out there
their stomach doesn't work right for
years after a bad case of food poisoning
months afterwards weeks after
and this is one of the foods to help
bring them back i've done it thousands
of times with people
so important to know um and so
anyway and i'm also going to talk about
how potatoes aren't a white
processed food that's important too
by the way so you got to hear the
episode i just don't want to forget
about that because i can only give you
so much information here
so listen to the uncensored episode
i'm censored here you guys so keep that
in mind
um i gotta watch the keywords
information and stuff that i get
that i hand out it's really tough so but
what you do is go medical medium podcast
at apple podcast medical medium podcast
at apple podcast
the potato episode okay the nightshade
healer
link is in the description share the
episode so people can learn and heal
so share the episode please you know so
people can heal and
if you feel up to it and you like the
show
please then leave a review at apple
podcast for the medical meeting podcast
it will be really helpful
for a lot of reasons so other people can
find their way if you enjoyed the
episode if you enjoy the episode
um so key factor right here
anti-viral this is an antiviral food
why should you care anything autoimmune
is viral so hey i just got diagnosed
with an autoimmune condition
i got diagnosed with lupus got diagnosed
with multiple sclerosis
ra rheumatoid arthritis i got diagnosed
with chronic fatigue syndrome
fibromyalgia neurological lyme
and i got autoimmune now well
that's viral that's what that is i talk
about that in the books
and that's viral so these are anti-viral
food this is an antiviral food
right here so what does that mean when
you're eating this
you're actually working on healing and
getting better
getting better um
yeah michelle's right don't eat potatoes
with green skin
or sprouts i talk about that in the
episode so
here's the thing you're eating potatoes
to go after bugs that are in our system
gotta remember that so if you're
diagnosed with autoimmune
what's happening is you got this
underlying viral condition
okay it's the epstein bars it's the
shingles varieties
it's it's a mega virus people walk
around this all day long they're filled
with these bugs but the bugs eventually
get a little out of control
and then you get swollen joints you get
dizziness aches and pains ringing in the
ears you get hashimoto's thyroiditis
that's caused by epstein-barr virus and
so when you go through all that you're
having all these symptoms and conditions
and you get the the autoimmune diagnosis
then you're
you're dealing with low-grade viral
infections or sometimes more than
low-grade
well this is an antiviral food i talk
about this in the episode
so medical medium podcast at apple
podcast
guys why do i want you to listen to the
i have no advertisers so i'm not making
money
i have no infomercials i'm not making
money so
why do i want you to listen to the
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
so
badly like because what happens is if
you have all these advertisers on there
and sponsors and advertisers then you
end up you know you end up making all
this money right
and that's that would be a reason to
push you all there okay
well i'm not doing that so why do i want
you to actually listen to the medical
beam podcast at apple podcast
because i want you to heal because it's
a free resource
with no advertisements because it's
packed with information
and because i created it in a way that's
a docu-series
style podcast it's not coffee talk and
it's not throw away
so it's not like cattle call just
another guest on well another guest don
coffee talk another guest on disappears
forever coffee talk who cares
these are docu series filled with
information
so you can heal it's about you getting
better it's about you getting better so
you guys if your anxiety is up
and you're dealing with a lot of anxiety
a lot of emotional struggles right now
check out the three meditation support
meditations i think i have four
meditations on medical media podcast
that apple podcast
the brain meditation the fruit picking
meditation
that one right there the moon meditation
you guys are you keeping track
of the half moon because the moon
meditation is
critical on the half moon so i want to
tell the rain that
lorraine says your meditations are the
best so healing
lorraine do you know about doing them on
the half moon i bet you do
and that's a key time to do it that's
what i do and i do it on the full moon
for about
seven days during a full moon cycle and
then i do seven days during the half
moon cycle
because what happens it's all about the
magnetic pull
something changes the axis of the earth
where the moon is at that time
and you know where we are in our space
and time now
like in history each day as each day
unfolds so i like to do it use that
healing of the moon's power
thank you for doing the the meditations
and lorraine thanks for telling other
people about them too
because i i read all the comments on
youtube
and and and you're helping other people
it's incredible same thing with michelle
i see you helping people it blows my
mind
and same with loon too i mean it just
blows my mind because you guys get so
much compassion
it's crazy and everybody you know you
guys but
i want you to know andy choda too i see
each other on there and she's
just helping people out and i guess
that's what it's about right
it's it's about like if you're
struggling and you don't have
answers or you know your symptoms are
bringing you down and you got anxiety
and depression
and i don't want anybody living like
that
i want them to have a way out potatoes
are great
great option right there that's the
medical medium podcast
that's it and that's the fruit picking
one
so it's ptsd it helps heal anxiety it's
the fruit picking one
trying to make this go right and medical
mean podcast at apple podcast link is in
the description right there
so right now it's right now people's
anxiety is just through the roof
their depression is through the roof um
but you know i'm excited about these i'm
gonna eat these tonight i'm gonna cook a
whole big batch of them is what i'm
gonna do
and what i'm gonna do with my potatoes
tonight i wish
i already had some cooked ones and i
could actually show you and i'll do that
on another
live stream too is i'm gonna chop them
up after they're done
okay i steam them and i talk about that
in the episode you have to steam them
that's your best
bet for making sure get everything you
know um healing
but what you do is what i do is i make a
big salad i chop them up
i throw them on top of the salad i
squeeze lemon
all over it i uh that's what i love to
do
i put some onion on there that's me hey
that's me i try to put some green onion
on there i put regular onions on there
that's just what i like to do so the
point is
i want you guys to hear the episode so
you can learn about how to use these
babies
how to heal how to get your life back
each tool counts
every little tool counts medical
medium tool and i said medical medium
tool because people don't know
they never knew keep these plain keep
them steamed and
you know you can make them with other
food you can put other food in there but
try to keep the fats down
so you're not you're not dumping too
much fat on top of your potato sour
cream
cheese and and what else you know you
got to look out in butter you got to
look out
for that so so i want to talk about that
with potatoes is their anti-viral
so what they do is they have virus
killing properties
that means if you're already struggling
with something where you're sensitive
and you you get achy or your joints
bother you
or anything like that happens a couple
of things could go wrong
one is if you're eating potatoes and
you're eating them
with eggs if you're eating eggs in your
diet if you're eating potatoes and
eating butter with them
if you're eating potatoes and having
sour cream or milk or some kind of cream
or or butter with them like i said or
cheese or anything like that
if you're eating them with things like
that you're just gonna have more
problems because
dairy products feed the viruses so
that's what happens right there
it feeds the viruses and that's one
reason why you're going to get flare-ups
every now because you might be someone
that has like okay i'll try
a baked potato you go bake the potato
you throw butter in there and now you
get all the cinna flare up well you just
got to flare up because
the butter is feeding the bugs and
that's what happens there it's one
reason another reason why
that people feel like they may not feel
good after a potato some people is
because
they're killing viruses so here you are
somebody who's dealing with viruses
inside your liver
inside your body inside your intestinal
tract and
including also bacteria that shouldn't
be there like streptococcus and you're
eating potatoes and you're
killing these bugs when you kill bugs
and you get them out of the body
sometimes you don't feel so great for a
little bit
rebecca knight i've been told potatoes
aren't good for autoimmune diseases
there is so many different opinions it's
so hard
to know which way to turn well okay well
here's one thing rebecca that's so
important to know okay
um they don't know what causes
autoimmune so why are they the expert at
what to eat
i'm kind of confused about that that's a
head scratcher for me
um they don't know why anybody has
autoimmune they don't have answers for
autoimmune
everybody stays sick with their
autoimmune their whole life nothing
changes
they keep their lupus their whole life
they keep their fibromyalgia their whole
life
um the only thing they offer is drugs
and alternative medicine doesn't know
the cause of
fibromyalgia or lupus or hashimoto's
thyroiditis so
interesting how is everybody an expert
at what to eat and what to avoid when
they don't know why anybody's sick
once you realize that you know where you
can go a little bit because if you go in
here
and this right now thousands of doctors
are using this this book right now
around the world or the medical meeting
books
you learn what the cause of your problem
is i have it right in the book
when you learn the cause and you learn
what's in a food
then it rises above all that it takes it
way past all that
now you know why you're sick why i have
autoimmune
then you know what kills it off and
kills off the bugs that cause autoimmune
and you know how to heal and that's why
people heal with medical medium
information here's another thing
to keep in mind rebecca that's really
important is
medical medium information has already
been proven millions around the world
already doing healing thousands and
thousands of
of eczema cases reversed completely
reversed psoriasis cases when that never
happened in our history people just
didn't get
rid of their eczema that never happened
unless they just took drugs to suppress
it short time for a short moment
people just didn't just get rid of their
excellent psoriasis that started with
medical medium information
that never existed before that you just
debilitating cases of eczema
just didn't go away just because you get
rid of processed foods or try a fancy
diet
and it's already been proven already
happen so you have to think about that
so when you think about
who do i trust where do i go there's so
much information out there about
autoimmune and not eating potatoes
interesting because they don't know
what's causing your autoimmune
so why are they experts how many people
did they get better with autoimmune do
you still
have your autoimmune and have you
applied the information take the book to
your doctor go to the library get it for
free
get it for free library if you want um
so
and you can look up autoimmune here and
cleanse the heal so monica ellis says hi
there does the book cover lupus that
what you do is you go
into the autoimmune section and you'll
and you'll be
able to address it there it's an
important place to address it
i just you guys look you know what's
really sad really about what happens out
there and the misinformation it's sad
about
the misinformation about potatoes that's
sad all on its own
and i mean the misinformation there when
it's a healing food
when eating properly what you can
actually do for yourself listen to the
episode
and another thing is if you haven't
heard the episodes you
really should there's the apple cider
vinegar episode the brain fog episode
the b12
episode i'm not sponsored by this
company very important to know
um and so you guys i just want you to be
able to heal uh
catherine says can't wait to listen to
the podcast catherine
you gotta hear the potato one you have
to hear this potato one
so important um so
tori says steamed potatoes keeps more
nutrients intact
than baking the potatoes yes steaming
them is the key
boiling them you lose a lot of nutrients
for sure
boiling them but if you have to boil
them and make a soup
well them and make a soup you can do
that but really steaming them is so
so good and easy on the system it's a
gentle food
to heal your central nervous system
that's what it can do
help heal the central nervous system
helps with the digestive system
so i mean it's really
a great thing when you know what you can
do here catherine elizabeth
says food poisoning is awful um look
everybody almost everybody i know i mean
out there in the world they get food
poisoning it is
terribly awful it's unbelievable jerry
west says hi anthony
from new zealand yeah cool love your
podcast so helpful thank you
amazing amazing amazing so that's that's
that's so great that you're listening
um kathy lawson says hey i love
uh potatoes so okay there's olive oil
questions so no olive oil okay good
question so
angela so no olive oil on potatoes
here's the thing
of course you can put a little olive oil
in potatoes of course you can okay
and you can and that's fine you could
also have avocado with potatoes
you can have a little bit of coconut oil
with potatoes tahini with potatoes
if you're gonna have a fat with potatoes
and i talk about it in the potato show
please listen to the episode
i think you probably might have that
might have that's why you heard about
that
um keep in mind that if you're gonna do
some plant fats with potato
tahini sesame tahini and avocado
are two great plant fats that you can
actually you know use with potatoes so
if you have a little
tahini on top of your potato it's one
option
the other one is um avocado
on potato that's kind of like the
avocado toast but you put on avocado
potatoes avocado potato
but keep in mind that even then
it's still best without having a fat
with the potato but those are the best
options and you can of course you can
it's still great and the potato is still
healing
the potatoes still going to help heal
the body absolutely
um darcy lee good to see you i did the
freezer bird podcast this morning so
good the freezer bird podcast episode
the meditation just blows my mind i did
it a couple days ago
blows my mind i do the moon meditation
the brain meditation
the freeze of bird meditation the fruit
picking meditation
this you guys got to try them okay you
gotta try it's a free resource
um could i have charged for those
meditations yes
i could have charged for them i could
have packaged them up and sold them
for a couple thousand dollars you buy
into it you could get four
of my meditations and guided meditations
i could have easily done that
i could package up programs with this
new york times best-selling book i could
package up programs with all the medical
medium books sell them for thousands of
dollars a piece so no one gets
no one gets the information unless they
pay 2 000
a program that's what everybody else
would do in the industry building a
platform
selling their products i don't do that
i'm just letting you guys know i don't
do that
you can get it on sale at amazon you can
also get it free at the library
okay and that book is saving lives right
now
and the medical medium podcast is free
resource and it's a docu-series
on podcast link is in the description i
just want you guys to know that
because it's important it just is and
so you know anyway did you hear the b12
episode
that's important there too and i want
you guys to just have
options to heal anilia says i just had
dinner
from potatoes and shiitake with some
salad i followed your advice for one
year
and my health becomes better and better
thank you so much
incredible that's so important to know
because i know you're doing the right
things you're taking care of yourself
catherine elizabeth says
we need your meditations um yeah
especially
the la past few days are you guys doing
them so what meditation what i do and
with everything that's going on now i
did free as a bird a couple days ago
so here's the fruit picking meditation
that's one i like right there sorry you
guys i'm trying to get it situated
link is in the description medical media
podcast at apple podcast it's a fruit
picking meditation right there
it's a free resource guided meditation
like i said i can package them up and
sell them
that's what i've been told to do it's
like no not doing that
not doing that i want a free resource
you guys can heal
and that's what's going on so
judy says you and the information you
share are life saviors
uh i've been doing celery juice and
heavy metal detox
daily for a year healed hashimoto's
wait a minute there's somebody that was
on here that has hashimoto's i hope she
stayed on here
and she sees the comment that you healed
your hashimoto's with the information
so important and that's an autoimmune
condition so you got to think about
that so anyway and potatoes are a food
to help
heal autoimmune how can you go wrong
um this is interesting maynard spaceship
hey good to see you
i'm glad you're here today i lost a ton
of weight eating potatoes
yes i talk about it's a weight loss food
yeah it is it's a weight loss food
okay you know it's it's a weight loss
food
so important to know it really is
charlene says i have sweet sweet
potatoes avocado oil and herbs that's
delicious
that's actually delicious combination
try having
regular potatoes they offer more
sweet potatoes offer certain things
regular potatoes offer
all kinds of other things really
important now um fern says what are your
thoughts on plant-based
butter i don't like it i would use
avocado
for butter any day for 35 years that's
what i've been teaching about
taught it in lectures 35 years 30 years
ago over 30 years ago i taught in
lectures
i taught doctors about it i've helped
thousands upon thousands of people
one-on-one throughout the years and i
always said use avocado as your butter
for your potato or anything like that
that would be your plant-based butter
is avocado keep that in mind anyway you
guys so cool so link is in the
description
the potato episode is out
check it out the nightshade healer i
didn't even scratch the surface to the
amount of information
in the episode and susan said your
potato salad recipes are my all-time
favorite you guys
go to medicalmedium.com and i got potato
recipes on medicalmedia.com
lots of potato recipes my god so check
that out really you know
anyway bless your heart proud of all of
you guys
truly don't fry your potatoes don't fry
your potatoes
nadia says where can i listen to the
brain fog
message the brain fog message brain fog
episode
please listen to it link is in the
description nadia link is in the
description
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
don't miss out subscribe to
subscribe subscribe subscribe okay
anyway take care and i'll see you guys
next time