we're live right now
we're live on youtube facebook
tick tock and clubhouse
and pick your pick pick which one you
want to be in
um we're talking about being sick is the
new normal do you ever think about that
you know being sick it's normal to be
sick
yeah it's fine perfectly fine
everybody just has to get used to it or
were supposed to be used to it or maybe
we
are used to it right it's the new norm
medical meme information has always said
that
it's the new normal everybody
is supposed to have a symptom or a
condition
right or some kind of
symptom condition mix right we're live
on tick tock we're live on youtube we're
live on facebook we're live on clubhouse
just letting you guys know
we like to do it live and
is it what do you guys think is it okay
that everybody
you know it's the new norm everybody's
sick is that okay
i mean it's actually unusual
if you're somebody that doesn't have a
symptom
right it's a small crowd you guys it's a
really really really small crowd did you
know that
really small crab and there's people out
there you think are healthy
and you think they're strong they're
healthy
but they're gonna get a symptom
they're gonna get one it's coming their
way
that's symptoms on its way
okay i'm just telling you now and that's
how it's going now is it because
everybody's jeans went bad did our jeans
all go bad in one shot literally in one
shot is that what happened did
an alien spacecraft just send a ray down
some kind of laser gown to make sure all
our genes went bad in one shot
right did the gene fairy just enter
everybody's home on the planet
and bless them the gene fairy blessed
them with this
this gene you know our gene demise
our broken gene system is that what it
is
the you know like why is it it's the new
norm
what happened no one's questioning it no
one talks about it really
unless they heard it from medical medium
and then went out there and of course
didn't cite it back we know how that
works you guys it's it's it's
it's rampant out there never citing
medical medium information back
right using his information right
spirit spirit of compassion's
information and then
saying well hey medical medium he
doesn't know anything where's his
science
meanwhile they're using medical medium
information
and good to see you guys coming on like
i said we're live on facebook live on
youtube live on tick tock live on
clubhouse
awesome to be here lorena i saw you pop
on there i'm making a potato bowl you
guys
let me get started a little bit and
start sauteing some stuff are you okay
with that because we're talking about a
powerful topic a really
important one and this topic is
really in my opinion critical critical
and if you're just coming on here you're
going to want to fasten your seat belts
because i got some stuff to say
it's important let's just cut up some
red bell pepper get it in the pan right
now
so you guys i just cut off the top like
that you see
cut off the top right pull out the
center
toss the center aside got the empty
shell right there
and then this part here i take and i use
two so i'm just gonna throw it in the
pan just so it's
cooking along do you guys think it's
strange that it's a new normal
endometriosis if you don't have
endometriosis as a woman
that's strange really strange
right but guess what every single woman
is getting endometriosis
that's where it's heading what happened
didn't extraterrestrial come down
and all of a sudden grant that condition
on every single woman coming up
you know it's the new norm i can keep
keep going going going
headaches are the new norms every con
anxiety is the new norm right
i'm chopping up some red bell pepper in
here how do you guys feel about that
is something wrong um
you know is something wrong and did our
jeans all go bad
to create the situation you know
um i got
i got an appointment coming up you guys
phone call coming in i hope it doesn't
get in our way
good to see you guys michelle l good to
see you guys see all you guys coming on
here
i'm gonna read some comments too and
even answer some questions if i can as
well you guys i'm gonna just
cut this onion right here just gonna
play a little bit of an onion game right
here
the censorship is just incredible right
now
the censorship on medical medium um
actually it's it's
really awful i'm going to get another
onion i
just that i cut that onion open it was a
bad onion
so just give me one second here i think
i got one right here
let's try this one you guys check all
your notifications
i'm noticing on youtube everybody's
notifications are being kind of shut
down
and if you got on here chances are your
notification is working but
everybody else that's not here it's not
working same thing on facebook
notifications they're just turning off
all the notifications off of
you know a whole thing i hear some
people they literally can't even find it
even when it's live it's not even
possible
so there's a lot of head games going on
out there
i'm going to chop up this onion get this
in the pan
so we're going to talk about why
everybody's sick and getting sicker
i'm trying to be light-hearted about
this planeman says i didn't get any
notifications from youtube and facebook
only from clubhouse really interesting
definitely
so i'm getting some onion in this pan
right here you guys making a potato bowl
um sauteing some onion some mushrooms
too
so i'm gonna do some mushrooms as well
here's the sad thing let me just give it
to you guys straight
here's the sad thing the amount of
sickness we're about to see is going to
be unreal
but the media is not going to be talking
about it just pretending everything's
same as always everything's fine
everything's good
but the amount of sickness coming
it's gonna be even more than
unprecedented than before let's put some
mushrooms in here too i'm just trying to
get this going real quick you guys
um
some mushrooms doing a little dish right
here
waiting for everybody to come on as well
you guys are live on tick tock
live on youtube live on facebook i got
notification from facebook the feed is
bad
yeah well they're probably kicking a lot
of people off that's what they do on
facebook and
ig um
you can go to youtube you can watch it
on youtube you can do that
live on youtube right now you guys
so the bottom line is
we're coming to a place where it's
all going to be about everybody being
sick
all the social media channels are going
to be
about everybody being sick okay
all the tv shows coming out in the
future
are going to be about everybody being
sick
right and
everyone's going to have a symptom
hello how are you today what kind of
symptom do you have
hello uh mrs robinson
how are you today what kind of sip oh
you have a
migraine you have anxiety you have
depression hello
mr ferguson how are you today what do
you have
prostate problems kidney your your
kidneys are bad
what else mr ferguson
let's get some mushrooms in here i just
before i get really rolling you guys i
just want to get this
i want to get this going i'm sauteing
right now
saute
hello mary sue how are you today
endometriosis what else do you have
going
fatigue
chris you seem fine to me
right what kind of world are we living
in
hello postman the postman's at the door
what kind of symptoms do you have today
sciatica
frozen shoulder
i mean what kind of sick world is this
but it's perfectly normal perfectly
normal
think about that right
perfectly normal
i just got a flower delivery today
the person delivering it was very sick
zelda says i actually believe many
people of today
like to be sick they want to be sick
because they have nothing more to fill
their lives with
hello yeah i have severe fatigue
yeah no i just want to be sick yeah i
lost my job
i can't feed my kids
am i sick no i just want to be sick
uh-huh yeah
uh-huh i went to my third doctor
uh-huh i have a debilitating migraine
yeah he prescribed more drugs
i was in the er because of one of the
drugs
it's because i want to be sick
uh-huh i yeah
i like to be sick uh-huh
yeah um
what else yeah i um
i saw another neurologist and they did
an mri and i was so sick after the mri
i want to be sick i have nothing to fill
my
life with yeah my life is so boring that
i want to be sick that's what this lady
zelda said
uh-huh yeah i want my fifth doctor
appointment wait a minute i want my
tenth doctor in my 50
50th doctor appointment i'm broke
i don't feel good
mm-hmm severe crippling anxiety no i
want to be sick
it keeps me busy uh-huh it keeps me busy
i need to be sick uh-huh
yeah all of us pretty much want to be
sick we don't want to be healthy no
we want i want to be sick okay i gotta
go
zelda no disrespect
but i can't tell you how off the mark
you are
it it is there one person on the planet
that wants to be sick is there
one person on the planet that wants to
be sick
no one wants to be sick no one wants to
people want to live their life go where
they want to go
do what they want to do eat what they
want to eat
play what they want to play exercise the
way they want to play
have fun laugh people want to live their
life
they want to be productive they don't
want to be
sick people want to be productive
they don't want to be sick they don't
i'm gonna squeeze a little touch of
lemon in here guys i'm making kind of
like a little stir fry with no
oil no oil fancy that
fancy that
lorraine else is way off the mark
stacy people don't want to be sick
but want an easy fix in a pill form
i better get my pills out
where are my pills let me see
last time i took my last time i took the
pills out
um many people do many people do
many people want a quick fix absolutely
i would say
everybody wants a quick fix right
wouldn't you want a quick fix
like boom right well that's where the
whole placebo
thing is just total bs you guys you guys
on clubhouse
hope i'm not hurting any feelings you
guys on youtube and facebook you guys on
tick tock i'm hoping i'm not hurting any
feelings
okay but that placebo thing doesn't work
a sugar pill is not gonna fix you or no
one would be sick
on this planet they could just literally
give you a sugar pill
hey here's a sugar pill right here well
let's just get a sugar pill out for
monday tuesday wednesday thursday let's
get a sugar pill out right
you would be fixed no one would be sick
on the planet
it isn't about in the mind yes you
better have a positive mind you better
have positive thoughts
absolutely they're important you better
have references
you can do your mantras and affirmations
and you can stay strong mentally and
emotionally right
work on it for sure but when you're sick
you're sick
i know some of the most positive people
i've ever met my in the on the planet in
my life
and they're in bed they're bedridden and
they're positive
but if if they weren't sit if they
weren't
really sick you can give them a sugar
pill and they'd be fixed and cured
you could give them a sugar pill
and people want a pill they want a
pill to fix them people want a quick
fix they want you better believe they
want a quick fix
they want that quick quick fix
absolutely this is almost done right
here and then we're gonna
keep on cooking they want a quick fix
it's human nature fix me now fix me fast
let me have that pill and fix me
i'm making a potato bowl you guys and
this is part of it right here
and i'm going to get a bowl for this
potato bowl
do that
pick in a bowl we're picking a bowl
right here very nice bowl right here
yeah people want a quick fix they do and
i totally understand
see lovely says i started drinking
celery juice every day and my
anemic has gotten worse so my anemia has
gotten worse
well
yeah i'm a fly
do i see a receipt let me look
i see a receipt this is it's a medical
receipt
this is the medical reach medical
treatment receipt let me try
yeah yeah yep there's a medical
treatment receipt
let me get back on the wall
what's in the fridge i don't know let me
look
oh they're opening the fridge
well i just saw all kinds of stuff in
there you wouldn't believe what's in
there in that fridge
oh my god i saw eggs in that fridge
there's eggs in there i saw some cheese
in that fridge
uh-huh that's right
they're opening in the freezer and
opening the freezer this isn't ice cream
is that some ice cream what else
i'm looking i'm looking all kinds of
things
uh-huh
yep okay i gotta go
the flies gotta go
i want everybody to be the their own
detective don't i always say that you
guys
own detective right on clubhouse i want
you guys to be your own detective
right okay so so
we got to watch what we blame
we have to watch what we blame if you
blame
something that is completely harmless
but only reverses conditions and brings
people's lives back
but we don't blame all the stuff
we don't blame the nutritional yeast the
apple cider vinegar the vinegars
the over salting everything we don't
blame the protein powders
the colostrum if we don't blame the
collagen
if we don't blame the fish oil if we
don't blame the l-carnitine if we don't
blame the whey protein powder
if we don't blame the diatomaceous earth
particles the bentonite clay
if we don't blame all these things but
we
just blame celery juice for something
we don't blame the medical treatments
that were peer pressured in
we don't blame anything but the celery
juice
we're gonna miss out on an opportunity
to heal
and if we don't and you would you know
what i got a call coming in from science
research anyway
okay
[Music]
i think this is science and research
huh hey science of research
thanks for calling i can't believe
you're calling right now this is
incredible i'm making a stir fry
yeah yeah what do you have to tell
we had this appointment you science of
research you there
yeah oh yeah so i wanted to ask you
something you guys
right in front of everybody do you know
the cause
of autoimmune cause unknown
genetics really so cause unknown
science research can i ask you another
question do you know why people have
mysterious anemia
you don't know science and research
actually doesn't even know
huh what else can i ask you something
else signs of research
what's the cause of crippling anxiety
you don't know okay what's the cause of
multiple sclerosis
you don't know okay okay so basically
science research you don't know why
anybody's sick
yeah i know
i know i'm gonna hang up on you guys
okay bye
so this is actually cooked down just
nice what i'm gonna do is put it in this
bowl partially and i'll show you in a
little bit
and then i'm gonna brown up some
potatoes
it's really good that you guys are first
of all i want to tell you that i'm
honored you guys are all here in my
kitchen
it's a great honor truly okay i never
say that or i don't say that enough or
or however but um i just want to tell
you guys that i am grateful that you
guys are here
we're going to talk about some great
stuff we're talking about
the new normal it's normal to be sick
let's do that i'm putting this in here
all right so i got to throw some potato
on here really quick because this
skillet is hot so just give me a second
here
we're going to get some potato browning
up on this
um do you guys like being tricked
do you guys like being duped how many of
you love to be trick do you like to be
tricked
right you think it's funny
no right you guys don't like to be
tricked right
how many of you i wanna i gotta ask you
guys questions right
how many of you love walking into a room
opening the door to walk into a room and
a bucket of water dumps on your head
you guys love that i just want to know
you guys love that do you guys like when
you walk into a room clubhouse you guys
like that
walk into a room in a bucket of water
dumps right on your head
do you guys like that in clubhouse is it
should that be a new thing
we have everybody in clubhouse we have
everybody we we get somebody to put a
bucket of water above
above your door so everybody in
clubhouse the whole clubhouse community
walks into that room and a bucket of
water dumps on your head you like that
these potatoes are pre-steamed by the
way they're pre-steamed and now i'm just
giving them some browning
kind of browning them up toasting them
up here a little bit i'm gonna pop some
lemon
on these which you can do which is
really good
it's a little bit of lemon in here i'm
going to cut open this lemon too
do you guys like being duped do you like
when the wool is pulled over you
your eyes
do you like do you guys like being
tricked
no i don't think you guys like being
i'm just browning up these potatoes
really quick
but but that's that's what's happening
there's
masterminds all the time trying to
psych you guys out
[Music]
there's people out there in the
industries the industries
have think tanks i'm gonna give you guys
some the dirty business man
the dirty business i think you guys
should know
there's all these think tanks designed
where you have
12 people
okay
and these people are around a round
table and they have to come up
with deception how do we deceive
everybody in any way possible
[Music]
all right and you guys are all their
guinea pigs you guys are all their test
dummies
you guys are all there um
you guys are all there people that are
supposed to be
michelle says 12 angry men it's actually
really funny
you guys are supposed to be
there sheeple
you guys are the sheep
you guys have to make sure you guys are
the sheep
that's what it is it's important that
you're machine
right and
what they do okay
does they think that you guys are
gullible
they think you guys are gonna conform
[Music]
they think you guys are gonna do their
bidding
uh-huh they think you guys
are the sheep
and that's what they think you guys are
the sheep right
uh-huh yep uh-huh
that's right they want you guys to be
the sheep
and so you guys have to kind of fall in
line
like all the rest of the sheep i'm
trying to do this while these
potatoes are toasting on here so
just give me a minute you guys we're
almost there these are browning up nice
all the industries got your number they
got your number
they use the media they use the
advertisements they use the advertisers
they use all this stuff
keep you guys in line
you guys are being trained to accept
being sick as the new normal and not
question it
and not question research in science
every time you hear research in science
you have to bow you have to bow it
doesn't matter if it's the stupidest
study you've ever heard
right it doesn't matter if it's the
stupidest study
you've ever heard listen
it doesn't matter
all right this is all set toasted up
nice
let's get this in here
i don't know if you guys can see this
sorry about this where's my etiquette
where's my not showing you guys
right here and i'm gonna
this bowl is a little bit trickier so
we're just gonna
there we go nice
i get a nice potato bowl right here
and i'm gonna make a salsa too so i got
the potato bowl
so this is a deep bowl so it's got a
different different vibe to it right
different look
here it is you got the onions you got
the mushrooms you guys see this on tik
tok you see this on youtube facebook
mushrooms onions you got the red bell
peppers
right you got the and then you have the
potatoes that are nice and brown they
were pre-steamed and then i threw them
in the
in the on the griddle there and started
moving them around getting them nice and
toasty right
okay no oil in this so no insulin
resistance
really important to know no insulin
think about that a little bit because
everybody they're living by insulin
resistance and they're living by chasing
a high which i'll talk about again a
little bit
that's what they live by and the oil
causes your adrenal
your adrenaline to surge and flood the
oil causes adrenaline to surge and flood
so you get addicted to fat that's how
it's done right
and then now you're on this roller
coaster ride
it's to thin out your blood your
adrenals release all this adrenaline to
thin out your blood right that's how
it's done
yeah smoky mountain paradise i think i
see you guys
and yeah so anyway that's but we still
got more to go
and more to do
yeah you guys the industries sit there
and they mastermind a way to keep you
guys tricked fold
and duped the wool being pulled over
your eyes it's constant all the time
and it's it's happening in alternative
medicine it's just not just conventional
medicine
and it's supposed to be the new normal
and you're never supposed to doubt it or
question it and you're never supposed to
think science of research
is missing a beat you're never supposed
to think that they failed
the heck out of everything that they
failed us
that their failures absolute
failures failures failures and chronic
illness right
when someone's literally laying in their
bed they've seen 10 neurologists and
they can't function
and nobody knows really what's wrong and
they have 10 theoretical
diagnoses they failed them
that's what that is it's not the doctor
that failed them it's science of
research that failed the doctors and
failed the patients right and i believe
in science and research i do
it's not that i don't it's not that i
don't
okay but in chronic illness they have
failed
miserably denial is a place where
science and research lives
then here's how it works at science
research the industry itself
spends billions to make sure they police
you your police so that everywhere you
go
you believe they have they have your
back and they have all the answers and
everything's perfect in science and
research world
that's how it's that's how it's staged
and the minute you get sick the blame is
on you it's your fault clubhouse it's
all
your fault you guys are sick on
clubhouse it's your fault
yeah it's your fault you're sick that's
right
you guys are sick on youtube facebook
your fault totally your fault
science research they have all the
answers apparently they know everything
so you being sick it's your fault tick
tock
you guys it's all your fault that's
how it's set up to be so
you're not allowed to question the new
normal
where everybody's sick and mark my words
now here and now you guys haven't seen
anything yet to what's coming in the
next three to five years never mind the
next six months
okay and science research
where are they gonna be they're gonna
catch us are they gonna catch us when we
fall
oh don't worry they're gonna catch us
when we fall
yeah science and research well let me
you guys i'm gonna get my science
research blanket because
they're gonna take care of me hold on i
gotta get my science and research
blanket really quick okay
yeah okay you guys i need to get my
science and research blanket
oh my god my science and research
blanket right here
oh science and research oh my god
science and research oh you're so you're
so
soothing yeah you have my back
my warm fluffy comfortable science and
research blanket
wrapped around me uh-huh yep you got my
back
that's right um doesn't matter how many
times i have to take my child to the er
for mysterious conditions and symptoms
because science research has my back and
my baby's back too
i need another science research blanket
i better hurry up
because alternative science is so smart
too they all have our back let me get my
let me get my alternative my alternative
science and research blank as fast as
possible
oh thank god thank god i have my
alternative
research and science blanket right here
because
recent alternative medicine research in
science has my back too
yeah so comfortable nice what i gotta
huh yeah wait i forgot
the doctor's office is calling me that
right now and i
i have to be ready for my doctor's of
dr joel hoppy yeah
oh i'm just wrapped up in my science
research blankets my alternative and
conventional medicine science research
blanket
uh-huh they know everything uh-huh
what i have to get another medical test
because it's inconclusive really
i thought i have lupus i do but i don't
but i do um is there a cure for me
because science and research has
everything
they know everything do they have the
cure oh there's no cure
i just live with it for the rest of my
life should i be mad at science and
research
no no never be mad at science and
no they're my comforting warm blanket
because i can sleep at night knowing
that science and research has
my back i could just go to bed at night
science and research they got me covered
i could sleep at night
huh what what uh my husband's waking me
up right now
he says they have we have to rush my
other child to the emergency room again
because of the worst case of eczema okay
well doctor
oh you don't have an answer for my child
okay but science and research is so
comforting
they have every answer that's ever been
that's why on tick tock when all the
science research trolls
report you because they say that science
is everything
yeah it's so comforting same thing on
on facebook too yeah did you hear about
that medical medium put a post about
banana
and facebook banned it and said that it
didn't have science in it
yeah that's why we love science so much
it's so nice
is this no we're supposed to be sick my
children are supposed to be sick that's
the new normal
but isn't science and research so cuddly
and comfy
okay i gotta go okay
oh you guys i got to make some salsa
um let's go let's go we got to get back
we got to get back to work
we got to get back to work you guys
yeah um basically i'll give you another
what you want a nutshell you guys on
clubhouse you want a nutshell
i and i don't mean a nut in a nutshell
but you guys want a nutshell okay the
system's rigged
so that you guys are brainwashed by
the science and research cult
not only that there's a lot of cults out
there
it's not about freedom like here in the
medical mean community because you're
free to be
you're free to do whatever you want
right but
in the colts out there it's rigged
and they all do the same thing
they all parrot the same thing they all
mirror the same thing
they're all the smoke and mirrors right
right michelle miller right
and right chris you seem fine to me and
that's how it's done out there
okay and then they blanket it under the
nice science research blanket
that's how it's done and then every
single
person gets sicker and sicker and sicker
and sicker that's how it's done
and it's the new norm educating myself
good to see you today
that's the new norm all right yeah
tight werner says that's true exactly
exactly
and that's how it's done out there okay
um kathy says have an open mind yeah
have an open mind
it's a good one right there have an open
mind to what's happening out there
and you gotta understand something
here's how the colts work out there
they have think tanks like i was telling
you guys in clubhouse a little bit while
ago
right they got think tanks designed to
make sure
you never ever ever stop your addictions
you stay addicted you won't know you're
addicted until you get rid of it
you won't know you're addicted until you
get rid of it
okay you won't know you won't know that
every single bug in your body
wants to eat those eggs that you're
eating you won't know the egg addiction
until you
rid it until you rid the eggs
that feed every bug in your body that's
right
you won't know the addiction until you
knock out
that chocolate bar right
until you break that chocolate addiction
because the caffeine industry has
you brainwashed they need you addicted
for the rest of your
life until you're in your grave
until you're in there they the caffeine
industry
i wouldn't doubt it if they don't come
up with a drink
you give someone after they passed away
that's caffeine-based
like no no no just just pour it in their
mouth
pour it in their mouth it's a little
caffeine pill
for people who passed away make sure you
purchase it
make sure you purchase it it's got cacao
in it
it's got cacao science research says
cacao so good for you
make sure you put a little cacao pill in
the person's mouth
after they passed away i mean they are
literally trying to
to in every way possible
they're trying to make sure that's just
the caffeine industry i'm talking about
big pharma but guess what the caffeine
industry is big pharma you didn't know
that
you didn't know that i'm not talking
about the mom and pop
the mom and pop is that that love cacao
and they're all about
fair trade and sustainability and
they're like they you know that husband
and wife that's like let's start a cacao
company with
and we'll put little ribbons around the
cacao you know when you you sell it and
then they get it it's got a
gold ribbon on it it's got going across
and
you know you get your special chocolates
here and your special cacao this
this cacao's got cinnamon in it this
cacao's got nutmeg in it
and we just do this thing i'm not
talking about them they're good people
not talking about them yeah
healthy says i got shamed and attacked
on tick-tock for recommending someone
look into mm for their autoimmune yeah
so so the whole goal is
and i'm just going into caffeine for a
second i'm not talking about all the
industries on a whole right including
much of the alternative medicine
industry it's about making sure you guys
stay brainwashed your whole life
and making sure you stay confused and
making sure you stay
sick you have to stay sick
you have to yeah now it's about coffee
and tumeric right
exactly take turmeric which is actually
a great a great healing tool right
and now mix it in with coffee right
exactly let's
let's see you know that's what i mean
let's see how many people just
buy into it because of the addiction of
coffee right
and it's it's actually evil when you
think about it
but you know who who might say anything
i guess
everybody just do what you want to do
but
the bottom line and still gonna i'm
still gonna love you i'm never gonna
it's not about shaming i'm never gonna
judge you
i know you're caught up on the
addictions all of them
so i'm never gonna judge you ever ever
because it's not your fault you're
addicted it's not your fault that the
industry's found a way to brainwash you
it's not your fault
they want you sick they need you sick
okay here's what happens people are on
caffeine
right because they're not feeling good
they can't think straight
so instead of fixing the problem
of like the brain fog and the confusion
and the fatigue
and the energy loss instead of fixing
that problem right
instead of recognizing we have a crisis
in the united states we got a we got a
crisis worldwide
and we need to take care of women kind
and
find out why they're brain fogged let's
find out why women are brain fog
let's i got the caffeine industry uh is
actually calling me in a minute too
we need to find out why women are brain
fogged we need to find out why women
have no energy
we need to find out why women and men
don't
feel good and can't think and they can't
think straight and they can't
they can't then they can't get out of
bed the morning and they're just they're
groggy and they don't feel well we need
to find out
why everybody's feeling this way
and instead of
well caffeine incorporated
this is the head of the caffeine
industry globally of the world
i can't believe it yeah we got questions
for you
yeah how much time are you gonna give me
a few seconds
okay i know you're very important person
okay so
how come we don't look at to why
everybody's sick
and because why because you don't care
what do you mean you need them sick so
you need everybody sick so that they can
go on caffeine
so what happens if we fix everybody
and we get them off of the psychoactive
drug that you're pushing
globally you'll go out of business
your private jet what about your private
jet
you won't be able to pay for the for all
the people the crew on your yacht
the fleet of yachts that the caffeine
industry caffeine industry owns
so okay so
the deck hands on your yacht the
okay i get it so you have to let go of
all the deck you don't wanna
you don't wanna fire anybody that works
on your yachts
it okay so you're saying that we need to
keep
millions of women hundreds of millions
of women
addicted to caffeine burning out their
brains
their livers getting their children
addicted we need to
keep that going including the people in
africa that are
starving to death while they're cutting
your yep your cacao down too
including the coffee growers all the
coffee farmers
that die in the fields when water hits
them after being laced with all the
with all the with all the what what
you're about to hang up
what's going on you need your lawyer on
the phone why
huh you're going to patch in your lawyer
right now
okay fine patch him in hi yeah yeah hi
yeah it's anthony william and i'm just
talking to the head of caffeine all the
caffeine world
industries incorporated acne caffeine
yeah i just i'm asking why can't we just
get people off the psychoactive drug get
them out of the addiction so they can
heal
he was just telling me he doesn't want
to let go of his deck hands on his
yachts
he says he's gonna it's gonna create
unemployment issues
because he's gonna have to hire he's
gonna have to fire too many people that
run his yachts
okay so let's just keep every all the
women in and let's make sure children
are addicted to caffeine too
just so that your yachts can run okay
okay i gotta go all right
um i gotta make a salsa
you guys on clubhouse hope you guys are
hanging in there hey tiktok good to see
you guys
yeah it's good to see you guys facebook
youtube great let's make the salsa let's
chop up some tomato
we got some tomato going right here
let's get some tomato we're gonna chop
this up
gonna make a nice little salsa got a
bowl right
you guys are you making homemade salsa
or you guys just or you buy the salsa
with vinegar
right the teeth destroyer the teeth
annihilator
right actually kevin says you're a
legend i feel the same way about you
you're extremely gifted your videos are
your videos are just really special
um are you guys doing salsa with all the
vinegars
is that what you guys are doing look i'm
not blaming you
that's not it you know
not blaming you at all that's not it's
just maybe make a a salsa
without the vinegar the vinegar just
takes you to osteopenia
that's what it does and caffeine takes
your osteopenia that's a big one right
there
i look i've seen caffeine destroy a
woman's body
for decades and to the point where now
when menopause comes
it's all about well my hormones are
what's taken me out
that's what's destroying me it's my
hormones it's like wait a minute
hormone imbalances and everything that
all happened from
no one telling you you just did 35 40
years of caffeine
25 years of caffeine you didn't no one
told you
that you did all this caffeine you
literally destroyed
that the industries just wanted you to
destroy your bodies
until finally now they're gonna blame it
now all on
you know something else
that's how it works two i mean that's
one thing right there
look
i get it if if you need to sleep at
night
you need that warm fuzzy science and
research
blanket making you feel safe at night
so that if you ever got sick someday
they got your back it's gonna be okay
so bridgette says she craves vinegar
yeah i mean i don't blame you for
craving it just do you know what happens
but you're not craving vinegar by itself
right you're not craving it by itself
wait so you're craving vinegar so much
that you crack open that vinegar bottle
and you're just drinking it is that is
that how it works
with vinegar you crack open the bottle
and you're drinking it
right i'm just curious or do you crave
what you're putting it on
are you craving what you put it on i'm
going to chop these tomatoes up a little
bit more
are you craving with the vinegar goes on
because i got this feeling that vinegar
goes on fat
i got this feeling the vinegar
goes on fat your avocado
dish your salad with olive oil
your vinegar goes on dishes with fat
that's what i got this funny feeling i
got this funny feeling inside
that's telling me that which is really
spirit of compassion telling me what you
use vinegar on
um you should check out the vinegar
apple cider vinegar podcast acv podcast
i just saw on tick tock someone said
serena says apple cider vinegar 20
question marks
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
check out the apple cider vinegar
um episode just so you know
check that one out
and you'll learn in that episode that
if you care about your teeth serena do
you care about your teeth
i'm just curious do your teeth matter
serena do your teeth matter i'm just
curious
they don't matter they do matter right
they matter greatly
well then i would be cautious on that
apple cider vinegar
because literally that's why teeth are
falling apart on everybody
at this point as those vinegars and
apple cider vinegar is no accept
exception it is literally the teeth
destroyer
what do i have what do i have to gain
what do i have to gain about ripping
part apple cider vinegar
i don't sell a substitute i don't have a
medical medium
anti-apple cider vinegar substitute you
guys want the medical medium
anti-vinegar substitute
that's why i'm ripping apart vinegar
right no i don't have that
so why what am i gaining do you guys
ever notice that
what am i gaining with all the things
that i'm ripping apart i could come out
with a cacao bar tomorrow and being that
i know you guys are all addicts
with cacao it's not your fault do you
know how much cacao i could sell
dear god you hear that in a clubhouse
you hear that a clubhouse over there
right jessica john
right sharon you guys hear that kim you
hear that in a clubhouse
do you know i can put a medical medium
chocolate bar out
cacao bar ninety percent chocolate and
everybody's gonna be all high on it
and it'd be the medical medium one i
could put a little honey in there
i could have one without that a little
bit of sea salt in there
i could put out a chocolate bar sell
millions of chocolate bars
because medical medium because millions
of medical medium books
gone around the planet i can stop
millions of chocolate bars
and so what do i gain tell me
i'm here ripping apart cacao telling you
how it damages you
right telling you how you guys are
tricked and duped to eat it
telling you how science and research
doesn't know why your baby's sick but
they sure as heck know why cacao is good
for you supposedly
i can do what am i gaining besides a
headache
from all the tick top trolls what am i
gaining
right exactly so i mean
think about that one for just a few
minutes
think about that one lisa says is
autoimmune real or just
false label used when inflammation can't
be explained
but pretty much absolutely see
autoimmune
symptoms symptoms of what they demoted
immune are real everybody's sick
right but inflammation isn't just it
right it's what causes that inflammation
nobody knows
right medical medium information about
what causes inflammation
is the only thing out there that's ever
been sound in real answers for the first
time in our history
okay we talk about in the medical medium
book spirit of
compassion and i talk about how you've
got the epstein-barr virus
causing so much of that inflammation and
then you end up with an autoimmune
diagnosis
okay but your body's not attacking
itself so that's wrong out there that's
misinformation that's a theory don't you
love when science research
gives you a theory and then for some
reason we're supposed
to believe that that's some kind of
concrete fact
you know and i talk about this in book
one medical medium book one
secrets behind chronic mystery illness
and how to finally heal this is it the
new edition you guys i'm holding it in
my hands
right holding it in my hands
so science research is so smart
and cause of autoimmune is unknown
and all they can do is use a theory from
1953 that your body is attacking
itself which was a theory right
because they've never proved it or found
out that's even possible
it was a it was a suggestion
and so now what science research is just
iron clad
24 karat gold
that was the 1950s the 1950s you guys
this this rotary phone
is technologically more advanced than
the 1950s
this rotary phone right here is far
more advanced than the phones they were
using in 1950
when they came up with the theory that
that your body was attacking itself
so a 1950s theory
right of your body attacking itself
became 24 karat gold
irony is it became 24 karat gold to the
big pharma man
because they're banking on you guys
they're banking on you guys
bank bank bank i'm cutting up some
cilantro right here to put in my salsa a
little onion in here too is what i'm
gonna do
they're banking on you guys
they're driving around the range rovers
baby
they're range rovers yep
big pharma they got their maserati in
their garage
big farmers got their range rovers in
the garage
big big farmers got the beamers in there
they got their ferraris in there they
got the rolls-royces they got their
bentleys in there
bmws are a joke to them
range rovers a joke to the big pharma
boys
they laugh at somebody with a range
rover
spirit corrected me
i was talking about range rover
everything and spirit combat just like
are you kidding
bentleys and rolls right
the big farmer boys got the bentleys and
rolls that's what they got
cooking in there and they're banking on
everything they're banking on you guys
staying sick they're banking on you guys
getting much more sicker coming up
pretty soon
they're banking on all of it and then
they got you thinking
oh science research is going to catch me
when i fall
could catch me after the 50th
neurologist
right you guys on clubhouse jessica john
sharon
right right you guys
and know it's it yeah they're gonna
catch you
look i'm not insulting incredible er
doctors that have to put your broken
bones together
i'm not insulting the surgeons i know
personally
that change heart valves i'm not
those are mechanics those are mechanics
those are nuts and bolts you cut
out a part you keep the person half dead
so they don't awaken when you cut them
open
they you anesthesia the person to the
point where
they're almost dead but not dead
i talked to a lot of anesthesiologists
and they're like here's how it works aw
here's how it works we gas
them enough so we can put the knife in
replace the parts but yet not
kill them with the anesthesia there's
this borderline
right yeah
borderline michelle miller you're right
you're right but and so and then
but but science is good like that
if your body's been hurt by their traps
all through your lifetime the cacao and
the vinegar and your teeth are falling
out and all this other stuff happens
your appendix blows up because you
caught your third variety of
streptococcus
and in e coli caused your diverticulitis
you didn't know how to take care of
yourself all these years
and you got to get a piece of colon cut
out i talked to surgeons you got to get
a piece of colon cut out
you got to get your your appendix
removed you got to get a gallbladder
removed because it damaged from years
ago right
and you got to get that done okay
and we got some good surgeons out there
of course we got a lot of bad surgeons
and they make mistakes too i talked to
surgeon he's like well man there's a lot
of bad surgeons out there
yeah but science and research does the
nuts and bolts
pretty good nuts and bolts anything
past that it is literally just russian
roulette
it's russian roulette but lots of bank
lots of bank
rolls royces and bentleys off the
sheeple
and mansions too big old mansions and
yachts
yep that's right i know because i was
talking to my friend
fly on the wall right you guys know
flying the wall
you know our friend fly right he's seen
it
he's seen it
yep that's right
all right let me get a fork
three and a four got some cilantro and i
got to get some onion in here now let me
grab an onion
trying to finish up the salsa you guys
it's like this every time i play onion
games it's always an
onion game right
it's like i don't have enough onions but
yet i have too many onions but yet
sometimes the onions they go bad when
they're sitting around too long right
you guys know how it works that just
squirted onions juice in my eyes
that's what i love about live right
there
all right
we're gonna be crying
let's get a little red onion in this you
don't need a lot of red onion in here
lorraine did you see that you see the
onion squirt
that's one for the record books huh
seaweed hero did you see that
loon did you see that all right you guys
i'm making a really simple salsa let's
put some lime in there
the reason why you guys don't see me use
salt is because you guys have so many
deposits of salt inside your body you
don't know
here's how salt works did you know you
can have
salt crystallizations crystallizations
of salt
inside your liver inside organs
connective tissue
salt deposits inside your brain that are
not being productive they're not working
you guys on clubhouse this is really
important
these salt deposits they become these
crystallizations
that eventually get seen on an mri as a
mystery condition
do you know that we salt ourselves to
death we fat ourselves to death
okay and then science and research
throws studies that are useless at us to
death
it's it's it's insane we caffeine
ourselves to death
yeah we vinegar ourselves to
death we alcohol ourselves to death
that's what we do yeah we do
salt deposits can sit inside you and not
dissolve
did you know that they can crystallize
and trap cells and cells get all
dehydrated in these clumps inside your
body did you know that
yeah that's how it is
so we keep on dumping more salt we salt
ourselves to death dump more salt dump
more salt you know what
you know what some idiotic trainer is
going to tell you
put a pinch of salt in your in your
water grab a pinch of salt in your water
you need salt grab a yeah you should be
getting it from like
celery and spinach and lemons
lemon has sodium in it natural occurring
sodium
right the real kind and it's okay if you
guys use a pinch
of really high quality salt okay here
and there
it's just that the reason why i'm so hey
no salt
because so many of you guys have salt
packed in your
body it's packed in there it's packed
away
in there okay and restaurants and foods
and vegan food and all that is loaded
with salt
that's that we've been trained to have
that salt taste
needing that salt lick like being
addictive to sodium
we can be addicted to the bad sodium
because our body wants the good sodium
but instead of drinking the celery juice
we're going to pound all this bad salt
i'm going to put a little cayenne in the
salsa so get ready for that
i got a couple different options right
here i got this dried
cayenne right and i still got to make a
little bit of a salad real quick too
so let me do that let me put a little
let me put a little bit of the super
chili in here
okay a little bit of the super chili
let's do that
i'm not mincing this super chili really
intensely
because i know that if i mince it more
and more that salsa is going to be real
hot it's gonna be real hot
it is it is all right so i got a nice
salsa a real easy one vinegar free
vinegar free one step to reversing a cut
from a knife that's right
thousand cuts death by a thousand cuts
just reverse the cut
boom didn't add vinegar in there boom
didn't add a whole bunch of lump of salt
in there
boom just reverse two cuts
see right let's go the opposite
direction
instead of instead of the direction that
the alternative movement wants you going
into 24
7 just a slow direction to your death
but yet they get they take away your
processed foods right on clubhouse you
guys heard that before
keep away your processed foods keep away
your fried foods your fast foods oh
brilliant real smart
real smart keep away those
right and then and then you know have
your balance of
carbs have your balance of fats have
your balance of proteins but not know
why anybody's sick and not know how to
fix anybody
right let's uh throw together a little
salad
um one thing i like in my salad is this
beautiful green leaf lettuce did you
guys see this right here
okay
yeah of course you're gonna feel better
get rid of uh fried foods and greasy
foods and you get rid of all the cakes
and cookies and donuts and all that
of course you're gonna feel a little bit
better yeah you're gonna that's one step
that's a step drink more water another
good step right there
drink more water
yeah right common sense stuff
common sense stuff let's make a little
side salad this is going to be good i'm
putting some lettuce in here
this is green leaf lettuce
but that's not enough when you're sick
that's not enough when you're getting
sicker that's not enough if you've been
injured by a new medical treatment
that's not enough
a lot of keto people are gonna learn the
hard way in the next one
to five years man they're gonna learn
that their exercises
and their keto clean keto diet wasn't
enough
and now they're gonna be on the doctor's
search i'll go to this new functional
medicine doctor he's got all the answers
let me go to this new functional
medicine doctor she's got all the
answers
let's try another 14 vials of blood
let's try
another 16 vials of blood
let's get another eight vials of blood
i'm gonna do cilantro in this side salad
just so you know
i'm using cilantro as a leafy green you
guys
if you see right here i'm chopping it up
a little bit
extra cilantro is a leafy green right
there this medical medium information
i don't use other people's information
never did you hear it here and you think
you heard it somewhere else that means
they got it here
um you don't need a lot of cilantro but
there you go you got that right there
okay
it's up to you you know i mean i like a
lot of it i like using it as a leafy
green
so so making a little side salad you can
put a little onion in your side salad
too
nice and thin
a little bit of onion using cilantro
as a leafy green it's mm-info not using
a pinch of it
people use a pinch of it
like i was saying before if you wanted
to use a pinch because you don't like
cilantro i'm not going to shame you for
it and i'm not going to judge you for it
i want you guys you know to also you
know work in the comfort zones you guys
have
but i'm giving you opportunities also to
heal the more cilantro you bring in the
more you heal
you know that is a really good a
powerful tool right there all on its own
right so i need a couple more things for
the salad right here
um so i got onion in here i got
cilantro in here i got the leafy green
right green leaf lettuce
okay cucumber is what i need but
i'm gonna have to look for that and then
we'll get a cucumber in there
um i'll do that now you guys bear with
me gonna find a cucumber
crap the phone's ringing
hey yeah i'm on the carnivore diet
i'm on the carnivore
uh uh kind of keto carnivore
um diet yeah
not eating much anything else trying to
keep my bloating down keep my weight
right
what what do you mean what do you mean
that's the atkins diet
no it's not it's a carnivore diet
you mean it's just the atkins diet from
1980 what
and it never it didn't fix anybody
i thought it was new i was watching a
youtube i thought it was
new i thought it was the carnivore diet
keto diet carnivore diet all that kind
of thing you know keep your carbs out
the whole bet just do meat maybe some a
little bit of like a hard cheese or
something
that's the atkins diet really
it's already been there done that people
lived and died
really so i'm just a new fool trying it
but i'm feeling better on the carnivore
diet i'm just eating meat
a few eggs and the hard cheese it's
because
i got rid of like so much of the other
crap i was eating yeah true i was eating
a lot of stuff i was having pizza on the
weekends too
all right so what do you suggest
something better so you're saying it was
already done
it was done over and over again why do
people keep on getting tripped then like
me
how am i why are people constantly
getting tricked then
because every five years no one knows
history
so we just don't know history we don't
know any of our history then we don't
know all the mistakes that have been
made
we don't know how many people died from
antibiotic treatments with lyme disease
they just they're all gone
so there's no history like oh history
repeats itself constantly because of all
the screw-ups they're never really
oh they're never really taught to
anybody so what
what do people learn in school though
so no one's being taught the constant
mistakes over and over again
including in health all the disasters we
just repeat it over and over again
oh all right i gotta think about that
gotta wash this cucumber for a second
you guys
yeah hey did you ever think about that
one right there
yeah it's kind of funny had a doctor
called me up a while back
i haven't talked to him in years it says
aaw
like what i'm trying this new carnivore
thing a patient told me to try it
i'm like really didn't you try that many
years ago because what are you talking
about
i said didn't you try that many years
ago that was the atkins diet many years
ago he goes you're right i never even
thought about that
i go didn't the atkins do that the
acting side didn't work for you right
that's what you told me that's what he
said
i'm not saying anything bad about it or
not not
not saying anything bad about it but he
said no it didn't work for me i said
well you're redoing it
you're doing it he said how do you like
that
all right i'm gonna chop up this
cucumber a little bit here
now i don't i'm not putting tomato in
this salad right now because i have this
incredible
salsa right here so what i'm doing is
you know i like adding the salsa to my
salad this is a little side salad i like
adding my salsa to it
i'm just chopping up a little bit of the
cucumber right here
yeah lorraine i had to run out for that
cucumber
i can't win i can't win
i'll tell you you guys the whole tomato
thing's a night shirt
the nightshade thing the nightshade fear
that happened
can i give you a little can i give you a
little inside scoop on something
you guys are you're okay for this you
guys are in clubhouse roger
right all you guys there john right jess
and all you guys out there right did you
know that you know where tomato got the
bad
wrap right we used to have
lead plates so everybody ate off of lead
plates
100 years ago or more right and
so what happened was anything that had
any kind of
acid right like anything
that was kind of slightly even anything
moist or wet
right so like cucumber cut
open in pieces or tomato
cut open in pieces okay this is
important to know
right anything wet or
a soup in a lead bowl
okay anything like that would bring the
lead out
you get more lead off the plate anything
wet
that had any kind of mineral composition
tomatoes are high in minerals
right anything with a mineral
composition tomato
any kind of soup any kind of fruit
anything and
what it would do is when you put
anything like that in any kind of
minerals any foods
plant foods with minerals in them tomato
being a real
wet juicy mineral rich food
with a little bit of that acid right you
put that in that lead bowling lead plate
and then you draw the lead out
and that's why tomato and a whole bunch
of other foods got a bad rap
many years ago soup had a bad rap a
hundred years ago from lead plates
lead bowls people would be poisoned
after eating their soup
and then they'd be going through what in
the soup just poisoned me
because now you know my husband's laying
down he can't even breathe or move
we're all sick here at the table what
was it so everybody's like somebody
poisoned soup somebody poisoned the soup
but what was happening is we started to
learn that eating off of
lead plates and bowls was really a bad
idea and the tomato caused
like caught a bad wrap because
there used to be fried green tomatoes
fried green tomatoes fried green
tomatoes that was a big thing
fried green tomatoes that was a big
thing many many years ago
that was a really big thing and it was
fried in
oil and juice and all that and they
would go on the lead plate and
it would just kind of that wetness would
just bring out that lead
okay it's one of the reasons why i took
a bad rap
not because of night shade
everybody was eating off of lead plates
a lot of things took the bad rap too
a lot of things took the bad wrap so you
got a little side salad we're good we
got a little salsa here here's my salsa
right now this is my potato bowl you
guys
there's the potatoes right here on the
side i'm really psyched to have this
and that's the onions the the mushrooms
okay and this is if you like cooked food
you can eat salad if you're a raw fooder
if you're raw food or you only do raw
and that's it i totally love that
369 cleanse advanced you know that yeah
i talk about that it's just it's you
know all the time
living foods all that stuff but you can
still do your salads you can still do
your salsa
you can still have that it's perfectly
fine
you guys i'm heading off to ig i'm
heading out and then i'm going to turn
tick tock back on i'll turn clubhouse
back on too
this is this is the salsa right here i'm
going to put in the potato bowl as we
speak so i'm going to put a little bit
of this hot
salsa right here on the on the potato
bowl
so i'm going to sprinkle a little bit
around you can keep on adding it to it
you can put this on your salad too i'm
going to put a little bit on my salad as
well
excited about that there you go
so homemade salsa just put it on my
potato bowl what do you guys think
what do you guys think right and that's
salad on the side right there incredible
you guys heading off to
ig and tick tock again
yep looks amazing i am just eating m
potato salad and lettuce credible you
seem fine to me chris says tomatoes heal
inflammation
i had high histamines and avoided
tomatoes for no reason
that's because of the colts the cults
out there
they're the brainwashing cults of
alternative medicine and there's a whole
bunch in conventional medicine
and that's how it's done and there's the
science of research cult
and there's alternative medicine cult
it's all out there i'm not saying
it's all bad that's not what i'm saying
i'm just saying it's a landmine fee it's
a field of land mines that's all i'm
saying
my job with spirit of compassion was to
be able to tell you hey wait
wait that's a landmine wait no that's
good
wait that's a land mine that was my job
spirit of compassion has given me no
that's a land mine over there
right that's a lit nope that's okay
that's okay that's safe that's safe but
everybody else in the industry is all
about
market market market market sell sell
sell market market signs and research
so what would market market
market sell sell sell signs research
bullets
doesn't matter what land mines you step
in you guys i'm going ig and tick tock
i'm turning the clubhouse back on just
give me a few minutes i got to clean up
the
space for a little bit and remember
you're you're a high chaser until you're
taught
that they wanted you to be a high chaser
and then you learn
how to back out of that high chasing
sustain yourself
and when i if i hear that word
sustainability one more time i hear that
word fair trade one more time
all i do is i kind of line that up too
how about if we sustain ourselves
how do we learn how to sustain ourselves
how do we learn
how to be fair to ourselves and our
bodies you know
and we need to switch those words around
really take care of us instead of
downing a whole bunch of
cacao or matcha tea because it's
sustainable
and i'm sorry there's nothing about
cacao that's sustainable
nothing they're torturing people who cut
down that stuff right now
on this planet it's an evil industry i
love you guys
i'll see you on tick tock i'll see you
back on ig in a few minutes
and uh clubhouse i'll see you guys there
too take care