excited about this i kind of gathered
all kinds of stuff that was in my
refrigerator
and i'm going to make a great salad it's
important to know how to use leafy
greens how to incorporate them into your
life i'm also going to be talking about
vinegar
like acv apple cider vinegar other
vinegars i'm going to talk about
eggs so i'm going to do a little whole
thing about eggs too
so hey and gluten going to talk about
gluten that's just a few things
and so you don't want to miss this live
and let's get started
so you guys uh what i'm doing is i'm
going to steam up real quick in a pan
hey everybody coming on here some
cauliflower
some asparagus i'm going to put some
asparagus i'm going to chop some up
right now and
so basically what i'm going to do is
some lightly steamed asparagus and
cauliflower is going to go on top of
this potato
leafy green salad so i'm excited about
this
i don't want the asparagus to be real
small i want it to be kind of hunkier
pieces so
that's how i'm doing them here you know
you don't want to chop them so
tiny where they're in the smallest
pieces
good to see you guys coming on we're
going to talk about eggs
we're going to talk about apple cider
vinegar
might talk about b12 as well so we'll do
a little b12 talk
how it works inside the body what
happens how to kind of like
self-diagnose
all right be your own intuitive healer
so give you like tips on that
i'm gonna talk about gluten too as well
because you know hey
even though people say they're gluten
free a lot of people they end up getting
gluten inside of them you know they end
up eating gluten
happens all the time
um i was talking to a doctor the other
day and he said to me
he's teaching his patients how to
self-diagnose
that's what he told me i'm like really
you're a doctor
you're teaching them to do that he says
yeah i'm teaching them to
kind of have a feel as to hey when do i
go need to see a doctor
you know what's my symptoms learning
about their symptoms and stuff so
it's a cool doctor really it's teaching
people how to take care of themselves a
little bit
dr phone md
danielle says hi i can't heal histamine
intolerance
even even using your cleanse
what what else are you doing is it just
a cleanse did you do
one cleanse did you do a little
cleansing
have you did the 369 advance
have you done that so that's something
to
think about um how much fat are you on
that's another thing too when you get
off the cleanse are you tanking the fats
are you taking the nuts and seeds nut
butters oils
avocado are you doing anything else are
you doing animal
animal fats at all are you doing that
i'm cutting the cauliflower in half
these these little
florets right here
and is your histamine issue
really part of your issue that's another
thing too
is it just is it something someone's
just told you about hey you got high
histamines that could be your problem
are you
are you dealing with something else are
you dealing with some kind of viral load
so you're dealing with a viral problem
and you got a lot of symptoms
did you read the cleanse the heal book
and kind of get it
in some insight to what could be wrong
have you done the mono eating if you're
really worried about histamines maybe do
the mono eating how about that
that would be a good thing to do um i
just put some
cauliflower right here in the pan i got
some asparagus so i'm just going to
lightly steam this up this is going to
go in the salad
the salad is going to be really big
actually there's a lot going on with
this i got a lot of stuff here
um what do you do about post covet
symptoms i saw that question
um a lot of people are asking about what
do you do about that stuff
you know the funny thing is is in
medical medium new edition revised and
expanded
i have a whole section about the plague
about what happens the effects with
people
the aftermath all of this stuff so it's
in here
so this is on amazon.com
link is in the description
so i got some cauliflower some asparagus
going here so if you guys just got on
here everybody coming on here going to
talk about
um i'm going to talk about gluten going
to talk about b12 going to talk about
eggs i'm going to talk about apple cider
vinegar and other vinegars
that's just some of the stuff and cover
caffeine a little bit again so we're
going to cover a whole bunch of
different things
lots of stuff to talk about when it
comes down to histamines
the reason why someone has a histamine
problem is because they're viral
so you got to keep that in mind so if
someone
is viral low-grade viral infections
then your histamines raise and then what
happens is
the foods they're really just kind of a
confusion they become a confusion
in in it all but first of all certain
foods will feed the viruses
creating more histamines so and certain
foods will
kill the epstein-barr virus in shingles
virus cytomegalovirus simplex one virus
causing histamines so if if histamines
is something that you're monitoring or
someone's looking after your doctor's
looking after these histamines and
they're all worried about histamines
histamines but they don't know
what is happening like what's causing
the histamines why are these histamines
happening
so if you're eating foods to feed
pathogens like epstein-barr shingle
sediment
virus hhv6 hhv7 simplex one simplex two
and the list goes on if you're eating
foods to feed some of these bugs in your
body
then histamines raise right
then when you eat foods to cleanse these
bugs out
histamines raise because you're
cleansing and shaking up all that
garbage and toxic stuff that's sitting
inside your liver
so if you're trying a little bit of a
cleanse like
like the cleanse the heel one of one of
the cleanses or you're doing a little
3-6-9
and you're not sure where to go it takes
time because that liver is really mucky
really dirty filled with all kinds of
toxins filled with all kinds of bugs
with all kinds of pathogens
and it's just it's stocked up in there
and then what happens when you start
cleansing and cleansing it out you're
getting all that garbage out and that
could raise your histamines
just like the histamines were raised to
begin with because of all that garbage
building up
invite the light said i think i i think
potatoes bother me
bummer i'm making a potato dish making a
leafy green salad if you want to just
keep the cauliflower
and the asparagus in there without the
potato you're welcome to
um but potatoes
don't feed bugs it's really healing food
healing food on the digestive system
um very healing
what other foods are you eating invite
the light is there anything else
you you know you're doing you're staying
away from vinegar staying away from the
nutritional yeast right
staying away from those things um stay
away from gluten of course you're off
the caffeine right staying away from the
caffeine so you don't burn out the
adrenals
staying off the milk cheese eggs butter
all that's gone
and any new pharmaceuticals happening a
lot of people
they'll do new pharmaceuticals and all
of a sudden something's going on and
they're like what is it is it my food
meanwhile they had a new pharmaceutical
going on
so i got this about the steam up
lightly steaming some cauliflower got
some asparagus right here
so another thing about histamines if you
have old pharmaceuticals sitting inside
your liver and organs
you got benzodiazepines in there you got
old cold medicines in there antibiotics
anti-inflammatories whatever you have
that's still anti-depressants
anti-anxiety meds whatever you have
that's sitting in your liver
that stuff starts to come out those
histamines go up
up and histamine levels are kind of like
keeping an eye on just a marker like
what's going on inside the body nobody
knows but the histamines up
glad you guys are coming on there's no
oil
in this steaming it up just got some
water in the pan
waiting for that to get hot so i'm going
to start cutting some leafy greens
and making this out i got some spinach
right here
you can leave them whole leaf i'm just
going to chop them up a little bit
because this is a really big salad so
it'll help to
make it a little smaller in a way
you guys ready to talk about some stuff
let me just get some spinach in this
bowl right here
you guys have you ever noticed when i'm
making meals for you
it's rare there's a fat in the meal
right
you don't see any cheese thrown on top
of here which is fat you don't see eggs
thrown on top of here hard-boiled eggs
right you don't see that
okay you don't see any nut butters you
don't see tahini on here
you don't see avocado it's not that
avocado's bad for you avocado's not bad
for you
it's just you don't see that because
here's the thing everybody is eating fat
all day long almost every single meal
they eat
has a fat in it right and then their
livers get burdened down and they get
the weight later and they get the
stagnant
sluggish liver they get the depression
the metals oxidized they got all kinds
of problems
and what happens here is
the reason why i do all these no fat
meals i'm hoping that you guys maybe
make one and you're like hey that was
really good i didn't
need to drown that with oil i didn't
need to drown that with
you know lots of nut butter or avocado i
didn't need to put
cheese on top or anything like that so
i'm putting spinach in here i just
chopped up some spinach right here
so leafy greens are critical these are
trace mineral salts just so you know
this goes to the brain
this is good for the brain which is
leading me to the egg topic pretty soon
um i just want to show you guys how to
make healing
meals that don't have vinegar loads of
salt
all these fats all these oils all this
nutritional yeast
i want you guys to have a chance to heal
and not be
have to inundate yourself on all with
all this stuff in there like
vinegars and fats and oils and salts and
like because i want you guys to have a
chance to really heal
learn how to heal take care of yourself
i don't want to throw all that stuff in
this stuff then you guys don't heal
i'm going to chop up a little bit of
parsley right here why is nutritional
yeast bad
it's a neural antagonist it's irritating
on the nerves it's irritating on the
central nervous system it's irritating
on neurons
nutritional yeast
has a glutamic acid naturally embedded
into it
that's just one reason why it's it's not
that good
that glutamic acid attaches itself
to neurons wreaking havoc
okay okay i'll give you a couple other
things it does all right let's go into
that
let's talk about nutritional yeast a
little bit that was on my list today by
the way
chopping up parsley it's going in my
leafy leafy green salad if you guys just
came on here i got cauliflower i got
asparagus steaming up in here so
just going to kind of move it around a
little bit i got this steaming up
this is going to go on top of the salad
it's going to lightly lightly steam
these
for a little while nutritional yeast not
only has
a natural glutamic acid
that's a problem putting some
parsley in the salad
it's also an irritant to the intestinal
lining
so nutritional yeast is an irritant to
the intestinal lining if you want ibs
and digestive problems to get worse due
to nutritional yeast
it's one thing right there these are
sunflower sprouts
if you guys just came on we're going to
be hammering nutritional yeast for a
little while
so sunflower sprouts these are really
pretty
right don't they look great i'm going to
chop up some of these put these in a
salad
here's another reason why nutritional
yeast really stinks everybody says b12
is a nutritional yeast b12 b12 no they
add it
and they add a really bad one so they
add a
toxic type of b12 a synthetic b12
that's toxic that's what they add so you
got to think about this right
my acupuncturist says heavy metal detox
smoothie is too cold for me and it's
quenching my digestion fire i use frozen
bananas
boy there's a lot of science and
research in that one huh
i wonder what scientific study or test
determines your fire and your gut as
being
being quenching you're firing your guts
being quenching by
the heavy metal detox smoothie
look i'm not gonna pick on your
acupuncturist okay
but i've talked to thousands of them in
the last 35 years
and their training is about hot and cold
liver heat dampness spleen dampness
pancreas dampness
fire okay and so that's what their
training's in
right and i'm not ranking on that at all
i got a lot of close friends that are
acupuncturists with three decades of
practice underneath them
it's not not it
it's just that i always go by one rule
and one rule only do you know
why someone is really sick because
millions of people have been at two
their acupuncturists
and haven't recovered from severe lupus
multiple sclerosis okay crohn's colitis
eczema psoriasis i have not seen a
severe
case of eczema one where the person's
raging with eczema
and they can't live their life i have
not seen that dampest spleen
hot cold fire
fix it whether they're taking away cold
foods
putting in hot foods never seen because
the reason why unless you know why
someone has eczema
unless you know why someone has
psoriasis you can play all the guessing
games you want
and it's not going to fix somebody i
can't tell you how many people with
raging eczema has laid
they've laid on an acupuncturist table
suffered through the needles told to
stay away from anything cold because of
dampness in the spleen
and that and then they just that wasn't
an answer
i'm not trying to be difficult
i got a lot of respect for practitioners
of all kinds
a lot of respect
what i would do is the first thing i
would do is don't have it icy cold
defrost the blueberries
but see your acupuncturist might not
want you doing raw foods
so that might be an issue too a lot of
acupuncturists be like no only cook
don't do anything raw
no raw foods only cook only cooked
so a lot of a lot of um
acupuncturists might do that but if if
the concern is about it being
cold have the wild blueberries out
overnight
let them defrost let them become room
temperature make sure your bananas are
room temperature
does your acupuncturist know that if you
have toxic heavy metals it causes
anxiety depression no they don't
because they had never been taught that
so
if you have anxiety depression bipolar
ocd parkinson's
memory issues alzheimer's dementia the
list goes on to personalization
that's caused by toxic heavy metals so
the thing is is like i'm not saying you
have one of those conditions but if you
if you go to an acupuncturist and they
say you can't have
a smoothie because of dampness of the
spleen or something
and you're sitting there with severe
depression anxiety to personalization
alzheimer's dementia
you're not going to get any help because
you got to get the medals out but the
acupuncturist doesn't know that you need
to get your metals out you see how it
works
just think about that a little bit
i've never met an acupuncturist in 35
years of doing this work that knew about
viruses
they know about them now through the
work of the medical medium and all the
books that are out there millions of
books getting out there
but they never knew i'll tell you i'll
tell you i talked to the best
acupuncturist schools
some of the leaders in the best actual
acupuncture schools in the last 35 years
they didn't know viruses caused anything
they didn't know about the epstein-barr
virus and what it caused they didn't
know about shingles and what it caused
trigeminal neuralgia
they didn't know chronic fatigue
syndrome me they didn't know multiple
sclerosis was caused by epstein-barr
i've talked to leaders of the movement
over the last 35 years in acupuncture
schools and and they didn't know what
causes those things they were kind of
like just trained in one way where it's
all about
the meridians it's all about the
pressure points it's all about
it's all about dampness of the spleen
it's all about that kind of stuff and i
i
got total respect for that i'm not i'm
that's not i'm not judging anybody
it's just that i've had to teach a lot a
lot of
high ranking people in the field of that
medicine
about viruses and why their patients
were suffering with chronic fatigue
syndrome fibromyalgia
pots rinald syndrome
lupus whatever
this is steaming up it's coming out good
a little longer than that
um
i'm going to put a little celery chopped
up celery in this real quick
let me do that
i'm all about the real problems you know
the real issues to get better
see what happened was
i had to talk to 250 000 individuals
one-on-one
before the publications of medical media
medical medium books
and they already went to every single
practice some 30 doctors and different
practitioners some
50 doctors and the reason why
i even i'm even doing what i'm doing all
these years was because doctors and
practitioners and acupuncturists and
nutritionists and naturopaths
sent people to me with bizarre symptoms
tingles and numbness aches and pains
ringing in the ears vertigo skin
disorders of all kinds intestinal
disorders of all kind with no
answers
you don't think i've heard that a
million times don't drink a smoothie a
cold smoothie because it's gonna
blow your fire out all right well
don't eat a smoothie that's going to
help get the metals out kill off viruses
and clean things up
so you can actually get better
viruses and bacteria inflame nerves they
inflame the intestinal tract that's the
real issues that's what happens deep
down inside
and then your hydrochloric acid weakens
that's what causes weakness of the
digestion your hcl blows out
caffeine
you want to blow out your hcl
just get that liver stagnant and
sluggish fill it with fat
here's the here's the sad thing right
everybody's inundating everybody with
fat so every single practitioner every
single
every single nutritionist every single
doctor they're all about high fat high
fat eat lots of fat then you blow out
your liver you weaken your hcl and you
just stay
sick
all right you guys but actually
i'm gonna it's a lot going in the salad
i already put a whole bunch of sprouts
in there these are sun sunflower sprouts
by the way
really amazing this is parsley okay are
you guys doing parsley
are you doing it you're having it in
your diet these are leafy greens a
little spinach left over
i'm gonna do a little bit more parsley
inside the salad
those are pea sprouts i said sunflowers
bro i have a whole bunch of sunflower
sprouts
but those are those are pea sprouts
sorry about that
i'm making a potato salad steamed
cauliflower
asparagus is going on top i got onions i
got tomatoes here
i'm making sure there's lots of leafy
greens because of the mineral salts for
your brain
make you think clear you don't have to
be on caffeine for the rest of your life
when you get enough mineral salts over
time building back your neurons
everybody's on fat i get it everybody's
on fat everybody's eating fat
they're told to eat fat you can't get
off of it it's an addiction because what
you do is the more fat you eat
the more your adrenals have to actually
thin out your blood so you're high in
adrenaline
the more fat you intake in your foods
milk cheese butter
eggs pork
beef chicken not saying you know
you don't have to eat any of that um nut
butters
seeds oils coconut oil sesame oil
olive oil right
avocado the more fats you do
the more your adrenals have to
overcompensate and have to thin out your
blood
if you fill your bloodstream up with fat
all day long that's what everybody's
doing including chocolate that's another
one
you're forcing your liver
to produce all this bile to try to thin
out the blood all this bile
you're forcing your adrenals to pump out
all this epinephrine to thin out your
blood
you become this blood thinning machine
your whole body's purpose
is to thin out your blood you guys so
when you're doing fat all day long fat
for breakfast fat for lunch fat in the
middle of the afternoon
all your chocolate fat at night for
dinner all your chicken
it you got to lower the fats because
you're walking around with your body
trying to thin out the blood constantly
that's what you're
doing your body's killing itself to thin
out your blood
all that epinephrine is cranking out of
your adrenals to thin out your blood
your liver is pumping all this bile to
break down the fat to thin out your
blood you know why
because fat in your blood takes out all
your oxygen
and your brain starves of the oxygen and
once your brain starves at the oxygen
your adrenals are flooding all this
adrenaline we gotta thin this out we
gotta thin out this blood
and everybody's walking around like a
time bomb a time bomb
someday for a heart attack or a stroke
because their blood
is filled up with so much fat so i'm
just trying to make a fat feel
a fat free meal for you guys
it's fun all right so
what i got in here so far i got pea
shoots
right i got spinach in here all the
leafy greens and i got
well these are sprouts which is
incredible um and i got parsley in here
so
just mixing it up a little bit so what
i'm doing
hey you know the number one food group
out there in the world
it's eggs and caffeine
it's a number one food even more than
bread
eggs and caffeine even more than gluten
we're going to talk about gluten if you
guys just came on here i'm steaming up
cauliflower
asparagus i'm making a potato salad and
we're going to be talking about
apple cider vinegar we're going to talk
about caffeine we're going to talk about
um talk about gluten we're going to talk
about eggs
so i think i'm coming along pretty good
right there these are
these are car cars these are red oranges
they should be red inside
okay
here's a food that nobody eats
like they should right they'll do 10 000
chocolate bars
in 15 years 10 000 chocolate bars
but they won't do 10 000 of these
you know the whole world is set is set
up so you guys
age as fast as possible it's all about
aging
they age you the caffeine ages you
really fast
all the all kinds of different
techniques people are using to try to
heal can age them fast
cutting an onion right now you guys
i mean caffeine will age you quick high
fat diets will age you
fast you'll age really quick
with a high fat diet vinegar
will age you quick apple cider vinegar
you want to age quick you want wrinkles
by 32
just make sure you do apple cider
vinegar every single day it'll actually
help
you get there for wrinkles at 32
wrinkles at 28.
you'll have to go and you'll next thing
you know you're all worried and you have
to
you'll be thinking about botox or
something
i think this is steaming along really
good the salad's coming along good
poison ivy said oxygen i need to verify
with that science it's interesting
well can you verify this
250 million people in america alone with
symptoms
and conditions with no answers can you
verify that one
because i want to know how to verify
that let's verify that one
okay how about this one let's verify
this one
science said that eggs years ago
will give you a heart attack eventually
fill your heart up with cholesterol
now science says eggs are good for you
so what do you want to verify because
science stomps on itself constantly it
changes every year
so i'm confused are you trying to verify
something so that
it can be changed in one year from
another study
or change in six months because no
studies they all they're all stomped on
each other
they're com they're all run over by the
next science study
every six months by the next one every
year there's not one science study you
could actually
hold or talk about that hasn't been
stomped on
just shortly after
so what's happening is there's a whole
bunch of studies out there that that
are null and void you know do you ever
avoid a check
do you ever write a check and you wrote
it wrong and you were trying to write a
check and you wrote a wrote
wrong in your checkbook and then you
wrote void across it
well that's what science is it's a big
void
every single study has void written
across it a year later
every last one of them every food study
has void written over it
every single study
i want to know i want to know when are
they going to come up with that study of
why everybody's sick in the united
states and globally why everybody's sick
with the symptom and condition and
there's no answers
do you think everybody wants to be sick
because it do you think
the 250 million americans that are
really sick
right in this country do you think they
want to be sick
and they just don't want to embark on
what science has to offer to get them
healed and better
is that what it is do you think 250
million americans never went to go see
their doctor
because they don't want science to help
them no
they do they want science to help them
they're desperate everybody is
and science doesn't help them everybody
stays sick so
the six billion people on this planet
that have symptoms actually probably six
and a half billion people's honest on
the planet
that have symptoms and conditions do you
think they
don't want science to help them do you
think they just want to stay sick
six and a half billion people just want
to stay sick
i want to know where that study is
and here's the other thing no matter how
or what you say
science only has one answer a couple
little answers
it's it's your genes and that's why
you're sick it's your body attacking
itself
autoimmune your body's destroying itself
that that's an answer
the other answer is maybe hormones if
you're lucky that's an answer
um
and here's the new one from alternative
science by the way
here's a great one from alternative
science you're creating it with your
thoughts
you're sick because you're making
yourself sick
because you're you want yourself sick
that's the alternative medicine new
thought
that's their new science they believe
that you want to be sick
that you're making yourself sick with
your thoughts you're not good enough
you're not thinking good enough you're
not
you're not doing you're not mastering
your mind that's why you're sick so what
science are you talking about you talk
about alternative science because they
just believe you're sick because you're
not mastering your mind
now or is it conventional science which
just believes it's your genes
but no i but i love i love the question
i love the science stuff
[Music]
meanwhile it's not everything else it's
not the toxic heavy metals the mercury
aluminum cadmium lead
nickel that's in your brain it's not the
radiation falling out of the sky it's
not the radiation
on your plane flight that's more than an
hour it's not the radiation when you go
through the airport and you get
completely contaminated with radiation
your luggage is glowing
your luggage luggage is glowing and then
you're poisoning your children because
your luggage is sitting next to your
children after it's gone through the
machine
it's not that it's not the viruses and
bacteria that are eating people up alive
out there it's why they can't function
and they're sick
it's not the metals feeding the viruses
so people can't function either it's not
any of that no
science is so smart it's your genes
science is so smart it's your body
attacking itself
it's not all the caffeine you're doing
because it's the number one food group
next to eggs
so it's not all the caffeine and eggs
you're doing that's your food group
that's everybody's number one food group
it's eggs and caffeine it's not that
that's not why you're sick
i better find some science fast
science is gonna save us science is
gonna save us oh my god they're gonna
save us i'm a dog waiting for a bone
science is going to save us is it
another study coming around the corner
because i've been sick for 20 years with
hashimoto's
[Music]
anyway all right we're making a salad
you know it's incredible how everybody
is waiting for science to save them
with chronic illness ask anybody with
raging
eczema psoriasis did science save them
what about vitiligo did science save
them
what about multiple sclerosis about
parkinson's
i mean we got great surgeons and your
gallbladder explodes you need a good
surgeon
absolutely but i'm talking about chronic
illness with everybody walking around
like wounded soldiers
can't find answers they're just
suffering fatigue
depression anxiety they can't function
they don't feel good
body aches and pains dizziness skin
problems skin disorders
anyway here's what happened with eggs so
let's talk about eggs for a little bit
i think it's time so eggs were used
in labs many years ago to feed viruses
so that's what happened so eggs
were used against us they took the egg
right actually a survival food i have
nothing against eggs
i thought it was a good survival food
you know for like for centuries
because people could survive on it but
in the 1920s
1930s right around the 1920s actually a
little before that they took the egg
and they decided to use it
to raise bugs in the labs so
your herpes simplex 1
was raised in the lab your cold sore
is patented it's raised in a lab
it might be a mutated version now you
might not be patting it anymore
the original ones were patented
so your herpes simplex one your herpes
simplex 2 your epstein var your sediment
virus your shingles whatever it is
that's causing all your conditions they
were raised in labs
on eggs so they took an egg
and they fed that it's they actually
they cracked open the top they open the
top they put
they put the viruses in the viruses and
the bacteria the streptococcus
they learn how to grow them they learn
how to keep them
and now epstein-barr has over 60
varieties of mutations
shingles has over 30 varieties of
mutations as the years went on
everybody passing them around you know
around generations of passing them down
through utero
generations and passing them down
from from spreading them generations of
of
you know drinking off somebody else's
bottle drinking off somebody else's
glass oops now i got epstein barr
going into a public bathroom having the
water underneath splash
up splashed up your butt and now you got
streptococcus
now you've got strep throat a month
later and you're at the doctor's office
nobody knows why you have strep throat
everything was going okay
now you got a uti now you got chronic
sinusitis
now you got bladder infections now you
got yeast infections which is
streptococcus
um so the eggs raised
the bugs that were released out into the
world
that we have within us so the simplex
one
that was created from the egg so you
love eggs so much
but the eggs just feed that bug and then
causes more trouble as time goes on
all right so the this is good these are
steamed down good
i'm gonna shut this off
hey i just saw something this guy is
fear-mongering
it's pretty funny you say that
were all those women that had anxiety
back in the 50s 60s 70s and 80s
and they were they were knocked out
thrown on a table probes stuck up their
sinuses up their nose the front of their
brain taking off of them taking off of
them was called the lobotomy because you
had anxiety
hundreds of thousands of women had the
front of their brain removed
because they had anxiety
you just don't like truth that's all if
you don't like truth
i get it so you know what stay on your
caffeine
you know believe that the world is
perfect
if you want don't worry about all the
people who are suffering sick with
chronic illness who can't live their
lives
and they have no answers
but you know what lorraine l says it's
truth mongering more like it
it's about getting people better so you
actually have information
look if you got chronic etis chronic
bladder infections if you've got cfs
you've got fibromyalgia if you've got
lupus if you've got any kind of disorder
and you're eating eggs wouldn't you want
to know that if you stopped eating the
eggs you're one
more step closer to healing and getting
better or should i be worried about fear
mongering and be like no then just eat
your eggs don't don't come out with the
truth don't help people don't talk to
people
all right so let's keep on making this
so i'm going to chop up some onion i'm
going to do thinly sliced onion i'm
making a potato salad
but it's with leafy greens this potato
salad isn't with mayo
[Music]
just cutting up some onion nice and thin
so
i'm not going to cut these pieces up
real small so i don't want to do that so
i'm going to put a few on here i'm going
to put a few on later too
i want i want the onion pieces kind of a
little bigger even though they're sliced
then
you know everybody's on blood thinners
because the high fat diets by the way
their adrenals get burnt out it can't
thin out their blood anymore
cardiovascular problems
i think i'm going to cut up some
potatoes
these are these are gold potatoes look
at those
cheryl says is that is that why they ask
if you're allergic to eggs
before they give you a flu shot and
never understood that
eggs are in all pharmaceuticals just
just a 4-1-1
on that just a wake-up call eggs are in
all
pharmaceuticals
chopping up some potato here
eyes are watering from the onion
that red onion was strong wow that one
got me
eggs are in all pharmaceuticals
the silver toxic heavy metals
eggs will feed every single bug every
single pathogen you're worried about
candida
you're worried about sibo
you're worried about what are you
worried about nothing you don't think
bugs do anything you don't think you
have any bugs
you just think your body's attacking
itself for its jeans
well i mean i just got to give you the
4-1-1 on that one too it's bugs
so i'm cutting up a few potatoes
throwing it on top gonna put the steamed
veggies in
so egg is a good source of protein and
fat
let me tell you something about what
eggs do when you have endometriosis
pcos and fibroids
eggs grow fibroids
worsen pcos worsen endometriosis
that's what eggs do so
eggs are
an instigator of those conditions if you
have a reproductive system condition or
disease or anything like that
eggs will worsen it the worst thing you
can
ever do is eat eggs with pcos
the worst thing you could ever do
but yet you know no one no one knows why
you get pcos
they don't know what causes it they
think it's genes no one knows why you're
sick with any conditions or
endometriosis or any kind of
reproductive system condition nobody
knows
but they'll tell you what to eat and
that's how you eat lots of eggs
no science behind it whatsoever
got a tomato right here everyone's on
eggs
everyone is on eggs even vegans are on
right that's why vegans don't rip apart
eggs you know why
because they go back to them later on
the minute they get sick or something
goes wrong or they're like
wait a minute i'm getting sick and i'm a
vegan
they run back to eggs they start to
doubt themselves
they start to doubt why they're vegan if
you're vegan stay vegan if your
plant-based stay plant-based
if you're animal protein stay animal
protein if you want but just
stay off of eggs throw in some tomatoes
on here
everyone's sick everyone's getting sick
don't get fooled when you see young
people that
that escaped sickness early on
don't really have anything going on but
they get a cold they get a uti once in a
while they get some acne
don't get tricked because they're just
going to get sick when they're 40 years
old just like everybody else is now or
38 or 35
they're just gonna get sick and
everybody's eating eggs but it's not
questioned it's never questioned isn't
that funny everybody's on caffeine
everybody's eating eggs that's the two
food groups
two number one food groups caffeine and
eggs but it's never questioned
meanwhile everybody's getting sick but
those aren't questioned ever
they're not even looked at as an issue
but yet it's the number one
food group and if we're always going to
walk around saying
food makes us sick food is thy medicine
food is what keeps us going food's what
protects
us food is what you eat is what you are
whatever you want to do realize then if
this is the number one food group which
is eggs and caffeine and we're all sick
on the planet
huh no one's looking at the number one
food everybody's eating
these tomatoes look really good
i'm gonna cut up some more tomatoes put
some more onions on top and i'm going to
put some
putting some onion on here so listen to
medical medium podcasts at apple podcast
have you guys been listening to my
podcast
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
i have an egg episode with a lot of a
lot of questions you know answered on
that
i'm going to put some of these in here
some of these steamed vegetables
i steamed them up in the pan got some
asparagus
cauliflower right here you guys
science is so smart right
that they want you to be on lots of meat
if you're anemic right
that's kind of always perplexed me it's
a head scratcher for me
because everybody who's anemic they're
on meat
so you i can't tell you how many times
i've talked to people who are anemic
and they said the doctor wants me to be
on meat i said well what's your diet and
they said well i eat meat
i go you you've always eat you've always
eaten meat
like yeah i've always eaten meat then
how does that work your doctor tells you
to eat meat because you're anemic but
you've already been eating meat your
whole life
do you guys see the irony in any of that
cause of anemia is toxic heavy metals
plus viruses low-grade viral infections
such as epstein-barr
that's the anemia virus
and they feed on iron there's certain
varieties of epstein-barr
certain mutations that love to feed on
iron and that's where we get the
the mystery anemia
aretha says i thought tomatoes
are inflammatory
they're not inflammatory that's a that's
a myth
absolutely but pizza the tomatoes are
really inflammatory on pizza because
your pizza is going to have cheese it's
going to have
which is really highly inflammatory it's
going to have gluten in the crust
which is highly inflammatory it's going
to have lots of oil in there
lots of salt salt on a high levels
inflammatory
meaning salt that's added in like sea
salts and
rock salts but or
pasta with tomato sauce on it right
it's not the tomatoes that's
inflammatory it's the gluten in the
pasta
it's the cheese it's the parmesan cheese
parmigiano-reggiano it's all that on
there
gianno it's that's what makes it a
problem
tomatoes are anti-viral tomatoes are
healing
there's vitamin c in tomatoes so
these are actually this is actually a
healing food we need a fresh tomato
not a green tomato it's got to be a nice
ripe red tomato look at these tomatoes
is that is that incredible right these
are antiviral
antibacterial see i love foods that are
antiviral
because when you eat the asparagus
that's antiviral
okay the asparagus right there antiviral
cauliflower the sulfur in cauliflower
which is what we're partially made out
of is antiviral right
you got all the different greens in here
antiviral
so anti epstein-barr anti-shingles
anti-you know neurotoxins
so the reason why people get inflamed is
they'll have low-grade epstein-barr if
you want to learn about this you want to
know how to heal
i mean the new edition check it out
revise and expand it medical medium new
addition learn how to heal
your conditions and symptoms learn how
to find out what's going on what's wrong
with you because you can find the
knowledge in here
bring it to your doctor talk to your
doctor
all right guys i got the salad coming
together let's see what else is going to
go on here i'm going to put
sage so i got some sage right here
some fresh sage
[Music]
yeah doctor prescribes iron pills
absolutely
doesn't know why you're you're anemic
though
doesn't know how to fix it it's why
millions and millions and millions
hundreds of millions of people walk
around anemic
and it doesn't get fixed because nobody
knows why
putting some sage on top of here
put a little fresh sage that's fresh
sage going on top
put a little bit more onion on here what
i'm going to do
[Music]
slicing it kind of thin
so talk about vinegar for a little bit
too so let's go into a few different
things well i got you guys here
[Music]
by the way there's an r.a protocol in
the book rheumatoid
arthritis protocol in the book right
here medical medium new edition it's in
here
michelle's asking what else you got
i don't know if that's to the meals or
something else
putting a little extra onion on here i
put some sage on there
put a little bit more onion on top i'm
going to put a little bit more tomato on
top of the salad too so i still need
more
of that might garnish it with a little
bit more parsley too
what you'll know about these meals that
i'm making you guys
i'm trying to offer healing healing
meals that aren't loaded with fat on top
of it to get your insulin you know
resistance off the charts because that's
what the fats will do when you pound on
the oils on top of this and
get your you get insulin resistance and
i don't want you to get insulin
resistant
these are fat free meals
helps to protect your pancreas your
liver
your pancreas your liver your adrenals
these are meals without vinegar meals
without pounding the salt
meals without pounding the oil i'm
trying to give you
nutritional yeast vinegar
salt fat free meals
so vinegar pickles are the inside of
your organs
dehydrates you dehydrates it sucks the
water
out of every cell in your body so that's
what vinegar does
every time you eat vinegar you're
pickling yourself
just like pickles in a jar and when you
add vinegar and salt together
you pickle yourself even more okay and
you don't want to be a fermented food
like you don't want to be
a fermented food you know that's not the
goal
that's not what your body wants it
doesn't want you to ferment it it
doesn't want you to suck the life out of
it
your body is always subjected to all of
our idiotic ideas
here on earth that's what it's subjected
to it's subjected to
caffeine it's subjected to eggs it's
subjected to
because now eggs are are not good
anymore because what i told you guys
about
what they did to them they ruined them
on you it subjected like
to the nutritional yeast subject it to
the vinegars like i said subjected to
all the salt
subjected to all the oils
fermented foods was a survival food
because in the country
you took your garden vegetables
everything you had
left and you took them and you stuck
them in a big container
and you fermented them so
that you can stay alive when winter came
because you had no electricity you
couldn't you couldn't have you didn't
have a freezer
to freeze your food you didn't have a
refrigerator to keep your food you know
fresh
plus you didn't have options to get more
food coming in more food coming in
it was a survival tactic around the
world
okay because when winter was approaching
your garden was picked it was done you
get one last term
you know turn up you get a few more
greens or onions or whatever you get out
of your garden
and then it's done for the year you take
everything you had cabbages whatever it
is and you shove it into that
and you ferment it to make it last
longer for survival it was just a
survival tactic
it didn't mean it was the answer see the
world has changed you have fresh produce
now
you don't have to go back to that you
got fresh produce you could take care of
yourself
you got fresh priest you know pea
sprouts fresh
parsley spinach
you don't want dead decaying food
and that's what happens fermented foods
not like when you cook something down or
steam it or you have all these raw
vegetables fermented food
is dead it died it lost its
life and the bacteria on
fermented food is death borne
bacteria that's what that is it's not
living bacteria when you pluck parsley
out of your garden
it's got microorganisms on it that's
alive
that's living because the plant's living
when you take this and you ferment it
and it dies now the bacteria
is for death it's like when an animal
dies in the woods
it gets overcome by bacteria
that's death feeding bacteria
that's why you know when we die we get
overcome
by bacteria really fast that's why they
embalm us to stop us from breaking down
when vegetables and plant life die it
gets engulfed by bacteria
but we're not supposed to be eating
death ridden bacteria
we're supposed to be eating
microorganisms that are on your spinach
leaves in the garden
that are on this orange on the surface
if you grate a little bit of the orange
peel
um you know on the sage in your garden
right here
fresh fresh picked asparagus
that's the bacteria that we're supposed
to consume
rose says well i guess you are the
authority then
peace out glad eating more vegetables
and removing animal
fats helps people nothing new here
that's
a head scratcher for me rose to be
honest with you
because uh the whole high fat
movement going on that's been going on
forever well
medical medium information 35 years ago
put the pin in that bubble about fat
being bad
so that's 35 plus years of work for
medical medium to teach people low fat
so interesting because guess what
it was a small health movement back then
and i talked to everybody i lectured
about it
i wrote about it you name it and the
circuit
back then 35 years ago knows who i was
and knows who i am till this day
and knows why avoid fats is out there to
the extent it is
even though it's not really out there
because everybody's pounding the fats 24
7 and the keto diet is basically out
there
you know doing that whole thing with
fats and all that another thing too is i
don't say get off of animal protein
that's another thing too so it's like
removing animal fats well
first of all if you want to eat chicken
you can eat chicken but you can still
heal if you want to eat animal protein
you could eat animal protein
but you can still heal you can i've been
talking about you got to lower it
and know when to lower it when to eat
your animal protein
how to get your morning cleanse in the
morning so you're not doing
fats in the morning that's medical
medium information not doing fats in the
morning
so all that's important too um there's
so much detail in it it's not just as
simple as eat some fruits and vegetables
and you're good
what about all the wild foods that are
in the mm protocols what about the wild
foods
what about the no vinegar with no
nutritional yeast oh that's out there
um sorry but i'm the one who put that
out there about no nutritional yeast
no vinegars and all that other stuff too
and then the true cause is a sickness so
if you're not learning about the true
cause over here about the fact that ebv
causes fibromyalgia because
that's published material for medical
medium or
shingles causes trigeminal algae which
is published material for medical medium
it's important to know all these little
details i love when someone tries to
round it off
and say hey you know sure nothing new
here some fruits and
vegetables and get rid of animal protein
i mean
that's all great then if that's the
answer and it's nothing new then why is
everybody sick
and why is everybody sicker than ever
before and why is everybody in the
health movement getting sick
and running for their lives to the other
side animal protein people running to
their lives to the vegan side vegan
people running to their lives for their
lives in the animal protein side because
they're all still sick having problems
oh my acne is back again i thought my
vegan diet would fix it
whoa wait a minute i was eating fruits
and vegetables oh wait
uh wait my uti's are back i thought my
animal protein keto diet would fix it
i'm back on vegan everybody's running
back and forth
and because nobody knew it was pathogens
so medical medium information is the
first time ever
we got answers and more people and more
healing stories than ever before in
history from mm info so yeah
you want to just you want to throw
everything out of context not look at
the details
say hey nothing new to figure out here
good be on your merry way i'm glad
but i'll tell you when you get real sick
down the road and
you can't get better no matter what
vegetable you're trying or whatever
somebody's telling you to do or whatever
collagen someone tell you to take
whether animal protein or not when you
can't get better down the road
and you're 40 years old or whatever
you're 42 years old and now you're sick
and you saw your 10th neurologist
remember medical medium information
because it saved a tremendous amount of
lives around the world
right here revised and expanded
but i'm glad you're here though i hope
you stay on um
annette so fermented veggies are dead
but cooked or not
correct i'm so confused
correct okay so
cooked is the state we put them in so
that's the state
we put the food in okay
so when a vegetable is alive
and dies and decays
a natural death okay
that's a different situation
we don't take you have to understand
when we eat animal meat you kill the
animal
right so people do they kill the animal
okay and that's forcing
that to die you see
we forced the food to die in the moment
people kill animals to eat animal
protein they force
the death on the animal right it's not
an animal dead in the woods that died
no one will touch the meat the meat's
gone bad
now the raccoons and the coyotes are
coming
you see the difference so if an animal
dies naturally in the woods
and it just falls to the ground right a
bear
a deer whatever kind of animal or a cow
in a field
just dies and falls over and it's
sitting out there
and it's starting to decay it passes a
deadline
there's a difference there you're not
going to go out there be like that cow's
been dead for like
two days i'm gonna go cut up a piece of
meat you're gonna be scared to death of
that cow
scared the death of that meat but when
they
fresh kill and preserve the food
it's a different story when you have
fresh produce and yes you steam it
it's it's a variety of killing it but
not the same
thing what happens is there's not going
to be any of that death bacteria growing
in this steamed cooked food right now so
when you steam a cauliflower you steam
asparagus
there's no bacteria that's going to want
to surface
and start to devour it through a natural
process that we're not supposed to be
involved with
we're not supposed to be eating death
bacteria there's none of that here
we forced this to cook bacteria is not
going to overcome it
and it's freshly cooked that's the whole
point
it's not like decaying fruits and
vegetables
or decaying vegetables really and then
it's sitting in vats while the death
while the grim reaper the grim reaper's
bacteria comes and overtakes it the
stuff we're not supposed to really eat
and um that's how it works
the bacteria that's inside your small
intestinal tract your duodenum small
intestinal tract and colon is not the
bacteria that's on fermented food by the
way i'm just giving you a 4-1-1 on that
that's not what it is
the bacteria that you want inside your
colon
an intestinal tract okay your duodenum
small intestinal tract and colon
is the bacteria that's on something you
picked out of the garden that has
elevated biotics on it that's actually
living on the leaf so that when you eat
the parsley in that moment
you're getting that elevated biotic
that's where you get the microorganisms
and it goes down into your helium then
it sits down in there and it creates b12
now if you ferment this parsley
and ferment it and that
grim reaper's death bacteria okay
is in there with it that doesn't go down
to your helium it doesn't even make it
down
there it gets killed off by your hcl in
your stomach
it's not the bacteria that actually
produces b12 and it's not the beneficial
bacteria that actually gives you life
so it's important to know all right
put another potato on top of here
actually you know what i'm going to put
just finish this tomato right here
now you can do vinegar that's not that
doesn't have the bacteria and you can do
acv
that has bacteria mother right
well that mother never passes your
stomach
it gets eaten up by your hcl whatever's
left of it
something now i'm gonna put a little bit
of this orange squeezed on top
now personally me i would like a nice
fresh juicy orange like that and not a
fermented one
[Music]
squeeze a little orange on here
i'm going to put a lemon on here too
vinegar robs minerals from your teeth
and bones
more vinegar you do the more you lose
your teeth later on
vinegar is the teeth dissolver the teeth
destroyer
that's what it is it robs calcium from
your bones
calcium from your teeth
because when you put
acetic acid inside of you you need your
body to dig out calcium
so your body has to find calcium because
acetic acid is so acidic it's so bad
that you need your own calcium to try to
neutralize it
your body pushes out as vinegar sucks
the life out of you it sucks the
minerals out of you it sucks the calcium
out of you
your body pushes that calcium out of
your teeth like here here save my life
your body tries to save itself by
emitting
calcium from your bones and teeth when
you take vinegar i don't care if it's
acv it's all the same
look there's all kinds of different
spices you can put on a salad
all right so let me just give you a
quick run down here i got tomatoes i got
onions cauliflower asparagus right
right everything's in here spinach pea
shoots
and uh parsley um i'm gonna put a little
chili powder on top
can't help it
vinegar is a like it's a preservative
it's you ha i'm not on a preservative
diet
i don't do preservatives all my stuff's
all natural um why are you putting acv
on your food that's a preservative it is
yeah
it's a preservative acetic acid is a
preservative
putting a little chili chili uh pepper
on here
it's acetic acid
it's a preservative you don't want
preservatives because you end up
pickling your own organs
your liver it goes into like
shock when you dump too much vinegar in
there because it goes up into the liver
and when it goes up into the liver
you're pickling your liver
you already have salt in your blood
because we have sodium naturally
occurring in the bloodstream
right i'm not even just talking about
the sodium we're adding and what happens
is when you
put vinegar and sodium together
you're now really preserving your organs
you're pickling your own organs
look i don't have fun telling you guys
all this stuff
all right this is onion powder
it's got really a great flavor when you
put it on top of like a potato salad
with all these vegetables
there's not much on there i probably did
a teaspoon and a half and a little bit
of ground coriander i'm going to put on
top too
a little bit on top
um so you got to think about that
it's just like a jar of pickles you
stick acetic acid in there
and you stick salt and now you got your
pickle in the middle
and the life is sucked out of the pickle
which is the cucumber the life is sucked
out of it the more vinegar we do
and the salt we do we're slowly sucking
the life out of our
we're trying to preserve ourselves we're
preserving ourselves
in a bad way you see how it goes
and then on top of that all the other
stuff we do
some of the most powerful people in the
world always reach out
um some of the best doctors in the world
reach out
and they're always they always tell me
the same thing many of them ask me the
same thing what
is what should i look out for what
should i do
you're the number one health author in
the world seven years young seven years
running
millions of books around the world more
healing stories than ever seen in
history
what what do i knew it what do i need to
do that's with people the most powerful
people in the world who reach out to me
like what can i do anthony
and i'm like first things first get rid
of the vinegar
right there get rid of the eggs and
they're like what what
i've been to 100 doctors the best
neurologist in the world i travel around
in my private jets everywhere
and go see the best healers ever what is
this
and i'm like no vinegar like okay i
better write this down
most powerful people in the world they
got the best doctors the best care they
can find
let me write this down and with all that
help they're trying to find and the best
healers are still sick and like
i'm like yeah get rid of the vinegar
okay get rid of the caffeine
huh caffeine i heard it was good for me
no get rid of the caffeine
get rid of the eggs eggs i have a
hard-boiled egg every morning get rid of
the eggs
like why because it's feeding your virus
that's making you sick and giving you
your lupus
it is i haven't heard that anywhere
you know anyway that's just one of
dozens of examples put a little lemon on
here to finish this off
you guys i talked about b12 a little bit
i want to run this b12 thing by you
right here
here's what you have to understand if
this has nothing to do with animal
protein me liking animal protein or not
has nothing to do with this it's
information you have to see it like this
if you're somebody that thinks you're
getting your b12 from your animal
protein you're not
because b12 produced by
animals isn't the b12 your body utilizes
it's there for the animal our bodies
need a certain type of b12 okay
one either produced by us or one
that's a methylcobalamin
adenosilcobalamin so that's the vimergy
one that i take every day
so that's how our bodies work
so if you're not eating all of the
garden
vegetables that have the microorganisms
on top
to create your own b12 and your ilium
then you need a supplement that's how it
works
and so like that's the one i recommend
all the time is the vimers you want i'm
not sponsored
but if you think you're getting b12 from
your chicken you're not because the b12
is create that your chicken creates
is b12 for your chicken that was when
your chicken was alive
it needed the b12 to stay alive that b12
identifies with its own nervous system
and brain
and the same thing with the cow the
cow's b12
is produced for the cow's nervous system
and brain
the b12 we produce is produced
for our nervous system in our brain
right and our organs
that's how it works with b12 so hey no
you're getting pl
your vegans don't get b12 well animal
protein people don't get b12 either
plant-based people don't get b12 they
don't
no no one's getting b12
no one is unless you're eating
enough vegetables greens
out of your garden or picking
fresh berries out of your garden
and there's the microorganisms on top of
there that microorganism goes down to
your helium and creates your b12 right
but people lack this
and they don't have enough of those
fresh picked vegetables with
microorganisms
on it and so plant-based people
animal protein people vegetarians
they're not getting b12
so in order to heal and heal
neurological problems you've got to
supplement with b12 i've been saying
this for years
and i've recommended different b12s over
the years
that's the best one there is on the
market today in the highest quality with
no junk and no preservatives know
anything and it's the vimorgy one
so if you guys want to know the b12 i
use it's the vimergy these are victor
i-m-e-r-g-y
but b-12 is make or break in your
healing process
i'm going to be straight out about that
it's make or break in your healing
process
b12 is critical you got fibro you got ms
you got lupus
you got dysautonomia you got whatever it
is pots you got parkinson's you got any
kind of condition
it could be memory issues anxiety
depression b12 is
make or break it really is been saying
that for years
i talk about it in the books i got the
b12 i talk about in the new edition
okay it's make or break
and that's the difference and i teach
doctors that all the time
if they're not getting enough b12 well
hey mr william well the only thing is is
they look like they
they test okay for their b12 that
doesn't test
how much b12 is in their brain and
nervous system you can't measure that
there's no blood test that can test how
much is in the brain and nervous system
or in the liver you don't know so you
have to keep the b12 going i teach
doctors this all the time it's make or
break to the finish line of healing
anyway you guys it's a full moon
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
free meditation you guys know it the
moon meditation
you guys should take advantage of it do
it the next few days i have been i've
been doing the moon meditation it's a
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
it's the moon meditation
it helps heal emotional wounds from
betrayal trust
broken trust broken betrayal
all kinds of emotional wounds hardships
breakups and relationships wounds that
we've
stinging in our life people letting us
down
right being let down whatever it is
happening or if you're just struggling
with a chronic illness
the moon meditation take advantage of it
have you guys done it i know many of you
guys have
yep yes love the moon meditation
um carol says he has incorrect
information about b12 b12
is bioavailable from meat it's funny
because there's no science that
determines that
so i guess you're just making it up
because
i have a source so carol i actually have
a source of information that's already
proven to track record and healed
millions around the world
okay so that's already there i don't
have anything to prove
but science has a lot to prove because
they haven't proven that
there's no science study that says it's
bioavailable for meat
they haven't even determined that they
can't even measure that so
science has let you down okay but
apparently
the information to get people to d the
tools they need
from my source hasn't let people down
and millions of heli are healing because
of it
and bodies are still a mystery to
science why people are sick so
okay science knows that they believe
that they do
well 250 million americans are sick with
conditions and symptoms
billions around the planet are sick with
symptoms and conditions
but they know all of a sudden that meat
is bioavailable they can't even measure
that they can't even test that
think about it it's not even testable
there's no study that actually shows
that they can actually determine if it's
bioavailable
that doesn't exist so i get it throw
stuff out there if you need to
totally get it but you know it
your information is wrong that's all
your information's incorrect
but you know what the street cred is
here
millions have healed raging eczema
psoriasis disorders
all kinds of different conditions
anxiety disorders gut problems you name
it have healed when nothing else could
that right there is already a proven
track record
and that information came from my source
and my source
says okay instead of science says my
source says
that the b12 produced by an animal is
made
for the animal that animal had no
understanding that it was going to be
used for people to eat
animals the animal's body wasn't
designed or made
to determine it was going to be eaten
someday that's not what happened
so the animals b12 is for the animal's
nervous system to survive
it's not for a human's nervous system it
does not code
over to a human to a human's nervous
system
your b12 that's produced in your
intestinal tract
is the is the b12 that's for your
nervous system
so just a little food for thought there
you guys check out the moon meditation
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
listen to the b12 episode that's what i
would do
um anyway heading to ig
and tiktok you guys i love all you guys
i love even the questions
that you know are like hey you're wrong
or whatever it is i love all you guys i
appreciate you being here seriously i
hope you're here next time carol i hope
you're not here next time
throw some more questions at me when you
can i love it
because i want to help in any way i can
and it's great stuff um
patty smith says love your excellent
information i learn each time
36 years as a pharmacist a monitor here
patty
thank you for being here truly i'm
heading over to ig and
tiktok at the same time and if something
happens like a glitch on ig or something
um just watch me on tick tock it's in
it's a way better view i notice
than ig lately it's like you see a lot
more
okay i'll see you guys i love you