live live on facebook live on youtube
making a potato bowl it's gonna have
some nice onion in there
it's gonna have asparagus see i got
beautiful asparagus right here you guys
and it's gonna have potatoes too so i'm
gonna chop up some asparagus and get it
going right away
we're talking about today how incredibly
important it is
when you're sick that everything you do
matters right we don't want to go 10
steps ahead
and then go 25 steps
backwards we don't want to do that right
we want to go
ahead and if we go backwards a little
bit
it's only in the natural process of
healing and then we go ahead even
more so it's like the three steps up two
steps back sometimes
boom three steps up again two steps back
right
three steps up again two steps back
and we don't wanna go ahead
we don't want to go three steps up
25 30 steps back and that's what's
happening with so many people trying to
heal with so much information out there
just letting you know
i want you guys also to check out a
podcast episode
that i just listened to that blew my
mind okay it's reframe with jenna
zoe that's the podcast right it's it and
it's incredible it's with heal with
amber
right amber visicarro some of you guys
probably know who amber visicaro is
right
she's healed with amber and here with
amber's on there
and she's talking to jenna zoe and
they're both seasoned
in so many experiences in health right
and they're talking about medical medium
information and i listened to it
and i was blown out of my seat when i
when i was listening just blown off my
seat really
so check it out it's reframe with jenna
zoe that's the podcast
it's the podcast episode 24. with jenna
zoe
interviewing amber visicarro which is
here with amber
and after you know after you guys you
know later on when you get a chance or
anytime
you know whenever you get a chance a
link is in description for this podcast
episode
that i heard you get a chance share it
with everybody you know share it with
anybody and everybody
when i listened to it i was like huh i
was just blown away they're discussing
medical medium information discussing
their experience
anyway we're live right now making a
potato bowl lorraine l i saw you come on
michelle
i saw you come on elena's on people
everybody's coming up right now
and coming on and this is an important
episode
because you don't want to go you don't
want to go
10 steps ahead and 25 steps back
and what do we what do we need to not
let that happen how
do we avoid that from happening
how do we look out for ourselves as
we're trying to heal
like how do we avoid potholes i call
them potholes i always did right
snags potholes right
and i want to talk about that but i want
to cut up some asparagus margaret
margaret valentine good to see you
coming on you seem fine to me
chris chris what's up
what's happening christopher you're
going to be uh watching ig later
um going to be on ig later tick tock
right
3692 even after that
i'm going to steam up some asparagus
right here i'm going to get it cooking
yeah so we're doing that
um let me go get a utensil too
cooking utensil that would be nice to
have one there
i got asparagus in the pan so you guys
it looks like we're censored
tonight to a point that's to a level
i've never seen before
so there's only 200 people on in total
between youtube and facebook
so we are actually we're actually
super duper uh super duper
censored so this is very interesting
um that means no one's allowed to come
on tonight so if you guys made it on
it's a miracle i'm just letting you know
it's a miracle
um so anyway
seriously that's like as censoring as
censoring can ever be
well look it's an intimate small crowd
it's good i like that too so i don't
mind so i'm gonna get the lid on here
just moving around getting it to kind of
take so i got some asparagus i'm
steaming up i'm making a potato bowl
and i want to tell you guys first of all
what i do every day
right or every other day and so forth i
take a bunch of potatoes i cook them up
i steam them up right in a steamer right
and i have all these potatoes and then i
put them in the fridge
and i don't put a lid on them in the
fridge because the potatoes can get
kind of spongy right so
i don't like to um i don't like to put a
lid
on a bowl and have potatoes in it that
way
i like having the lid off the bowl when
it sits in the fridge so when i steam a
whole bunch of potatoes
i like them kind of like dry like a
little bit dry
and to do that as i put them in the
fridge it's just the way i like it you
might like it where they're
moist after you steam them and they're
moist right you might be somebody that
likes that way
hi monica glad you're coming on there um
and so what i like to do is keep them
kind of like in the fridge
with the cover off right of a bowl
or you know no saran wrap on there or
anything like that and then i like i
like the air just getting to them in the
fridge
and then they stay where they stay in a
way where they keep dry inside
just a little trick i want to give you
right now nicholas says how long do you
steam them
you got to steam them until the fork
goes through them right that's what you
want to do
you don't want them hard in the center
you want to steam them and it
it depends on where you are what
altitude you're in
right and around the world could be at a
higher altitude lower altitude
so can't i can't give you a time because
it may not be the same time
right and you might have hard water you
might have
soft water all these things make a
difference right so
when you're steaming but you want to
steam them till the fork goes through
right you want to catch them
you don't want to overcook your potatoes
but you want to make sure they're
steamed all the way through
so your fork goes through right so that
could be 45 minutes for someone it could
be 40 minutes for someone
depending on where they live what kind
of water they're using it could be an
hour this is in you know important
information right
and so these are steamed potatoes
they're already steamed
and then i like have it i have like this
big bowl of steamed potatoes right guys
and then i could use them in the way i
need to use them
where i could use them for different
things and i'm going to reheat them
in this pan in a little while and make a
potato bowl so
i'm excited all right so i got the
asparagus steaming
right here yeah
27 minutes for you chris wood really
when you steam potatoes
wow just saw ashley kevin hey ashley
glad you're here
yeah amazing um so anyway guys
[Music]
uh got this to this steaming so let's
talk about some fun stuff
and cover some important information
right what happens
with what's going on out there there's
so much information just swimming around
in the alternative arts right
so what happens is you get sick okay
you go to your conventional doctor right
and your conventional doctor is like
let's just try to figure this out
and you're in for the ride okay it
happens to people who are really sick
where
or they're getting sicker they're in for
the ride now doctor wants to draw some
blood
they take a little too much blood you
know they take a little too much
blood they're taking five full vials
seven full vials
10 or 12 or 14 full vials and they start
removing your immune system right
without realizing it without even
knowing what's wrong with you to begin
with so they start removing your white
count
right your red count right pothole
number one pothole number one
okay and i've talked about that you guys
know how it works where you can talk to
your doctor
about like half files and so forth
because the labs take half files the
labs take quarter vials right
and then maybe scheduling more
appointments at the doctor for blood
work where you're doing some tests so
you divide the tests
um elena anthony my white blood count
went back to normal range
after your protocol and supplements and
they were
really low for the last five years thank
you so proud of you i'm so proud of you
that matters because that can really
help you heal
incredible and so you go to your doctor
and now your doctor's like well it's
trying to figure out what's wrong with
you right
and they run some tests they'll do some
blood work
and what happens with people that's just
the beginning of the rodeo
so that's just the beginning of the
rodeo that's the start of the rodeo
you know that's the start of the musical
chairs they haven't even gone into
alternative
venues yet alternative medicine yet
alternative directions yet
they haven't even gone to there they're
just in the realm of like you go to your
first doctor
and what happens is then when you're not
getting better
you go back to your first doctor then
you go back to your first doctor and
then you go back to your first doctor
and then a family member is like you got
to go see another doctor
or your doctor says you got to go see
another doctor a specialist and now
you're off to see another doctor another
specialist
and this could last 20 years for someone
doctor doctor doctor specialist
specialist doctor specialist dr gp
specialist dr
dio whatever and then all of a sudden
now
you're into alternative medicine and now
you know you're into naturopath
herbalist naturopath herbalist
nutritionist naturopath herbalist
functional medicine doctor
chinese medicine doctor herbalist
naturopath functional medicine doctor
now you're doing this right
and and then but what's happening too is
in the alternative arts healing arts
there's all this information that's
swimming around
and that information doesn't mean it's
the best information
okay doesn't mean that's the information
or the tips
or the different trends or the different
style that's out there or the different
diet is gonna be
right right but one thing's for certain
is elena says they took
one or two vials from me this time thank
god
and i wouldn't allow more mind-blown
mind-blown because i know you're taking
care of yourself
mind-blown all right incredible
okay it really is that's incredible
all right so michelle l says i've done
it all
and michelle i i i believe you i know
you have
i know you have so anyway we end up
trying all these different things all of
a sudden and we don't know what's really
working or not for us
kind of up and down up and down we don't
know what's really working you know is
it the keto diet well you got off
processed foods so that's helping
is it maybe you went vegan and you know
you because of you went vegan you got
off all these
processed foods right fried foods maybe
you're trying a bunch of different
supplements so your doctors are loading
you up with all these different
supplements and maybe there's something
in some of those supplements that's
actually giving you something yeah
but there's also things that we get hurt
by that sends us back right i've seen
for years good hearted good
compassionate natural doctors
or naturopaths or really good
chiropractors
or you know good md's right whatever
that are giving out all these
supplements they wholeheartedly want you
better
they want you to heal but there's
alcohol in all their supplements alcohol
i've seen this for years
okay i've seen this in the alternative
healing arts
with uh with a natural doctor
out there okay that has a lot of
programs out
all right and but was just
constantly dumping all these alcohol
you know all these alcohol filled
supplements and
that's already a no-no you can't get
someone to the finish line
when maybe one person you'll get close
enough because you're doing all these
other good things
but the alcohol supplements will it will
stop somebody from getting to the finish
line and then we go backwards
or that's just one thing right just
using it as an example
and so and and then there's the whole
thing where
when someone gets sick and they're
really getting sick and they're really
sensitive
and anything could kick him downhill and
then now we're in the land of the lost
and it matters like we can lose
ourselves we can lose ourselves in that
fight
um kim kim pave said
i couldn't even get out of bed and
listen to your podcast on my way to the
mayo clinic for answers with my
anti-nuclear antibodies next day
i bought your book a juicer celery and
three days later i felt great
now i'm honest now i'm on supplementing
heavy metal detox
and 369 cleanses and feeling amazing
thank you incredible
incredible i mean and you know how to
stay out of trouble
you know how to stay out of trouble
because there's all these land mines and
i call them land mines
i call them land mines by the way uh
uh oh karen churchill was diagnosed with
15 autoimmune diseases dot dot having
follow
followed aw that number is going down
one after the other
even had my doctor say i could not heal
from diabetes
incredible really incredible um
i gotta play onion games lorraine
lorraine
i have to play onion games again so
letting you know the onion games are
going to actually happen with this meal
um and michelle i think michelle said
that too ichoda you're here tonight
amazing so
um anyway guys we're talking about how
to protect yourselves what to look out
for you don't want to go 10 steps
forward
and 25 steps back you don't want to go
three steps forward and
10 steps back right you want to go three
steps forward
another three steps forward another two
another one step forward another two
steps back
but you're already way ahead of where
you were when you started and then boom
three steps forward again now you're one
more step
ahead of the two steps right and so it's
this whole thing
even if it feels like you went 10 steps
back
but you're healing and moving forward
than you ever did and i want to talk
about something else but we don't want
to really go backwards and we
never get to heal and we're stuck and we
can't go forward and we never get to be
where we need to be
we can't get there we don't want to go
there we don't want to be there right
really important um
so let's go into a different aspect of
this which is critical let me get the
white blood cells in the cpc off my
my little counter here my little uh
board
and let's talk about like some of the
fundamental
like like rules i could call them roles
i guess right because we can make our
own rules
right and we can make our own
way right and we can choose what we're
what what we want to do in medical
medium information what direction we
want to go in right and one of the re
one of the ways i do it with friends or
family
that decide hey i want to do this right
a friend will call me up i haven't
talked to in years
be like look i need to heal
i'm really sick what do i do and i'd be
like first of all
get rid of the troublemaker foods how
many troublemaker foods
can you ace or 86 how many troublemaker
foods can you
get out right like which ones my friend
be like well
what do you mean like milk cheese butter
okay that's important right there for
troublemaker foods
and
and you know so for example like
okay everybody loves the cheese sticks
right they love the cheese sticks i got
some cheese sticks here right
everybody loves their eggs it's a half
hard-boiled egg right everybody loves
your cookies
everybody loves their bread right
okay that's one there everybody loves
their chocolate too right their ice
creams
everybody loves all that and it's like
what can we remove
right some of you guys are like that's
easy i don't need any of that but then
i'll talk about other stuff too that we
got to worry about
um and in a friend of mine like what do
you mean i can't have cheese
so okay i don't eat cheese that's what
they'll say right i've heard this a
million times i don't eat cheese
i hardly eat cheese i don't eat cheese
meanwhile if you really go through
everything
that they ate that week there's cheese
everywhere it's like oh yeah they had a
slice of pizza sure they had something
else they had a salad with cheese
crumbled cheese on top right they had
something with blue cheese they had
something with something else they had a
you know whatever it is cheese is
everywhere okay pasta
with cheese on there right and so
that's one thing right there that just
has to go if you want to heal it's about
moving some of these these things out
these are basics though
they weren't basics they weren't basics
35 years ago
right people wanted to chop off my head
when i would say you got to get rid of
the cheese it was so
foreign so foreign and so unbelievable
people would look look at you in
disbelief you're even saying remove the
cheese 25 30 years ago 20 years ago like
remove the cheese what
and you know and that's that's how it
works and then the gluten too
there's another thing you want to get
the gluten out of there austin you're on
tonight
good to see you get the gluten out get
the cheese out
get the milk get the butter out you
can't
heal and still eat butter now someone
will disagree
someone will disagree with that right
there someone will say that's not true
i got off the processed foods i got off
of fried foods
i started eating a very healthy organic
pasture-raised diet i started you know
taking care of myself i got this
incredible you know cheap incredible
butter
right i got this great butter and i
churned it myself right which is better
than buying store-bought butter
definitely and better than buying butter
that's not good
i raised the animals myself or i bought
it from a farm where i
take care of the animals they raise the
animals and i can
you know and the butter is so good and
i'm healing
well then you you just aren't that sick
you're just not that sick one thing what
people will do too
is to state their case they'll say they
were sicker than they
were now in all fairness
anybody who's sick with a symptom i'm
fighting for
always remember that but i also know the
reality
when it comes to stating your case on
social media i've seen a lot of people
where
and i've talked first of all i've talked
to a lot of doctors that know
their patients cases right and
everything i took a lot of different
people and i've heard from
all kinds of people along the way too
professionals that
tell me well this person yeah they got
some fatigue but it's nothing like this
person who can't
budge and get out of bed so see the
differences but yet the person who's got
fatigue
might might might actually express
that they can't get out of bed but
they're out every day
right they're out of they're living
their life still you know
and i get it there's moments where they
probably can't get out of bed there's
moments where they're stuck
but then there's somebody who's really
stuck like really stuck where they get
out and they're like
can't even they can't even get through a
kitchen
chore they couldn't even imagine being
here and doing this
like for like a half an hour it's not
going to happen
right but then you can get somebody
who's yeah they got fatigued yes they're
sick
yeah they got some low-grade viral
infections yeah all the things that
medical medium information is about
right
but they're able to actually still take
care of themselves they're able to still
do things they're able still to function
right but
but and you know and that kind of person
might go on this clean diet right and
then do this
homemade butter thing and be like i'm
getting better
i'm getting healthier i'm doing the
clean butter but when you when you're
really sick
though right and really struggling
that's when you know mice are men
that's when you know make or break
that's when you know do or die
that's when you know is it right or
wrong that's when you know it's going to
work or not
that's when you're going to go good or
not right which just that's when
it's going to be the deal breaker the
deal breaker right
you can go around not that sick
i got this gluten-free bread i could do
the coconut ice cream
oh no that's the coconut vegan ice cream
yep
yep that's right okay i can just go
through life
yeah i'm sick i'll go see my
acupuncturist for a little tune-up
i'll go see my massage therapist for a
little tune-up you know
i'll go hop into a sauna somewhere you
know i'll go do an infrared sauna
i'll do a foot bath right yeah i'm not
i'm yeah i'm sick
i'll go to see my functional medicine
doctor he'll load me up with the
supplements he thinks
he'll load me up with the gut health
supplements he'll load me up with ever
right
but they ain't that sick
it's it's there's these different levels
of there's the not so sick and i've
talked about this
guys and there's the so sick there's the
sick there's the not so sick
and the sick and then there's the not
sick they're not sick yet
right and right there's a not sick
so sky bird clay said i stopped taking
bp
meds because my bp was always up
my bp is going down with celery and
detox
with a heart and lots of eating clean
can't wait to get my supplements and
start the 369. cleanse sky bird
incredible
incredible mind-blowing so you know
you got the not so sick and you got the
sick
right they're not so sick can afford to
play around
do some yoga here i'll go do this juice
here i'll go do this gut health product
here i'll go do this protein
protein powder here i'll dump some apple
cider vinegar here i'll go listen to my
guru here i'll listen to my other doctor
here i'll go get a ton of blood taken
out
here here right whatever and they're
hanging in there
they're hanging in there they're not so
sick okay and
but when they're not so sick start going
over time whether it's five years later
two years later whatever it is
or they're not they're moving out of
their 20s
they're not 21 anymore they're not 23
anymore they're not 25 anymore not 27
anymore whatever it is moving into the
30s or they're not 35 anymore and
they're moving and
and then they're getting sicker it could
be any age this happens
and that's when yo
it's make or break all these things
count
every last bit of it all these little
things
matter you're traveling and your luggage
goes through that radiation right
that luggage luggage goes through the
radiation and you're traveling
right you know what i love about live
you know what i love about doing it live
you can actually not put enough water in
a pan because you're too busy
too busy teaching and you lose you lose
your asparagus are actually done so i
got to take them out
but anyway the point is is when when
we're in that position
right where every little bit counts
you've got your luggage glowing in the
dark because it's going through the
radiation machine
okay and you're getting all that
radiation because your luggage is so
filled with it because i talk about how
you got to throw out your luggage over
time
i talk about that i'm going to actually
take asparagus out and get it ready
because i got to cook some other stuff
for you right now
um and but the bottom line is
all these things matter and
you guys i love having you in my kitchen
i got to be honest it's the best okay
it's the best to have you guys in the
kitchen
these are actually really done they
cooked really quick
do you ever guys guys ever find
asparagus that are
um you ever find the asparagus that are
big like this
these are new asparagus they're not the
old asparagus canes you know i'm sure
you guys know your asparagus by now
right
many of you probably already have known
it all your life but
these are the young asparagus right here
the thick ones the thick juicy ones
they're so good for you but listen
here's the other thing doesn't mean
don't do your asparagus right
understand this part right here is that
is that you can do the skinny asparagus
which is an older asparagus meaning the
canes are older the asparagus is older
right
and it's medicinal too there's two forms
of like medicinal when it comes to
asparagus two levels of medicinal
there's
level there's a level of medicinal with
the young asparagus which is juicy like
this
okay there's a level with that and then
there's a level with
um and there's a level with
uh the older asparagus which is like
really spindly thin have you guys ever
seen that
it's really thin
so what i'm going to do is chop up a
little onion so we're going to play
onion games as lorraine
l said
i think couple people were saying it too
which actually made me laugh
someone might think what's medical
medium talking about right now it
doesn't sound that interesting
um but this is this means everything
when it comes down to healing just so
you know it means
so much when it comes down to healing
i'm gonna be straight out about
you guys can you hang on for one second
i just gotta get some onions
i'm back
medical medium in the house if you guys
just came on i was talking about earlier
how
uh jenna zoe
is a ho is the host of her own podcast
uh reframe with
jenna zoe right and she had amber
socarro on and that's heal with amber
okay and they're talking about medical
medium information
i just listened to the podcast episode
and i was blowing off my seat
just letting you know check it out when
you can you guys like check it out the
link is in the description
they're very seasoned with what they
went through themselves
um amber's very seasoned with how she
helps people so she actually
works with people and she's very
seasoned
healing with amber and um
i was mind blown on how much knowledge
they had in general
i mean because because the knowledge was
they had just so much experience when
you hear their experience you're just
like oh my god
i mean it's a lot of experience and then
talking about medical medium information
anyway i recommend listening to it
so i'm currently going to caramelize
some onions if you guys don't mind
i got the heat up on this all right
and onions can kind of when you
caramelize them they can kind of
maybe one onion's all i need for this
that could work good
[Music]
so okay so anyway back to the potatoes
we'll cover that a little bit too
um after you caramelize the onions i'm
gonna work with the potatoes
right and um you guys if you just came
on here i got some incredible
asparagus the big juicy ones i put it in
the side of the bowl because what i'm
doing is i'm making a potato bowl and
i'm gonna do the asparagus the potato
and the onions
it's gonna be a great great bowl of food
yeah i'm not crying while cutting them
that's coming elena
that's already on its way it's already
on its way
so tara appleman good to see you
incredible
honored you're here um it's an honor to
have you here
awesome tara's so awesome um so these
are pre-steam
potatoes is what these are so
pre-steamed potatoes
and i'm going to chop them up in cubes
that's what i'm going to do in a little
bit the onions are already hitting me
so letting you guys know lorraine you're
laughing um
so i like to prep ahead of time on this
dish so i already have my potato steamed
i'll make a big bowl of potatoes put it
in the refrigerator
let it sit in there and as i was telling
everybody earlier i don't put a lid on
it because they get too moist in there
and they start getting a little moisture
built inside of it and they get a little
spongy
so i don't like that i take the lid off
so the lid's not there
and then i keep it in the fridge and i
let them kind of dry out so if i need
them in there for a day
or another day and i need them in there
i have them there and i could use them
for all these purposes that's what i
love
um so you know uh
you seem fine to me chris hey talk about
gout
gout's the liver that's the liver that's
when the liver is it
the liver has said i can't handle
protein anymore
or fat the liver's just like i'm done i
can't handle protein or fat anymore
[Music]
and sometimes the liver can get pushed
over the edge for people
and then then the liver gets deficient
like it gets deficiencies
so your liver is now deficient your
liver is your vitamin converter
that's your vitamin and mineral storage
bin right
the liver just holds it all chris thanks
for uh
because i wanted to talk about gout a
couple times and i keep on i keep on
forgetting and i
i want to talk about gout definitely
so when it comes down to the liver
okay if your liver is really
overburdened
really overburdened okay and you're
getting those purines and stuff
and when the i just want to keep an eye
on those
hold on
i don't want to do what i did to the
asparagus with the onions this time
and you know what happens is that when
people are worried about their diet
they're worried about purines and
everything else and
all that's happening i want to talk
about that
what i what i worry about when you have
gout
what i worry about is protein and fat
protein and fat
that's how it goes wrong with gout
that's my concern
and a concern that i've taught doctors
over time it's a very important concern
and um gout is something that
is fixable it can heal it probably one
of the easiest
one of the easiest things that can heal
that that i've seen
it's like diabetes too you know diet
type 2 diabetes easy to heal gout
easy to heal that's when we just have to
care for the liver
and you know what happens with gout is
chris you know what happens a lot of
people without not everybody so
you know a lot of people look out
they'll have uh
skin problems dermatitis they'll have
eczema they'll have psoriasis when they
have gout
right they have skin issues or their
skin is just terrible
their fingernails are terrible their
toenails are just
god-awful right like a lot of that
happens too now you might be somebody
with with
gout and you don't have any of that yet
and you might have a different variety
of gout where it's not like
out in your feet it's not gout in your
toes and ankles
it's gout somewhere else in the body and
the doctor's like i don't know what to
call this thing i'm pretty sure we're
dealing with gout
you know smoky mountain paradise good to
see you
and so the whole thing with gout is
about cleaning up the liver my
number one concern is protein
and fat those are two things that the
liver said
i'm done with i can't handle anymore i
don't want anything to do with it i
can't handle the protein can handle the
fat and that's what the liver does
then you go deficient people with gout
they get all these
mineral deficiencies all these vitamin
nutrient nutrient deficiencies these
phytochemical compound deficiencies
that's what they get
because their liver is like well i can't
process the vitamins anymore i can't
store the vitamins anymore
there's too much fat in here there's too
much desiccated protein stuck
inside the liver everything's gummed up
that the inner works
that the waterworks inside your liver
are
just done you know the liver is not it's
not that you're
in liver failure or anything like that
that's not at all you can have gout your
liver seems okay i've seen people with
gout
don't even have elevated liver enzymes
so if their liver is trashed
because it's not it's not always black
or white black and white it's not always
like that it's not always just
you know it's not it's not two plus two
equals four when it comes down to that
so somebody might have
somebody might have um elevated liver
enzymes
with gout someone might not right
someone might have a bilirubin off the
chart
with gout someone might not right so
these things are really important to
know but that's that's what i
always tell people so if you're on a
vegan plant-based diet
be careful on how much fat you're eating
because your gout is going gonna be
there
even vegans get gout vegans have gout
you know it's like
yeah i know it's amazing how there's a
whole bunch of vegans and plant-based
people out there and once they start
improving with a vegan plant-based diet
right they're not out of the woods yet
but they think they're out of the woods
yet and then they just get sicker later
because they're doing all these other
practices they got the fats cranking up
they're cranking the fats up they got
other stuff going on and you know they
just get in trouble
um sarah hazel i thought keto was the
healthiest diet until i ended up with
gout
yo that's what happens the ketos for men
that aren't sick what's the ketos for
keto diet
the old keto diet used to kill people
did you guys know that
did you guys know that the old keto diet
used to kill women
yeah uh i'm not exaggerating
i'm straight up i was telling a doctor
that the other day and he said you know
what i remember there was this case
where there was a woman in his practice
that
that that left his practice and it was
years ago and she just
did this keto thing and she had no
glucose gold or system go to her
neurological system had no glucose her
brain was missing the glucose and she
was on a keto
the old keto diet was you you can't have
a starchy vegetable
and you can't have a fruit you can't
have honey you can't have anything the
old keto diet now
when women would adhere that when they
would
when they would go by that playbook and
do it perfectly
no honey no maple syrup no coconut water
no uh no avocado
the old keto diet you weren't allowed to
do the avocados right avocado has sugar
in it
see you know they brought the avocado in
in the newer
keto diet you see the old old keto diet
killed a lot of women
they died they just died they were sick
no one knew what was wrong with them and
they died they lost the glucose to their
brain and they died and they
ceased they ceased living okay now
the new keto diet turned into a non-keto
diet it's not the keto diet anymore they
use the same name
keto but there's sugar in it
everywhere there's sugar in it
everywhere is the avocados there's nuts
and seeds there's nut butters there's
sugar and all that
right there's fat in there and then the
new keto diet's got berries in there so
what happened was medical medium
information was
against the old keto diet
okay and
medical medium information has healed
tens of thousands of people over through
the years tens of thousands before
publishing the book
right the books the first book right it
changed the
shape of all the diets out there now
whether they understand that or not
whether people know that or not
the keto diet of the old day i i
forewarned
women about because it kill it will kill
you
you lose your glucose to your brain and
if you're sick you could die because of
that right
so i'm just caramelizing these onions
right now which are coming out nice this
pans really hot
as we speak um so let me just
kind of talk a little bit more about
this this is really an important
topic it's a part of how things are just
all screwed up out there
so now the keto diet see ketosis
your body would go into ketosis if you
took sugar away
right well now the keto diets
they have sugar in there so you don't go
into ketosis so why
is it called the keto diet you you ask
yourself that
i ask you to ask yourself that i'll ask
myself that right now okay
why do they call it the keto diet when
you
can't go into ketosis anymore because
they have berries in the keto diet
and they have avocado in the keto diet
you can't enter
the ketosis state so why is it called
the keto diet anymore
because in alternative medicine there's
a billion and one screw-ups
even your simple wholesome keto diet of
the day
that's in the magazines that's online is
screwed up
and wrong wrong in the sense where they
don't even understand it
yeah no i'm on the keto diet i'm doing
the i'm a i'm a guru i'm a trainer i'm
on the keto diet
right but they're on the keto diet
but they're not on a keto diet you can't
go into ketosis
you can't when you eat an avocado can't
you can't you can only go into ketosis
if you with frame from
every single starchy vegetable every
single form of sugar every single
carbohydrate
and you just rely on meat alone
andrea are you are you saying we
shouldn't have hardly any fat at all
what do you think about eating avocados
nuts and seeds olives coconut and olive
oil those are all healthy fats you just
mentioned
andrea all healthy fats depends on how
sick you are
right if you're 21 years old you're not
really sick
you've got a little acne and you want to
clean up your diet you want to stop
eating at the fast food restaurants
you want to stop partying right you know
like keep the alcohol down
clean up your diet start to live a life
where you're like
you're into health now you want to do a
little lifestyle channel or something on
social media and you're 22 years old or
something
and you're now doing avocados nuts and
seeds and nut butters you're doing
peanut butter smoothies you're doing
peanut butter acai bowls right
yeah you can get away with it if you're
not that sick you get sick man you wanna
you wanna back down on those fats
whether you're plant-based or
animal protein you wanna back down all
those fats so i'll talk about keto for
another minute too
so these are getting caramelized right
they're coming out really good i'm about
to put them in a bowl
so
all right and then
but the keto diet today is not the keto
is not a keto diet
what it is it's just a clean diet right
but
when you're sick even the keto diet of
today that has taken medical medium
information and placed it into it which
are berries
no one cared about berries it's 35 years
of medical medium information going all
the way back when i was trying to teach
everybody about berries berries berries
no one cared about berries right
and and so now that the keto diet has
berries in there
you're not and you're you're actually
being protected a little bit so your
keto diet can actually get you by but if
you're a woman
and you're sick right and you need more
you'll need more than just your plain
old clean new
keto diet keto diets are for men that
aren't sick
they want to lose a little weight and
they want to hop in the gym and start
working out and then tell women
tell women how why they're sick
and then tell women what they're doing
wrong you need honey you need to be on
the keynote keto diet like me and get
into that gym
the keto diet is for like is is is
really
designed for men that aren't sick right
the keto diet can yeah sure if you're a
woman and you're not sick and you want
to do the keto diet and you get into the
gym and you clean up all the
donuts cakes and cookies you're going to
see benefits but if you're
really struggling with the condition
whole another bald part
that's when the keto diet can make you
sicker and get you in trouble
and that's what happens okay so i'm just
putting these onions in here
like this now i'm going to cut some
potatoes up
so i'm going to do that now um
okay cut some potatoes up
i'm going to cube these
if you take somebody that's really sick
and they got they got neurological
symptoms
they don't know why they're sick they've
been to a bunch of doctors maybe they
were diagnosed with lyme disease maybe
they were diagnosed with something else
and they're really struggling okay and
you take
you take um these potatoes are already
steamed keep that in mind if you guys
just came on here
they're already steamed so i'm making
the potato bowl
which is really fun to make
what was i frying the onion in a little
tiny bit of water
no oil needed no oil needed
at all so
now i'm gonna put a little these are
already steamed these potatoes so i'm
not gonna really i don't want that pan
filled with water i don't want this
potato soup
okay so i don't want this potato soup
these are
potatoes right steamed potatoes in here
making the potato bowl
so
am i totally again you know there's
protocols by the way
for gout in the medical medium books so
in the books
cleanse the heal as a protocol freak out
in here
i'm not against the keto diet you know a
clean diet
if it's if it's helping you stay out of
you know standard american diet junk
food cakes cookies donuts
um fried food i'm on board
but if you're really sick we got to go
to the next level you know
we just have to
yeah you know
i've said this for years right
burger king used to say
burger king used to say we're the next
level we frame
we sorry we flame broil okay
liver rescue my book level rescue too i
can show you talks about gout whole gout
thing in there
um all right there we go we got our
potatoes in here
burger king would be like we flame broil
that's like the next step that was the
next step above
what they used to say mcdonald's burger
king used to say we're the next step
above mcdonald's we flame broil
that's what they used to say right and
then you know
and then you can go to the next step
above burger king right
and now you're at another restaurant and
they're using
more they're doing more vegetables more
salads right
so then you're at that place then you're
at the next level right
next next restaurant chain that next
restaurant chain
they're doing a little bit more salads
they're doing a little more vegetables
now they got avocado going in there so
now they got guacamole in there right
but they're still doing other stuff
right so you're going there's these
tears right
well it's kind of like this you can be
keto diet but take it to another level
you can be another you know it's just
like it's all about the next level the
next level the next level keto diet is
just
is a place you can go but
it's interesting stuff actually
so i got some potatoes going on here
ashley kevin
what what is the brand name for celery
force candace it's
um vimergy so is it having a celery
force there's celery force right there
i recommend it to friends and family
that you know it's like it just
for me it helps me it perks me up
that's you know for me um
incredible i love it for the brain
so i got some steamed potatoes on here
toasting up right
here which i'm excited about
so right now i have this bowl building
up i got the asparagus right here you
see this i got the caramelized onion
right here the asparagus now i'm going
to get ready to put potatoes in here too
very excited
i'm going to toast up these steamed
these are steamed potatoes came out of
the fridge today
so great like how easy is that they're
already kind of browning a little bit
this pan is really hot right now
athena says thrush is a possible cause i
get that from using
steroids
that's interesting
so um so the point of this look the
point of this live right now we're live
on youtube we're live on facebook the
point of this live is to talk about how
we can avoid
getting stunted getting stuck
getting pushed back and knowing
information knowing the knowledge is
really important right there
angie wynn says what's your opinion on
b12 injections
well yeah
yeah yeah i just got my b12 injection
uh-huh
yeah i know i get them once every other
week
mm-hmm what they use the bad b12
you mean you mean not like intravenous
like iv you mean the injection like they
stick a needle in your
arm to just jam you and your arm or your
butt
that's the ones i get right yeah they're
bad
what why are they bad
oh your body just your body
when it comes down to b12 your body
likes to
receive it orally so your body
likes to get oral b12 i see
so you don't bypass the liver your whole
process your digestion process your
liver
so the b12 has to go
in your mouth and then find its way
down to your ilium let me see if i got
an ilium here
uh uh-huh
so your helium down on the right side
that's where the small intestinal tract
connects to the
large intestinal tract that b12 has to
find its way down there
because that's where you produce it and
then
that gets driven up into the liver and
then the liver converts it
ah i see i see so when you
stick b12 in your bloodstream directly
in the arm
like this you're not utilizing it
and then maybe could even build an
allergic
allergy to b12 without the doctor ever
knowing and then there's an allergy to
b12 i see
all right i got to look out for that i
think what i'll do is just focus on the
b12 drops in my mouth okay bye
um
so what i like to do for friends and
family
right these are potatoes are actually
coming out these are coming out like
hash browns
whoa love that like hashbrowns you guys
so what i like to do with b12 oh here's
here it is
um the liquid b12 right here is the
adenosil cobalamin
and methylcobalamin and the b12 shots
unless you got a doctor that's doing ivs
that's different going directly into the
vein
um um cali says i got terrible allergic
reaction after b12 shots
i'm not a fan of b12 shots i've seen too
many people get allergic reactions
there's
there's preservatives in b12 shots
also the chance that your body could
build an
antibody against the b12 because the b12
is entering without your body's
permission
when you enter it in the mouth or in the
vein itself
through intravenous either or right
mouth is the best i've always
recommended right
when you enter it in the mouth you're
you're giving your body's giving you
permission right when it goes to the
outside of the body
and when it's a shot a needle it's going
against the body's permission
the body might build an antibody to it
so that you become sensitive to b12 i've
seen this over and over again
i taught about this too for years and i
still can't believe
it hasn't gotten out there well if i
keep on getting censored like i am today
on facebook and youtube
it's me it's it's a no wonder why it
doesn't get out there
um but anyway the b12
that's the liquid one the venus of
cobalamin and methyl
methylcobalamin combined right the
combination that's the word the liver
loves the most
what i recommend i'm not sponsored by
these guys but i recommend this one for
my friends and family that's the vimergy
v is in victor i
am as mary ergy dot com vimrgy.com
what about intravenous vitamin c that's
in your vein
sammy sammy loom that's in your vein
that's not a shot like the b12
shot right the needle going into the arm
directly into the muscle in the
bloodstream
when it enters into the vein like a lot
of a lot of practitioners do
do uh ivc they throw some
methylcobalamin
in there they throw uh uh you know
multivitamin they'll do the injection
in your vein right that is different
your body won't build an antibody
against it
these are turning into toasty hash
browns and they're going to go in my
potato bowl
how does look i can't wait to eat this
i'm going to be i'm going to be shoving
this down right in between this
now and tick tock
and then it's the right kind you can get
intravenous stuff but is it still
preservatives
there's intravenous vitamin c that's not
the good kind of vitamin c
you have to you have to make sure that's
not corn derived
vitamin c intravenously that's something
to know there
but getting back to what we were talking
about earlier 10 steps forward 25 steps
back
we got to be careful got to make sure
your iv
your ivs through intravenous the vein
right
if you're doing nutritional therapies
through ivs that there's no
preservatives
important that one there all on its own
or the vitamin c is a corn derived
that's another one too
okay these are actually done
they're nice and toasty i am gonna put
these right here
see if i can do this right
um so anyway
all the all this is important
information there's so many tidbits
can i give you a quick rundown you guys
right
if i was trying to heal i'd stay away
from
apple cider vinegar nutritional yeast
diatomaceous earth particles
sodium bicarbonate right just lost one
i would stay away from bentonite clay
i'd stay away from clays
in general okay i would stay away from
from that i would stay away from zeolite
i would stay away from alcohol and
supplements
preservatives stay away from natural
flavors stay away from msg stay away
from milk cheese butter gluten eggs
i'd stay away from so many things
because it's critical
if you want to heal see guys you can do
a couple things with this what i like to
do is just throw a little sprinkle a
little touch of
um well here's the thing you guys
there's a medical medium hot sauce
there's a medical medium ketchup there's
a medical medium honey mustard
or mustard there's a medical medium
fresh salsa there's a medical medium you
can find these things right
and i'm going to mix this
but you know what i'm not going to mix
it because i wasn't planning on mixing
it
all right but i'm gonna lift up the
onions right here
lift them up and lift up the asparagus
because i buried them is what happened
okay i could i could have used two
onions because that's what i was
that's what i needed so
there's one onion in this one here's the
caramelized onions
here's the potatoes that were steamed
originally and then
then kind of like refried in the pan no
oil
right incredible that's your asparagus
right there that's steamed and cooked in
the pan
how amazing is that you love the medical
medium salsa
kalyn michelle love the medical medium
salsa i do too
love the medical medium salsa
now um you can put
cilantro on the bottom of this right so
i got some cilantro here
now what i didn't do is i didn't put the
cilantro on the bottom and place this
all on top but you can
how amazing you guys i'm heading off to
instagram
in a few minutes i'm heading off to tick
tock so it's tick doc and instagram live
and then after that i'm heading to 369
on instagram and tick tock and that's
going to take us later into the night
uh why not zeolites they dehydrate
they rob you of electrolytes they're not
the same zeolites uh
years before they take electrolytes when
you're sick and you got neurological
problems it's the last thing you want
and um there's a lot of zeolite that's
pushed into the medical medium community
now they're saying oh you need to have
that with your medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie no you don't
no you don't the only reason why zeolite
never gave anybody any benefits no one
saw benefits with zeolite all these
years it's been happening for 20 years
and no one saw that right
but the heavy metal detox smoothie
macromedia heavy metal detox movie gave
people benefits so what
they do is they try to say well take
that with your take it too with your
heavy metal detox smoothie and as people
get benefits from the heavy metal detox
smoothie they think it's a zeolite
because
there's 20 000 admin now and mlm
marketing and
pyramid schemers working on it now and
be like no it's your zeolite that did it
and they're all like there's just
everybody's trying to sell a zealot
i'm not saying that the people are bad
they're doing it not at all their hearts
in it they're compassionate
um people i'm i'm sure and all this
other stuff and
i'm just saying that it's not the first
time people try to hop on the medical
mean bandwagon and try to push stuff
that medical medium doesn't recommend
all right i love you guys heading off to
ig and tic toc
and thanks for