live live on facebook live on youtube
live on clubhouse at the same time just
letting you guys know
and it it's really a great day because
i'm excited to talk about our topic
today first of all making a potato
waffle
which is really fun all on its own right
and if you guys are just coming on live
on facebook live on youtube that's how
we do it
live on clubhouse too and the really
awesome thing about
today's topic is how can i protect you
in
any way possible even if it means i
get the beat out of me for doing it
you know it's like how do i protect the
chronically ill
people with symptoms and conditions
people who have been
through hell and back people that have
literally have to rise out of the ashes
and get their lives back
how do i protect you guys
while getting lashings
left and right right you know and so
it's it's like this
look at it this way you know i'm not
about making friends
okay if i'm gonna make friends
then you guys are just going to get the
same old run around
you're going to get the same old run
around
that's what's going to happen so if i
worry about the apple cider vinegar
dealers
okay you know if i worry about them and
don't worry about you guys then we're
gonna you know
there you go you guys are gonna be all
losing your teeth right
if i worry about the caffeine people if
i worry about the cacao
people don't wanna get anybody pissed
off in the health world
don't want to get anybody upset in the
health world right okay
and i worry about the caffeine in the
coffee people the big coffee moguls
the coffee industry and everybody else
who's trying to make a rishi mushroom
coffee
or something else if i worry about any
of that if i worry about that i don't
want to step on toes
and i want to make all these friends you
guys are going to get thrown
under the bus that's the bottom line you
guys just came on here live on clubhouse
live
on facebook live on youtube making
potato waffles
which is actually one of my favorites
because it's a treat for today
so how do i look out for you guys how
do i look out for you guys
and keep it real like i always have
never contradict myself like i haven't
in 35
years like how do i keep
that record of making sure i got your
back
and that's what it's about making sure i
understand what you've been through
making sure i know the details the
details matter
the details matter okay and i've seen it
in health scene all right
the health scene is like this empty
shell out there
okay it's an empty shell of people right
now
trying to find their way right and sell
their merch
sell all their merch right sell all
their products and sell their merch
okay but what happens is as i'm trying
to protect you guys and trying to
protect the people that are sick and
trying to protect protect the people
that eat it as i'm doing that right
what happens is i'm stepping on toes so
i'm stepping on the nutritional yeast
people's toes
look out i'm stepping on the apple cider
vinegar
people's toast right i'm stepping on the
caffeine people
the matcha tea people don't piss them
off
don't piss them off you piss them off
man they'll report you
everybody's going to want to report you
right how do we how do we take him down
after 35 years of making sure that more
people have healed from chronic illness
than ever before in history
like how do we do it right it's like and
that's the thing
i can't be i can't sit there up at night
thinking about okay who am i going to
piss off next who am i going to piss off
next
who's it going to be the chocolate bar
people 90 cacao people who's it gonna be
the ayahuasca people am i gonna get the
ayahuasca people all pissed off now
they're gonna be mad now because they
want to have their plant medicine micro
dose
and they think that you know like and
i'm trying to forewarn people saying
that's not going to heal you
that's going to hurt you like you know
so
you know it it's like who else right is
it the collagen people because that's a
whole
scam all on its own you guys are it's
all about
brainwashing you guys you guys need to
know that
that the system set up an alternative
medicine to make sure
they brainwash you guys with everything
they got they want the yoga mamas and
the yoga studios doing all the kombucha
tea which turns your blood into acid
and sets you back in your health they
want everybody jacked up
on caffeine they want pregnant women
eating chocolate bars this is how the
system's built
i'm the only one that's that that
goes against all the the crap
and the only one that has the record of
millions healing
worldwide with chronic illness which has
never been seen before and you think the
media would pick up on that but they
don't want to because what happens is
this isn't the world where you know when
people heal that's a good
thing it's the you'll know you'll know
if you've been seasoned enough you guys
will know
if you've been in it enough you'll know
the system
doesn't want you better it just doesn't
and the alternative system is all about
making sure
everybody's hands are greased the
alternative market the alternative world
his hands are greased man
it's all about hands or hands or greased
and
don't step on this person's toes you
give me that i give you that who cares
about everybody else who cares about
everybody else on mattress island who
cares about the 22 year old on mattress
island who cares about her
who cares who cares if we trick her out
and she's doing
coffee enemas and cacao and she thinks
and she's and she's sick and can't get
out of bed and she's doing nutritional
yeast and doing
and doing you know collagen and doing
apple cider vinegar and doing
diatomaceous earth particles all this
bad stuff
who cares doesn't matter as long as she
can pay
for it as long as she should get on
there and see oh that podcast doctor let
me just
i'll buy his to his products or her
products you know
and but nobody's looking out for anybody
um anna hey well said it's so true
always a new fad but a new fad that's
not there to protect the
one that's sick now let me get let me
tell you just this first
first of all you guys let me just get
this straight okay there's the
not sick okay there's the not so sick
which one are you guys
which one are you guys there's the not
sick
there's the not so sick and there's the
so sick okay so so sick which one are
you guys
which one or which one were you right
right which one were you
okay that's another thing too okay
because they're not
sick they could they can dabble they can
play a little bit of this playing a
little bit
i can drink a little wine here and there
i can do my cacao
i can do whatever what i'm okay we i can
do this and that
doesn't matter i can have my eggs
and eat it too i can have my eggs and
eat it too right
i could do anything don't need to get
rid of eggs hey somebody
listening right now you guys might think
eggs are perfectly fine like what do you
mean i never even heard eggs are bad but
they're bad and i've always talked about
why
right and so if you're not sick
you can play around you've got your
workouts going
you can do your protein shakes even if
there's
msg in your protein shakes you can have
your nutritional yeast you can throw
your apple cider vinegar gummies down
even though you're gonna lose your teeth
down the road from it it doesn't matter
when you're not sick you can play around
you can afford to play around until it
chips away at the stone
until it's death by a thousand cuts
right
but then what if you're not so sick
right so you're still kind of sick but
not so sick little acne
got a little skin stuff going on you get
a little brain fog intermittently you
get a little energy loss your workouts
aren't as easy to do
you're not so sick right but you're
still doing the same old stuff
you're still playing around with neem
oil still playing around diatomaceous
earth still playing around bentonite
clay gut health products protein powders
all the bad stuff
still playing around with alcohol and
your supplements still playing around
with msg natural flavors in your protein
powders right
and it's not really taking you out yet
it's not maria says i'm healing thanks
to you i'm honored you're here
you guys were live at clubhouse live at
facebook live on youtube just so you
know right now
julius is not so sick but getting better
thanks to you
julia honored you're here so excited
glad you guys are here
if you're not so sick you can also
afford to kind of do
good things and bad things mix you can
have some vegan pizza
make sure there's vegan cheese on there
you're not so sick so the vegan cheese
isn't gonna make you worse yet in the
moment but if you're really sick the
vegan cheese will kill you
right so it's like if this is how it's
done you're not so sick you can keep
your caffeine going on i'll still do my
coffee drinks i'll still do my cacao
you're not so sick right you can still
do this you can still do that to play
around you can go up and down
you can do a little bit of medical
medium stuff the lemon water you can do
a little bit of medical medium stuff
the the you know the the the celery
juice right you guys
you can do a little bit of medical
medium stuff heavy metal detox smoothie
and you can do it and you can do the or
you can do pieces of this that
fragmented into the other health
communities pieces of it
or you can do some supplements that are
in the health communities now because of
medical medium 30 years of medical
medium pushing out the cat's claw
pushing out the right kind of zinc
pushing out all this stuff the vitamin c
dr fawn md
death by a thousand cuts and then they
blame medical medium not the cuts
exactly exactly it happens all the time
you're not so sick you can play with
that knife
you can you can play with that knife
here a little cut here no big deal
i can spare that i'm not that sick
another little cut here i can spare that
i'm not that sick right and then hey
lorraine l good to see you good to see
you um just saw you
shoot up there the comment it says your
material
your material saved me from serious a
serious operation at mace
incredible really is it is and
so yeah it's it's melissa said what's
wrong with
neem oil it's it's one of those trends
where
no one knows why anybody's sick nobody
knows why anybody's sick
okay that's how it works you think they
do but they don't
unless they took medical medium
information now if that's really tough
to digest it just know it's a fact
medical medium information derives from
the publications of medical medium the
information that gets out there and
sifts out there right
30 years of lecturing and teaching
doctors so many pieces of
it the health the health field was
really small back in the day
and i taught in it and taught in it and
taught in it and the people
most powerful people in the world coming
to me for help after seeing 50 of the
most
best doctors in the world right and i've
seen it all out there you know
and what happens is there's a lot of
trendy items out there
that are out there but the people who
put them out there
don't know why anybody's sick they don't
know what causes your excellent
psoriasis but neem oil will fix you
don't know don't know what causes don't
know what causes uh your vitiligo
right collagen will fix it though it
will really
because it doesn't you know don't know
what causes your lupus
right diatomaceous earth particles to
fix it uh it will
because it doesn't makes you sicker okay
so this is just you know little examples
right i got the waffle maker on you guys
i'm making waffles potato waffles
um got that heating up i'm gonna peel
the skin these are steamed potatoes
right here
you guys see and i'm going to peel the
skins back a little bit
guys i brought the lights down a little
bit does it help on youtube
because everybody was complaining it was
totally bright
courtney m.a good to see you i wish i
could show you a picture of my fridge
right now
filled with everything you show us that
is incredible
that's it that's absolutely incredible
and with the comments you guys we're
live on youtube facebook and clubhouse
right now so glad we're all together
andrea healing every day thank you so
much anthony in spirit of compassion for
the life-changing information
amazing amazing i'm peeling back some of
these skins on these
steamed potatoes because i'm going to
make these potato waffles gabrielle
healing because of you
incredible when i quit eggs
solved my planters issue in 10 days i'll
tell you why planter
warts are a virus
viruses eat the undeveloped
protein in eggs right
so viruses eat see these eggs right here
the undeveloped protein
in eggs they were trained you think the
planter's wart virus just appeared
where did it where did it come from
would it come from
that the earth someone was walking
barefoot
80 years ago a hundred years ago
they were walking barefoot you know 70
years ago
and all of a sudden they picked up the
planters wart virus
planters warts that's a virus that was
released into our environment that was
raised in labs
a lot of our miseries most of our
miseries
are man made man-made
and that because there's a sinister plan
with all that i'm peeling some of these
skins back right here
um kelly warring i was fooled into using
all that crap acv
kombucha diatomaceous earth
uh c-a-c-p protein powder yep
all kinds of supplements that never did
jack for my health jack that's the word
i
use cacao yeah cacao and um
yeah i totally understand and it never
does but can i tell you one thing though
can i tell you something guys
just so you know there's a lot of fancy
doctors that don't practice
medicine they don't they don't work like
dr faun does every single day
dr fun md they don't work like a lot of
incredible doctors do every single day
they they they say they're doctors but
they sit there selling merch
on on the internet they love to sell
their products they don't know why
anybody's sick and then what do they do
they try to rip down
medical medium where where literally
it's the land of so many people getting
the freedom of their life back and get
from debilitating diseases
but what happens it and and you know and
in the life-changing books right
it's like look you know are we in it to
help people
are we in it to try to hop on other
people's platforms and destroy them in
any way they can
right so people love to do are we in it
to help people are we
playing tit for tat you know it's um
jealousy games right
and you know what happens is that i'm in
it to make sure
we got people who are chronically sick
we got their back
because no one knows what it's like to
be in their shoes
unless they've been there unless they've
been there good too i'm not just talking
about a little bit
unless they've been there right that's a
whole another thing amy bachelor
good friend of mine seven years on
medical medium healed on
so many levels wisdom to handle anything
that crosses our path
amy batchelor i had i got to touch
base with you sometimes see how you're
doing i mean amy is a good friend of
mine
it's an amazing soul amazing person um
i'm glad you guys are coming on tara
appleman
good to see you um incredible
glad you're here glad you're here today
um
amazing amazing so you guys let's talk
about a little bit i'm just peeling some
skins off these um steamed potatoes i
didn't do it earlier
i'm doing it now just just to let you
know there's no confusion we're live on
facebook live on youtube and live
on clubhouse which is awesome so we're
live on
three platforms right now and i'm
excited trisha marie good to see you
truly um so
my waffle maker says i'm ready
i got some skins off these potatoes i
think that was good enough
got most of them off you can leave them
on and still mash up your waffles i mean
you could if you really wanted to
but i'm going to mash these babies up as
we're talking about some great stuff
so let's always say if you want to get
better
you have to know a couple of things this
is so important
okay if you want to get better first of
all you have to know why you're sick
like really why you're sick not because
someone told you your head was chopped
off
in 1734 in england in one of your past
lives
because that's not why that's not why
you're sick right now okay let's go
let's do another one
it's important to know why you're sick
instead
m sky good to see you good to see you
i'm sky you're you're
you caught this live sometimes you
always i think sometimes you said in
comments like i missed them live
em sky um or
you know sometimes people are told they
just manifested it
okay it's it they created it did you
guys create your sickness
i wanna know did you guys create it
on clubhouse did you guys create your
sickness did you manifest it
did you did you think some bad thoughts
and that's how you got sick are you a
bad person
are you faulty because that's another
thing all on its own
people are told that they're they're
they have a fear of healing right
do you guys have a fear of healing i
want to know
um because that's what people are told
they said well you got a fear of healing
or you
attracted your sickness
you attracted your sickness right
and um still mashing it
you attracted your sickness you created
it karma is karma
is karma got you this car is that why
you're sick
you guys i want to know who believes
it's karma
must be karma right paying your dues is
that what it is
well is that is that how it worked do
you think a two-year-old manifested it i
want to know
see an incredible i noticed that the
spiritual healing movement which
back before medical medium really got
out there i mean it's been 35 years now
with medical medium right but
right at the start though you know it
wasn't the millions
right now that are learning about
medical medium info right
um it was obviously a smaller crowd back
35 years ago right of course
and but what happened is that back then
everybody was still doing the spiritual
stuff that same thing but people were
still sick
and they were just like well i guess i
attracted i guess it was my karma or
something like
but you know it all falls apart when you
think about
did did the two-year-old manifest it
because i'm kind of curious
you know like what happened there what
about the five-year-old did the
five-year-old have some bad karma
no right no there's reasons why we're
sick
and and the thing is with the trendy
traps out there you guys and the trendy
products and the trendy traps
right okay out there the people putting
that stuff out there they don't know why
anybody's sick
they don't know why it all comes down to
the same old kind of like theories well
was it gut issues was it candida
was it what is it like you know why are
people sick
do they manifest it i'm not saying to
not think positive
absolutely think positive i want you
guys to have
your dreams your aspirations your
affirmations
your mantras you wake up in the morning
i got mantras and affirmations
i wake up in the morning i'm going to
fight for the chronically ill that's
what i say that's what i say
first thing in the morning right i wake
up in the morning
i'm going to fight for the chronically
ill that's what i say
just like that yeah that's one of my
mantras
right april um
you're the only one who's told me why i
have eczema it's life-changing
information
it millions of people have excellent
right
and they don't know why and there's
people with eczema that don't
trust they don't trust that maybe
medical meme information is good because
some troll got to them right one of
those trolls that said i tried it it
didn't work but they never tried it
right or when some troll comes on in and
hammers them you know and says no
don't do the medical medium stuff he
talks to a ghost or something right
and you get this you get this and these
are these are discriminators right these
are spiritual racists you know and the
funny thing is
is everybody's supposed to be so
spiritual like so
spiritual right now everybody is just so
on their game with being spiritual
that's that's what you see out there now
right
but quit to discriminate
against something that's been working
for decades now getting people's life
back
lives back and healing right and then be
like no no that guy he's you know he's
he hears a voice no way that's that's bs
you know it's like oh i thought you were
spiritual i thought you can handle that
you know i thought you can handle that
you know what i mean you're at your yoga
class or you're doing whatever you can
handle that you're
you're spiritual right and but you know
it's amazing how that works but there's
a lot of discrimination and it sets
people back because
now someone's going to be afraid to heal
their ex about meanwhile there's
tens of thousands of people that got rid
of their excellent psoriasis
like how important is that to get rid of
your eczema your psoriasis it's one of
the greatest
greatest precious things that could ever
happen to someone unless you know what
it's like to have that bleeding
cracked skin man and be suffering like
you are
unless you know what that's like right
unless you've been in that person's
shoes you won't know
you won't know you know you won't know
and when you get there someday
yeah you'll learn fast that guess what
no one knows what causes x
psoriasis except medical medium
information and then when i
when i hear from somebody and someone
says hey you know aw
you know i just saw someone say how
copper
is behind eczema but they didn't cite
you
that's another problem all on its own
not citing medical medium information
so now there's a tidbit of medical beam
information that gets out there right
just like the lemon water flushing the
liver
medical medium information right but now
it's it's like common law out there they
even pretend there's science behind it
well that's funny because it comes from
medical medium
which comes from above which comes from
spirit of compassion right
it's like it's like okay um now it's
yeah this gets copper out of your out of
your system
for example copper there's no science of
research that says copper causes
exopsrisis that's medical medium
information
right and it doesn't get cited the sad
part about
it not getting cited is how's that
person gonna heal now
they're just going to take somebody's
gut health product or something and
still
or they're going to take somebody else's
whatever or they're going to take
something that doesn't work
like zeolite and they're going to just
you know and meanwhile they have a
tidbit
but the details matter as michelle l
says and i see your comment
comment in youtube a lot she says
details
matter right and that's what it is it's
about the details mattering
is it mattering yeah i'll say it's
mattering
and you know the whole thing it's
important
so you guys i'm going to put this i
think these are pretty mashed up pretty
good actually there we go we'll mash
them up a little bit more
so you guys we're live on clubhouse live
on youtube live on facebook
margaret valentine good to see you
i i read a comment that someone shamed
you at a retreat
for being concerned about fat and i
think someone was putting
all this fat on top of potatoes or
something or they told you
it was okay at the retreat that's what
they told you
and then they said why did you do that
and they shamed you or they shamed you
the other way around i can't remember
but i read that story that story hit me
and it just it just
the story hit me because it was like
yeah exactly
it's not easy out there in the health
field the way it works you guys i'm
putting
my potato on here i just i had a weak
spoon and it just actually did a little
snap
lorraine what do you think about that
one
um but i'll tell you right now i'm gonna
get another spoon in a second
it's it's really incredible how things
work
out there i've seen a lot of that in
retreats too i've
seen a lot of shaming go on in retreats
i'm not saying retreats are bad i'm not
saying anything like that i'm just
saying
validate someone's experience out there
validate their stories right and that
leads me to the next part
right is here you are you
heal you work your butt off you're doing
some medical medium
information okay you're working hard
you share your story and someone comes
on there and says
it didn't happen it didn't happen
right or it's in a doctor
or uh it was a sugar pill
right it was a sugar pill so i'm
actually got my potatoes in here you
guys
i'm gonna replace my wooden spoon
um that was one of my favorites
ah here's a there's a nice big wooden
spoon here
so and that's another thing too is
you're not allowed to heal
um lorraine totally your humor
most people who say they did mm too
never read one of the books right
they'll say
they'll say you know they never never
mind all seven of the books they've only
read like
no never even read one i've seen that
before too and the
the in-depth healing information in the
books is a whole other thing that's a
whole other
but what you'll find is people who heal
and they work hard and they get rid of
their lupus their lyme disease with
medical medium information they get rid
of their cfs right on clubhouse you guys
any of you guys got cfs
cfs me right the brain inflammation
fibromyalgia how about that one too all
kinds of gum
and teeth problems that happen to so
many people um
another thing trigeminal neuralgia nerve
pain back pain neck pain
head pain right you guys um
and all of that and i'm cooking these up
nice
let's see if i know how to use this
today the waffle machine
all right so that's cooking got the
potato waffles brewing
so there's so many people out there that
healed with medical medium information
but what i'm noticing out there is that
there's a cult out there and this cult
is probably
one of the more evil cults and it's a
science and research
cult the science and research cult is
devised of a bunch of people who haven't
been sick yet
and they're there to tell you you didn't
heal
because science didn't approve of it
right
this is the jim jones cult of all time
is science research right
you know like the jim jones cult right
was was everybody
took the kool-aid took the sinai and
they died
right they killed themselves and
and it was just a horrifying horrifying
nightmare
okay a thousand people they all drink
kool-aid with cyanide and they go down
science research is just like that but
they're the longer
version they're the micro micro
dose they're the you're you're drinking
the science and research
kool-aid right right and there's a
little bit of cyanide in there
but you just don't die fast you just
stay
sick and sick while science and research
strings you out
and strings you out and then just just
they
chip away at your soul that's such
science and research this just
chips away at your soul with all their
paid for fake studies
and they chip away and then while you're
waiting on your last breath
they finally come out with a new report
they
finally come out with a new report that
matcha tea
has a new antioxidant in it and you just
lost 30 years of your life
hanging on by a thread hoping to god
science and research
would actually save you and they don't
they don't they're the ultimate cult
literally the ultimate cult right now
you can't break them they're just like
robot robots in their cult where's your
science where's your science well that's
funny because where's your science
so where's your science where's your
research that's funny because where's
your science in research right
where's yours because what i'm noticing
now is that people who are saying that
in the cult
so all the cult people in there right in
science research here's what they're
doing
they're throwing you a link to a
citation
right they're throwing you like a
to a paper not even a study
so you got all these papers out there
they're just
they're just observational papers
there's no conclusion
there's no facts in them there's nothing
so the science research cult is so
twisted and evil they don't even give
you a study
you don't even get a study anymore
there's no studies in there it's an
article so let's just link an article
that was hearsay
and we'll link that we'll throw that in
somebody's face and say well here's
here's some science the science research
cult is actually got to such a dangerous
point right
where and they they don't care if
anybody heals
they don't want anybody to heal it has
to be under science's
jurisdiction right so you guys don't
deserve to heal
you don't you don't deserve to heal
unless science
says so unless science says
right and science in the end is a whole
bunch of paid for theories anyway when
it comes down to chronic illness
science isn't math you guys this is so
important to know
like science isn't math two plus two is
four
science research is two plus two is five
that's what it is in science and
research it's
there it's not math there so when you're
accountant or
somebody or somebody you're adding up
some numbers if you guys are budgeting
yourselves out for the week right
if you're budgeting yourselves out for
the week and trying to figure out what
and how would i pay for groceries this
week and
what do i need to how do i pay the light
bill keep that on
light bill is 37 dollars and 42 cents
let me pay the light bill right
science research is not that it's a
theory
compounded by money hungry beasts behind
there
that makes scientists do what they tell
them or your
asses on you're you just you just lost
your job
right you lost your job and that's what
happens
and you better produce an
outcome you scientists better produce an
outcome or your ass is grass
you you're not going to be feeding your
families you're not going to be
recommended for the next scientific
study as a scientist
scientist you're done so you better give
us something
you better give us something for the two
million dollars we just put in you
better give us something for the 10
million dollars you've been putting in
um and so all of this is important
you know um so with comment uh
mv uh von doom
says why is it taking so long for my
symptoms to clear
sign and um why is it taking so long
let's just check this waffle for a
second to you guys i want to make sure
i'm not burning it
so there's a lot of factors to
understand
guys i just got to pick this up you guys
hanging in there on clubhouse i gotta
pick up the phone for a minute
that's on youtube hello
yeah i'm gonna fly uh-huh
yeah yeah make a noise why do you want
me to do that every time
it's annoying all right
[Music]
what it's annoying yeah i told you it's
annoying why are you making me do it
yeah i'm on the wall right now okay what
is that person doing
i i've been keeping an eye on that
person
uh-huh yeah they they've been to the doc
they went to the doctor and they they
they had their blood drawn uh-huh
i saw it they had seven full vials drawn
yeah yeah removed part of their immune
system
uh-huh what else did they do let me see
i'm gonna fly in the wall let me see
uh i see a receipt for a new medical
treatment
uh-huh yeah i see a receipt for a new
medical treatment
uh-huh yeah the newest one uh-huh
yeah yeah yeah no i know
i know all right what yeah i'm flying
the wall uh-huh
yeah no what i saw a piece of chocolate
yeah yeah i saw a piece of chocolate it
kind of looks like this
uh-huh kind of looks like this yeah
yeah it no it's it's it's cacao
it's it's clean chocolate though it's
good chocolate it's clean chocolate
uh-huh okay i'm a fly in the wall but i
got a waffle to make so you got to make
this fast uh
yeah okay no i saw some caffeine some
other types of caffeine
yeah i'm a fly in the wall and i saw oh
what's that too many fats i know
well there's too much fat there's olive
oil and there's
i saw a little bit of vegan cheese yep
and i saw
uh-huh and i s which supplements i think
those supplements
don't have good stuff in there might
have a little alcohol in there
yeah and what about yeah there's some
vinegar in that dish
i saw some vinegar in that dish uh-huh
no too much fats for the week yeah way
too many fats for the week
yeah okay well i gotta go i gotta keep
i gotta keep buzzing around this is
gonna keep buzzing around
so and okay okay but wait wait wait i
see something else
that person's under some stress yeah
they are
a relationship something went wrong in a
relationship a while back uh-huh
i heard them talking to their friend
about it yeah i know that's a big
trigger
okay i gotta go this is this is
what happens is a lot of times people
don't heal fast enough because they got
a lot of obstacles they'll take out a
new medical treatment maybe they had
some antibiotics a while back
maybe they they're under some stress and
duress maybe
they're doing some things like too much
fat in their foods like they got too
much avocado but yet
in order to heal if they're really sick
they need more stuff going on are they
doing the right
supplements the right kinds of
supplements are they doing
all of the right brands and things that
are really helpful you know
are they are they doing brands that
aren't helpful are they
are they doing things with alcohol in
them and acacia gum and citric acid and
msg and natural flavors are they doing
collagen are
they doing fish oil all these things are
rough on their system are they doing
caffeine what are they doing you guys
are they doing corella
are they doing like the neem oil
diatomaceous earth particles bentonite
clay
gut health products like gut health
powders
which are really aggressive and and
abrasive what did they do in the past
did they do coffee enemas in the past
how about that
did they do something else that wasn't
good something with natural flavors
natural flavoring
berry flavor which doesn't bury you guys
on clubhouse letting you know it's not
berry
berry flavor is msg strawberry flavor
berry flavor in something you know
flavoring
right that's that's that's msg you guys
right on youtube
are they doing msg nutritional yeast
with msg and the bad b12
in it that's what they put in the in in
the nutritional yeast right
you seem fine to me chris good to see
you yes setback stink
right good to see you today um ashley
kevin good to see you
so what else is happening lunell what
else is happening so many things are
have natural flavors
and how much blood was drawn it could
have been six
months ago and you suffer six months
later you guys
you know elizabeth good to see you
natural flavors it could be six
months ago six months ago
okay and um still cooking this up a
little more
it could have been six months ago you
had 14
vials and you pay the price six months
later
it takes three to six months just to get
your immune system back to square one
after having
70 milliliters of blood drawn 80
milliliters of blood drawn
it takes that long to get you guys back
so what else is happening
you know the setbacks how do we move
forward and what about the perfumes and
colognes right
what about those what about that
you guys on youtube right you guys on
facebook you guys on clubhouse what
about the perfumes you doing perfumes
because you knock your immune system
right down it's like this
it's like you got kicked out of a boat
right you're wearing your clothes and
it's saturated with water
the time the water is soaking up you're
out there in the ocean
and you're starting to drag downward
right
someone throws you the crappiest life
preserver you grab on to it it's just
keeping you up enough but yet
not pulling you out of the water and but
yet you're going down and you're choking
on the water you're coming back up it's
almost pulling you out
but you're going back down right because
you're doing the colognes and perfumes
you're doing the scented candles and the
air fresheners you're doing the
hairsprays and the aftershaves
you're smelling someone else's
aftershave
right this stuff knocks us down you're
doing your deodorants you're doing your
hair products
you're doing makeups that have all kinds
of stuff in it that's not
good in there right i'm not trying to
say you got to live in fear but
but there's there's things to do when
you're too sick sometimes but remember
when i told you if you're not so sick
you guys
if you're not so sick or if you're not
sick
there's difference than when you're sick
then we gotta we gotta figure out
then what pathogens is happening what
bugs are going on right
what bugs are happening what strains of
bugs what's streptococcus in your
system what's staff with staff what what
what c
diffs in your system what h pylori's in
there what different types of strep how
many varieties what epstein-barr
right courtney says sick right
what what do you have going on the
shingles variety the cytomegalovirus an
aggressive ebv causing hashimoto's
fibromyalgia lupus
right your lyme disease because ebv
causes your lyme disease right you guys
on clubhouse you guys know that by now
if you know medical medium information
right that's teaching people out there
in the world or do you have two or three
epstein bars
people have two or three or four of them
some people have six of them seven of
them
yeah so you can have all this going on
lissy cohen good to see you today
um you have you have all this going on
okay and new relationships we pick up
bugs all the time
that's life you want to live your life
on planet earth
someone else is going to have a
streptococcus because they have utis
or they've got chronic sinusitis and
they're going to have
a antibiotic resistant streptococcus
because
their strep was always there was always
fed their antibiotics like you're back
at the doctor's office
yep you got another sinusitis chronic
sinusitis let's give you another
another antibiotic and you meanwhile
your streptococcus is getting stronger
then we get into a relationship and we
pass that streptococcus to someone else
now they have this antibiotic-resistant
streptococcus and they're getting utis
so it's like we get we we're in this
place psyllium is horrible by the way
mats is psyllium husk psyllium husk is
terrible it's it's very irritating
very irritating it really is i think
these are done now
very irritating got to look out for that
but we're up against so much
and in order to heal i said it said it
before and i'll say it again
you got to know what's wrong with you
and then you got to know about the
pitfalls
and with me i can teach you about the
i could get i could get my my my butt
beat in all the angry people trying to
protect their livelihoods think about
that right
think about that okay you're
you're an acv dealer now right you're an
ac nutritional yeast dealer now right
whatever it is you're a cacao dealer now
right
you seem fine to me chris oh good to
know about the husk
you're you're uh you're you're you're
you're trying to make a living on social
media right you're a practitioner out
there and you're trying to sell all your
stuff and you get when
the medical medium is talking smack
about your products that are keeping you
going and you're selling to all your
people that come to you
you're going to want to jump on that guy
you're going to want to jump on them
you're going to want you don't care
about you don't care about the sick
people you don't care about learning
about it you don't care about people who
are sick you don't care about the
chronically ill you just want to jump on
his ass
and you want to take him down well
that's what i've been up against for 35
years you want to take him out
that's what you want to do because how
dare you be talking about that cacao
powder
how dare you be talking about that
reese's mushroom powder with the with
the coffee in there right
the rishi coffee how dare you gonna talk
about that coffee bad
how dare you gonna talk about all that
other stuff bad
we need to take him out let's report and
report and report him
let's let's let's make sure we do
another story in a post
let's come up with all kinds of stuff
he's charlton
whatever right you take them out that's
what you try to do
but here's how i work you know you do
that
and it wakes me up and it wakes me up
because i can go to sleep
ah i'm gonna go to sleep ain't nothing
happening out there
you know i could go to sleep now
everybody's healing they got the books
they're
they're gonna have their lives saved
what what what
yo what you just woke me up what someone
did a bad post
wait some did another fake story about
me oh what
hmm and i just dropped a little stretch
and i get up and i said okay
all right you want to play that way okay
because i'm gonna make sure
i'm gonna make sure the world knows how
to heal
and we're not gonna take any crap and
that's just the bottom line
it's like you know a friend of mine says
don't wake him up
the guy's already worked for 35 years
he's worked his butt off he's
a large part of the alternative medicine
foundations built off of his back
and he did it without wanting to take
the credit
because he lives a spiritual life he
listens to a spiritual
source and it's like it's like
don't wake him up though right and
that's what they continue to do
so they get mad because they're they get
mad because they're selling their stuff
and they're like well he he's he's he's
trying to protect pregnant women
he's trying to protect pregnant women
and not let them eat cacao
right while they're pregnant but
that's making us look bad because we
tell pregnant women they can have all
the chocolate they want
and they can get their baby all high
right
so isn't that a beautiful waffle right
there you guys on clubhouse i wish you
could see this
i wish you could see this waffle so one
thing about the clubhouse app
that's probably not fun so you don't see
anything
but i got an incredible waffle in front
of me you guys are clubhouse you should
eventually watch the replay of youtube
you know but yeah and then and then it's
the psychedelic
you know the psychedelic stuff out there
too people don't realize
that caffeine is is a psychoactive drug
right so here you are you're pregnant
and you get told caffeine is fine right
because
pregnant women now are told you can have
a little bit of chocolate just
moderation
you know i mean do we need to call a
baby like do we need to call a baby
like let's call a baby now
in the womb let's call a baby in the
womb okay
hold on it's raining
hello little baby hey little baby
hi hi
yeah yeah you hear me okay
uh-huh um mommy's being told
yep by her practitioner and by all those
all those trend setters and influencers
uh-huh
mommy's being told that a little bit of
cacao
in her smoothie is is okay they say it's
just in moderation are you okay with
that
no why what's going on
you know when mommy's high really
why how do you know because you get high
oh my god okay i think that says a lot
right there
uh-huh um so what happens what
when the chocolate wears off you go into
the tremors
and shakes uh-huh mommy think
mommy just thinks you're kicking because
you're happy
uh-huh it's not mommy's fault we know
that
no no we know it's not mommy's fault has
nothing to do with that
we just know what mommy's being taught
every day in the alternative arts health
community
i know okay i'm gonna let you go back to
sleep okay
don't worry okay bye
yeah so medical medium information
is about making sure that
you have every chance and freedom and
choice to make
but but real information
like real yeah it's ugly
it's ugly information yeah
i i get the cacao people upset the
coffee people upset the matcha tea
people upset
the apple cider vinegar people upset the
diatomaceous people upset
the egg people upset me and the egg
people
yeah get them upset that's not good
right
and these are just a few a few people
and but it's either that or
i just give in contradict the hell out
of myself
give up and not care if you guys heal or
not
the problem is i know why you're sick
they don't
they don't know why you're sick they can
play in
any realm they want and try to bank on
anything they want and bank and bank
they could do all their subscription
charges on all their websites
they can do whatever they can make you
you have to pay 400
to sign into something right
okay and the science websites because
you're desperate to heal and you pay 400
and 200 and 700 you sign up to the
website so you can surf through their
papers of
junk right and not get answers
and then in the end they got a little
product area and maybe i'll buy this
like special
cider vinegar maybe i'll buy this other
fish oil they have with their their
their bs
claims and stuff and nobody's looking
out for the mommies the babies no one's
looking out for the people who are sick
nobody's looking out they don't even
know why you're sick
it's unbelievable when you think about
it
debbie loves stone why is coffee enema
and diatomaceous earth not good how do
these two things cause harm to the body
okay first of all coffee enema let's
just cover that real quick right there
while we're right here anyway right your
stomach
is there to buffer a poison caffeine
is a psychoactive drug that we're not
supposed to consume
it ages women quickly beats their
adrenal glands down
gives them difficult pregnancies and
births for baby births
and it causes all kinds of wrinkles in
the skin sun spots malaysia
all that on the skin and hair loss for
women right because women aren't
technically supposed to lose their hair
they're not supposed to
okay it's not like men right women are
not supposed to lose their hair
but they lose it because of caffeine
that's one reason why they lose it their
adrenals get beaten down by other things
but
caffeine is really a poison right and
then it keeps them high and addicted and
they spend a whole life addicted and
that's how the caffeine industry wants
them they want them addicted but
what goes wrong with when it's a coffee
enema
is nothing's buffering that poison
from getting to your liver and brain
one when you put that coffee up the back
end
nothing buffers it for your brain and
heart
it goes into shock including your liver
it goes into shock
when it when you drink it the lining
of your mouth your esophagus okay
your stomach and your duodenum
are pretty darn strong for a reason
they're there
to buffer a poison because here's the
deal you guys want to hear something
cool
okay back thousands of years ago
and even not even that far right we
survived by saying
i'm hungry i see a plant on the ground
with a weird berry
i'm gonna risk my life and bite that
berry
and everybody standing around me is
gonna say you're either gonna live or
die
and if you live we might be able to eat
that food did you know that
human beings have thousands of years of
that right
trial by era making mistakes in the food
you pick
you eat that berry and if that berries
poisonous
you die right in front of your family
and everybody else
right or you get poisoned sick right
that's how it works but your stomach
is the buffer the buffer your stomach
is engineered naturally
not synthetically not gmo engineered
it's engineered in a way created in a
way
to buffer what poison can possibly enter
it
right so i'm gonna eat that root because
i'm
starving to death whatever climate or
area i
am on the planet i'm starving my butt
off it's make or break do or die
i better just eat those shoots i just
found that popped up in
in the springtime because if i don't eat
those shoots i'm in trouble
you pluck those shoots out and you risk
your life on them that's how it's done
back then right i'm gonna eat
that mushroom it looks good
it's sitting there i don't know if it's
a poisonous mushroom or not
but i'm gonna eat it and that's how it
was done all these years
nobody knew different they didn't know
if this was poisonous or not
they didn't know you could eat this or
not eat that they didn't know
but your stomach buffered the poison it
gave you a chance to not
die fast right caffeine is a poison and
the stomach is built to
buffer it to a degree so it can't hit
the brain
fast enough it can't hit the brain it
can't hit the heart fast enough
you don't get the brain and heart rush
fast because those are the two organs
that your stomach is trying to protect
you from i mean to protect poisons from
getting to
right and so what happens is
that you put you put a poison up your
back end you put poison
into your rectum you get poison
into your colon from behind
right there's no buffer it's not built
like that
no buffer at all at all it goes directly
into the bloodstream in an instant
there's nothing to buffer that caffeine
anybody who's okay and here's the other
thing why are you doing a coffee enema
doing a coffee enema because you're sick
you think anybody's gonna just do a
coffee animal when they're feeling fine
and life's great they're playing playing
tennis and drinking their margaritas
and drinking their glasses of
champagne life is good and they can do
what they want
go where they want exercise when they
want sleep when they want
do anything they want right you think
they're gonna go rush out and get a
coffee enema
no we do it because we're sick and we're
looking for answers and now we're on the
road looking for coffee enemas now
but what goes wrong is that when you do
the coffee enema
you kill your adrenals the adrenals get
a direct attack of caffeine
and it causes them to blow out and if
your nervous system is weak tingles and
numbness maybe you have aches and pains
what do you got neck pain back pain head
pain
what do you got what do you guys got you
got tingles numbness ringing in the ears
well you got anxiety tightness in the
chest tightness in the throat
what do you have we have jaw pain teeth
pain what do you guys got
right you know ethel says i really like
this guy hey i'm honored
i'm so glad you're here you seem fine to
he says chris
no one puts it this way right
what do you got wrong with you
depression anxiety depersonalization
bipolar
what are you dealing with fatigue uh
blurry vision
uh floaters in the eyes flashing lights
in your eyes and head
are you what are you dealing with
insomnia back pain
feet pain plantar fasciitis what are you
dealing with well guess what
those are all nervous system stuff all
nervous system you put coffee in you
that's caffeine that jacks up your
adrenals both caffeine and your
adrenaline destroy your nervous system
so let's just put coffee up the back end
because nobody knows why anybody's sick
anyway
think about that every single clinic or
anywhere or anybody who had the idea of
putting coffee
up somebody's behind didn't even know
why you were even in there to begin with
sick with your neurological symptoms
how stupid can you get not the people
getting the coffee enema
the people out there delving it out like
without even a fraction of understanding
right but the answers are here they
exist
there's thousands of doctors around the
world using medical media books and
learning this so they don't put their
patients through it
right but the more and more people that
get healed the more and more censored i
get
the more more people that heal the more
and more the world says
whoa that's just too many now
how can this guy's information be
healing that many people
because it's uncool we have to shut this
down we have to calm it down
you know and i was given this gift for
you
i'm not a smart guy and i told you guys
over and over again
monica says plantar fasciitis caused by
coffee no not at all but it's a really
good question that's caused by
epstein-barr
plantar fasciitis is caused by
epstein-barr it's a nerve inflammation
caused by low-grade viral infections
coffee just
keeps it around and makes it worse and
agitates it
that's what it does and coffee weakens
the central nervous system and plantar
fasciitis is your nervous system your
tibial nerve
just gets inflamed right digital nerve
just gets inflamed
all of that it could be coffee much
teach chocolate the whole bit listen to
the podcast that medical mean podcast at
apple podcast you guys
right and then then there's the whole
roost with
supplementation out there the garbage
supplements the stuff with alcohol
people took for years the stuff with
natural flavors and all those things
and that's why i offer that directory
you guys
on medicalmedium.com you know and
because it's important to know the best
brands because guess what that's make or
break in healing
i've seen a bad b12 not move the needle
and a good b12
move the needle and that's the
difference the b12 you guys know that i
use is the vimergy
and that's the one right there the
vimergy visa and victor i
am as in mary e-r-g-y it's the mephica
balaman with the dinosaur cabala man
right
it's a vimergy.com stuff i'm not
sponsored but when the stuff is right
it's
right and it moves the needle from what
i've seen from my friends and family the
whole bit you do what your doctor tells
you to do i'm just telling you
what i've seen move it move the needle
no natural flavors
right the whole bit so important to know
but and no citric acid and all that
other stuff you guys just made waffles
got them right here um i'm gonna get
these eggs off the table
here these little eggs off here you can
get the books free at the library that's
the other thing and one last thing is
medical medium information is
all free it's all for you guys and
clubhouse all free
guys on facebook youtube that's the
whole point get it for equal library if
you don't want to buy
on sale at amazon or barnes noble
you can access all of medical medium
information for free the medical media
podcast at apple podcast
there's no subscriptions there's no
anything i don't have that you guys
notice on youtube i don't have
any ads or advertisers have you guys
noticed that yet
no advertisers no ads you know
and yeah right and and no ads and
advertisers on my podcast
my podcast is the number one podcast out
there in health
so you guys and and i'm the one only one
doing that on that level
so anyway guys look i'm heading off to
instagram medical medium instagram page
right
and i'm gonna turn clubhouse back on so
you guys on clubhouse
i know you guys are probably doing stuff
you know living your life but if you
want to listen we're going to do
an instagram and clubhouse that's where
we're going next i got this maple syrup
i'm going to pop it on here
before we roll so here's a nice maple
syrup right here
i'm gonna put a little bit on i like
putting a little bit more
on here's where you go wrong right you
go wrong when you add butter
to your waffles that's when you go wrong
this is where you go wrong right here
you see this baked potato i'm holding in
front of me i wish you guys could see
this on clubhouse
i'm holding a baked potato in front of
me and i got some melted cheese on top
that's where you go wrong you're adding
the fat to
the the carb right to the glucose you're
putting fat and glucose together
that's where you go wrong and it's
amazing about the potato
waffle right here i put the maple syrup
on and i got nothing to worry about
because there's no butter there's no
oils there's no avocado in here for the
moment i'm not saying you can't have
some of that in your life if you want to
i'm just saying if you want to heal
here's an incredible healing dish
heading off to ig
and i'm going to be live on clubhouse at
the same time i'm going to be on there
in a few minutes you guys look out
look out on clubhouse look out on
instagram and you guys come over with me
if you want to come over with me
and uh i love you guys