we're live live on facebook live on
youtube
and i'm making a delicious meal got some
red bell peppers
cherry tomatoes mushrooms
hot peppers making a hot pepper sauce by
the way
and i got some beautiful steamed
potatoes this is a low-fat meal actually
a
no-fat meal and steamed potatoes right
there
um everybody's in in just everybody's so
into eating so much fat and they don't
know it it's just it's fat everywhere
you eat a piece of chicken
i'm not saying there's anything wrong
with chicken i'm just saying you eat a
piece of chicken
you got the chicken fat right doesn't
matter if the skin's on it or not
you eat guacamole you got the guacamole
and people dump olive oil in their
guacamole i see that all the time you
guys hey good to see you guys coming on
they dump olive oil in their guacamole
right
as if there's not enough already people
make pestos dumping all that olive oil
right
nuts seed pastes nut butters
um coconut oil right everybody's putting
things in their smoothie it's like it's
all this fat people eating nuts all day
long and
i have another handful of walnuts it's
not saying that's bad
like bad but if you're trying to heal
or trying to lose weight or trying to
get yourself to a better place
it's the fats get in the way right so
these meals are all no fat because i
know you guys are on the fat you're just
and i get it you're on the fat whether
it's milk cheese butter eggs
chicken meat you know uh fish
right you just got the fats going all
the time
uh seeds nut butters you know walnuts
almonds
macadamia nuts pine nuts sesame seeds
tahini right
even hemp seeds right so we're doing all
these different seeds pumpkin seeds
now i see people walking around i got my
pumpkin seeds i got my pumpkin seeds i'm
doing my pumpkin seeds yeah
yeah pumpkin seeds are amazing way
better for you than chicken
no that's true right way better for you
than
chicken pumpkin seeds right but still
it's a lot of fat so then the blood
stays thick and if you're
sick if you're sick and you're doing
all this fat it's almost impossible to
heal
i'm going to say it again if you're sick
and you're doing all this fat
it's almost impossible to
heal and i mean heal i mean heal down to
the
bone i'm talking healing all the way
down
to the root all the way down
to the ground like right there
and healing deep deep deep
in order to heal that deep you can't
have the fats high
so that means if you're animal protein
person time to lower it and take a break
if you're a plant-based person time to
lower it and take
a break colleen mcgraw says what about
protein
what about it what about it that's the
whole thing they got you brainwashed
that's how they do it you know i think
the phone's ringing they got
us brainwashed is what happens
how do i know when the phone's gonna
ring
yeah yeah hey what year is it 1933.
yeah 1933. did the deal go through
did the deal we made with big pharma
and the institutions the academic
institutions
yeah did the deal did the deal go
through
about what we're about to do to the
entire country
yeah we're gonna brainwash them about
protein
uh-huh did the deal go through
yep yep all the industries yeah big
pharma
yeah and uh-huh and the institutions
the universities yeah
we need to indoctrinate everybody into
our dogma we have to convince
everybody that protein
is what runs everything where do you get
your protein we want to hear that for
the next hundred years
next 200 years where do you get your
protein where do you get your protein
where do you get your protein
what about your protein we want
everybody brainwashed
what year is it 1933 and the deal's
about to go through
is everybody going to be there all the
board members
everybody going to be there because
we're going to sign it where's the
where's the piece of paper after we sign
it make the deal
it goes in the vault it's trusted it's
grandfathered in
yeah no one's even gonna get it no one's
even gonna figure it out i can't wait to
hear 1970
50 yeah i can't wait 60 years from now
in the 70s when everybody's going where
are you getting your protein
where are you getting your protein i
can't wait until the 1990s when
everybody's like protein
protein can't wait to get your i can't
wait till the year 2000
when everybody's like get your protein
get your protein where's your protein
where's your protein
i can't wait yeah wait we're gonna go as
far as 2021
where's your protein 2021
oh my god this is the best deal we've
ever made big farm is so smart
we're gonna brainwash everybody all
right
yep yep all right little disaster relief
right here
disaster relief i gotta go you gotta
cook
lorraine a little disaster is it
disaster relief what
what was it so i'm going to be doing
some let me get some stuff steaming
what i'm trying to say is before i get
cooking is the deal was made
between the academic world the
universities okay
yes the universities globally
at least in the uk at least europe
at least here in the united states
the deal was made to make sure protein
was
the very thing that everybody had to
know like it's all about protein
that's that was the decoy the decoy
of a century right
and that's part of it right there just
you know actually kevin good to see you
michelle
good to see you guys coming on haven't
seen luau lunell
she she here tonight um
you guys i'm gonna do some
let's just make sure nothing breaks over
here
hey courtney mma laugh out loud
and i'll talk a little bit about protein
as we go along too so you guys know
what's happening
as well joni peterson
hey i use water instead of oil now
i used to use a lot of coconut oil and
avocado oil incredible what happens is
when you take those oils down
oils are so acidic so acidic
fatty acid fatty
acid i see we're being censored tonight
big time
um we can't even get above 800 it's
probably you know censored on facebook
fatty acids is what's happening so
that's what happens with the oils
the avocado oil all these oils yeah
avocado oil is a better oil
absolutely yeah these oils are better
olive oil is a great oil
right but it's really it's what happens
is our we lose our oxygen in our body
when we're sick or but oxygen helps us
heal it actually helps to kill it keeps
microorganisms like viruses and bacteria
down
and when we fill our bloodstream with
all that fat every day and day out day
day day and day out and our liver starts
getting congested everything starts
getting congested
and our liver starts getting all
congested our liver right here
it gets gets fatty liver and we don't
even know it fatty liver and then our
immune system drops
we have too much fat in our bloodstream
all the time and the fat starts
collecting everywhere that doctors can't
see they can't see until you're yeah 80
years old 60 years old but they start
seeing it then
we just start we but we break down from
all that fat right
and so you gotta have a moment yeah no i
know youtube sensor oh my god katherine
youtube censors us big time
are you kidding you kidding me we used
to get views
now it's like you can't even find me
like they just i don't pop up anywhere
it's like for some reason they clicked
me off as being one of those
yeah you can't even pop up anywhere i
don't know
all right so what i'm going to do is i'm
going to cut some stuff up here
get some red bell pepper steaming
so you guys know how i cut mine right
i mean i'm sure you guys did the same
thing right it's not it's
facebook doesn't uh circle your post
correct andy
plus people are really can't even get a
post out on facebook
uh meaning they can't share medical
medium stuff it's really rare
i think it's a glitch hopefully they fix
it
you know little glitch
it could be just a glitch right they
love me on facebook they love me at
facebook and instagram
they know i'm doing incredible things
for the world right healing people
it's gotta be a glitch
so i'm steaming up some red bell peppers
right here
you guys i just want to give you the
4-1-1 it's a special moon
um tonight extremely special moon
yep so make sure you take you you
you like look into it like we're talking
an incredible moon tonight
yeah full moon and an amazing one just
letting you know um
that means medical medium podcast at
apple podcast the moon meditation
so it means the moon meditation for sure
i mean i'm doing it i'm doing this i
already did it last night the moon
meditation i do it
days before the moon is full and then
days
after the moon is full so i do this moon
meditation right
and i do it because it's so powerful and
healing but it's such a
soul healer it heals the emotional
wounds the old betrayal and the old
broken
trust and get broken promises and being
let down and
getting backstabbed in her life and all
these things that happen to everybody
where
there's always something we go through
emotionally
losses right hardships great losses
right and all these wounds they stay in
us and they stay in us and they say this
um nicole says i added you to my
favorites and it has helped incredible
nicole thanks for being
in here tonight leanne um
let's see yep i never get youtube
notifications on you no
yeah exactly exactly i mean
it's incredible really how they do that
carolina how can how can we stop
spider veins we're talking about the
liver when it's the spider veins
lowering fats is is is already a helper
to stop them from growing
the more congested the liver gets the
more
spider veins and varicose veins we we
end up having we end up getting so i'm
gonna put some mushrooms in here
okay about two cups of mushrooms let's
start chopping these up right now
um do some mushroom slices
i don't want to slice the mushrooms too
small
right let's get them steaming
good to see you guys but you know what i
got you guys
i got you guys
so who needs who needs it's okay for
censored
um dr fon people throw shade at night
shades but the info is not true oh do
they ever
man dr fawn they attack nightshades like
never before
right when isn't it funny though
attacking nightshades when no one knows
why we're sick who's attacking
nightshades they don't know why we're
sick
they think it's autoimmune which is
today's topic autoimmune
doing some mushrooms right
doing some shrooms right here in the pan
the good ones not the ones that mess up
your brain
right that's right
that's right mary i heard coconut oil
and mt's mct
is a good is good for dementia and
alzheimer's too do you agree
no it makes it worse
makes it worse
i'll tell you why let me get a couple of
mushrooms in
hold that thought hold that thought
okay just get a couple of mushrooms in
here we got some mushrooms going
we're good there all right
frying them up in a pan
all right and then let's get half an
onion in here too okay i'm gonna go with
red
just crack the onion open
uh oh the onion
mct oil coconut oil good for alzheimer's
eh
tell you why it's not and i'll tell you
why you're bamboozled
with that information tell you why we
get bamboozled with that info
it's actually sad let's do a half an
onion here
put this onion over here
i don't want the onion diced too small i
still want them kind of hunky
let's get the onions in here
it's a great dish we're making let's get
these steaming
let's hit the oils really quick here's
what happens when you
when you're consuming oils right it
rushes you to alzheimer's
it rushes you to dementia is what it
does
you see that spec that i put on there do
you see that spec
right aluminum right here do you see
that
do you know why we get alzheimer's and
dementia
because of aluminum and mercury
predominantly mercury
in our brain this is the best lesson you
can ever learn right now about this this
is really important
ready metal
rusts and oxidizes
and bleeds and corrodes
and out pockets when oil
is around it oil
is around it keep that in mind keep that
in mind
oil makes the metal corrode
faster and it
makes it move into adjacent tissue
everybody has aluminum and mercury
inside their brain
the higher the fat diet whether good fat
or bad
fat the quicker you go to alzheimer's
dementia depression
anxiety depersonalization bipolar ocd
i don't know did i miss a bunch i bet
you i did schizophrenia whatever i miss
probably missed a bunch right and
what happened ptsd too a little bit of
that
okay so what happens is oil
right oil
will make the metal out out pocket
so you got the metal in there but the
metal will expand
it will run and bleed from the
oil so whether it's mct or coconut oil
what nobody's telling you
is they don't no one took a bunch of
people with alzheimer's
right and a bunch of people dementia and
just gave them
mct their all their diets
changed other supplements were brought
in
okay fast food was removed
from from people and that's something to
understand how it works right
it's not like you got somebody with
alzheimer's and dementia nothing's
changing
they're still doing everything they do
nothing changes and all of a sudden let
me give them a little coconut oil and
their alzheimer's got better no
ah never happened never happened never
will
never did so just know that right
plus it's a theory that it's helpful the
theory
is built on this preface it's built on
this foundation of
our brain needs fat give our brain
healthy fat and we get better
alzheimer's
is the brain give our brain healthy fat
then alzheimer's gets better this is a
massive mistake in the industry
it's an embarrassing mistake because the
brain
dies without glucose fast
in five seconds if your brain doesn't
have glucose it starts to die
it starts to die die
die say it again die yeah your brain
starts to die without glucose
in five seconds
it starts to die okay that's what
happens
in 10 seconds it's dying
without glucose right your brain doesn't
start dying
because it's without fat in your
bloodstream
you can have no fat in your bloodstream
your brain doesn't die
you take out the glucose your brain
starts to die
linda i just joined this video do you
have a book out to help
losing weight the safe way seems like i
have
uh raise every night and am not going
anywhere with it
um that's a great book right there new
addition
medical medium get it free at the
library if you want uh cleanse the heel
is a great one for weight loss
too right there cleanse the heel just
letting you know
that's a great one get it free at the
library now medical medium new edition
is on sale at amazon.com i think it's
close to 40
off i saw that yesterday i don't know if
it still is but it could be
this is 16.99 51 off on amazon.com you
can also get at barnes and other places
local bookstores or get a free flavor if
that's what you want to do
um so this is critical information
though you guys let's talk about it for
a minute all right i got the bell pepper
steaming i got the
onions going lorraine i better not
forget
i burnt i burnt the crap at everything
the other night
um thank you anthony for spending
your valuable time with us instead of
with your family
you know it means means means the world
that you even know
like my dedication hearing your voice
brings me peace and hope and i
appreciate all that you do much
more than you know um cocopine
2011 i'm honored truly
um casey no wonder my brain is fried
thanks aw i'm studying up on all your
work now i have so much
gumption to heal i love that word
gumption really cool
great word anna is it true that women
need more protein during pregnancy
it's what's being pushed by the national
health guidelines
huh interesting of course it's pushed
that's what i was talking about before
about protein is the protein
brainwashing scheme of a lifetime was a
deal brokered in 1933.
so it's important to know what happened
is protein was
was used as a weapon in 1933 big pharma
and the academic world both combined
to make sure that you would think
protein is the answer
it's it's one of the biggest scams of
our lifetime it's so sad one day i'll do
a whole protein show because there's so
much information involved with it
but yeah that's how it works what you
need
is mineral salts and glucose you need
calories when you're pregnant but proper
calories mineral salts and glucose right
that's what you need protein isn't it
isn't what your
baby is is utilizing right it's not what
mommy's utilizing in order to create a
healthy baby and that's that's a massive
scam
i mean it just is um and yeah they're
pushing that information but they push
misinformation
every day in every way out there right
and you know what
here's the best part about it i'm going
to tell you right now
the misinformation pushers don't know
why anybody's sick so if mommy gets sick
check this out when mommy gets sick with
fatigue
right hair hair thinning alopecia
all right aches and pains when mommy
gets sick with hashimoto's thyroiditis
okay when mommy gets sick with
ra right or lupus or anything
the same people saying mommy needs
protein
for her baby are the same people that
don't know why you're sick
does that make a lot of sense to you
think about that one
that is a head scratcher times a
thousand for me
that's a head scratcher times a million
so okay
wait a minute okay so all right you got
all the answers
oh okay you guys got all the answers um
it's protein that i need for my baby
okay but
how come you guys don't have one single
valid
answer for why 250 million americans
alone
right their mind all around the world
are sick with symptoms right
so i that's a funny one for me
so we're experts at what mommy needs
when we don't know why mommy's sick
we don't know why mom mommy has
postpartum depression postpartum fatigue
postpartum sickness thyroid disease
we don't know why mommy has breast
cancer we don't know down the road we
don't know why mommy has anything
anything at all but we're experts to
what mommy needs
mommy needs her protein for her baby
right we don't know why mommy's ever
been sick
any mommy's been sick in decade after
decade after decade
we don't know why any mommy's been sick
for the whole century for the last
century
and this century already but we're
experts at what mommy needs
we're total experts right
when you think when you put it in
perspective when you place
that into perspective you you're already
like wait a minute
right i mean it's beyond common sense
like beyond
amy gallbladder inflammation help
yeah the you know like if i had
gallbladder inflammation if i did
keeping the fats down is critical right
steaming up some keeping the fats down
is critical that's part one
the more fat you eat
okay whether it's healthy fat or fat
that's not healthy
the more bile has to be produced
so your liver is killing itself to
produce that vial right
so your liver is just killing itself to
produce
bile right okay so your liver is it's
it's over working right so it's gotta
spew out all this bile you keep on
putting fat in
you just keep on dumping in and you
might be like what is he talking about
fat
you know chicken fish beef milk cheese
eggs butter
bacon pork pork chops whatever right ham
okay nuts seeds oils coconut oil right
sesame seeds whatever it is right all
that fat right olive oil
your liver has to kill itself so now you
got an inflamed gallbladder
the gallbladder is inflamed right it's a
little gallbladder
your gallbladder's inflamed and we're
we're now overworking the liver and the
liver has to
produce all this bile and shove it up
the gallbladder like send it up the
gallbladder
now the gallbladder is over stressed it
has to work hard
to even sustain itself when you got a
gallbladder infection of any kind which
is usually streptococcus
when you have a streptococcus
gallbladder infection and you got all
that bile spewing up
and it's overburdening that gallbladder
that's one reason why we can't heal we
can't heal it
another reason the more fat you dump in
the less oxygen in your bloodstream the
less oxygen in your bloodstream
the more pathogens like streptococcus
can take over
and create that inflamed gallbladder so
you got that streptococcus
inflaming the gallbladder right and a
lot of people's gallbladder it's
inflamed by streptococcus bacteria
and then all of a sudden we're dumping
in fats left and right and streptococcus
is like woohoo there's no oxygen in our
blood
there's very little oxygen in our blood
now we roll the roost let's keep on
going with this infection let's keep on
going with this infection here's the
other problem
the more fat in your bloodstream the
less the nutrients
the less phytochemical compounds that
are antibacterial can get to your
gallbladder so now
if you eat a red bell pepper which
happens to have vitamin c
which is a phytochemical compound which
helps destroy pathogens right
like your streptococcus and you're
trying to eat all these and you want
your onion
you get your onion that can help you
fight infections right
you get your garlic that can help you
it's anti-viral antibacterial right
but those phytochemical compounds can't
get to the organ
because there's so much fat in the
bloodstream blocking
glucose sugar from taking those
nutrients
into your organ now we're not even
getting the fighting power we need
there's a lot of information right here
just letting you guys know
i mean it's intense and i'm rolling it
fast
genetic disease sadie bear genetic
disease okay so
uh i'll answer that in a second i think
a phone call was coming through that i
had an appointment
had an appointment with my doctor
hey dr joby thanks for calling
phew so what was my diagnosis
you're my 10th doctor it's genetic
what do you mean what do you mean
genetic
i was fine years ago
so when did my genes go bad
dr joby so you mean to tell me
all right i'm in my i'm in my 40s
yeah i'm 41 years old uh-huh
and i've been fine up until i was 39
and now my genes just went bad
so now this this disease this disease
i'm getting is genes
okay so everybody who's getting sick
it's their genes everybody
um oh what about people who are born
with problems that's genes
well wait a minute why that's genes too
i don't get it because
so wait a minute okay if you don't have
problems your whole life and then you
get a problem that's genes if you're
born with a problem that's genes
what so everything's just genes okay so
dr joby so
what's my what do we do we can't do
anything really because it's jeans
rest okay so get some rest all right
what else
um stay out of trouble keep the stress
down
uh okay well what if i get
better it's remission so if i get better
my genetic disease is in remission but
wait a minute i thought
genes when they're bad they're bad so
you mean my genes completely
healed when i'm in remission no
they didn't heal my genes are still bad
but when i go into remission
i'm in remission so okay so if i get
better
my genes are still bad that just doesn't
make any sense
um this is confusing me
all right is everybody's genes going bad
i hung up on the doctor i had an
appointment with the doctor today just
hung up on him
i'm making hot sauce this is steaming up
nice
actually that's cooking up really good
that's almost done
um i'm gonna take the lid off
evaporate some of that juice
um
you know it's like when babies are born
with cancer that's not genes
that's that's an immune system
deficiency off the running
and it's important to know how this
works right they just want to pinpoint
everything with genes if a baby's born
with cancer
that's a viral infection because because
cancer is caused by viruses unless you
get asbestos or you get
you get unless it's a lethal solvent
and you know that you know that's a
different story right but outside of
those very rare cases
cancer is viral right viral
cells going awry but you have to but but
you can't
just get cancer from viruses viruses
need toxins so they need
a certain amount of a toxic slop and
brew to feed off of right
so viruses have to feed off of a lot of
metals
and a lot of other toxins that's what
viruses have to do
and then the virus feeds off all these
toxins
and then gets stronger and starts to
mutate
and as it starts to mutate we have a
different viral cell
doctors um and sophie
doctors are telling me they can't help
me out because
i am adopted they say it's genetic
that's it's real oh my god i'm s
and sophie this breaks my heart that you
have to hear that
um look i want you to listen to your
doctor i want you to go see your doctor
of course and all that but but if that
was me
i i would be yeah i would be upset
because
you know if that was me and that's what
i was told
i just i would just i wouldn't even by
being disbelieved
so we're making some hot hot sauce here
well that's what they'll tell you
that's so sad really it's so sad that
they tell us that
adhd and autism they'll say adhd and
autism is genetic no it's not
it's toxic heavy metals that's what it
is there's answers to why we have
problems there's actual answers i'm
making some hot sauce i'm going to do a
half
a half cup of chopped red bell pepper
which is the rest of this pepper right
here let's make some hot sauce real
quick
i'm going to use the rest of this pepper
for this hot sauce
i'm using a food processor i'm trying
that out i've done that a lot with
sauces and stuff so i do like it that
way
get some pepper in here let's get some
cherry tomatoes in here too we don't
need a ton of them about a third of a
cup but i'm gonna throw
a few of these in here
cherry tomatoes so
um fresh red cayenne pepper if you don't
have that use some chili pepper flakes
right here
got the chili pepper flakes right i'm
glad you guys could be on here today
with me
we're live facebook or live youtube but
i'm going to throw one of these
really hot peppers in here
i don't know how much kind of pepper
torture i want to be in tonight so maybe
i'll use
a smaller one these are really hot and
when they get blended these are super
chilies right
cayenne is what you use super chill
these are super chilis right there
that's going to be hot that's going to
be hot
i'm going to put that in there don't
fall for the nightshade
bs very important
if super sensitive it's like well are
you sure you're super sensitive
to a nightshade so if you took a fresh
delicious
heirloom tomato and you cut that tomato
in half and you had a piece of that
fresh tomato
you sure that's causing the trouble
um there's no cheese you sure there's no
cheese in there there's no oil in there
see because um
i'm gonna grab something right here
where'd you guys go where'd you go so
you see like
okay i can't tell you how many times i
heard
in 35 years right i'm sensitive to
tomatoes
and they had pizza and they're saying
it's the tomato sauce and the pizza
right
when really we're talking about the
cheese and the oil
and the gluten right that's an example
all on its own it's really important to
know
i'm gonna put that nice pizza over there
you know if you're mono eating
and you keep out the oils and you keep
out the bad stuff and you keep out the
milk cheese butter and you keep all that
out
and you're and you can determine really
what am i sensitive to and even in that
situation if you're cleansing a lot of
poisons out you may not know
you know you may actually be like whoa
i'm actually doing some cleansing and
detoxing you know there's a whole thing
about detoxing where people are like i
heard that word before it's
whatever but you know when you do it
right and you're healing yeah you will
be cleansing and a lot of poisons will
be going out
a lot of people do fake detoxes they
take a bunch of toxic products they get
sick from the toxic products and then
they call it detoxing when really
they're just sick from toxic products
um so keep that in mind right there
a lot of people drown there they have
tomato and ketchup with all the vinegar
right
that's a problem all on its own all the
vinegar the vinegar is making them sick
um by the way people make mistakes i'm
going to talk about this let's i'll talk
about this in a second but i want to
finish this up
what happens with potato as being a
nightshade family right or
eggplant eggplant parmesan
right eggplant parmesan right the
parmesan
right fried eggplant in oil the fried
oil makes people get all like feeling
like they're busted up right
it's tomato sauce with cheese in it
and all kinds of stuff pasta with cheese
on it right
these things you know it's baked potato
with sour cream
and butter and your mashed potatoes it's
just combinations
a lot of that's what's happening right
but a steamed potato doesn't cause a
problem with someone
um a lot of people make mistakes with
with i'm gonna give you some tips right
now if you have digestive
issues of any kind like you're sensitive
you're inflamed in your digestive tract
because a lot of people are inflamed in
their digestive tract
and when they're inflamed in their
intestinal lining because they got
streptococcus they got inflammation
caused by
pathogens and they're inflamed they
don't feel like they're digesting
anything and so when you eat like
when you eat like raw spinach or raw
lettuce or raw red bell pepper
like i can't eat that red bell pepper i
can't eat a raw piece of onion i can't
digest it but what's
happening is they're digesting it but
it's actually
touching everything because you're in
flames so you feel it right
so then when they eat an egg right so
then when they eat an egg
okay and they have that egg they don't
feel it because it's not touching
anything it turns into glue and it's
just moving through here into
its glue it's not rubbing right
but when we eat our lettuces and our
spinach right raw
it's rubbing it's moving through us
right you guys
okay so you feel it if you're in flame
doesn't mean you're not digesting it see
but here's the funny thing you take
vegetables right vegetables
and you don't steam them long enough
till they're soft
you're gonna feel those rub everything
too so
the difference is here is when you steam
a vegetable or cook a vegetable
you kill it right yeah you kill it yeah
it's not raw
you kill it you cook it right but when
you do that
you get the nutrients and all that but
what happens is that
this is done right here i'm going to put
some potatoes in here what happens is
that
it's not cooked vegetables
are easy to digest when they're soft
when you cook them
raw vegetables many of like lettuces and
and spinach and all that are easy to
digest
right when when they're raw
right but when you cook green beans and
cook carrots but you don't steam them
until they're soft
in any and anything like red bell pepper
anything you don't steam them
until they're soft what happens
is that they they tend to they tend to
rub
things along the way not break down as
easy
right you've got to steam them soft if
you're sensitive you're not sensitive
with any kind of digestive sensitivities
you can just steam them lightly i do it
all the time i steam my stuff really
lightly right
but i like steaming them more more with
you guys because i know a lot of you
guys
have a lot of sensitivities but we need
our vegetables
um so what i just did is i just put
in here i got some onion in this bowl
i got some uh red bell pepper in here
right okay now i'm gonna do now i'm
gonna start working on
some potatoes
now i'm gonna start working on the
potatoes i'm gonna just take some of
this out here
there we go all right
and i'm gonna i got steamed potatoes
right here remember i keep a whole bunch
handy right you guys
and i'm gonna cut up some nice pieces
right here
okay in the pan nice hot pan i cook cook
them ahead i keep them in the fridge
covering a lot covering a lot of cool
topics that
count back to alzheimer's and dementia
no the more fat you do the quicker you
get there
the more fat you do the quicker you get
there the more protein you do the
quicker you get there
yeah the more protein you do the quicker
you get to alzheimer's and dementia
reason why most proteins have a lot of
fat in there
keep that in mind so um
you know that's important to know so i
got some potato in here i'm gonna do
another one
so i'm just kind of cubing them a little
bit you guys guys with me
i'm really happy we're here today
i wasn't sure if i could even do a live
today i wasn't sure i got a lot
lot going on there's just a lot going on
and it's hard to always
you know be able to do this but you know
what i pushed myself and i said we're
going to do this no matter what did it
um anyway i'm getting some potato going
in the pan just getting it nice and
toasty a little bit so i got a sauce i'm
making so i'm going to put a clove of
garlic in here you can do three cloves
of garlic uh
i'm gonna do one clove of garlic for
this because you know what i already
i already put um a really hot pepper in
this one
i just put a clove of garlic in there
right
okay if you're sensitive do less do a
quarter
do a quarter clove or okay and that hot
spice might be hard on you right
uh three tablespoons of lime juice
let's go with some limes
let's do that start getting some lime
juice in here
lissy cone hey what are you on facebook
or you on youtube is this recipe in the
book i want to make this tonight laugh
out loud where is this
you know the books too you actually know
the book unless he's a family friend
dear friend of mine
and knows the books inside and out read
every word and knows them
like knows them i'll post it it will be
posted tomorrow
let's see i'll post this tomorrow so i'm
just getting some lime juice in here
okay potatoes are done
toasting up browning up nice
and this is the medical medium let's see
this is the medical medium hot sauce
on the on the blog it's already there
what i love about this is got some juice
from those onions
and mushrooms and red bell pepper in
here right
incredible turn that off
get these potatoes in here
[Music]
so good so good
i got the potatoes in there too so it's
coming together right
got the onions this is a potato bowl got
the onions and the mushrooms right here
and the red bell peppers cooked down
here i got this
incredible like broth juice that's
that's on the bottom and i got these
these toasted up potatoes right here
these potatoes were steamed beforehand
keep that in mind you guys
keep that in mind if you stick raw
potatoes in there you got to cook them
for a while
to get them to cook right
keep that in mind all right let's keep
on working this let's get some lemon in
here
quarter cup of lemon juice goes in this
dressing let me get a strainer
somebody said the other i don't know if
it was what was it it was recently or
something he said
you got a metal strainer mr heavy metal
guy
[Music]
mr heavy metal guy worry about your
metals
and you got a metal strainer true
i do and i'm not worried
because i've been doing that heavy metal
detox movie for a long time
and it gets more metal out of you than
you can put in you
it's all about getting more metal out of
you than you can
put in you right
okay so what else do we need here we
need some raw honey
let's go with a little bit of raw honey
okay
three tablespoons of raw honey
we put a really big amount here
nice nice get the raw honey going
okay and um i think that's it i'm going
to blend this up let's just
get get it out the honey off the spoon a
little bit
so i'm making the
the sauce the hot sauce which i'm
actually really excited about
give this a little whirl you guys with
me let's talk about some other stuff and
i want to answer some questions too
hold on a second here
make sure this is together there you go
do a little pulsing here
nice i'm gonna put this in a bowl
[Music]
let's spin that
i'm gonna spin it a little bit more i'm
gonna put in a jar
you guys okay with that i put this in
the jar
doing some food process processor action
nice i can already tell that this is
going to be hot
you know it it look put a little cayenne
there you can do that you can do it you
don't have to make it super hot but i
actually
i actually made this one super hot okay
sorry
all right let me just put this in you
guys see if i can do this without making
a mess
so i'm just getting the hot sauce in
this jar right here
all right um now
you can put a little bit of this i'm
going to take a tablespoon i'll take the
tablespoon that the honey
right with the honey not great um
and i was going to put a little
tablespoon on here drizzle it on right
you don't have to use a ton of it put it
in the fridge for a little bit
and then i'm going to cut up some green
onion
put on top too okay so i'm putting a
little this hot sauce on here
i'm pumped up about this this is
actually really exciting
i'm i'm actually really excited about
this let me chop up a few green onions
you guys okay if i do that
[Music]
you know i woke up this morning and i
was thinking about all you guys
and i was talking a spirit of compassion
right
talking to spirit of compassion and
i said i said most high
since i was a child that's one of my
nicknames there right
i said what more can i do and he said to
me
people are in need of this information
and it's about saving lives protecting
lives too
right
don't take your eye off the ball
all these years 35 years you haven't
contradicted yourself
you've been true to the information
you've been fighting for the chronicle
spirit said
and we got to keep the mission strong
putting a little bit more of these green
onions on there i can't help it i love
it
as i said after that i
getting myself ready this morning it was
about 5 30 this morning and i said
god give me strength
a lot of people are gonna get sick in
the coming years
we're gonna see autoimmune like we've
never seen before
and so i was chopping up a little bit of
parsley you don't need a lot of parsley
here
put a little on top okay a little bit of
parsley
that's a dish and i'm pumped about
eating it i really am
okay all right i'm gonna get a lemon
slice here
you guys okay with that
get a little lemon slice on the side
you can do a lemon slice in different
ways um
i'm going to do it this way here here we
go
sometimes i like doing the lemon slice
like that look at that i don't know if
you guys can see it so easy i'm gonna
put it on the side
like this put it right on the side in
here when i got that
so it's incredible the potatoes here i
got the mushrooms red bell peppers all
of it
the sauce on top i'm so excited about
this
diane i just have to say i am a chronic
migraine sufferer and i spent years
trying various different meds
but since i've started the celery juice
i've had an incredible
improvement in overall health the needle
moved
you moved diane you moved the needle
you did it you moved the needle
right right that's what that is and
the disrespect out there towards celery
juice the disrespect
out there towards the chronically ill
right
and it's kind they're constantly
insulting chronically ill 24 7 out there
but yet you've got the health scene
pretending they actually care about the
chronicle when
i've seen leaders in the health scene
they don't really care they care about
their pocket their dollars
they care about their fame they care
about their empires they're all building
on their podcast they care about
their empires right and then they dangle
carrots in front of everybody
you know like as if they're doing like
enough right
and then they tear apart celery juice at
the same time seen that over and over
right because
why build celery juice up and make it
into something big when no one can make
money off of it and
all it's going to do is get anthony
william the medical media more
well-known so let's keep the down low on
the celery juice but make sure
we're drinking it and the meanwhile the
sad thing is
if we cared about the chronically ill
and we cared about people suffering like
diane
you with your migraines then we would be
we would be really really making sure
everybody knew about how this needle
could be moved and
and we'd have uh two billion people
drinking celery juice right
got a migraine chapter in the book
and new edition migraine chapter so
everybody knows okay
there it is and um it's the revised
expanded new edition
so i made this incredible dish right
here i'm heading to ig
and tic toc fasten your seat belts i
don't know what kind of mood i'm in
tonight
but um we'll see
because we're going to be doing ig in a
little while i don't know if it's going
to be 10 minutes or something like that
i'll probably clean up a little bit
straighten out just for a couple of
minutes i might take a quick jab at this
dish right here but the suffering has
just begun
chronically ill or as far as what's
coming
with autoimmune diagnoses and where
we're heading in the next year
and two years and three years and next
six months and
yeah even if no one sees the numbers yet
right because everything gets suppressed
you know yep ryan lau hello
we'll see you there amazing kailyn
mitchell
um see you there anthony awesome i'm
honored
michelle constantine celery juice cured
my acid reflux i've been drinking it
every day i had reflux
for a lifetime even as a little kid
thanks so much just incredible
incredible you guys gonna come to me
with to ig
um i think a lot of people don't come to
ig with me because they think it's the
same show
it's not the same show i mean i do a
different show each time by the way you
guys before you all go seriously
before you all go moon meditation i'm
doing it tonight
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
the uncensored version of the moon
meditation right
it's a special moon tonight very special
moon tonight
use its powers use its magnetic
powers to help you heal the moon
meditation
try to access for the emotional wounds
and the soul healing right
so i'm doing the moon meditation today
i'm doing it tomorrow night the next
night after it because you still have
that powerful moon
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
everybody should be doing it share it
with everybody tell everybody a friend
and everything
even if someone's like i don't want to
do that she'd be like no do it do it
all right ig and tick tock head in there
can't wait love you guys