I'm reading out a brain saver about pots
a lot of people live with pots now the
detailed information is so comprehensive
inside brain saver it's mind-blowing so
I'm going to read a little bit to you
right now people living with pots really
struggle the unpredictability of pots
symptoms can be maddening for many in
most cases of pots it takes months to
years of Doctor shopping to get
validation for their symptoms and that's
what I see out there all the time with
pots all these years it takes doctor
after doctor after doctor to finally get
some doctor some professionals say I
think you have pots ma'am
because of these symptoms is byproducts
and toxins built up in a stagnant
sluggish liver being released and
collecting around heart valves so check
this out so in a stagnant sluggish liver
right here all these toxins build up and
then they finally get released out of
the liver and then they collect around
the heart
pot symptoms go Way Beyond problems with
getting up or leaning forward so it's
not just about oh let me get up here
whoa whoa let me lean forward it's more
than that or leaning down because pots
is a viral
neurotoxin Disorder so I'm talking about
viral neurotoxins creamy pots in the
brain saver books right now right one
reason pots is so difficult is that it's
a chronic viral infection in pots the
Epstein-Barr virus has been in the liver
for a long time so anybody with pots
anybody with pot symptoms they have the
Epstein-Barr virus sitting inside their
liver not for a short amount of time in
their life not for a month but more than
a year in fact years years in pots the
Epstein-Barr virus sits in the liver for
years and collects neurotoxins that
cause pot symptoms ranging from the
dizziness people go through right and
then the difficulty with exercising and
that's one of the reasons why they get
the diagnosis of pots because they say
the doctor oh I can't exercise because I
get dizzy I get lightheadedness I faint
I get fatigue I get the brain fog nausea
chest pain the blurred vision the racing
heart unstable blood pressure when the
liver is stagnant and sluggish
overburdened and filled with years worth
of viral toxins various areas of the
liver become blocked that's a whole
nother problem with pots
areas of the VIS the liver actually get
blocked so you might get a blocked
section of the liver that means the
blood vessels inside the liver tissue
get clogged up with byproduct from the
Epstein-Barr virus
this makes it harder for blood to get
drawn through the liver to get to the
heart putting the heart under a
continual strain so here it goes your
heart is trying to pump all the blood
from your liver up into it but when the
liver is stagnant sluggish and blocked
in certain areas and that's the whole
thing with pots and people have pots the
liver is blocked in certain areas so
then when the heart is sitting here
trying to pump and pump and pump it
can't do its job it's struggling and
this brings us into pot symptoms right
pot symptoms so here you got your liver
it's blocked in certain areas
and here's your heart and it's pumping
it's pumping away like this right
but it's pumping harder people with pots
can feel their heart beat sometimes
pulsing through their like neck through
their ear through the side of their face
their forehead in their throat somewhere
or in their chest more or when they're
laying down in bed people that are on
mattress Island they've been laying
there for a long time for a lot of hours
during the day or on the couch Island
because they're not well you can feel
the heart and then you're telling your
doctor well I feel like my heart doing
something or I feel heart pressure and
what happens is that's the heart working
hard trying to get blood up through a
stagnant liver when certain areas of the
stagnant liver are blocked blood vessels
are blocked to a degree with neurotoxins
and toxins from the Epstein for our
virus so we're reading the pots we're
right here in brain saver books you guys
order them when you get a chance you
will be surprised when you start reading
these really eye-opening
so we'll go into this a little bit more
viral neurotoxins are also floating
around so here's another thing so many
people who are pots they have these
viral neurotoxins floating around
saturating and inflaming the vagus
nerves whole other problem so then you
have all of these neurotoxins that are
floating around and when they float
around they land on sensitive nerves
vagus nerves so the vagus nerves coming
out of the brain stem right here coming
out going through the body and what
happens is these neurotoxins land on the
vagus nerves and start to swell the
nerves and now the person with pots has
the dizziness they have a little bit of
the vertigo they have all these other
issues going on because their vagus
nerves are inflamed
so let's keep on going there's so much
detail comprehensive information about
illnesses in brain saver it'll blow your
mind but that's the whole point you
become an expert when you have this much
detailed information that no one else
has you become the expert you control
your health when you become the expert
which is really powerful
if the vagus nerves are inflamed higher
up let's go into that right here so if
your vagus nerves are inflamed higher up
heading to the brain stem down in here
right if that happens let's go let's go
find that spot then we get different
symptoms that's a whole other problem
that occurs so if the vagus nerves are
inflamed higher up closer to the brain
that inflammation on the vagus nerves
from the neurotoxins can create symptoms
when someone is just getting out of bed
so let's go into that for a minute
you're laying in bed it's time to get up
you get up and boom you're hit you feel
kind of weak you're not feeling that
strong your legs kind of feel like
they're being weighed down you're
getting kind of heart symptoms you feel
like you're getting a little tachycardia
that can happen too that that's what
happens when the vagus nerves higher up
are getting inflamed
and there's so much information I can go
on and on in here that's incredible so
let's go into this part
okay that inflammation from those
neurotoxins can create symptoms when
someone is just getting out of bed
picking themselves up off the ground do
you have pots has that ever happened to
you where you actually pick yourself off
the ground and you get hit you're like
boom standing up quickly you bend down
and you stand up quickly bending down
right you try to climb up a hill or if
you're trying to actually climb up a
hill that's another thing exerting
yourself in any way for some people it
feels like having sandbags on their legs
where they're walking and you feel like
you have sandbags on your legs full body
weakness your arms feel really weak or
even feeling like you're about to
collapse that's what so many people go
through everybody's pot symptoms vary
because everybody's immune system varies
everybody's viral load
varies everybody's viral mutations of
the Epstein-Barr vary and everyone's
liver capacity for the toxins varies
that varies your symptom and you know
what's interesting all these years you
don't see any of that information out
there you don't get the details you
can't become an expert when you don't
know why you're sick it's in here and it
is packed really packed
so let's go a little bit further because
we can keep on going
often these days people don't get a pots
diagnosis by itself isn't that weird
isn't that funny so if you had a pots
diagnosis you got pots and something
else you've got pots this this this and
this someone with pots has often seen
multiple doctors and received other
diagnoses have you gotten like another
diagnosis so you were actually pots and
then you got another diagnosis for like
another different condition often pots
gets wrapped up into Lyme disease some
of you guys probably had that like with
it fibromyalgia where you've got
fibromyalgia diagnosis and a pots
diagnosis lupus a lupus diagnosis in a
pot's diagnosis
vertigo diagnosis mecfs or chronic
fatigue because someone is experienced
various symptoms when you when you're
dealing with pots you could also be
dealing with all these other symptoms so
when you go Doctor shopping you get a
bunch of different labels to take home
you know instead of your bag of goodies
or your haul for different shoes and
clothes and other things are food at the
grocery store you come back from your
doctor shopping with a haul of diagnoses
and labels okay
the distinction is that in pots the
liver is more stagnant and sluggish more
overloaded with neurotoxins then here's
the thing that's the whole point how do
you even know the difference of what
this symptom is that condition the
details in here matter that's how
incredible it is it's telling you right
now the difference the distinction is
that in pots the liver is more stagnant
and sluggish it's not getting sluggish
more overloaded with neurotoxins which
means that certain areas of the vagus
nerves and up more are puffed out and
inflamed the more you have toxins and
poisons and neurotoxins inside the liver
the more the vagus nerves are going to
Puff out causing more inflammation
bringing you to all kinds of things so
when you do certain moves like movements
exertion
um Can it can prompt dizziness
lightheadedness vertigo struggle or
breathing or tachycardia the combination
of a liver that has blockages Along With
viral infections creates the
unpredictability this is just scratching
the surface the pots protocol is in the
protocols book the pots information is
in brain saver but it's more than that
seven heavy metal detox cleanses brain
shot therapies if new tool too from
medical medium information when you get
these books you become the expert and
that's how you become empowered I've
been saying this for years you want
empowerment with your health you don't
want anybody else to own you you want
you to be you then learn the information
to what's wrong so you can then fix it
and become that expert that I'm just
scratching the surface of the brain
saver books I'll see you next time you
guys