right now mono eating cleanse
challenge this is the preliminary this
is the beginning this is to prep
be prepared we need to be prepared
what are you guys doing are you guys
ready for it do you have any papaya can
you find that
if that's not something you're
interested in the moderating cleanse
because we'll talk about the different
different options and stuff are you
doing banana is that something you're
doing right
are you doing the steamed potato one
where it's potatoes
how about that right and you have your
celery ready too
is that going on i mean this is serious
business here
you do have some lettuce for the next
few days
got some other things here too some
other options to talk about but
or maybe even peas do you have some peas
that's another thing as well glad you
guys are coming out we're live on
facebook live on youtube 11 tick tock
we're live on clubhouse we're talking
about the mono eating
eating challenge that's tomorrow so the
mono cleanse that's what we're talking
about it's gonna be tomorrow the next
day the next day three days
i'm coming on for a reminder answer some
questions too because a lot of people
are asking can i do my heavy metal detox
during the mono-eating cleanse
so that's that's a question there can i
eat different things can i do
watermelon during my mono eating cleanse
so
everybody's got a question i know you
guys are going to have some questions
i'm going to look out
and i'll i'll try to read some questions
also on tik tok as well
i'm gonna juice a little celery for
myself i didn't even have any today
i hope you have some celery ready for
the cleanse it's important it's really
important so for example
if you choose say the steamed potato
mono eating cleanse
you're still going to need your celery
because celery juice is really important
right there
if you choose the banana version right
that's another one too and do you have a
medical medium cleanse the heel
because without the guide it's going to
be
harder to do yeah you can be there
because i'm going to be doing it for
myself the model eating cleanse
challenge
you could be here for it you can work
with the stuff i'm going to teach you or
show you but do you have cleanse to heal
and that's really important it's an
important piece because
the mono eating section right here in
the book
so and the details are in here so you'll
see right here you guys
mono eating cleanse see on tick tock see
on
youtube and facebook right there there
you go
so the mono eating cleanse that's it
right there see i got little postage
notes right there
too good to see you guys coming on happy
about that
so you guys can do a couple of different
options in here there's
and i'm going to give you just the
rundown right here right off the running
okay
you can do a banana mono eating cleanse
with
optional lettuce because lettuce should
be in there and banana and i'll talk
about what else we can do
papaya is a moderating cleanse too if
you can get a hold of papayas then you
could just do papaya
banana and papaya is optional
so both so if you want to do banana and
papaya
and then you have your lettuce that's
the other option there
steamed potatoes is an option
with lettuce okay steamed
peas is another option so steamed peas a
lot of people they can't get a hold of
potatoes or they can't get a hold of
papaya they can't get all the banana
then you got the steamed peas
right then there's an option where you
do steamed
winter squash you guys see the butternut
squash right here
but you can do the steamed winter squash
and then
pick some green beans or some brussels
sprouts or some asparagus
for the end of the day as well and have
that with your lettuce so
that's another option there too so you
have all these now there's people that
are saying well hey can i do watermelon
yeah you can do watermelon
but the whole thing with watermelon is
you better be doing your celery juice
you can't just say hey
i'm gonna do watermelon for the next
three days
and not do your celery juice you need
those mineral salts or you're gonna just
you're gonna hit that place where
boom you're basically just doing a juice
fast that's all that is
because watermelon doesn't have enough
calories
to sustain without all of a sudden
making it where you want to break or
you've got to have the celery juice in
there if you go that route
and so and if you're doing the
watermelon
version right that's the one you pick
because some people are like i love
watermelon it's watermelon season where
i am
let me do that you've got to be doing
your celery juice
you should be bringing in some lettuce
okay so
if you don't mind some lettuce in there
bring in some lettuce
okay and you don't want to do it term
the mono eating cleanse
has been designed from spirit of
compassion to do long
term if you would like long term if you
want
and that long term is to heal things
so it's to really heal deep issues
crohn's colitis celiac ibs
cramping bloating flatulence gastritis
acid reflux gastroparesis
so the mono-eating cleanse is designed
for deep
healing from intestinal disturbances
intestinal problems
recovery from food poisoning right
recovering from that recovering from a
stomach bug
recovering from the stomach flu the mono
eating cleanse is designed to recover
some people give the stomach flu so bad
they're ripped to shreds for months they
can't get back on track their guts are a
mess
and the motto eating cleanse is to get
somebody back on track to bring them
back from stomach flu food poisoning
anything crohn's colitis ibs
acid reflux gastroparesis like i said
diarrhea
constipation so the money mono eating
cleanse
challenge we're doing is really designed
for someone
to heal along the way and
it's all talked about right here in
cleanse the heel
so in if you guys don't know amazon.com
us
okay you can get it on sale 51 off right
now
or look for it at the library but make
sure you have this because this guide
is incredibly important for this so if
you guys just got on here we're talking
about the mono eating cleanse
challenge that's coming tomorrow so it's
gonna be three days
it's gonna be thursday friday saturday
you don't want to miss it i'm going to
be doing it and showing you guys what to
do and everything this is kind of like
preparation
this is preparing that's what this is
do you have cleanse to heal number one
okay we'll go through it
do you have cleanse to heal okay that's
the first thing right there
right that's one thing there okay do you
have some celery do you have that
just gotta go through this you guys do
you have some lettuce that's butter leaf
lettuce do you like a green butter leaf
do you have lettuce
okay are you gonna do the banana one do
you have bananas are they ripe enough
are they ripe enough do you have bananas
those are right those are actually
almost
a little a little past with the way i
like um
is it okay to take heavy metal detox
smoothie with mono eating so let's cover
that a little bit there's gonna be
a heavy metal detox cleanse challenge
that i'm going to be doing for
next month right that's going to be next
month's healing challenge right
heavy metal detox so that's what it's
going to be right so
the mono eating cleanse is set up for
people who got the food sensitivities
right they got all kinds of stomach
problems
they've got all kinds of chemical
sensitivities food sensitivities
food allergies so you have all these
other things too okay
they got you know like the the
inflammation inside the
gut so inside their gut they're inflamed
they don't know it but they got bad
bacteria they got viruses they got yeast
and mold
they got fungus deep down in their gut
and it's all
in here so the medical medium
mono-eating cleanse is something to get
someone back on track get out of sibo
get rid of that get
get into a better place move past these
problems the inflammation
so a lot of people that use it including
hives right including hives because it's
the liver being junky and everything but
a lot of people use the mono-eating
cleanse to save their butt
to heal and recover they're kind of
sensitive so they're not doing much of
anything else so they just keep it the
monolith
you want to bring in a heavy metal detox
bring it in after a few days
bring it after a few days that's all do
the mono eating cleanse without it just
for a few days
why not if you really don't want to lose
the mud if you don't really don't want
to lose the heavy metal detox smoothie
keep it in keep it in but that's going
to be your own
version right i mean not you meaning
like your own little
kind of customizing you're customizing
the medical medium tools
so if you want to be if you want to be
that person you said like i still want
to do my heavy metal detox movie but
still want to do the mono eating cleanse
okay
we can we can hybridize it
customize it that's what you're doing
you're customizing it your way right
so i'm going to use this medical medium
tool the heavy metal detox smoothie
and i'm going to use this medical medium
tool
some mono eating and that's what you're
going to do
but depending on the person what's going
on you know you may get different
results that's why the monoleading
cleanse is designed a certain way for
certain gut
problems but yes you could do the heavy
metal detox smoothie question
answered yes yes yes another question
was the watermelon answer that one yes
you can do that that's going to be a nut
you're doing a medical medium tool
and a medical medium tool you know and
that's what you're doing
you're doing the celery juice you got to
do the celery juice you're going to play
with watermelon
for those few days you got to do the
celery just while you're playing with
watermelon
and you might want to think about still
having some butter leaf lettuce
instead of just doing all watermelon all
watermelon all watermelon
okay you've got to have enough of the
mineral salts
with that watermelon keep that in mind
you have to have the mineral salts with
that watermelon if you're going to go
that route
okay so the bananas look a little
browner than normal right but
they're not that right they're ripe
enough
just right what happened is i wash my
bananas
they just come from the store i'll just
oh i'll just wash them
is what i do so when you wash bananas
the skins on the outsides do this
so that's what happens when you wash
them i know people they buy them in the
store
they grab them they crack one open and
eat one with their hands
and what they don't realize that a whole
bunch of people are going through these
bananas in this door it's like i don't
know if i want that bunch let me put
that back i don't know if i want that
bunch
they're grabbing the carriage there's
all kinds of strep and
e coli on their hands and all kinds of
herpes simplex one on their hands
you know for playing with their cold
sores or something and there's all kinds
of different stuff
on their hands all over the place
there's feces on shopping carts
there's always feces on the handles of
shopping carts just you know there's
there's always feces on that
so when i so so what if i get bananas
from the store
right and it's not in a case because i
like to get a case of bananas this time
i didn't get a case of bananas so i got
like
single bunches so i just gave it a wash
that's all so i'm using it because i
don't want to put this on my cutting
board
just right it comes out of the store you
put it right on your cutting board
i don't want to do that it's not a smart
move that's why it's why people just
they're like hey i'm doing your stuff
and all of a sudden i'll feel good with
something i remember over the years but
spirit of compassion would be spirit of
compassion be like yeah because they
just
bought stuff through all their
containers on their cutting board
through all their stuff on their cutting
board all kinds of different bugs and
things
feces from shopping carts and other
stuff just all over the stuff
and then the other thing too people
don't realize in the warehouses
where all the grocery products are
there's rats running through
all the grocery stores there's there's
rat poison in the corners of grocery
stores all the chain grocery store
chains
there's mice there's roaches there's
rats in the warehouses of all the
department of groceries doesn't matter
what department it is
whether it's wheat whether it's produce
whether it's whether it's
non-perishables
whatever it is um you got you got like
all that going on so and i've always
known
that like if you are you're into canned
food you want to wash the can off
the lid on the can even if the lid on
the can looks fine
so you got your can of beans or
something someone will buy their can of
beans or something
they'll buy the can of beans and then
you don't know it but there's rat
there's rat feces that you can't see on
top of the can
people don't realize this so that's why
i just like keeping things a little
cleaner
ja nina says uh the cleanse was help my
cleanse was helping me so much
as i have great gut problems
yeah the mono eating cleanse great for
helping out the gut issues
if you're somebody that's just new to
this you're new to the medical medium
information you're new to the medical
medium books
this is a book to have right here
uh and this is a book to have for this
kind of thing that i'm doing doing the
mono eating cleanse
challenge i'm challenging myself i love
that right
there's a question that comes up all the
time in sweet potatoes can i use sweet
potatoes for the money and cleanse
yeah you can you can but there's a
reason why
when you open the book and you read in
here
there's a reason why life-saving
information is set up in this book like
it is
and how it heals people the reason why
it's not there's all this this stuff
isn't like
it doesn't say in here mono eating
options
okay make sure you use sweet potato for
a mono eating option
doesn't say that doesn't say make sure
you eat sweet potato it doesn't say that
because i'll tell you why
sweet potatoes are a little bit more
or a lot more fibrous they have strings
in them
so sweet potatoes have strings in them
so here's the thing
say you're somebody with crohn's colitis
say you're somebody that's got a lot of
gastric
problems where you can't even eat
anything like you can't even eat
anything i have to look out for
everybody right look at a lookout for
people who are in that condition
right and their gut their guts inflamed
they got pockets and narrowing in here
so they got narrowing problems inside
their gut they got
pockets inside their gut right sweet
potatoes are fine to eat
but if you're going to eat large amounts
of them or more of them and just eat
them every day mono eating
they have a lot of strings they have
fibrous strings in there you ever see
those before in the sweet potatoes
when you cut a sweet potato there's
there's it's like
it's like there's arteries in them you
can't see them a lot of them are small
you can't see those passageways in the
sweet potato
well those you know they're they get
bulky
they get bulky inside the tummy so
you've got somebody that can barely eat
anything they've got all kinds of
problems
they're gonna feel the sweet potato a
little bit more i want people to get
everybody to get a chance to heal yeah
sweet potatoes are great to eat it's a
great food but
but the reason why it's not in here is
mono eating cleanse
is geared up for people that got some
messed up
guts messed up guts so what i do is
the steamed potatoes the regular
potatoes are great
they're great for the monolithing if
that's the direction you want to go
so what i have to say you guys
and you can use the red the red potato
not sweet or yam but the red potato
that's not
it's you know it's red or gold or russet
right
regular potatoes what i got to say is
are you prepared
what are you going to do are you going
to do the banana
with lettuce celery juice you can do
papaya
lettuce and celery juice are you gonna
do papaya and banana
do the steamed potatoes
are you gonna do steamed peas as an
option
with lettuce celery right are you gonna
do the steamed winter squash
right that's the butternut right there
steamed winter squash
is that what you're gonna do and so
these are different options right here
and getting the book is critical
so you got all the details because the
questions are gonna crop up once you're
in this thing you're gonna be like oh my
god i got a question
oh my god i got another question let me
get online and start asking questions
meanwhile it's right here
important enough so when we're healing
the gut food allergies
difficult difficult gut issues gut
issues of any kind got problems of any
kind okay
people don't know what to eat
and they run into this whole thing we're
like what do i eat
what do i eat what do i eat what do i do
what like what can i eat and that's
that's what people run into
oh i tried that but my stomach's not
feeling good i tried this but my
stomach's not feeling good
i heard this is good for me i heard
that's good for me and a lot of times
it's gonna leave people down a path
of gut destruction because now you're
going to be dumping gut powders in
you're going to be trying everything
you'll be trying bentonite clay then
you're going to be somebody trying
charcoal then you're going to be
somebody trying whey protein because
you're like i got to get my protein
and then that protein robot thing kicks
in i know some of you guys don't like
when i do the robot
i know i know that some of you guys
might like it some of you guys don't
like it but then the robot
kicks in selena how about the people who
eat the bananas
the peels uh it's not a great
thing to do there's a tannin in the
banana peel
so there's a certain tannin in there and
you don't want to eat the banana peels
they don't do a whole lot for us and
it's something that's
irritating on the lining really
irritating on the lining
and so the whole point is
you love the robot well you know the
thing is everybody becomes a protein
robot
it's like where do you get your protein
that's what people are going to be like
they're like where's your protein though
so they're like where do you get your
protein
where's your protein where's your
protein where do you get your protein
protein
everybody's like the protein robots is
what they are and uh that's the mini
robot
the point is is that everybody's going
to be like well
where's mono eating cleanse where's my
protein that's one thing we're going to
talk about we'll talk about something
else as well
yeah the whole the whole thing is
about healing some important
organs in everybody so let's go into
that for a couple of seconds all right
let's do that i'm also going to run some
celery juice i need some for today
myself let me push this forward a little
bit
my buddy here all right
so here's what happens
your liver gets dirty it gets stagnant
it gets
abused by the industries not by you by
the industries we get taught to just
destroy your liver that's what we get
taught to do
we get taught to eat so much protein and
fat
that we just kill our livers that's what
we get taught isn't that great
we're taught that that that's just what
what happens
and so the liver gets stagnant sluggish
it starts to break down
and then it can't produce the bile it
needs to produce so the bile reserves
drop gallbladders get all skanky and bad
and problematic they get all they get
all
toxic the gallbladder gets all toxic
all filled up with junk right and so
we start to get like minor versions of
organ failure as the years go on yeah
you can have organ failure for 50 years
you can have organ failure so when
someone's heart is failing
they try to keep you alive as long as
possible they try to keep your heart
working as long as possible right and
and you can have you can have heart
failure for years
but what people don't realize is organ
failure is something that just
lasts for decades and so many people
it's a liver
failure that's the organ that that goes
into this place
gallbladder failure for years you just
it's it's
what's happening is your liver is
failing to produce the amount of bile it
needs to break down
fats your stomach
is failing to produce the gastric acid
the hcl
to break down your proteins and then we
just fat ourselves to death
fat ourselves to death protein ourselves
to death that's what we do
that's what we do we fat ourselves to
death and we protein ourselves to death
hopefully this doesn't fall off right
now
so we end up eating all the fat we have
our fat we fry our eggs in butter
we do our scrambled eggs and oil
whatever
i know that many of you guys are like
why use coconut oil for my eggs you're
not
you're not full in your body man it's
all the same when it comes down to fat
even though it's a better fat than
butter
and so we just keep on we just fat
ourselves for years and years and years
and that's what happens
you know we have the bagels how many
guys do bagels
like how many guys do the bagels cream
cheese the bagels and different things
right
and we do that and overall over time
we get ourselves in trouble i mean how
many burgers have you guys had over the
years right
okay so we break down our gut we break
down our gastric system
we break everything down how many of you
guys got this in the house right now you
know what i love about the mono eating
cleanse
it's not going to be mono eating eggs
every now and then somebody like
well i only eat cheese i only eat eggs
and i only eat meat so i'm model eating
cheese eggs and meat and i'm like oh my
god
what you're doing is you're killing your
liver you're killing your
stomach glands you're killing your
pancreas
you're just you're feeding all the bugs
so
the point is is that we got some
things to repair over time and i'm not
going into all the details
man i'm not going into all the details
you guys
i'm not like the amount of stuff we do
and take
that just rips us down inside right
so the moderating cleanse is a chance to
recover a chance to come back
even if you don't know you're down in
that place where you're hurting
because you can't sense it yet or feel
it yet you don't know your liver
stagnant sluggish yet you don't know
you're hurting you don't know you got
problems yet
right you don't know and so let's talk
about what the mono eating cleanse does
one of the things is okay it provides
protein
yes bio available protein
that's what it provides so keep that off
your worry list
because people will have that as a worry
right provides
omegas yes it does it provides
phytochemical compounds antioxidants
antiviral compounds anti-bacterial
compounds glucose
mineral salts and that's just
some of the things it provides important
to know
so i want to tell you guys something and
we get turned into this like protein
robot
and we do and here's the funny thing
protein doesn't kill viruses
it doesn't kill bacteria and everybody's
sick because of pro
because of bacteria and viruses right
protein doesn't take out toxic heavy
metals so we can do all protein protein
shakes protein everything
it doesn't take out toxic heavy metals
it doesn't kill bugs
protein doesn't get rid of yeast and
mold and unproductive dangerous
fungus protein doesn't get rid of
petrochemicals and plastics
it doesn't get rid of radiation
it doesn't do any of this stuff so
interesting right
so we got to do other things to get your
organs repaired and get the bad stuff
out
everybody's eating everybody's eating a
ton of protein
everybody's eating a ton of protein and
they're sick
and they stay sick and they stay sick or
they wave back and forth from being sick
to a little better being sick to a
little bit better
and they but they get in trouble either
way keep that in mind
so ask what your protein is doing for
you because apparently
medical research and science doesn't
know what protein does for us
they don't know because they don't know
why we're sick but they tell you to keep
on taking the protein right
i'm talking about plant-based vegetarian
i don't care what
side of the aisle you're on okay animal
protein diets keto
paleo whatever you choose or do whatever
fancy name comes around the corner for
diets
protein doesn't get rid of the toxic
heavy metals protein doesn't get rid of
pesticides or besides fungicides protein
doesn't get rid of petrochemicals in the
solvents
protein doesn't get rid of the scented
candle chemicals and the air freshener
chemicals
protein doesn't get rid of the bugs the
viruses the bacteria the mold the yeast
the fungus
protein doesn't do any of that so you
eat your protein all
you want all you want still be in the
dental chairs getting your teeth all
drilled and
[Music]
all your teeth getting you know it's
implants and
root canals you'll still get that you'll
still get your gallbladders removed just
to get your appendix removed you'll
still get
you just whatever you'll still get sick
you'll still stay sick the whole bit
and that that's what will happen and
you know the bottom line is
well the bottom line is that hold on you
guys
got a little tech problem
the monolithing cleanse is to restore
and heal that's what it's for
it can be done long term it could be
done a year
it could be done two years it can be
done
for a month six months eight months it
can be done
long term short term we're doing a three
day mono cleanse challenge i'm pumped up
i'm excited
intestinal tracts get inflamed with bugs
that's what they get inflamed with
so our guts get inflamed with bugs
that's that's what happens okay
and um they lose all the body parts they
just fall apart there on the ground
so what happens is that everybody's got
little buggies inside their gut
they got inside their colon they got
inside their small intestinal tract
and you can take all the probiotics you
want you can take all the microflora
products you want you can do all the
microorganism products
you can do the fecal matter implant
which is insane
which is absolutely insanity you can do
anything you want with your gut
do your coffee enemas if you want to
which is insane
just terrible you can do all these
different things
you can add all the fermented foods you
want with all the fermented
the fermented probiotics and all you
want there
and all that's going to do is nothing
because your bad bugs
don't battle the good bugs your good
bugs don't battle the bad bugs
to put all the good stuff you want
you're still going to be inflamed
you're still going to have problems you
still end up with the acid reflux later
you know your h pylori won't go away if
you're somebody with h pylori don't even
know you have h pylori your e coli won't
go away eventually it'll cause
diverticulosis divuticulitis down the
road
it'll happen when you're 60 years old
just it's going to happen
might be 25 now and be like no i'm doing
the good stuff for my gut whatever
when you're 50 just you're going to be
like oh my god i got to get what 12
inches of my intestinal my colon cut out
so
it happens to everybody so the mono
eating cleanse
is about starving
the bad bugs that's what it is
so it's like three days of starving the
bad bugs
and then working on healing also
inflamed
tissue healing inflamed tissue you guys
you guys just got on here medical medium
cleanse the heel in front of me right
here
this is an incredible healing tool
packed with information do the mono
cleanse
challenge the next three days i'm doing
the preliminary
we're talking about preparing tomorrow
it's about starting i'm pumped up
check this out when you can because this
is it's it's really important to have
the details
which it's critical so amazon.com us is
off on this book try to find the library
if you want it for free
but read read the mono cleanse
challenge okay chapter in this book so
i'm in here now so i'm talking about the
different options let's go into it a
little bit
let's remove this intestinal tract off
the cutting board
and i'm glad you guys are here i missed
you guys by the way
i think it's been a little while since
we've been we've been doing the lives
dr faun md good to see you
glad you guys are coming on so
banana is one option right there so if
you're gonna do the banana one
you want your celery juice okay but
let's just go through it a little bit
let's do like a little test run
first of all i got some water here gonna
wake up in the mornings
part of the mono eating cleanse
challenge wake up in the morning i got
my lemon
right i'm gonna do lemon water
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water right off
the running
there you are right you wake up in the
morning flush
that liver flush the liver now remember
there's no overt fats in the mono eating
cleanse
you're not mono eating avocado
you're not doing that you're not mono
eating steak
you're not mono eating eggs you're not a
mono eating butter
you're not going to be mono eating any
fats there's not going to be any of the
fats there's traces of fats in all of
the foods in the moderating cleanse
but you're not going to be mono eating
any overt fats any
radical fats that's what i call radical
fats right you want your lemon water
first thing in the morning you want to
cleanse
out the garbage you want to cleanse out
the stuff that's been building up
inside the liver so you want to cleanse
that liver
is what you want to do right first thing
off the run
kenneth says i always look forward to
your lives my days feel more
complete i feel like i have some someone
behind my back
supporting me i i got your back i do i
do
i want you to know that i care about you
guys and i want you guys to have answers
once you guys have have options choices
right tools really critical 16 to 32
ounces of lemon water you start out your
day with that you flush out the liver
you flush out the poisons get them out
get them out first thing you got to do
you guys okay
next thing you got to do is celery juice
just reading comments too as well
next thing i'm going to do is celery
juice and i'm going to actually pull the
juicer out now because
i didn't have any today and i'm going to
run some if you guys don't mind and
we're still going to talk about
the model eating cleanse challenge
it's important to have the book read the
book
really important so you want 16 to 32
ounces of celery juice
right so you're gonna juice a little bit
of that real quick
you need the mineral salts you need the
trace minerals
you know when i hear someone do like the
carnivore diet i'm like oh my god it's
just a matter of time yeah you're
feeling a little better
for five seconds but it's a matter of
time
before you just run out of everything
your body needs
to restore recover and heal clockwork
there's not one carnivore person
carnivore diet person
that doesn't just blow themselves up
from doing that
it's just terrible right you've got to
have the mineral salts
when someone adds celery juice to
whatever mistakes they're making
it actually allows them to keep on
making mistakes did you guys know that
there's people out there like
well no i still i still want to have my
cheat night
i still want to have my cheat meals but
i'm still going to do my celery juice
well you know what's allowing you to
have cheat meals and not get too injured
by it is your celery juice
so but just think about if you
if like you're doing the mono eating
cleanse
[Music]
[Applause]
if you're sensitive if you've got tummy
problems
you don't don't do 16 to 32 ounces
you know if i if i was sensitive if i
had so many problems i would do like
four ounces
you could do that that's all right you
work your way up
you work your way up you guys everybody
on here just want you to know
the medical medium mono cleanse
challenge starts tomorrow i'm just
prepping you guys meaning providing
some answers to some questions if you
just got on here
watch this live again on youtube
if you want we're live on youtube
facebook clubhouse
tick tock
[Applause]
you guys have your papayas
you guys have your bananas
i have steamed potatoes over here i got
papayas
i got bananas you guys got your peas
you know doing the steam pea root is
pretty awesome
too steamed peas you do your your lemon
water in the morning
you do your celery juice
[Music]
there's questions can you still take
your supplements
can you still do that if you're doing
the mono eating cleanse
there's a section in the chapter that
talks about that
you still want to do supplements
[Applause]
yes and you can read about the
information
so i'm just juicing a little bit of
celery juice
sameel says can i do supplements
now here's the thing that's a really
good question too can i do supplements
right
well what supplements are we talking
about we talk about charcoal
probably like some bad probiotic blend
are we talking about
a protein powder are we talking about
some big multivitamin powder it's got
garbage and junk in it
msg are you talking about stuff with
citric acid in it are you talking about
whey protein powder are you talking
about
bentonite clay are you talking about
zeolite
are you talking about chlorella what are
you talking about
because all these things are irritants
and problems
to the intestinal tract they're all
irritants and problems the intestinal
tract
so you know when someone's like yeah can
i still do my supplements
well you could be doing stuff that's
really irritating really problematic but
i'm not telling you not to do them
you do what your doctor wants you to do
i'm just telling that that's what i
would be asking myself right there okay
and i cover this in the medical medium
cleanse the heel book so
it's like there's a difference between
doing supplements
and there's a difference between doing
irritants and
and supplements that actually cause
problems that don't do anything for you
and you don't realize it
it's all of that so here's what can
happen you're doing the medical media
monocles and that's actually bringing
your liver back
and you're taking all these garbage
supplements you know and
just that could happen too i'm not
saying you're doing that i'm just saying
people do that
[Music]
so i'm just doing a little bit more
celery right here getting
[Music]
[Applause]
a little bit more in here
everything freezing on you guys out
there
[Music]
all right just want to juice a little
bit of celery and there we are
i'm going to put this away
yeah got my celery juice
just love that dry pulp and just a
little bit of pulp but dry
it's amazing when that stuff is dry like
that that's incredible no other juicers
do that
it's the only juicer that does that i
love it
it's going to strain this you got to
strain your celery juice the reason why
i'm actually juicing celery right now
is not just because i want some myself
but because i want to remind you guys
you have to strain
your celery juice
you have to celery juice shouldn't have
any fiber or pulp in it
or it's not going to work to its maximum
level
and if you're going to be doing the mono
eating cleanse cause i'm gonna be doing
that
then you want that maximum right
if you can't do lemon water and you
can't do lemon or you don't have a lemon
do water in the morning first thing
okay it's it read about it in the
substitute section in the cleansing heal
book
you can do that to read about it in the
cleanse of heal
so we'll run over some stuff janet says
do you need to eat the same thing
all three days or can you do papaya one
day squash the next day okay good
question
look if you do papaya one day
banana the next you do papaya one day
steamed potatoes the next if you do
papaya one day
whatever and you're doing you know
winter squash next don't want to lose
that one
if you do that you're you're you're
basically customizing medical medium
tools that's what you're doing
so you're customizing medical medium
tools it's not meant to be like that
yeah you can do it but you're but you're
customizing you're kind of
you're you're changing up medical medium
tools right that's what you're doing
so there's no law against it right
you can do banana one day you can do
papaya the next
steamed potatoes the next so you mono
eat one thing one day you might wait one
thing
no another day you model it because you
basically do what you did basically
you're doing mono eating for one day
model eating for another day just
changing it up right that's what your
heart desires that's what you want to do
something you can do
is it meant to be like that it's not
meant to be like that but if you find
but at the same time and i talk about
this in cleansing heal just so you know
if there's something that you're not
jiving with something you're feeling
like you're not
gelling with right and if you're not
jelly you don't want to do the steamed
potato one and that's what you're doing
for a day or two
you can switch it up 100 you can and
then start doing papaya but the goal
is to be on one of them eventually for a
while
that's the goal you know you want to be
on one of them that that
feels good to you so if steam peas feel
good to you
every day so you do your lemon water you
do your celery juice
you do your steamed peas you do your
lettuce and steamed peas
you do it twice during the day right
then do some
then do some more water throughout the
day
and your day is done and you did one day
of a mono-eating cleanse
try to do the steamed peas again the
next day if it's gelling
if it feels good if it's you feel you're
happy about it right
do it the next day you could
recommend a juicer yeah melanie the
juicer is
this one right here okay it's the omega
mm-900 hds but just just so you know
it's the mm-900 hds
so it's not any other omega juicer this
is the one that's the celery juicer but
it does other things too
it's a celery juicer where the pulp just
comes out bone dry
right apollo says so stay with
one for three days that's what i'm gonna
do
i'm gonna stay with one for three days
that's what i'm gonna do
yeah so anyway that's the juice right
there mm-900 hgs
there's a sale coming up on that juicer
in like a few days or something i'm not
sure what day it is but there's a sale
coming up where it's 20
off so if you wait till then that's a
good idea
but reading the book is important as i
said
multiple times already that it's really
that important to understand what's
happening in the book like
because if you do change it up you know
if you do change it up it talks about
what you know what how it works
read the book for details that answers
hundreds of questions with the minor
eating cleanse
but i'm going to help as far as like
make this as simple so let's cut let's
cut right to the chase
right do you have your celery
really important do you have your
bananas if you're going to go the banana
root
do you have your lettuce because that's
in there every day
that's in there every day you can have
that do you have your lemons
or limes if you want to do limes do you
have your lemons
right do you have your peas
if you're gonna do the peas so keep that
in mind
right if you want to go winter squash if
you look in the book and you see there's
a winter squash
option are you gonna do the winter
squash option
so be ready for it right there's an
option in the book right here i'm going
to read it
it's an option of doing steamed winter
squash
plus one or two of these other items you
ready
steamed winter squash
plus brussels sprouts you guys might
want to do this one right
or asparagus or green beans
and brussels sprouts or green beans and
asparagus
so here's the option winter squash
right and then you can bring in
some green beans steamed green beans
some brussels sprouts or some asparagus
that's just an additional option that's
in the cleansing heal
book it's letting you know
so so much it's so much
important information in here it's
ridiculous it's just so much information
these plans are ideal for someone with a
hyper-sensitive intestinal tract i'm
reading right out of here on page 189
okay because the food options are
actually
soothing they're soothing as they move
through your system this mono eating
cleanse
for people who have sensitive guts or
problems with their health
so when you're doing the mono eating
plan you're
starving the very things making you sick
the pathogens the viruses the bacteria
which are behind gut disorders
mono eating offers your body a gentle
detox
one that doesn't overwhelm your system
it's really important
so i'm just reading a little bit of that
information there
what people experience when their guts
are inflamed they experience discomfort
as food is moving through them
that's what they feel they start to feel
a problem from food moving through them
that's how it works so when you're
inflamed you guys
right do the props help at all when
you're inflamed
your small intestinal tract gets pockets
of inflammation in here
your colon gets pockets of inflammation
and as
food moves through whatever that food's
going to be here's a brussels sprout
as brussels sprout is moving through
your colon
right okay
it's going to be rubbing and touching
inflamed
colon tissue people don't realize it
doesn't mean the brussels sprouts bad
that's not it at all
it just means you're gonna feel foods
that have fiber you're gonna feel those
kinds of foods right
and when you're eating an egg
when you're eating an egg you're not
going to feel the egg moving through
here because all you're going to feel is
nothing because it's just going to be
glue
it's going to be like this liquid
mucousy glue
that's just in the middle of your
intestinal tract moving through
you're not gonna it's not touching
anything so you'd be like well eggs work
really good for me i eat a lot of eggs
meanwhile
the very thing in eggs are gonna make
your condition worse so your
diverticulitis diverticulosis your
crohn's colitis your ibs your celiac are
all going to get worse over time from
eating eggs
the mono eating cleanse
and cleanse the heal
right the mono-eating cleanse and
cleanse the heel
is gentle enough
but also starves the very bugs that are
inside your gut that are keeping you
sick and inflamed
so that you can heal over time that's
what it's about adele says no eggs ever
again
when it comes down to watermelon if you
guys want to do if you're going to
choose watermelon to mono eat
i'm just going to give you a couple of
tips you better be doing celery juice
or you're going to hit the wall you're
going to hit the watermelon wall
because there's not enough calories or
mineral salts in watermelon
because basically if you're just doing
watermelon by itself and watermelon's
great i mean i've done long-term
stents of eating watermelon but i've
known how to balance it where you've got
to have some lettuce
you got to have some celery juice
okay the reason why watermelon's not
this 100 like
perfect option in the cleansing heel
book in the monocline section
is because there's not enough calories
in the watermelon
and you end up doing kind of like a
watermelon juice fast right that's what
you're doing
but doing you can't do a watermelon
juice fast
long term so how are you going to then
heal your guts if you need to do the
monoclines long term
so the mono cleanse is designed where
you can actually do it long term
to get to the finish line and get rid of
your problems and start healing things
that are deep within that's the whole
point
but absolutely you can do a three-day
watermelon version
you're using a medical medium tool right
the watermelon juice the medical medium
tool
that's fine you're using that and
you're customizing for yourself to do
some to do some mono eating cleanse
right it's fine
but make sure you got some butter leaf
lettuce in there or some kind of lettuce
in there and make sure you got your
celery juice and make sure you got your
lemon water you have to have the balance
of all the different phytochemical
compounds
the mineral salts they have to be there
the antivirals antibacterials right
can i use honey in the lemon water
during mono eating i'm pretty sure you
can
yes can do it i knew that question was
going to come up
yeah you can i'm pretty sure i have it
in here as yeah
i mean these are vol these are medical
textbooks
so much information in there then
there's the how to transition on page
211 you guys how to transition
from completing the cleanse so here's
what you don't want to do you ready
you did the mono eating cleanse you guys
are like pumped
you did the mono eating cleanse and all
of a sudden now you're like
back cranking your coffee right away
right you're cranking your coffee you're
just eating whatever
your your boom you're into your steak
you got butter on everything
right you're cracking your eggs you're
doing your eggs
okay you're doing lots of avocado
you're doing your nut butter so you just
got off the bottom eating cleanse and
now you're like i need to dig into that
peanut butter man i need all that fat
like i'm hungry for all that fat
because one of the things that's going
to make you hungry
on the mono eating cleanse is you're
going to be probably withholding the
calories and not eating enough
got not eating enough you might be like
okay well i just had a potato today
i just had one steamed potato today i
had my celery juice i had my lemon water
like
anthony's gonna do i had my lettuce and
i'm
starving so when you come off the
monowing cleanse
you're gonna be like i need butter i
need
eggs i need burgers i need fries or i
need nut butters
peanut butter almond butter
right so what happens is that
what you did was you were just you were
you were eating very
little so what you don't want to do is
eat
very little on the moderating cleanse
you want to be able to have some good
servings if you're hungry have a few
potatoes
that's what you want to do if you're
doing the steamed potato root you just
don't want to have like okay i'm doing
the mono eating cleanse and i'm just
going to do
a got a steamed potato in my dish right
here you don't want to do that
that's not a good idea it's not a good
idea you're going to be like
we're like okay well i'm doing the mono
eating cleanse here
and i have my steamed potato
because that steamed potatoes only got
what 30 calories it's like
like literally like i'm gonna have my
steamed potato here i'm on the mono
eating cleanse
give me freaking starving now what
happens is you're allowed to have some
food
you're allowed to have some food on your
mono eating cleanse
you're allowed to have some food do
16 to 32 ounces of celery juice
right hold back the salt and the
seasoning
on on everything during these three days
okay but you can squeeze lemon on
everything so you can be like all right
well i'm gonna have
some food or squeeze some lemon on there
on the potatoes
that's what you want to do right
this here celery juice is a critical
part of the mono eating cleanse because
it
it cuts the cravings mineral salts help
to knock the cravings right out
so you you can have your first meal
afternoon
because your celery juice is cut in some
cravings
kimberly miller the papaya banana mono
cleanses saving me
and healing my debilitating intestinal
tract disorder i can't tell you how many
times just so you know
i can't tell you how many times over the
last 35 years
thanks to spirit of compassion giving
the information down to me
of what that papaya and banana mono
eating cleanse has done for people
i have saved colons you don't even know
how many feet of colons and intestinal
tract has been saved from the mono
eating cleanse
in the last 30 plus years i mean
thousands of feet of colon and
intestinal tracts were saved
thousands and thousands of feet miles
long just so you know
miles long going back 35 years
okay the papaya and banana monolithing
cleanse
has stopped so many people from having
to get 12 inches or 24 inches or 32
inches or 36 inches cut out of their
guts
that if you added it up the medical
medium mono eating cleanse
has saved thousands of feet of colon
i mean i'm talking in the miles worth
miles miles of small intestinal tract
long
that's what it's done that's what it's
done
so read the chapter make sure you have
this
critical to have the details
critical critical critical critical this
is it
you gotta have that right gotta catch
the details right
and then i'm gonna be live right one
o'clock pacific
west coast time tomorrow four o'clock
eastern
east coast time in the us live tomorrow
on youtube facebook took putting tick
tock back out and then
a little ways after i'll be on ig
because i'm going to go to ig in a
little while too
details matter sarah they do you guys
they do they do
just remember there's a sale running
that i'm not in charge of
amazon they they make the pricing the
way they want it but amazon
has this book 51 percent off
amazon.com us 51 off at 16
it costs more to print it it really does
i'm not saying that it actually costs
way more to print the book
irene how many papayas do you eat per
day
details are in the book it answers that
it answers the amounts like like that on
that level
but what i what i would do okay if i'm
doing the papaya one
i would have i got a papaya over here
whole papaya
buy one there it is right i would do a
papaya
a day said i would do for sure cut the
papaya in half this is a large papaya if
you got small papayas do more of them
right i i mean me i would do a papaya
and a half
in a day doing my celery juice well
lemon water papaya and a half that's
what i would do
right if you're just doing papaya okay
you may not want to do that much papaya
if you're doing bananas
because if you can choose the papaya and
banana version
and cleanse the heal so you can choose
that one you guys
the papaya and banana version and
cleanse the heel so keep that in mind
right so you can do like you can do a
few bananas
during lunch a couple bananas later if
you wanted to a few more bananas later
on
you got your papayas too if you're
somebody that's like ah can't do papaya
uh
can't do banana and you even have an
option of doing cucumber juice in the
afternoon too you can do cucumber juice
in the afternoon remember this is the
mono cleanse
and that's what it is and you can do
that option potatoes you might be
somebody that's like look i want to do
steamed potatoes
that's my that the one i want steamed
peas is another one read the chapter
chapter several times it's pretty easy
to do just read the chapter several
times
the steam p version is amazing too
okay you guys so you got that
as an option so i am totally
totally totally down totally psyched
totally pumped big time
because so uh teresa says add lime with
papaya
yes you can you can boiled potatoes okay
that's a really good question steamed
potatoes
boiling them does something different
really important to know okay
when you boil potatoes you boil a lot of
the carbohydrate out of the potato
so if you boil a potato okay
you lose a lot of the glucose that
you're going to need
when you boil potatoes you might need to
eat more potatoes because you boil them
they end up because the glucose gets
boiled not
all of it but the glucose gets boiled
out of the potato
and then those natural sugars end up in
your broth they end up in your
like the liquid you're dumping out
that's such an important question
can you blend both pie and banana yeah
you can what i like to do is i like to
blend the papaya
in a food processor right and then i
like to chop up little pieces of banana
i like to dip them into the papaya and
i'm going to do that i'm actually going
to show you guys that in the next three
days how
how i'll do like how i do the papaya
banana
some pump anyway guys make sure you got
the book
in your hands it's important
i'm moving off to instagram i'm going to
let everybody know
there prepare them as well
okay and you guys on tick tock i'm
turning tick tock back on
so everybody on youtube facebook you
guys i'm going to ig
i'll be there in about 15 minutes you
guys on tick tock i'm turning you back
on clubhouse i'm turning you guys back
on
what do you recommend for lyme disease
or southern tik tok you got to read the
lime section of
of the clenzie hill book it's so packed
would it what about the skin on the
potatoes you don't you don't have to
have the skin on the potatoes if you
want to
and you can have them on on there you
can do either or
either or if you're somebody that's
really really hypersensitive like you've
had
surgeries you've had inflammation you've
had all kinds of you know
in like serious issues with your guts
you can always take the skin off
the skin though is antibacterial it's
antiviral potatoes are antibacterial
antiviral
even without the skin they're
antibacterially antiviral
jody manics i have been eating four
whole papayas plus bananas and lettuce
every day is that too much are you happy
with it
seems pretty good to me they gigantic
papayas they small papayas
you know and you gotta think about you
might be somebody that's
uh 95 pounds you might be somebody
that's 250 pounds
you might be you know so it's it all
depends meaning like you might be
tall you might be petite
you know it depends i mean it all those
things matter
i talk about that and cleanse the heal
but if you're happy with that
you're eating that sounds good
sounds good you guys i'm excited going
to ig now heading over now
and uh but the reminder is because the
question about the juicer there's a sale
coming up for the mm 900 hds just to let
you guys know
it's coming up eventually um
pretty soon so if you guys don't have a
juicer it's a great one other than that
i'm just trying to prepare
everything for you guys with you guys
okay
make sure you eat enough bananas though
if you're doing the banana mono eating
cleanse make sure you're doing enough
bananas
okay everybody is different somebody
might be good with eight bananas
somebody might be good with 10 or 12
all depends on what you're also used to
eating too don't under
calorie yourself because then you might
hit the wall because you're you're
hungry
and then when you come off the mono
eating cleanse you're like tanking the
nut butters
you know when it didn't have to go down
like that
i love you guys i'll see you soon maybe
15 minutes right i'm heading over to ig
okay hope to see you guys soon
awesome