foreign
's Bar and Grill
yep we have a three-day wild blueberry
challenge yep any customers here yeah
checking these here
oh I didn't feel a shot glass for
chickadee I feel actually terrible about
this
oh boy
sorry chickadee
yes anyway yeah three day wild blueberry
challenge is what we're doing the 15th
through the 17th
that's right we're gonna be talking
about all kinds of stuff about the wild
blueberry and how it's helped so many
people and everything did you say
antioxidants yes you did I heard that
chickadee did you have any yet did you
try the wild blueberry juice chickadee's
favorite thing in the world is wild
blueberry juice
yes chickadees the only customer in here
today at aw bars and girl it's been kind
of slow lately
yeah that's okay check it chickadee's
friends are asking to come here too so
just give me a second here chickadee's
friends are
yep would you guys like one too either
one of you
okay all right I'm gonna go there's I
think there's people coming in now
hello you guys medical medium three-day
wild blueberry challenge I am pumped up
like nobody knows like really pumped up
because wild blueberries are incredible
they have a survival Instinct people
don't realize you can burn it down to
the ground and it rises out of the ashes
oak trees can't do that they can't do
that it's impossible so
this is incredible so wild blueberries
wild blueberries wild blueberries okay
let's talk about I have some notes with
me right here let's see what my notes
are
my notes say this check this out day one
of the wild blueberry challenge wild
blueberry shots uh-huh
I'm about to tank those by the way
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie how cool is that right isn't
that gonna be awesome
medical medium extractor smoothie that's
day one check that out that's day one
let's talk about day two wild blueberry
latte we'll have the wild blueberry
latte please warm wild blueberry Bowl
that's day two ready day three this is
exciting you guys I'm so pumped up about
this it's ridiculous day three honey
orange and wild blueberry refresher
that's gonna be killer that's gonna be
killer and potato waffles with wild
blueberry sauce
how about that this is the wild
blueberry challenge I'm pumped up about
this
three days link is in the description
link is in the profile you don't want to
miss this we're talking about
antioxidants
power of antioxidants right so that's
going to be a big part of all on its own
right chickadee are you okay over there
you haven't touched the wild blueberry
juice so I'm just wondering what's wrong
okay all right well you're you'll you'll
you'll get to it I'm not trying to
pressure you on any level go to
medicalmedium.com
because if you go to medicalmedium.com
or just hit the link right there in the
profile or description and you can
download your free pdf by the way this
is a free Wild blueberry Challenge and
you can download your free pdf about
what you need what you know the whole
bit your grocery store lists all of that
because these recipes are awesome and
you want to be prepared so this is about
preparing for the wild blueberry
challenge that's how awesome this is and
fun this is so I'm excited about this
you guys if you go to medicalmedium.com
you can check out that area there for
all your information
so sign up to participate in this free
challenge the link is in the profile and
the description so I'm excited so you
know I want to just say a couple things
about like the wild blueberry it's
underappreciated underestimated under
under known all of those things right
we're talking about a wild food there's
a big difference between a wild food and
then a not wild food that's one thing
and the other thing too there's a big
difference between a filler food that's
not necessarily a healing food and a
healing food there's a big difference
between a healing food and a filler food
right so we eat food but some foods
they're just not healing foods they're
filler Foods they don't have the power
to be a healing food they may not be a
bad food but they don't have the power
to be the healing food right so when
you're talking about a wild food
especially this blue blue blue wild food
you're talking talking about survival
Instinct you're talking about wild
survival Instinct been around for
thousands upon thousands of years
literally have gone through
everything under the sun drought floods
all of it right Tundra cold Tundra and
it's here another thing too is
which I want to mention is you can burn
the wild blueberry down to the ground
and it will rise out of the ashes and
that's what I want in my body like I
want in my body something that has
survival Instinct you can burn it to the
ground and it rises out of the ashes
that's what I want inside my body that's
the key right there that's a big one so
it's not just about antioxidants because
lots of things do have antioxidants it's
about what kind of antioxidant do I want
an antioxidant that's been in something
that has survival instincts something
that has adapted for thousands of years
right do I want that antioxidant to me
that anthocyanin that blue anthocyanin
or do you want do I want another
antioxidant to me and that's the
difference right there since one of the
reasons why I always loved while the
blueberries and I'm going to talk more
about wild blueberries during the wild
Blu-ray challenge if you guys just got
on here
we're having a little drink
um I got chickadee here and his friends
and we are just celebrating for the
three-day wild blueberry challenge
coming up so we're celebrating so I'm
actually really excited about this so
we're just where are my bottles
backwards what the hell's going on here
anyway
so we're celebrating and we are getting
ready for this three-day challenge if
you guys want to know the details it's
November 15th through the 17th I am
going to be live each day and we are
going to make recipes you guys just came
back on here I see a bunch of you guys
are coming on here day one wild
blueberry juice shots that's what day
one is chickadee can I can I steal this
from your friends for a second
um
so good
sorry you guys
Jackie B
Jackie B I read your review
on Amazon
I'm pretty sure that was yours and I
actually almost I was on the edge of
crying I'm not kidding you did those
quotes on there I think that's yours
where you did those quotes on there
and it was like all these different
quotes
literally I was on the edge of crying
during that review I'm just trying to
see if I could even find it really quick
what did you say there you said um I
already have most of the ingredients
just wondering if I need to double up
the ingredients
if two of us are doing the challenge
right yes double up or triple up on the
ingredients depending on how many people
the shopping list covers one person so
when you go to medicalmedium.com you
guys you'll see the shopping list covers
one person is what you'll see so you can
double up you can triple up the whole
bit you see me on my phone right here
messing around because that's what I'm
doing
I'm on my phone and uh
honestly
I'm just looking here
and unless it's not here oh here it is
Jackie B I think this is you and forgive
me if it's not
and I think this is yours right here you
titled your review on Amazon the truth
will set you free and with that freedom
a new life away it's oh and yeah here it
was so it is the quotes you do have that
here you see you have a quote saying you
need to see a different doctor people
would say as unpaid medical bills piled
up your scan showed a little
inflammation at the bile duct but
nothing we're concerned about quote the
gastroenterologist this this right here
had me in tears when I actually read
that I mean literally that was just
unbelievable
Angie um young bird
what brand is that wild blueberry bottle
it's Wyman's I work with Wyman's because
I want to keep this stuff around I want
it here for everybody like this this is
like gold because the process to
actually take a wild food
out of
right out of the field to take a wild
food and to press it what they do right
the press machine they use and to get it
in the bottle and then they get it to
people is unbelievable
it's 10 right now off the wild blueberry
juice right now it's 10 off uh go to
wymans.com and check it out it's 10 off
but the point is is that what it takes
to get this powerful antioxidant food
out of the field and then into the
bottle is mind-blowing that part alone I
don't want this to disappear so I'm
working with them because I want to be
able to you know once in a while let
everybody know this is unbelievable
stuff I want them to stick around
because it's a mom and pop
that literally they take it out of the
field and they press it so that people
have this gold so yeah it this wild
blueberries mean everything to me people
don't realize what they really mean to
me I remember being a child just laying
in Wild blueberry fields and just being
in a sea of wild blueberries and just
eating them until I couldn't eat them
anymore and and that the experience is
just incredible
um
let's see Melody says I don't know where
to find the shopping list
medicalmedium.com if you can't see the
link in the description in the profile
go to medicalmedium.com you'll find it
there you'll be able to download your
free pdf about your grocery shopping
list so you do want to see that you guys
when you get a chance it's a three-day
challenge it's coming up chickadees will
be there chickadee and chickadees
friends will be there which I'm excited
about so
um yes we will all be there so let's go
over it one more time what's gonna
happen so you guys are prepared as much
as we can prepare right okay day one
wild blueberry cheese shots
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie nice medical medium extractor
smoothie whoa whoa
warm while blueberry Bowl that's day two
wait a minute no sorry day two it's wild
blueberry latte and warm wild blueberry
Bowl can I get anything right lately or
day three honey orange and wild
blueberry refresher waffle with wild
blueberry sauce I am totally psyched I
can't even tell you guys how psyched I
am I mean I really am and chickadee is
like two as well are you ready to drink
your shot chickadee another question why
isn't Wyman's wild blueberries organic
well I've talked about this many times
and I will talk about it during the
challenge and what that means okay it's
a wild food meaning it takes care of
itself got to keep that in mind a wild
food has an immune system that's why
it's important that's why it has
survived thousands of years that's why
it needs barely any care whatsoever
that's why you can burn it to the ground
and it will come back up I want to talk
about that for a second
okay oh another thing too Wyman's
doesn't use pollinator killers
and guess what organic food crops where
they spray
organic food is sprayed with pollinator
Killers it's sprayed with nicotine a
pollinator killer all the bees die when
it's sprayed with nicotine think about
that so Wyman's they don't do any
spraying and when they have to Once in
so many years or whatever one field the
whole thing is it's not a pollinator
killer and here's the other thing too
they always they test and there's no
pesticides at all so there's no
pesticides pesticide residues in their
tests so they are an incredible wild
food wild food company and people don't
realize this when you're dealing with
wild Foods you're dealing with less need
to have to care because the food defends
itself and protects itself and that's
something people don't realize so what
they do is everybody's like oh well what
it's not a game but they don't realize
it's oh it's above organic wild food is
above organic in everything
phytochemical compounds antioxidants
it's above organic and people don't
realize that that's the difference right
there I can go on forever about that and
I will talk about that more
um
so and Wyman's is going to let me know
when it's available in Europe okay so at
the beginning of the year they're going
to try to have this wild blueberry juice
available in Europe by the way and you
guys know I work with Wyman's because I
want to protect this what I think is a
treasure and what I believe is a
treasure because this juice the
blueberries coming out of the field as
well the wild food coming out of the
field and the pressing and to get it in
here this is potent stuff that's all I
have to say it is so potent you know
they're very important everybody's
asking Europe like when can I get the
juice when I when can I get the juice
and wines is doing everything they can
and it's no
it's it's no joke on trying to do that
and that's what they're doing you know
so hmm
bartender
give me another
so good
so I got rise with Melton says yes
finally in Europe I'm gonna be pumped
about that too seriously really
important
see you guys we're doing the wild
blueberry challenge a three-day wild
Blu-ray challenge I'm already getting
drunk on the juice we're doing the three
day wild blueberry challenge
15 through the 17th I'm excited I'm
going to be there
I'm gonna be there
so
what do we have here oh Natasha gray
says hello I want to be a part of it all
I am in Mexico and cannot get my hands
on wild blueberries I know nothing
compares to them but would love to know
what I can do
if you cannot for some reason get wild
blueberries it won't be the same power
as like if you do the regular
blueberries it won't be the same kind of
incredible thing if you can try
blackberries as as blackberries are more
potent and stronger than a regular
cultivated blueberry so if you go to
the grocery store in Mexico you can't
get the wild blueberry
just keep in mind that if you get the
cultivated blueberry the big blueberry
and the clam shells that's not going to
do it you're better off getting the
Blackberry in the store the blackberries
more powerful than the cultivated
blueberry but not more powerful than the
wild blueberry but more powerful than
the cultivated blueberry so if you have
to do some blackberries that's something
you do but there's got to be a way even
in Mexico to figure out how to get
some type of wild a blueberry product
and so forth just you know go to
medicalmedium.com check everything out
and see if you you can get any leads
that way
anyway you guys this is incredible it's
a three day challenge I'm pumped up
we're gonna be making some recipes doing
some fun stuff I'm just telling you
about what we're gonna make it's
incredible the wild blueberry cheese
heavy metal detox smoothie the medical
medium extractor we're gonna make the
latte shamima I was on your website
recently and was blown away at how much
information you were making available
for free and how organized the
information is
I'm honored seriously I have never
encountered anything like it still
trying to digest how you continue to be
so generous God bless
and make sure it comes out of my own
pocket that's what I do and it comes out
of my own pocket shamima I literally
comes all out of my own pocket that's
that's what it is see empty Pockets
right now they're empty oh there's some
lint a little lint in that pocket
so yes I want to make sure that what
happens is that I have to pay a team I
have to pay people I do it all out of my
pocket I make sure that at any dime that
I make it's all going into free
everything going into the website free
information free everything go get the
brain saver books and the medical meme
books at the library for free if you
want brain saver is 40 off right now
where's my brain saver books
really I got a brain saver book right
back here
and I got a protocols book too because
brain saver is two books
right 40 off amazon.com us right here
the brain saver books packed with wild
blueberry information
right here
40 off these books are incredible Bibles
right here unbelievable information in
these books by the way anyway I want
everything for free
that's what I wish all the time so
there's no pay firewall I call firewall
because you get burned in the other
websites and health out there you go
searching through the other websites in
health and you get burned singed because
everything's pay this uh do this pay
this pay walls do this subscription fees
it's like okay come on are we in it to
actually get the chronically a little
better are we there to screw them over
24 7. I want to know the difference
right that what are we doing like what's
the point
so I want to make sure everything's free
as possible that I can do on my end you
know so that's you know that's what I
like to do you guys so it's a free
challenge I'm pumped 15 through the 17th
it's going to be incredible I'm Gonna Be
Live chickadee and chickadees friends
will be there hopefully even more people
will be there and we're gonna be doing
the wild blueberry shots day one medical
meme heavy metal detox smoothie medical
medium extractor smoothie mind blowing
by the way
day two wild blueberry latte which I'm
pumped about warm wild blueberry bowl
for day two day three honey orange and
wild blueberry refresher potato waffle
with wild blueberry sauce
right
um
okay the strong heart says where do we
buy online go to wymans.com the wild
blueberry juice they got there so
wymans.com you can go into the store and
and get Frozen wild blueberries too you
know that's it's so incredible Haram
says flu season advised for kids please
the medical medium books are always
packed brain saver protocols in the
medical medium books right here so
there's protocols in there for this ask
your doctor what's right for you but the
protocols are here so I am giving you
where that information is flu protocols
for all ages are in these books They are
packed with information
Boom for real you'll be so excited when
you see it it's really incredible
the flu is out right now and the flu is
strong so flu Protocols are in the brain
saver books yes indeed
including
medical medium shock therapies including
so much information which is so
important in the brain saver books guys
I'm excited about all of this right now
everything about it I am pumped so when
you're talking about wild blueberries
you're talking about the power
of the Earthly mother you're talking
about the power it provides you're
talking about survival instincts for
thousands upon thousands of years you're
talking about drought flooding
freezing cold
the Earth changing
you're talking about everything and
anything when it comes down to Wild
bloomers and the survival rate of the
wild blueberry you can burn it to the
ground here's the thing when someone
just said to me the other day right
why do you say when the wild blueberry
Burns at the ground and it comes back
doesn't everything come back no a bird
has to bring a seed
a bird has to drop a seed has to poop
out a seed a squirrel has to bring in
acorn back to scorched land and plant a
new tree when you burn an oak tree down
it doesn't come back up it's not
possible I'm just telling you right now
when you burn an oak tree down they
don't come back up when you burn an oak
tree down
it stays down and that's it and it
doesn't come back up
so it's important to know the wild
blueberries they can be burnt to the
ground right to the Earth fire hot ash
all of it and then they come out that's
an adaptogenic power like adapting for
thousands of years of fire and flood and
freezing cold that's what I want inside
my body that's the fuel that's the food
I want inside of me that blue food
Brandon says I was going into aw
withdrawal after not seeing you after
the 10-day brain shot challenge I am
here and a phone call is probably on its
way too so I hope I try not to interrupt
while we're doing this but it happens
I am going through a troll myself I'm
going through a withdrawal of seeing you
guys of course because I love to be here
and I love to help in any way I can so
when it comes down to like survival
Instinct
and adaptogenic Power
that's a big deal right there adapting
to the Earth's changes well that's the
food I want in me
antioxidants that are different
antioxidants right antioxidants that
come from a wild food with survival
Instinct that's an entirely different
story the wild blueberries not a filler
food the wild blueberry
is not a filler food right
a filler food is something that doesn't
have all these like the healing stuff
going on it's not a healing food
the wild blueberries are up here it's
wild it's incredible really
Lisa says you deserve it all pink phones
back woohoo they're back for a second
the pink phone is back for a second
incredible you guys so I'm excited about
the three day challenge are you guys
pumped up prepared I am I'm really
looking forward to it
hold on guys
AWS Bar and Grill
yep
hi Mrs Ferguson hi are you coming
downstairs
Mr Ferguson is still stuck on the toilet
what's going on today
constipated
he's got to get the wild blueberries in
him I keep on telling you Mrs Ferguson
that he's got to eat the wild lures he
doesn't want that what does he want hot
dogs and hamburgers
really what else
he had some nachos with cheese
okay and pizza the other night
okay I keep on saying you have to get
the wild blueberry juice or the wild
blueberries in him
so he's not sitting there for hours
wasting the day
okay yep
um yep it's not that busy downstairs we
only have chickadee and chickadees
friends
and apparently they haven't even touched
their shot so they'll be here for quite
some time all right
Kirsten says I feel so much more alive
since doing your protocols incredible
that means the world to me because
that's what it's about that's what the
Blood Sweat and Tears have all been
about
intentful Spirit kids brought home
another bug from school I'm hearing it
every minute right now I'm hearing that
everywhere uh family friends everybody
friends people I'm hearing that
everywhere so kids brought home another
bug from school now I'm sick on the
couch and I'm so grateful for all the
tools you have shared with us to kick it
incredible in the brain saver books I
got all kinds of information about the
stuff going around the bugs going around
all of that including medical medium
shock therapies ask your doctor what's
right for you you can check out my
supplement directory at
medicalmedium.com if you want to know
about the best stuff so medicalbeam.com
and the supplement directory
so there's the brain saver books
see you guys it boils down to this
you're looking at those anthocyanins
you're looking at anthocyanins
that have been here for thousands upon
thousands of years more so than that
anthocyanins that come from a plant that
can't die
oh
seriously
I'm going to take one of chickadee's
friend shots
bartender give me another
really good really good I'm gonna pour
you guys a couple more because I feel
bad
I don't know why I do that to you
chickadee haven't touched your shot
I really think you should uh think about
having your shot there
you only have so much time to get drunk
the hours are going by chickadee
and your friends they're not even
getting drunk yet either on the wild
blueberry juice
so you guys I am really excited about
all of this because it is going to be a
blast
three days I'm gonna make some recipes
I'm gonna make some waffles when's the
last time I had the griddle out here
like when's the last time I've Had The
Griddle out there and I'm making some
stuff
some waffles and some pancakes and
whatever the heck we're gonna make
I know it says Anthony can you speak on
the different properties of different
Regional species of wild blueberries
if it's a wild blueberry whether it's
high Bush or low bush
it's got incredible instinctive survival
Powers you gotta remember that now the
incredible thing about the wild
blueberry these wild blueberries here
right the North American low bush
right low to the ground
it's a whole other thing too that's just
incredible but any wild blueberries you
can get your hands on
amazing amazing amazing
you guys I'm pumped up can't even tell
you
Mary Kay says why haven't you talked
about how amazing the recipes are in the
Brain book
thank you Mary Kay over 100 recipes and
they are incredible
so good and I and that's the thing we're
gonna do some of the brain saver recipes
in the challenge that's coming up so
we're gonna do some of these that's
what's exciting look at all these
incredible recipes right here this is
insane
all right here we go look at these
recipes
unbelievable actually you guys see that
I'm just going through them really quick
just some of these so many healing
recipes for the brain I'm actually
getting hungry right now
very hungry I am excited it just goes on
and on and on wait a minute there's a
whole recipe book you know what's crazy
recipe books
don't have as many recipes as this book
has this book is two recipe books
that's how crazy this is there's two
recipe books in this book there's six
books in each one of these books
how insane is that
you guys
all right all right
all right calm down come down
it's hitting me right here
do you feel the same way I do when you
just start sending shots of this down do
you guys ever feel that
that's my my third shot
bartender give me another that's my
third shot
hmm
chicken these friends are really upset
Bart down there give me another one
Chickadee I'm sorry don't be upset
please I know don't be upset
chicken is upset
don't worry
don't worry I got this one was this
yours chickadee's really upset here
about this
all right I'm sorry about that
I didn't mean to take that shot from you
you guys
three day wild blueberry challenge
coming up
15th through the 17th just letting you
know one last time we're doing a whole
bunch of recipes three days live go to
medicalme.com you'll see all the
information download your free grocery
shopping list you can be prepared
how incredible link is in the profile
link is in the description
so you're not going to want to miss this
and we're going to be doing everything
wild blueberry and we're going to talk
about some of the powers that the wild
blueberry possess
antioxidants antioxidants antioxidants
incredible
this is amazing I think I had three what
did I have three four five I had five or
six shots
and then
make sure you have your brain saver
books too and make sure you have those
ready over 300 symptoms conditions brain
shot Therapies
seven medical mean brain shot therapy
cleanses seven heavy metal detox
cleanses incredible over 100 recipes of
brain healing recipes that's just to say
the least medical medium shock therapies
all kinds of different flu and cold
protocols incredible information that's
Advanced way ahead in health than
anything else out there and the greatest
books of all time hands down
and the greatest books in history
greatest books of all time right here
you guys make sure you have these when
you get a chance all right
I will see you soon
take care of you guys take care of
yourselves have compassion for
yourselves and love you greatly and I
can't wait this is gonna be the best