live right now we're preparing
for the heavy metal detox cleanse
you gotta have the book it's critical
the details are in here about the
cleanse about what to have
how to do the cleanse and we're gonna
cover it we're gonna talk about the
preparations right here right now i'm
actually really excited we're live on
youtube facebook
we're live on tick tock live on
clubhouse right what you're going to see
for what you're seeing now in front of
me right frozen wild
blueberries i'm going to talk about if
you can't get the frozen wild
blueberries other options right
spirulina how critical that is okay
barley grass juice powder really
important all right
cilantro another one right there
we're preparing for the heavy metal
detox cleanse it's going to start
tomorrow
dulse so atlantic dolls
okay celery you guys see that that's
important
bananas you're afraid of bananas
alternatives papaya
alternative mango really important okay
oranges if you don't like oranges and
you're somebody that's like oh citrus
doesn't work we're gonna do then some
coconut water
but we're gonna make a heavy metal detox
smoothies
all week for the next few days we're
preparing for the medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse
it's going to go for the next three days
got to have the book it's on sale right
now
16 plus some change amazon.com
us make sure you get the book and have
it
try to run to the library if you can if
you don't have the money to get the book
on sale
but the heavy metal detox cleanse is
right in the book
so here it is it's on page 179
i'm going to tell you guys the
importance of this cleanse what it has
done
it has saved lives literally millions of
people have been doing the medical
medium heavy metal detox cleanse
and smoothie around the world for years
now
millions and they get their lives back
they beat anxiety
because of it they beat depression
depersonalization
bipolar parkinson's disease they beat
wilson's disease
they beat eczema they beat psoriasis
they beat conditions left and right
fatigue
and other conditions too the heavy metal
detox cleanse
has not only saved so many lives it's
it's
changed the way we heal in the world as
of today it's the most
incredible thing you can do is a heavy
metal detox cleanse
so if you guys are coming on and you
missed just the beginning here watch it
from the beginning next time you know
you can or when the video is posted and
over
but anyway we're live on tick tock
facebook youtube clubhouse and i'm doing
the preparations
for the medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanse i am so
excited it's not even funny so excited
you guys
now there are healing stories out there
around the world about what the heavy
metal detox cleanse has done
done and it's remarkable
about the children that have gotten
their lives back their health back the
children around the world
mommies children doing the heavy metal
detox movies it's
legendary to getting people back on
track
and healing them and that's what it's
all about
that's so important okay so
we're we're live right now we're
preparing for the medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse it's gonna be
tomorrow the next day and the next day
three days
that's what the cleanse is gonna be
gotta have cleanse the heel
so important right here it's on sale
amazon us
okay 51 percent off look at the medical
mean cleanse the heal book
the details are in there on page 179
we're going to run through it all and
we're going to start doing it now too
let's start running through it
go to the bookstore pick up the book the
clenzie hill book it's in bookstores
around the world
can't afford it even though it's on sale
go to the library
okay you can't wait amazing jennifer
incredible i'm so excited
so what do you need for this that's the
question right there just off the
running
what do you need for this cleanse you
need your cilantro
that's really important right there you
so get that on the list you need your
dolls
a little bit of that atlantic dolls okay
if you can find that
you need your spirulina
okay that's the vimergy spirulina that's
the best one that i use it's the best
one
that i know exists out there there's no
other that touches that
that's the one you want to try to find
first
okay it's the vimorji v isn't victor i
am as in mary e-r-g-y
bemergee.com i'm not sponsored it's just
the best stuff it's critical to have the
best stuff
if you don't have the best stuff you try
your best so and we can still do some
you know we can still do some cleansing
but
want to maximize it it's about
maximizing that cleanse
here's the barley grass juice powder
right there that's a vimergy barley
grass juice powder
okay so now if you can't get the frozen
wild blueberries these are not
cultivated blueberries so if you put
cultivated blueberries
in the cleanse it's not going to do what
it needs to do
so you may want to get a hold of
the wyman's juice right there that's an
option too
the wyman's uh wild blueberry juice okay
that's at shop.weimans.com
so that's an option right there i know
that a lot of people are using this
in their smoothie they can't get the
frozen wobblers they're also doing both
they're putting this in the smoothie
with their frozen wild black blueberries
so keep that in mind
that book is so amazing thank you thank
you
this book is incredible it's got the
heavy metal detox cleanse i've been
waiting for
a while to make sure we can do this it
was so fun um crystal clear says yes you
do sponsor bimrgy
i am not sponsored by vimrajee uh you're
on their website
uh i know them and i know lots of
supplement companies that put out good
stuff
they put me on the website because i
allowed them to do that
i endorsed them but i'm not being
paid by them i'm not sponsored just so
you know but i
endorse companies is what i do endorse
traditional medicinals
um and that's what i do so that's
different that means i approve
of the product so any lots of companies
if they want it to me to be on their
website this they have to call me up and
if their stuff is high quality i'd be
like yeah well whatever if it helps
people
um but yes i'm not being paid i'm not
sponsored
but this book right here has the heavy
metal detox cleanse in there
so important and we're gonna cover it so
what do what are we doing why are we
doing this
why are we getting metals out because it
gets in the way with your life it keeps
us sick it's so important to clean these
out
helena says i thought you'd do the heavy
metal detox with colette
you don't do the heavy metal detox with
zeolite a heavy metal detox smoothie is
not what zeolite very important to know
if it people are
trying to create their own heavy metal
detox
smoothies and stuff so there's imitators
out there because the
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie is famous millions of people
around the world
if you look at the gold label on the
medical medium books right here okay
and it says millions of copies sold in
the medical medium series
all around the world it's the number one
health books in the world right now six
and a half
years running and there's a reason for
that the heavy metal detox cleanse has
saved lives
and that's how important it is zeolite's
not in the cleanse
chlorella is not in the cleanse
bentonite clay is not in the cleanse
charcoal is not in the cleanse those
disturbingly hurt people okay there's no
zeolites today
that there were of the yesteryear okay
so that's important and bentonite clay
is
actually dangerous charcoal is dangerous
in the intestinal tract it doesn't take
out metals
that's important to know chlorella is
dangerous because
chlorella is riddled in bacteria most
most batches of chlorella it's caused
a lot of harm on people people have
literally had their guts torn apart
because of it
and so i don't mess around with
chlorella and it doesn't remove
toxic heavy metals so that's important
to know so
heavy metal detox smoothie works and it
works and it's gentle and it does
because of what's in here
so that's important to know right the
zeolites today
they're dusted with non-edible zeolites
that's why it's not good
that's why it's not good so i don't i
don't recommend those at all
as of today so it's important to know so
we're talking about the heavy metal
detox smoothie cleanse this is
preparation
i'm excited this is a big deal today
okay so um and zeolites don't get metals
out of the brain
they don't get metals out of the liver
just so you know chlorella doesn't get
metals out of the brain doesn't get
metals out of the liver
bentonite clay doesn't get metals out of
the brain doesn't get metals out of the
liver
charcoal doesn't get metals out of the
brain doesn't get metals of the liver
there's a reason why the heavy metal
detox smoothie medical medium one works
and how it's imitated
constantly around the world by people
trying to make their own brews
trying to actually first of all the
reason why we know about removing toxic
heavy metals is from
medical medium information so let's make
that clear
that's so important to know because
you're going to hear about metals and
what to do out there but it all stems
from medical medium information
originally 35 years
of helping get metals out of people's
lives out of their out of their bodies
so people can heal
information that toxic heavy metals
cause psoriasis and eczema
and brain fog is medical medium
information
just medical meme information anybody
using that
originally got it from medical media so
in order for us to know about anxiety
even healing from metals and depression
healing from metals
and multiple sclerosis and als
and brain fog that's from medical medium
information so it's a legendary smoothie
a legend legendary information including
autism and adhd
people they have to realize oh i heard
metals are behind adhd
and originally it originates and stems
back to medical medium information as
the original source
and first source of all that information
so if you just got here and you're like
what is this what does he do
well any medical medium stuff you'll see
out there you won't know it's medical
mean because people have
poached it so much sarah says the
smoothie has helped me so much
been drinking for almost three years
every morning incredible
and your story is so important post your
story
you know if it's if it's ig tag medical
medium
medical medium and tag at medical medium
so i can see the story
i can see the post i won't be able to
see posts on ig by the way
or stories on ig unless you do at
medical tag at medical medium and
hashtag medical mean
both if you do that then i'll be able to
see the story and i will repost the
story i will repost the healing stories
i want to just thank everybody
who's done the heavy metal detox
smoothie and the heavy metal detox movie
cleanse
the cleanse and got their lives back and
have spread that information out there
by telling others about
how it's helped them heal and move them
forward
it's so important for that and i'm so
proud of anybody and everybody that's
done the heavy metal detox cleanse
and i'm just really excited you guys are
here
april payne good to see you i see you
commenting on youtube periodically
you guys i'm just proud of everybody i
want to say that so we're doing
preparation
that's what it's about it's about
alternatives too um
the heavy metal detox cleanse challenge
starts tomorrow
make sure you have a copy of the book
page 179 is the heavy metal detox
cleanse
it's on page 179 in here critical to
have the book
right amazon.com us 16.99
right 51 percent off or go to the
library if you want and just get it for
free from the library or go to a local
bookstore
okay important to know so
that's where we're at right now so let's
go into this
preparation it's important
do you guys like apples because apples
are a good
part of the cleanse they don't go into
the smoothie but you want to have some
apples
that's part of it so you want to keep
apples around that's going to be
something you need
oranges is in the in the smoothie so um
if someone doesn't like oranges because
i like putting an orange inside the
smoothie
we can switch it up and we can do
coconut water instead of the orange if
you'd like or water inside the smoothie
but the most important ingredients
to the smoothie okay
are the frozen wild blueberries now i
know that some people can't get the
frozen wild blueberries right now
because we're in that harvest time
they're harvesting wild blueberries
right now
and so they will and then eventually
they'll get into the stores if you can't
find any
anthony your information is healed my
now nine-year-old daughter of her stage
4 ebv
amazing desire good just thank you for
for being there
or desiree thank you for being there um
so proud
alison heavy metal detox movie has been
life-changing for me
calmed my brain down because it got the
metals out
because it got the metals out does it
work without orange on tick-tock that's
a question yes it does it works without
orange so if you're somebody that's
worried about oranges for some reason
okay if you're worried about oranges in
this smoothie you can
switch it up and you can do coconut
water or water in there instead of
orange
if you're somebody that doesn't like the
bananas because bananas are in the
smoothie if you're somebody that doesn't
like the bananas
you can go with papaya i got a papaya in
my hand you see
right you can go with papaya you guys
you can go with mango
you can go with frozen mango giving you
all the options right now
if you do coconut water don't do pink or
red coconut water and don't do a coconut
water that has
additives okay
so we're going over the ingredients we
are preparing
i am excited if you guys stick around
for the show now
it's going to be fun because after we
talk about preparations and stuff and i
answer a couple questions
we're going to talk about metals we're
going to talk about
copper because everybody's playing
around with copper these days copper
jewelry
copper mugs copper thermoses we're going
to talk about how bad that is
and how important this is to even though
right copper jewel
jewelry we're going to talk about how
bad that is
so that's important talk about other
metals
the goal of the cleanse is to get metals
out of our body because we're exposed to
metals we're loaded with metal
we have different types of metal inside
of our brain
we don't just have one type of metal in
our brain we have aluminum in our brain
we have
mercury in our brain we have copper in
our brain linda says i can't access
adults at the moment
any alternatives i love the heavy metal
detox smoothie been doing it for almost
a year keep the dose out then
and keep the other four in if you can't
access the dolls
right you're still gonna get a lot of
metals out it may not be perfect but
it's still good
and that's okay that's all right keep
the dolls out for now until you can get
some
we're to talk about the brain a little
bit
can i pass the 30 beauty with fatina
says can i
can i pass the 30 minute mark sometimes
i pass it because i'm busy doing
something yes
of course you can you can pass the 30
minute mark all right
you guys just got on here this is
preparations for the medical medium
heavy metal detox cleanse challenge
for the next three days today's just a
preparation day right here we're doing a
live
quick preparation stuff i'm excited make
sure you have the book page 179
heavy metal detox cleanses on in here
it's on page 179 so important to know
the details i'm going to walk you
through two as well
amazon.com us make sure you get the book
it's 51 off loving vimergy really
um really stepped up my supplement game
absolutely absolutely the vimrgy
products by far just step up the game
like knowing no one's business like no
one can even believe
the difference is not just it's not like
just night and day it's
make or break it's make or break healing
that's the difference right the vimergy
spirulina
is make or break healing there is a
difference right if you have to use
another spirulina
use it but if you can get a hold of
emergency spirulina that's the one
so preparations
frozen wild blueberries not cultivated
blueberries for the heavy metal detox
cleanse challenge
not dino good to see you not cultivated
blueberries the big blueberries the
cultivated ones no we're talking about
the
wild blueberries anna the heavy metal
detox movie has helped me
heal my debilitating migraines that i've
had for over 25 years
you had heavy metal migraines
mercury in the brain mercury in the
brain
i actually have some mercury with me to
demonstrate
you don't never want to touch mercury
you never want to play with mercury
you never want to mess around with
mercury right
but that's what people have in their
brain they have mercury
that's what they have in their brain
they have mercury in there
migraines adhd autism depersonalization
depression
anxiety
before we go into the heavy metal show
right
because we're going to go into a little
heavy metal talk we're talking about
preparing
getting ready preparing important to
know right there
let's go through the steps real quick do
you have the cleanse the heel book page
heavy metal detox cleanse do you have it
51 off amazon.com us critical
get it at the library if you can get it
at the bookstore local bookstore get
barnes and noble wherever you are
right the sale though on amazon us is
incredible for that book specifically
do you have your frozen wild blueberries
don't use cultivated blueberries for
this
if you don't have frozen wild
blueberries do you have a wild blueberry
powder
that's the vimergy one visa and victor i
am as mary ergy
dot com do you have the the wild
blueberry powder if you don't have
frozen wild blueberries there's the wild
blueberry juice which is amazing because
i use that with the frozen wild
blueberries and i'm going to do that in
the next three days i'm going to put the
wild blueberry juice with the frozen
wild blueberries
right there's the weinman's right that's
the
shop. shop.lymans.com that's where you
get that
giving you guys options really important
okay and you can do less of the dosages
that i'm going to talk about
do you have we'll go into that in a
second do you have cilantro let's go
through the steps
do you guys have cilantro
do you have the vimergy
barley grass juice powder right
will this help with lime and nicole
here's how it works with lime
lime is viral and toxic heavy metals
mercury mostly so when people have lyme
disease they're high in mercury
whether it's caught on a blood test or
not because it gets in the brain
people get the mercury in the brain okay
but yes it's helped people with lyme
disease
so there are millions around the globe
that have gotten their lives back
using this powerful tool children
moms and their children dads
you know grown-ups kids everybody aunts
uncles
grandparents people have gotten their
lives back
depression anxiety bipolar
uh fits of anger that just aren't not
warranted
right fatigue brain fog
parkinson's als multiple sclerosis
lyme disease like you name it elena i
healed migraines too i had
daily 24-hour headaches for one year i
wanted to commit suicide
couldn't take it it was really bad time
of my life and lena you got better
so proud of you so back on to the steps
barley grass juice powder we got that
last but not least
the seaweed specifically atlantic dolls
if you don't have the landing golds we
can still pull this off
laying a heavy metal detox smoothie
healed my daughter's eczema and that
is incredible it's incredible and
there's thousands of that
story of people healing their x-men
their children too it's so incredible
it helped me it helped me haven't had a
panic attack
in three weeks depression is gone right
on tick tock
incredible this is a special special
situation here
it's a special gift it's a special gift
right because we didn't have any of that
in
in the chronic illness community we
didn't have people getting rid of eczema
no one got rid of eczema years ago
before medical medium protocols
everybody just stayed with their eczema
and took all their steroids
no one got rid of these things severe
depression severe migraines
these are things that plague people
until they died until they got older and
died
medical medium heavy metal detox booty
is part of what broke
that cycle this is such a big deal
it's the only thing in the chronic
illness that world that broke the cycle
now there's imitators they're doing a
little list of bentonite clay some
charcoal
some you know whatever there's some and
it doesn't work
it doesn't work chlorella chlorella
never worked
ashley um
aydah hello from slo
the whole point is you guys have to keep
in mind all right
people kept their symptoms they never
got rid of them all these years
all those years people that poured into
my office from around the world
they kept their symptoms until they
learned how to do the heavy metal detox
smoothie
so what we're doing the heavy metal
detox plans if you just got on here you
guys lorraine l good to see if you guys
just got on here
we're talking about the heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge in the next
three days i'm really excited
really excited
so medals get in our way of our life
depression
panic attacks anxiety neurological
disorders
bipolar ocd tourette's
ticks spasms right depersonalization
okay parkinson's wilson's
even addison's i mean
the whole thing metals have been
holding people back in ways no one can
imagine
and so once people stumble across the
medical medium information and they
learn
how to do that heavy metal detox
smoothie or that medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse
it's not only just liberating but it's
not only just life-changing
it means everything to get rid of 20
years of migraines it means everything
to get rid of 20 minutes
20 20 20 years hey somebody's sick for
20 minutes it's really hard
we're live lorraine but 20 years of
eczema 20
20 years of psoriasis 20 years of
depression 20 years of anxiety
20 years old lyme disease
and the heavy metal detox smoothie has
turned that around
the stories are incredible the history
of it so far is incredible
it's already proven it works it's
already
proven better than any scientific study
can
ever prove in our history that it works
the scientific method is you do
something over and over again in hopes
to even get a partial result
then how about millions around the world
doing the heavy metal detox smoothie and
heavy metal detox cleanse
getting more than a partial result
getting a complete result
that beats out the scientific method
it beats out all of that it's really
really special that's just not even
that's not even a word that
even equals or measures what it really
is when someone gets their life back
you guys i'm preparing you the next
three days heavy metal detox challenge
the cleanse is on i'm pumped quinn says
my dad told me he used to play with
mercury
told me they passed it around in school
yeah and that gets passed around
from generation to generation when
mercury is in your system it gets passed
around
from generation to generation to
generation right
sperm and egg sperm and egg that mercury
sperm and egg that mercury gets passed
around okay
it's that mercury we play in our hands
gets in our system
but if you don't have to play with
mercury to have mercury in your brain
it's in pharmaceuticals mercury's
it's everywhere it's in water so yeah
so important to know
let's go over it real quick let's get
prepared i got alternatives you name it
so what do we need you guys you got many
of you guys know many of you guys are
doing it and i'm proud of you
what do you need you need the frozen
wild blueberries
not cultivated if you don't have the
frozen wild blueberries
someday they'll come back in your store
i know that we're in between harvest
right now they're harvesting right now
this year's crop is being harvested for
the wild blueberries
for the future frozen wild blueberries
that will be in your supermarkets and
you probably still have them in your
supermarkets but take a look and see if
you find them right that's one thing you
need okay
if you don't have the frozen wild
blueberries do you have
the vimmer g wild blueberry powder which
is an incredible product do you have
that
so
do you have the wild blueberry powder
that can be used too
that's an option right there
and then there's the wild blueberry
juice is an option if you don't have the
frozen wild blueberries
right so that's vimergy.com okay
vimergy.com
these and victorimergy.com
and they get spirulina too and that's
shop.wimans.com right
blueberry juice do you have the
spirulina
that is a big part of it right there so
you need the wild blueberry
you gotta have a form of wild blueberry
in there
okay that's the spirulina
gotta have that right gotta have
the barley grass juice powder right
there
that's the bimerjee boom gotta have the
cilantro
gonna have the cilantro atlantic dolls
if you don't have the atlantic dolls if
that's something that's hard to find and
you can't get a hold of we can
we can we can still do this cleanse
without the atlantic dolls
giving you guys preparations okay ready
for this
orange is in the cleanse orange is
in the cleanse right if you don't like
orange
you can go with coconut water that's not
pink or plain water
bananas are in the cleanse if you don't
like bananas
you can go with papaya you can go
with mango as alternatives
okay so make sure we know the
alternatives do you have your apples
ready
it's part of the medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse
apples don't go in the smoothie but
they're in the cleanse
right you can do small amounts of
everything if you're sensitive
you can do small amounts of blueberries
small amounts of
cilantro small amounts of spirulina
right you can make a you can make or you
can do a smoothie
and do a smaller dosage of it depending
on who you are if you're not used to
eating
you know so much or however everybody's
sensitive we'll see in different ways if
people are sensitive in different ways
you might be something that's really
toxic and so you don't have to do
the full smoothie if you don't want to
rd thank you so much anthony i have a
couple of family members who are
allergic to fruits so the allergic to
fruits and vitamin c
would it still work without the wild
blueberries
wild blueberries are a critical aspect
of it right
you can try it without the wild
blueberry
okay and so um so you have some people
in the family that they have an allergic
reaction to
they don't have allergic reaction to uh
natural vitamin c
so they they don't have that because no
one can have an allergic reaction to
actual
the natural vitamin c that's it's it's
part of
you see without blood if if they're
alive
that means they're they're getting
vitamin c somewhere a little vitamin
c because we die without vitamin c
that's important to know
if you don't have vitamin c you die
that's why people on a ship
out in the water too long without any
vitamin c
they died before the ship made its land
so if a long voyage
if there was a long voyage of men on a
ship men and women on a ship
right and there was no vitamin c to be
had
that would be a ghost ship it would land
land in a port and everybody would be
dead
vitamin c we is one of those make or
breaks we stay alive or not so they're
not allergic to vitamin c
so that means the testing is accurate
inaccurate about vitamin c
and as far as fruits go they could be
allergic to fruit if there's
if they if they're like if they eat a
piece of fruit and their throat closes
up and they need the epipen
then yeah they're allergic to fruit
absolutely
but if that's not happening are you just
talking about a food allergy test are
you talking about food sensitivity test
because those are just
bonk bonkers those are bonkers out there
it
i've actually been teaching about that
to doctors too they actually there's so
many doctors know that know
now that those tests are just fraudulent
those are fraudulent tests
like you go and get a test and you've
got 50 foods on the test and they tell
you to not eat 10 different fruits or 20
different fruits on the test
that's actually a fraudulent test unless
you're eating a banana and your throat
closes up and you need an epipen and
you're in the hospital
then yeah you're allergic you're
allergic
but do with your doctor do you you know
have your family do what their doctor
tells you
so you would want to keep the fruits out
of the cleanse
that's what you or you're asking right
so the only thing i can say is you could
still do
some spirulina you can still do coconut
water yes you can still do it
and get some benefits absolutely so what
i
would ask your doctor if it's okay if
you can do the spirulina
the barley grass juice powder right ask
your doctor if it's okay to do those
ask your doctor it's okay to do the
cilantro ask your doctor if it's okay
to do a little atlantic dolls right and
ask your doctor it's okay to have some
coconut water in there too
or water you blend it up
and that's that's how you do it that's
what i would do for a family member if
this was happening to them that's how i
would do it so yeah you can still
do a portion of this cleanse without
having the fruit yes
joan um do you all get the heavy metals
tested periodically to see how
you're progressing it's going to be
totally misconceived it can be deceiving
joan when you have heavy metal testing
because
in the organ is where the metals are
they're in
they're in the organ blood testing
can't determine how much metal you have
inside your brain tissue or
your liver all that can do is determine
how much metal you have in your
bloodstream
and still it is inaccurate because there
could be more metal floating around in a
different part of your bloodstream than
the part they actually drew out of your
arm in that moment to get the to get the
test
so testing for metals is really your
symptoms
the personalization anxiety depression
bipolar
tourettes ticks and spasms parkinson's
alzheimer's right
chronic fatigue brain fog multiple
sclerosis
lyme disease als that's your test
that's your test because all those go
away when people are doing the medical
medium heavy metal detox cleanse around
the world
there's stories of people healing their
alzheimer's stories of people healing
all their problem their memory problems
their bipolar their schizophrenia
their depression their anxiety their
depersonalization
their als their parkinson's that's the
test
not a blood test blood test is what just
gonna drain people more of their blood
so that's important to know so you guys
we're talking we're doing preparations
of the heavy metal detox cleanse
challenge
i'm excited about can't say susan blonda
my husband used to think that he was
allergic to bananas oh my god so many
people think they're allergic to fruit
than bananas we switched to organic and
it helped but we realized that the
banana
was killing off the strip in his sinuses
so that was probably causing
was fruit is a messenger it does cleanse
and kill out bugs and it does cleanse
out toxins so it is
a messenger so that's what fruit is it's
a messenger
um let's talk about metals for a little
bit let's just
a little bit recap too on the book
amazon.com us get the book have the book
make sure it's there tomorrow because
the cleanse challenge starts tomorrow
page 179 the heavy metal detox cleanse
amazon.com us 51
off 16.99 sarah i used to have over 20
food allergies
now i have none thanks to medical medium
information
everyone needs to get the books to learn
how to heal themselves
the heavy metal detox smoothie was
integral
to my healing it's especially helpful to
completely cure
anxiety incredible so glad you're here
this is an exciting time you guys i'm so
pumped up about this i can't even tell
you so where do we get medals let's do a
quick rundown about that
where you get metals copper pipes
restaurants restaurants with copper
pipes okay it's important to know
restaurant water you didn't get coffee
in a restaurant before
tap water has copper in it and mercury
and toxic heavy metals
and lead and arsenic and then they run
through copper pipes
right that's one thing right there we
have copper in our body
so can we use kombu uh
other algae instead of dols i'd rather
have you not use dulce at all if if
you're gonna switch and use something
else
i mean kombu is okay but it's not gonna
get the metals out
kelp is okay but it's not good to get
the metals out they're good seaweeds
right but they're not going to get the
metals out
so just i wouldn't even bother i would
just keep it if you can't get the dust
then
then you don't have the dolls make sure
you have everything else so copper is a
big one if anybody has skin problems
like eczema psoriasis they have copper
in their system
if anybody has any kind of neurological
condition
there's copper in their brain right
stay away from copper thermoses copper
mugs
copper jewelry right stay away from
copper copper clothing copper and
clothing
that's all bad really really bad
it's important to know there so i got
some copper here
everybody has had food
from metal pots and pans in restaurants
they just scrape the bottom of the pots
and pans like you can't even believe
you wouldn't believe the gouges and the
metal pots in all the restaurants
restaurants around the world with their
big cooking pots
scrape you see you see the bottom of the
pots and the lines in there and the
grooves and the scrapes
the amount of metal people get from
cooking is off the charts right
off the charts it's a little bit
insect killer right
insect killer anybody who's had bug
spray in their house they still
are breathing in toxic heavy metals even
if it was five years ago
insect killers a big one right there
pesticides herbicides fungicides but
insect killer in the house
that's a big thing right there you got
metals in you that never
leave dental work
dental work right there okay fluoride
treatments
the metal stays in your brain in your
liver causes problems short circuits the
central nervous system
yeah cold white spring says i don't kill
insects smart move
smart move good to see you we got great
i'm glad you're here cold white spring
we got
braces people have had right any kind of
dental work
in plants and it's okay if somebody has
implants
we can't avoid metal all the time
but we have to get the metal that's
floating around in our body and going
into our brain in organs we have to get
that out
so if you got if you had dental work or
you've got nuts and bolts holding your
knee together
if you've got nuts and bolts holding
your hip or your foot together
that's okay but we still have to get the
residue that leeches out we have to get
that out
right dental work is a place where
there's metals even ceramic fillings
even non-metal fillings have metal in
them
every single composite every single
dental composite has a form of metal in
it by the way
small amounts but they're in there so
dental work we all get metal from dental
work and the fluoride treatment that's a
big one right there so i'm giving you
guys the run down really quick
perfumes colognes bam
boom bam you don't need to use it
to get the metals you just need to smell
it
you need to smell it yep
someone hating the taste of cilantro is
high in metals by the way i want to give
that little piece of information out
there
but you just need to smell it yeah
dino mosquitos talking about mosquitoes
they mosquito spray everywhere on the
planet did you guys know that
helicopters drop mosquito spray at night
all over the planet everybody's
breathing in mosquito spray
kelsey bach kelsey what's up 50 symptoms
you got better
good to see you i know you come in on
youtube a lot the heavy metal detox
movie
saved my career as a massage therapist
incredible
can't massage with severe eczema on the
hands
i'm so proud of you i can't even tell
you so proud of you breathing in the
perfume
and the clone you're getting metals air
fresheners
filled with metals scented candles
scented candles filled with metals
scented candles metals how much tuna
have you guys had that's what i want to
know how much tuna
right how much tuna have you guys been
eating all these years
yeah filled with mercury
that's right not to mention you're in
the can you're in the can
right there okay and if anybody says oh
the liners protect you that's not true
why do you think you still taste a metal
when you're when you're
eating out of cans people still swear by
it they taste metal because the liners
always leak
right so that's where we get them too
pencils someone's going to say oh i got
them
i got them because there's no lead in
pencils anymore
right it's graphite it's graphite
how many people though bite the eraser
and bite the aluminum piece at the end
how many people guess what i know so
many people over the years that bite
their
i mean they bite their pencil ends even
if it was 20 years ago
they ground that aluminum they got it
right in their system
okay you just touch those ends with all
that aluminum
deodorant you're telling me you never
used to you'd never use the conventional
deodorant before
anybody right
medications
medications any medication antibiotics
are
loaded with toxic heavy metals load it
oil right
any time you've ever eaten out of it
used it touched it
i'm touching it now but the thing is is
i do the heavy metal detox smoothie for
life
so i'm okay if a little gets in there
because something's gonna get in there
somewhere
but how much aluminum do you have
inside of you right
fish oil that's a pretty fish oil bottle
right there
i had to cover up the brand
[Music]
yep fish oil
right how much fish oil have you guys
tried trying to get better
your doctor told you to do fish oil
someone told you to do fish oil how much
fish oil have you guys done
i'm sure you guys have tried the fish
oil that's loaded with methyl mercury
all the fish oil and this stuff
keeps us sick and it keeps us down for a
long time
man that metal builds up it keeps us
down for a long long time
medications right how about soda
who's shrinking off the aluminum cans
how to hide the brand again
who's drinking off the aluminum cans
you're just
sucking off the top of there and then
the fluid from inside the can gets on
the lid in there
as you're drinking it starts to dissolve
that aluminum really quick
so just in the course of you sipping and
enjoying a beverage
you're getting so much aluminum
poisoning you couldn't even believe it
it's off the charts
not to mention the liner the liner
the fraudulent liner breaks down
in all the cans and a lot of cans don't
even have a liner by the way
don't even have a liner when your can
gets cold
it constricts right and when it
constricts the line or breaks
when your can gets warm from you holding
it outside
it's expands line or breaks liners
aren't even they're not even being
they're not even doing anything inside
these so this is all important
information
and these are just some of the places we
get metals and then the metals end up
end up inside the liver but they end up
inside every single organ
inside the body and they end up inside
the brain and then you get
that sadness you just can't pin your put
your finger on
and then someone's going to tell you
it's because you died in 1854
and that was a past life that you were
you you were queen victoria you had your
head chopped off
someone's going to say you were in some
kind of like battle in 1604
or in 800 a.d
someone's going to say you're you know
and that's what they're going to say
because you can't pinpoint that
depression that's sadness so they're
you're going to be looking for all these
answers because medical research and
science is not going to know why you're
sick with depression
and anxiety and sadness you can't
explain it's toxic heavy metals that sit
in there how many people
have been just they just don't know and
the metals are inside their brain
causing problems
then they oxidize and then we eat the
high fat diet so then we eat food
and then we eat food and we accelerate
we accelerate the metals
they start to break down and oxidize and
we eat food that breaks them down and
oxidizes if you guys just came on here
you got to watch the video from the
beginning
we're talking about the heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge it's going for
the next three days
i'm excited about it okay you've got to
have a few things you've got to have the
cleanse of heal book
it's on page 179 the heavy metal detox
cleanse this is for free
doing this for free you guys i'm not
taking it to a private platform and
charging
doing it for free i know someone's going
to pop on here like what's he talking
about
you know but yeah gotta have the things
you need
so how much sushi have you guys done
with all the mercury from the fish how
much
how much uh sushi have you done gets
into the brain
it's what it does tanya blows my mind
how much of these products i've used uh
innocently
i've struggled with fatigue and
depression forever no wonder we are all
getting sick
medals play a huge role and guess what
people around the globe are getting
their lives back and they're healing you
guys
on tick-tock they're healing you guys
they're healing
facebook youtube people are healing
around the world with this information
it's legendary the heavy metal detox
smoothie people are imitating it
people are talking about it in stores
and juice bars around the world in
restaurants the heavy metal detox
smoothie
has changed lives it's incredible curius
is battling depression for years
i'm healing again amazing carrie because
when you're
when you're doing the heavy metal detox
cleanse you're doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie
you're getting metals out of the brain
that's why depression goes away that's
unexplainable depression
i'm not talking about this depression
from a horrible loss
or a sad situation that happened the
terrible loss of struggle emotional
struggle i'm talking about
depression that's debilitating taking
you out when there isn't such a thing
pamela says i feel so tricked about fish
oil oh my god
pamela i i i i'll during the cleanse
i'll go through it big time about the
fish oil it's so bad
i've been told if you have depression
your brain needs more and more fish oil
that's horrifying horrifying
that will take you to a place of
alzheimer's down the road
so then when you're 75 years old and you
got alzheimer's
the doctors told you do more and more
fish oil more more fish oil
you know alternative doctors you name it
so
sad what about the things
sorry i tried to read the comments you
guys um
what about the fillings in my mouth the
heavy metal detox work so here's how it
works
if the fillings are leaching the heavy
metal detox smoothie and cleanse
helps to get that product that byproduct
out that's leaching right
so when you've got the mercury
so when you got the mercury right
it's important to um
so when you get the mercury in your
teeth right
okay that mercury is leaching yeah
and so what i tell people if you got a
mercury filling it doesn't mean you have
to get the
mercury filling dug out if it's in
perfect condition or it's in good
condition
right it you can keep the mercury
filling in there
but what you're doing is you're getting
rid of when you're doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie and cleanse
you're getting rid of byproduct that's
leaching from the fillings
so the byproduct okay in your
bloodstream and then goes to your brain
and all that you're cleaning up all that
mercury
is what you're doing if you are to
remove mercury fillings
i always say do one at a time
and i don't recommend taking them out
unless they're broken or
denatured or about to pop out or you got
to crack in your tooth and they have to
do it anyway
you know because they dig out the
mercury and then you you got more
mercury you better be on the heavy metal
detox smoothie if that's the case
but yeah so that mercury gets in the
brain that's what it does it gets in the
brain
that's what it does
so we're doing the medical medium heavy
metal detox
cleanse challenge the next three days
i'm trying to read comments which i'm
multitasking a little bit
trying to hear spirit of compassion at
the same time and try to talk about the
medical medium detox cleanse
which is safe for children it i
recommend children in my family i
recommend uh
pregnant women that are in my friends
and family people that i know
i recommend the heavy metal detox
cleanse for breath breastfeeding you
ask what your doctor what's right for
you so i just recommend that for my
friends and family but you can ask your
doctor what's right for you if your
doctor tells you not to do it don't do
it
julie haggerty says i went from 36
debilitating symptoms down to four
from the heavy metal detox god bless you
celery juice and medical meaning
protocol so grateful grateful
and you know what's so sad there's so
many people like don't do the don't do
the medical medium stuff
you know do this and do corella
chlorella
do charcoal oh my god it's horrible do
bentonite clay no don't do those do
you know it's amazing how much
misinformation out there you know it's
incredible
i spent 35 years teaching about toxic
heavy metals that's why we even talk
about it today
right so and and nobody knew toxic heavy
metals was behind one symptom or
condition did you guys know that
they didn't know it was behind one
symptom symptom or condition medical
medium put the information out there
about which symptoms and conditions like
eczema and brain fog that's from toxic
heavy metals they thought brain fog was
from not being happy did you know that
just recently in the last 10 years
doctors put out books and ph
phds put out books and said your brain
fog is from not being happy
unbelievable i got very sick after
removing my fillings
yeah that's why i tell people you got to
do one at a time if you ever do or don't
do it at all unless they're broken and
they need to come out
or something's wrong but that's why it's
so important do the heavy metal detox
cleanse clean that out that's the whole
thing to get all that stuff
out and and if you're getting fillings
out
space them out space them out with
enough time and talk about that medical
medium books
so what's the goal the goal is
if you're if you're not even
experiencing a symptom the goal is to
get the metals out so you never
experience a symptom
the goal is to get the metals out if
you're experiencing symptoms too
ip1 says i got 11 mercury 11 mercury
fillings that were buried underneath
old caps out in the last five years now
i'm dealing with eczema dermatitis and
psoriasis you also have copper
in your system too
copper as well and that's here
i highly highly highly recommend
avoid copper products copper thermoses
copper mugs
copper jewelry copper copper clothing
highly recommended it's toxic and you're
being
totally screwed over
i highly recommend you avoid fish oil
with everything you got this stuff is
methylmercury
the homeopathic version of mercury it's
worse than eating fish
i highly recommend you don't do
bentonite clay and zeolite and
charcoal highly recommend you avoid
avoid i know some of you say no there's
good literature and data on
copper thermoses and copper being good
for you you're wrong you're being misled
by that data
copper is so toxic right
that it does kill a certain amoeba
that was in the water that caused
dysentery thousands of years ago so they
used to put
water because they didn't have access to
water thousands of years ago
so they used in many many cultures they
didn't have access to water for clean
fresh running water
so in order to keep water still meaning
without it going real
rancid they used to put it in copper big
copper
uh vaults right to keep the watch so
that the copper would poison
any kind of critter in there like any
kind of big parasite or amiibos really
amoebas
amoebas don't like copper but at the
same time
the people poisoned themselves by
drinking that water but yet they needed
water so they had to drink the copper
poison
you don't have to drink copper poison
why are you being tricked to drink
copper poisonous water now
you can find water without amoebas in it
it was a survival tactic thousands of
years ago doesn't mean if you need to do
it now
why do you have to poison yourselves
with copper copper mugs and stuff
like why do you have to poison yourself
with copper uh
you know with copper mugs and everything
right
like let me just drink out of a copper
mug
because i want to be like it's 3 000
years ago when they didn't have any
fresh water
and they all got copper poisoning so
they wouldn't die from an amoeba
that's not your life now you can get
water and not have an amoeba in that
water
and you can avoid the copper poisoning
that shortened everybody's life
yeah they were able to drink a little
bit more water but they also died young
because of the copper poisoning so why
are we doing the copper stuff
my god if you guys you guys the one
thing you're going to get with medical
medium information you're just going to
get
like it is straight and you're going to
realize how much bs is out there
constantly
and you're going to realize how mislead
you are and how much misinformation is
out there it's so
sad let's go over the basics we're just
talking about metals how we get metals
so hydrogen metals aluminum byproduct
fluoride that's one deodorant that's
another
aluminum foil restaurant food
right aluminum pots and tans and
restaurants we've reloaded with
metals you guys it's what big part of
why we're sick soda cans beverages
metal right aluminum right medications
every medication's got aluminum in it
and other metals including mercury
right you got that perfumes colognes
fish oil giving you guys the rundown
boom boom boom fluoride treatments
dental work
implants composites of any kind even if
they're not mercury
they still got metals in them right
cooking utensils cooking products
it doesn't mean you you avoid every last
one of these
it just means that we have
metal and it builds up but we got to get
it out right
there you go these are just some of the
things tattoos
a huge way everybody's got so much metal
in them
is tattoo ink there is no heavy metal
free
tattoo ink news flash for everybody for
all the dudes
getting all those sleeves done all the
dudes
all the dudes and all the girls getting
sleeves done
getting tattoos and getting writings and
tattoos written across the ribs and
that's not heavy metal detox free that's
not heavy metal free
vegan ink is not heavy metal free it's
loaded with toxic heavy metals load it
and when you get that depression when
you're 40 years old after you got your
10th tattoo
when you were 20 and that depression
starts kicking in and that eczema
psoriasis starts kicking in you're 38
years old and now you're on steroids and
every other drug
you don't know and that's okay let's get
it out
you can still keep your ink and get the
metals out of your organs
metals is how the tattoo ink
pops you can't see
them tattooing clear unless light
reflects
against metal your vegan ink is loaded
with toxic heavy metals
that's how that you can see the tattoo
it's from the light
popping it the light has to reflect off
the metal
if you don't have metal in the ink in
your in your so-called
natural vegan uh toxic free ink
if you don't have metal in that ink you
won't be able to see your tattoo
you're loaded with toxic heavy metals
that's okay you can have your ink let's
get the metals out of your bloodstream
of course out of your brain your liver
in your organs we're talking about the
heavy metal detox cleanse
here we are preparing everybody right
now
you need the cleansing heel book it's
page 179
it's a heavy metal detox cleanse we're
doing a heavy metal detox three-day
cleanse challenge starting tomorrow
this is preparations you guys good to
see you
and i'm glad you're here i'm pumped i'm
excited about this
i can't even tell you how excited i am
susan it keeps freezing
of course it does is that facebook that
keeps freezing yeah it's facebook that
keeps freezing
yeah facebook and insta they just freeze
everybody out and kick everybody off
all right but i still want to do this on
social media i mean i can take it to a
private platform and have you guys sign
up but i was doing this
and we might do that but i'm not going
to charge it's always free
um i am going to get better do they come
out with laser removal it doesn't mean
you have to do
your attack you have to remove tattoos
to get the metal out you have to be
doing you have to be pro
proactive and getting the metals out of
your brain
you can get your tattoos lasered off but
you're gonna still have all the
ink the metal in your organs and
the laser doesn't remove the metals
it doesn't remove the metals in your
skin it's gonna still be in there
the laser just makes the tattoo
disappear over time
but the metals though they disperse and
they're still going to be
deep within the derma push down deep in
the derma
the point is it's okay if you have
tattoos you just have to clean the
metals out of the brain
where the tattoo ink eventually disapp
what happens is
over time the tattoo ink leeches metals
and gets to your brain every single day
from the first day you got it into your
bloodstream when they did it this is
this is
it and it's okay but we're doing the
medical medium three day heavy metal
cleanse challenge i'm pumped what do you
guys have are you guys ready
do you have your frozen wild blueberries
boom don't use cultivated blueberries
if you can't get frozen wild blueberries
make sure you have your vimergy
wild blueberry powder not sponsored by
these guys it's just an incredible
product so you got your wild blueberry
powder right there
got that what i'm going to do is i'm
going to put the wyman's
um wild blueberry juice i'm going to put
that in there you guys
know i work with wyman's incredible
product it's to make sure this product
stays around
it's unbelievable that's at
shop.wymans.com
carol i was experiencing panic attacks
for no reason
started doing the heavy metal detox and
panic attacks are gone depression gone
sleeping well at night healed so much
that is
better that is that is better
than science itself science research
doesn't know
that metals cause those symptoms
and it's medical meme information right
but you got rid of those symptoms
with medical medium information it's
incredible
and it outbeats science because it's you
you proved it right there
it's really remarkable all of it
so you guys i'm excited about the
cleanse challenge
i'm hoping you guys join make sure you
have your book page 179 amazon.com us
16.99
take advantage of that 51 off sale right
there go to your bookstore look at it
look for it in the library if you can
grab a copy in the library i know the
waiting list is rough in there so i
don't think you're gonna get one in time
and make sure you know what you're
getting make sure you get the spirulina
you got that
make sure you got the barley grass juice
powder make sure you've got your
cilantro
dulse if you can find it
i'm putting wild blueberry juice here's
wild blueberry powder from bemergy i'm
putting a lot of blueberry juice in mine
it's not barley grass barley grass juice
powder you guys
and we ran over some of the places where
we get the metals
we talked about some of the symptoms and
diseases that metals caused we talked
about the brain a little bit
and we are gonna be doing it
i am pumped up can't wait
was listening to you and ch
happy i found you on facebook
wow incredible you were on clubhouse and
now you're incredible glad you're here
you guys um
i'm heading off to ig if you get kicked
off
ig go to tiktok if you can i'm on
clubhouse
2 later as at the same time as ig and
i'll be on tick tock so i'll be on tick
tock live
clubhouse live and ig live all at once
if you're
you catch me on ig and the powers that
be at ig
allow you to be on for more than 30
seconds before kicking you off
that's amazing if you're kicked off go
to
tick tock or pop on clubhouse to listen
sarah i've been doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie every day for five and a
half years
whoa can't imagine life without it
you know i want to add to this point so
many people they go off of it for a
little while and they
have to run back to it because they feel
the difference
like say people are traveling and they
don't have access to everything
and they're traveling and they don't
have access to a heavy metal detox movie
right and then man they all of a sudden
get back on it and they're like thank
god
because now i could feel better now i'm
feeling like i'm moving forward and you
can feel the difference
i see that all the time out there guys
share your stories
let people know share your stories you
know so they don't get fooled by
imitators
with all the bad stuff that hurts people
hashtag medical medium and also tag at
medical medium if you do a story out
there so that i can see it i can't see
it unless you tag at medical medium and
hashtag it as well
now you guys are sensitive because
you're really toxic you do four ounces
of the smoothie
start with that and you build yourself
up either way we're doing the heavy
metal detox cleanse
tomorrow challenge starts i'll see you
guys on ig in about 15 minutes
can't wait love you guys
heading over there now i'm gonna turn
clubhouse and tick-tock back on