we're talking about skin problems
because one thing that's getting worse
with health with everybody these days
every single five years that passes is
skin problems people's skin is falling
apart out there that's all you hear out
there now they got this problem they got
dark spots they got all kinds of acne
they got all kinds of scarring they have
to get exfoliations they got to get you
know all kinds of different facial care
skin care because people's skin is
getting worse than it was years ago like
years ago 20 years ago even 10 years ago
we had a fraction of the skin problems
we have today we're talking about the
medical medium Skin Potion it is
something that just works hands down
just the facts just the record it
actually works and so one thing I'm
going to do is make the Skin Potion but
I want to just move over real quick to a
quick announcement I'm going to be
speaking in
Colorado at the Gaia heel conference I
don't know if you guys got a ticket if
you already did that already if you're
coming but it's going to be exciting
because I'm doing a light blast but I
just have to forewarn anybody who's
coming it's a high altitude light blast
it's there's a big difference and um I
guess what I'm trying to say right now
is if you're in that audience there Live
while we're doing the High Altitude
light blast it's going to be intense so
I'm kind of giving you a little
forewarning I feel like I have to it's
my responsibility
um high altitude light blast means the
light hits you from a little bit of an
angle and it hits you faster a little
bit harder because we're 5,000 plus feet
above sea level so what happens is with
the normal light blast which is still
intense where there's Miracle healings
Miracle changes in people's lives with
that one the light when it finally hits
it hits a little bit softer and it's a
little bit less intense and it comes
Direct on top of the crown of the head
with something like the Colorado light
light blast the last time I did a light
blast in Colorado was maybe N9 years ago
I think it was N9 years ago could have
been 10 years ago like don't quote me on
that part exactly the month or the year
but close to 10 years ago and that's the
last time I did the light blast a high
altitude light blast in Colorado it was
in Denver at the time and people were
just they were hit hard it was an
incredible experience the whole bit now
I don't live in Colorado
doesn't mean I'm not going to eventually
think about maybe getting a place in
Colorado and living there for a while
it's very possible but um as of right
now I don't so like I said the last high
altitude light blast was a decade ago
and this one is coming up so November
9th I think that's the date you can
still get a ticket you can still be
there we still got some time I'm going
to do a lecture I'm going to talk about
some pretty intense things it's going to
be a little bit of a different kind of
talk and a little different speech from
s so it's going to be pretty intense
really it's going to be a lot of other
speakers too so if you had a chance or
if you're going you won't be
disappointed uh you won't be
disappointed I can tell you that like
true medical medium fashion it's not
going to disappoint anyway back to the
Skin Potion so there's skin problems
everywhere out there it's a serious
issue not just xoras not just dermatitis
not just bumps and all kinds of
different things not just
detoxifications of people skin and other
issues and skin Cancers and all kinds of
different stuff people are going through
that's getting worse skin problems are
on the rise people want their skin to
look good and what you'll notice in the
skin world is you'll notice 22-year-old
models modeling for skin products 22
years old or 20 years old or 24 years
old and you know that's that's kind of
like a tricky situation when a model
who's 22 years old who's getting
exfoliations and using so many different
creams and buttercreams and ointments
and all kinds of different um facials in
the whole bit and they're 20 years old
or 22 years old and they're trying to
sell a skin product or say their skin
looks good it's kind of a joke and no no
no disrespect on any level no insults
nothing like that that's not what it's
about it's just kind of observation of
reality of how it works and so you know
so the skin Market has really been taken
over by the 20-year-old or the 19 or
24-year-old who is getting a tremendous
amount of you know applications on their
face and skin work and their 20 so you
got to think about that right now and
the 22-year-old who's suffering with
skin problems isn't going to be the
model modeling skin ointments and skin
care and so forth doesn't work like that
so the models chosen to sell skin
products are models that already don't
have any skin problems to begin with and
they're 20 years old and they have no
skin problems yeah those are the ones
chosen to do skin product modeling stuff
and they're still getting their
exfoliations and their facials and
everything else and applying a whole
bunch of different stuff they have so
many techniques right it's all about
that so I I'm talking about serious
stuff I'm talking about any kind of skin
problems and stuff that people develop
over time and the irony is if you take
somebody who doesn't have skin problems
and they're 20 years old what are they
going to look like when they're 40 how
are they taking care of themselves do
they have the medical medium tools
because yeah everything just seems to
fall apart on everybody and that's how
it rolls out
there one thing about skin which is
critical as antioxidants you want good
skin you have to be doing antioxidants
just keep that in mind right there that
is a big one you'll hear a lot of
different stuff out there like this and
this about skin and all that it's like
antioxidants are the critical piece you
want less skin problems you want your
skin to heal one thing you'll never see
me promoting is that whole thing with
the roller with all the little tiny
prickly things on there and people are
doing this micro needling or whatever
it's called right was never a fan of the
micro needling thing where you're
sitting there and you're just you know
you're rolling that thing on your face
and you're doing this terrible idea now
that's the problem with the world of
Health it's the Wild Wild West I'll say
it over and over again where pretty much
anybody comes up with a cocka manyy
[ __ ] terrible idea puts it out there
seems like a good idea and everybody's
using it and they're micro needling and
what they're doing is they're destroying
their underneath their their bottom not
the bottom but the middle layer of their
Derma they're making it so they can get
Scar Tissue on their face so one of the
whole things about that micro needling
and it might not even be called micro
needling I'm so not into that that I
kind of left that out of my
Consciousness you know what I mean but
that whole thing with the roller with
all the different little tiny needles on
it where they don't go that deep but
they go deep enough and you roll your
face with it that was purported to say
well what happens is you're fixing all
kinds of scar tissue and all kinds of
stuff like that no no no no I should do
a podcast about that I really should
there's only so many damaging and and um
uh problematic things I can do podcast
about if you heard my last podcast I
don't know if you heard the last one I
just put it out there medical Me podcast
go to Spotify go to Apple and you can
hear that last one it's just
mind-blowing the the things that people
do that is not good for them and all
that so the problem is when you do that
roller like that and you're you're
so-called stimulating so you can get
collagen growth first of all collagen
doesn't grow because of that collagen
doesn't grow like that you can't take
collagen to fix your collagen and you
you can't rub something on your face or
prick your face with a prickly device
you can't do that to grow your col
collagen it doesn't work at all it's not
how it um it's not how it
rolls so we'll talk about this too for a
little bit vitamin C if you just got
here you see some products in front of
you see the micro C okay that is part of
the Skin Potion the medical medium Skin
Potion there's a reason for it so that's
the micro immune power
immune power your
skin has an immune system there your
skin has to have one of the strongest
parts of your immune system it's there
so you don't get infections when you get
cut so you don't die of blood poisoning
which is bacterial infection so you
don't die of sepsis your skin is your
protector from sepsis and so forth but
it's your Skin's immune system that's a
protector from sepsis and other issues
like that and infections and so forth
and constant staff infections and
everything and super bugs like Mera MRSA
right all that stuff so your skin is
your protector it's the sleeve over our
bodies and to keep our skin strong and
healthy and this is important to know
you have to have antioxidants if you're
a skin person if you're into skin if you
want to protect your skin it is critical
that you have the antioxidants and now
running out and going get get some
vitamin C out there might not be the
answer either because a
scorpicol it with skin cancers it's out
of control skin cancers are on the rise
they are on the rise eczema psoriasis
dermatitis Vitiligo is on the rise and
it's not going to be going anywhere
anytime soon in fact not only is it not
going to be going anywhere anytime soon
it's going to get out of control to a
level no one's ever even
seen it's going to be really really bad
so when it comes down to your skin you
have to have your immune system attack
attacked immune system attacked right
ATT intact and you have that's why I
like doing live you got to do it live
because if something happens or you say
something this whatever man you do the
best you can but you have to have your
immune system working it has to be
strong but in order order to keep your
immune system strong and take care of it
you have to feed it it's critical it
gets vitamin C it gets those
antioxidants that's a big deal skin your
immune system antioxidants and then you
can choose the different antioxidants
you can take you can find different
forms of antioxidants out there my
favorite is vitamin C vitamin C so says
is is the strongest and best skin
healer that's it bottom line if you
don't have vitamin C in your diet on any
level you die you die that's
it yeah you die your body falls apart
little bit after a little bit your
organs fall apart you go into organ
failure your skin falls apart first and
you die that's what happens without
vitamin
C science of research had to discover
vitamin C because they were forced to
keep that in mind this is important they
were forced to I just saw somebody say
what kind of vitamin C is that we're
talking about the vimergy stuff V is and
Victor i m is and Mary E rgy vimergy.com
this is the medical medium Skin Potion
that works that
works and you guys know I endorse these
guys because of what they're doing and
wait till you hear about how it works
and what's in here versus some other
vitamin C it's important if you care
about your skin this is important I know
there's so much [ __ ] going on out there
there's so many different things out
there and it's hard to even decipher
what's what but I'm letting you know if
you at all care about your skin at all
you care about your skin even the
slightest bit it's important it's
imperative that you understand what this
ISS the Skin Potion right and how it
works without vitamin C we die we cease
to exist our bodies fall apart and
that's it see you later that's it the
door closes you're gone now what happens
without vitamin C science was forced to
figure this out because people are going
on Long ship rides long boat rides
without a squeeze of lemon without a
piece of fruit without a fresh vegetable
that has vitamin C like just broccoli
alone is loaded with vitamin C people
were going on Long ship rides and dying
they were dying their bodies were
falling apart they were getting scurvy
their skin was falling off their bodies
it was growing thin by the month and
just opened up so what happens is if you
don't have vitamin C in your diet and
your skin decides to just just fall
apart and open that says a lot right
there it's a big deal skin and Vitamin C
go hand in hand hand in hand very
important to know people who have less
vitamin C in their diet their skin gets
cruder cruder cruder and cruder and as
they grow older it gets thin as heck
their skin gets so thin tears gets
thin that's what happens to skin when
you don't have enough vitamin C or years
enough of vitamin C so you can help
rebuild
collagen and help restore collagen and
help restore your Skin's layers in your
skin surface and the Deep
Derma so this is a little skin talk cuz
I think it's important so people know
these differences and understand what's
going on science was forced to find
vitamin C they had no choice they needed
to know why people were dying from a
Long Boat Ride they needed to understand
that they also needed to understand that
if someone was fed a certain amount of
food for a certain amount of time and
had a problem where their body fell
apart they needed to understand that too
one of the things they were looking for
and they thought was the Panacea was V
vitamin A they thought vitamin A was
everything that vitamin A was the
survival of
humankind and they thought that removing
vitamin A or diets of no vitamin
A was the reason why people were falling
apart with their health but they were
wrong vitamin A wasn't the Panacea of
Everybody's Health it wasn't a make or
break we're talking about a make or
break there's a big difference right
there make a
break one of the reasons why they
figured out vitamin A wasn't the answer
is they put some people on just straight
white
rice and
they didn't survive and then they put
other people in straight white rice
processed white
rice and they did survive and they're
like how is it where one person survives
one person
doesn't and they were doing vitamin A
with both and what happens is when
they're doing vitamin A with both and
they
realized some people survive some people
don't survive they found out that one of
the people one of the groups of people
that were
surviving were eating other
things and they're like well let's look
at the other things they ate and what
they found was it was vitamin
C the whole thing about not having
vitamin C in your diet for a long time
and your body falling apart and
dying is something they found out also
with the ships that I talk about taking
boat rides long boat rides in the ocean
3 months four months five months 6
months out at Sea eight months out at
Sea and then everybody just falls apart
and that's
that they were forced to over time find
out that we had to have vitamin C they
had to search for it it was the search
for vitamin C vitamin A was no longer
the big thing it was like okay vitamin A
and everybody thought that's the answer
but no it was vitamin C in order to stay
alive and stay healthy and be alive
vitamin C was critical if you guys
wanted know this is the vimer the micro
C now you probably heard of the micro C
at this point I I think it's famous at
this point for what it does for people
and how it helps people so that's the
micro so micro is a lot more known than
I am a medical medium that's how many
people are using it to get their lives
back recover and do things for
themselves you know so it's really an
incredible product right here so that's
the micro C it's the vimergy one right
so let's go into the Skin Potion a
little bit more people are are really
focused on their skin more than ever
because of social media because
everybody wants to look good for social
media not everybody but a lot of people
are jumping onto the social media
bandwagon and they want their skin to
look good they just do that's what
everybody wants to do they're also
photoshopping all their photographs so
everybody's doing the photoshopping on
photographs because of their skin
they're trying to photoshop every single
thing that shouldn't be on their face
they're trying to photoshop it out right
now it's all about skin and it's getting
even crazier but in order to get your
skin better you have to fix problems you
have to fix internal issues immune
system is a big one right there and then
free radical damage so you guys have
heard of free radical damage right
because free radical damage that's a
common term that's not a medical medium
term that's not MediCal medium
information free radical damage it's not
but there's something to be said about
it there really is medical medium talks
about what free
radicals what free radicals are which
free radicals are the problems that
nobody talked about so medical me
information is about so many different
things right like pesticides and the
herbicides and the fungicides and all
the difference of the fragrances the
Clones of perfumes all the different air
fresheners it was medical medum
information originally being put out
there for decades until finally it got
caught on and now it's all over the
place but mm INF
was all about what kind of free radicals
are we talking about and then the free
radicals produced in our body that's
originally where the term free radicals
came from free radical terminology was
all about free radicals produced inside
your body you guys causing problems
oxidative
stress
but what happens is if you don't fix
internal issues like fix the immune
system strengthen it help clean up the
liver a little bit get some problem
solved get the immune system functioning
like it needs to function if you don't
do that you can't fix a lot inside your
body you can't fix a lot of things
inside your body it's not going to
happen if you're somebody focused on
skin especially you're not going to
repair scar dish scar tissue damage
you're not going to repair acne damage
you're not going to repair
things if you can't take care of your
immune system and your Skin's immune
system it's not going to
happen so in order to repair skin and
get it healthy and get it looking
good and one thing happened where when
we were at the Cafe Gratitude right if
you guys were there it was amazing to to
meet you and see you a few people are
like aw your skin does look good it's
not I'm in person right in front of you
and it does look good um zarz over here
on YouTube aw skin looks even better in
person and it looks pretty good on the
video too it looks pretty good on the
video but you saw me in person you were
a foot I think zarz you were a foot away
from me I think everybody was a foot
some people were this close to
me I think a couple of people were
talking to me and spit flung out of
their mouth and landed on my lip and on
my mouth and on my nose what I'm saying
we were this close we were this
close
right and anyway the point I'm trying to
say is that um I'm not 20 years old I
don't get exfoli
ations I didn't get plastic
surgery um and I don't get facials in
fact I do probably real annoying
things like not wash my face for a long
time because I'm too busy working and
not focused on on personal
hygiene so I do a lot of things that are
not pro skin at
all but there's something I do do
and that's the whole point it's the
antioxidant factor it's the
antioxidant factor it's
that it's so many different foods with
the higher
antioxidants it's that too it's all
these things and things like the micro
SE so the micro is how I make the
medical medium Skin Potion I'll show you
in a minute I just want to cover skin
Health a little bit and there's so many
different aspects of skin health
so so lot uh let's see Lyn Fouch love
this potion so many changes with my skin
and internal I can feel it well that's
the thing like this has gotten popular
now the micro C because it works it's
working right so here it is right here
and it's working and the Skin Potion is
along with the MSM so it's the
combination right here so when you put
them together it takes it to the next
level level which is really amazing and
there's silica in here too in the whole
bit with the silica the bamboo
silica hiw I've been doing the Skin
Potion almost every day it's helping my
skin and immune system too win-win it
really does it does both Cen topaz thank
you on YouTube thank you for being here
thank you for sharing that I think one
of the hardships about skin issues you
guys is feeling that you feel insecure
you don't don't feel good about yourself
and if you have a skin condition I never
want you to feel that way ever I don't
want you to feel like you're not good
enough or you can't be in person
somewhere or you can't say hi to
somebody or you can't talk to somebody I
never want you to feel that way if you
do have a skin issue because it that
that's not about that but so many people
are suffering with how they feel when
their skin doesn't look a certain way or
they have acne or they have a scar a lot
of people have scars and the scars
aren't healing and they don't know why
so they get facial scars from acne and
other things from white heads and black
heads and different stuff and rosacea
over time rosacea can create the
scarring that occurs on your face in
your skin tissue and so like the rosacea
so if you're somebody you have 20 years
of rosacea or 5 years of rosacea you
could you can have like problems and
then you're wondering well what I going
to do how come this isn't
healing in order to heal like deep
seeded skin problems you have to have
the high intense
antioxidants you have to have the free
radical damage killer and
destroyers you have to have that vitamin
C you have to have that so there's
different antioxidants and there's
different antioxidants in Foods I've
talked about this all the
time but like moving the needle fast is
what matters in in a lot of ways like
you can't if you can't get a skin
problem better fast enough it could
really affect you emotionally mentally a
lot of people they need to get
themselves ready for something it could
be somebody's wedding it could be it
could be something else it could be
meeting somebody going on a date if
people they change their dates they
change the you know times you're going
to meet people they do all kinds of
different stuff they don't go to friends
weddings because to their skin and it's
really sad it's really sad and then they
end up using a lot of toxic things which
I want to say next the skin world of
health is mostly made of toxic crap
toxic crap people are using on their
skin or taking skin tonics so so to
speak you know taking skin supplements
that have garbage in them hair skin and
nail supplements are some of the
trashiest crap out there on the
market
fact
maltodextrin magnesium
sterate citric
acid natural
flavors whatever just loads of junk and
garbage and not not only that other
things you can't see that are not on the
ingredient list so what people are doing
for their skin out there is are using
toxic stuff that's added to their free
radical bump up they think they're doing
something for their hair skin and nails
and they're taking all the you'll see it
out there there'll be another 500 new
companies putting out a hair skin and
nail supplement because everybody's
desperate right now to get their skin
better but they're taking all this
additional crap from those supplements
in their body that's bogging down their
liver that's not helping them that's
setting them
back and that's a big problem here you
are trying to fix a problem you're
trying to fix your skin but you can't
fix your skin because you're adding to
the problem but you're yet you're paying
all this money constantly each month to
help with your problem but you're not
you're doing the reverse you're actually
adding to the problem and not recovering
your
skin I'm not saying every single skin
problem somebody has on their body or
their face is healable some people have
some really deep seated scars those SCS
are going to be there they've been cut
they've had 10 stitches they've had five
stitches they've had 50 stitches there
are people out there with a lot of
injuries and skin injuries they have
really bad Burns that went through the
Derma there's people out there that have
been burned on their skin where the
where the hot part that burned them
whatever that might have been went
through their layers of skin down to the
bottom of the Derma into the flesh so
then they have a
scar well but what I am saying is if you
want that to repair on any level or have
even a hope that it can repair you got
to be doing things
right so there's a lot of different
Trends and a lot of different
um different bio hacks for skin these
days and every time I see a new one I
instantly know that's not going to help
if anything that's going to add to the
problem if there is something that comes
out that's really good for the skin I'll
be the first to jump on it why
not I want to I want to do things too
that are
healthy but there isn't and that's the
problem so over here on IG are we
supposed to take vitamin or apply it to
our skin sorry for the question silly
question it's not a silly question it's
it's an important question you're going
to take this internally is what you're
going to do and ask your doctor what's
right for you you know ask them what
they think but that's the micro C powder
I'm going to show you that micro C
powder and that is the MSM right there
so these are both by vimergy now what
you're going to find in this powder and
I want to show you this so I'm going to
put it in the cap okay if you guys don't
mind all right I want to show you
this take a look right there you're
looking at a powder the micro powder is
what you're looking at right now you
guys see that on IG you see that on Tik
Tok all
right there's a miracle that occurred
with vimergy a miracle I call it a
miracle because it hasn't occurred
anywhere
else not that I know
of that Miracle is there isn't an anti-t
taking agent made out of something
sinister that you don't know that you're
taking there's no anti-caking
agent in this micro SE powder but guess
what in all your green powders and all
your powders I see a green powder when
you know I was over my family's house
the other day they had the TV on and it
was a popular green powder that's been
taking off they got like millions and
millions of dollars running in ads and
everything and it was loaded with
anti-caking agents inside of it but
nobody
knew it's a
Sinister kind of a diabolical
despicable world the health movement
it's grown pretty tumorous
it really
has I think what people need to
understand is like Purity it really does
exist just nobody knows what's really
happening and who's doing it so what
you're seeing right here with this is
there's
no anti-caking agents in there but
you'll have it in all your powders and
all your protein powders and all the
different patterns you take and do it's
all there it's in there that means
there's a portion at add it to it to
stop it from sticking just
because just
because that's one thing right there
that I call a miracle because vimergy
wouldn't do that that's why I endorse
them that's why I I dedicate time and
energy I do I don't own the company I
don't own a percentage of the company I
don't have stocks and shares I don't
have anything I don't have an interest I
don't have a stake in the
company I'm telling you and you have to
know that this right here is that pure
and that's why I love it so there's no
anti-caking
agents in here like there is everywhere
else and what those are made out of
usually is
corn it's usually made out of corn
powder that's what it's usually made out
of and if it's not corn powder it's
other things
so like I said I don't own vimergy and I
don't have any stake percentage of the
company and so forth but I endorse them
I do and I stand behind them so I'm
going to make this Skin Potion but we're
covering like details about skin and how
it works so I want to show you something
here one way you can keep your skin
healthy is your lymphatic system but
constantly doing lymphatic massage and
lymphatic drainage is just a Band-Aid
just a
Band-Aid now if you have if you're
somebody and you have $150 three times a
week so that's what $300
$450 a week and you're maybe you're
somebody maybe you're um an influencer a
social media influencer and you did good
or whatever it is and you can go and get
your lymphatic drainage three times a
week maybe you're somebody that's really
wealthy and you can spend $500 $700 on
lymphatic drainage go ahead but you're
doing a Band-Aid is what you're doing so
your lymphatic system is involved in
skin okay
it is your lymphatic system holds a lot
of trash and garbage and free radicals
and junk and all of that in there but if
you can't keep your lymphatic systems
immune system strong you're not going to
have a good chance of cleaning out that
lymphatic system and keeping it clean if
you don't take care of your liver and
keep that cleaner you can't keep your
lymphatic system cleaner
either what I love for the lymphatic
system is I love vitamin c not ascorbic
acid though vitamin C so the vimer right
there micro C isn't ascorbic
acid it's buffered and it's not ascorbic
acid scorc acid does not do the job and
taking a lot of it is not easy to do you
end up burning up your intestinal lining
your stomach your dadum and so forth and
that's something also that I find is a
Miracle with the
micro so skin problems let's head and
talk a little bit more about skin issues
and so forth our body tends to push
toxins out through the skin you guys
that's what our body tends to do push
toxins out through the skin one reason
why our body pushes toxins out through
the skin so much is because everybody's
liver yes everybody's liver is
struggling on planet Earth the these
days people are having liver issues and
don't even know it toxic livers from
pesticides herbicides clones perfumes
air fresheners stuff falling out of the
sky Chemtrails falling out of the sky
all the stuff we breathe in all the
stuff we're exposed to every single day
pathogens included and everything else
all in the liver solvents neuro
antagonists Pharmaceuticals all kinds of
stuff gets in the liver and stays in the
liver for an entire lifetime for
somebody when that liver gets clogged up
you're going to be p pushing toxins out
through your skin the problem with
pushing toxins out through your skin and
this is medical Med information right
here
too is that when you're getting all that
sun your that sun is hitting your skin
and it's hitting the
toxins it's kind of cooking the toxins
when you get your and that's not a good
thing I'm not saying don't get sun get
sun but what I'm saying is we have to
clean up our bodies a little bit we have
to clean up our livers we have to clean
up our lymphatic systems through
cleaning up our livers we have to clean
up our bloodstream we don't want dirty
bloodstream we don't want dirty blood
syndrome and people walk around with
dirty blood
syndrome so our skin gets all this crud
in it because we have crud inside the
body and it's all coming up through our
skin the cleaner you are internally the
cleaner your skin gets do you guys hear
that internally the cleaner you are the
cleaner your skin gets less stuff comes
out on your face less stuff comes out on
your skin less stuff you know is is
busting out
everywhere all of it that gets taken
down a notch the cleaner you are if
you're somebody and you're not going to
be able to clean the internal system up
that's okay you can use intense
antioxidant
therapy which is something like a really
high quality vitamin C like
micro and when you're doing that it's
helping your immune system it's helping
restore your immune system the vitamin C
is feeding the immune cells in your
lymphatic system and so forth immune
cells around your liver immune cells
around your skin and you're feeding
those immune cells and they're working
for your
skin free radicals are something
everybody's up against every single day
science was right about free radicals
the concept they didn't really know what
the free radicals were they didn't know
it's dioxins and all kinds of pesticides
herbicides DDT all kinds of radiation
exposure that's another thing too people
get radiation exposure every single day
and don't even know it they're getting
radiation exposure and that's affecting
their skin too it's giving them mild
skin
problems even their devices they're
playing with all the time but what are
you doing to protect yourself and that's
the key and that's why we're talking now
it's how do we help protect your immune
system make it stronger so it protects
your skin how do we rebuild our skin how
do we repair and heal up our skin so
let's make the medical M Skin Potion
right
now so over here Angela over there on
YouTube I've been doing the Skin Potion
every day for 11 months woo the
difference is my in my skin is dramatic
so
Angela thank you for your
comment be bum on YouTube Skin Potion
helped me when I was struggling with
severe healing problems after surgery on
my finger my skin was in very bad
condition and my finger almost had to be
removed I'm sorry you've gone through
that but I'm so glad you're doing the
Skin Potion and you're helping your your
your skin
heal and that's a big deal really big
deal crispy perspective over there on
YouTube your skin was glowing on the red
carpet thank you thank you I do the Skin
Potion Colleen aw your skin was your
skin was glowing dur during Cafe
Gratitude Colleen thank you thank you
for coming
amazing Barb Adler I shook his hand and
it was the softest skin ever why thank
you I have kind of a what is it a you
know I I do a good Shake in the sense
where and someone some but someone had a
stronger hand Shake than I did and they
grabbed my hand so hard and they
squeezed it I was like ow I thought I
had a pretty firm handshake and then
there was I think a couple of people
that really squeezed my hand really hard
there was this one guy I was like I
thought I was going to have a firm
handshake and be like cuz you know like
this with this guy which is really
really awesome um man that showed up and
he squeezed my hand he grabbed it and he
crushed
it and I heard like my knuckle like
literally had it like that that that was
pretty intense
but anyway thanks for saying my skin on
my hand was
soft Jewels over there in IG Skin Potion
is amazing visible difference it can
give you a visible difference for
sure IG over there Hill with Hannah here
with Hannah I have been doing Skin
Potion for a while now and I found it
amazing for my
skin so I'm going to make the Skin
Potion okay okay over there in IG I love
how this potion makes my skin look and
feel incredible Diane over there in IG
thank you for leaving your comments you
guys I want people to feel better about
themselves and what happens is when they
have skin issues it can be devastating
for a lot of people really devastating
now people do get used to it after a
while and they're just like well that's
just the cards I've been dealt with but
it doesn't have to be the cards you were
dealt
with you know I mean I understand that
phrase and that saying it's just it's
the cards I've been dealt with but you
know it doesn't have to be that way when
it comes down to her skin Ashley over
there on IG I have psoriasis and eczema
on my face and I am licensed um
esthetician you are the only thing that
has helped me get my skin back to
Glow that's a compliment that's a
compliment and I want people to know out
there that have skin problems like this
isn't any kind of
[ __ ] because that's what's going on
out there it's just everywhere about
skin it's so tiresome to see I can't
talk about the Skin Potion every single
day I can't I don't have the time I
probably don't have the energy I have so
many moving Parts there's so many things
to do and I've been really working hard
and working hard on some projects for
you guys that I think you're going to be
freaking blown away but I don't have
have I don't have the time to to try to
like change everybody's skin and sit
here and be like an infomercial for skin
I can't I can't do it so I can only once
in a while and this might be the the
last time I do this with the Skin Potion
for who knows how long I just but would
I love to be teaching people would I
love to be messaging the information to
people would I love to be helping
people and with their skin I would love
love love to do that if if you know
somebody spread this information so I I
don't have to work as
hard spread the information so I can I
can keep going and working on some other
things but tell somebody about the
medical medium Skin Potion so they can
get their skin in a better place tell
somebody's friends tell somebody so they
can get their skin in a better place if
you think that's something they want or
you think that's something they need but
yeah so let's make the Skin Potion right
here but the stuff that's out there in
the crap that's out there is disturbing
I think the collagen thing has been
really a total let down is all the
collagen BS about taking collagen and
your skin getting better it's ridiculous
I actually looked at an influenc
recently that somebody brought that
brought uh my attention to and it was
like 12 years ago like 10 years ago or
something they were doing this whole
collagen thing and selling this collagen
right and they were 10 years younger
they look like crap right now I saw them
if that's what their college in
supplement did for them in the last 10
years oh my God I'm not going to say any
names right here but they looked
awful like their skin was torn apart
like it was terrible and I'm like that's
10 years of collegen supplements and not
knowing what heals skin and not know not
knowing what works it's just sad to see
all this stuff like I said I can't sit
here every day and try to try to message
about skin I can't do that Mary over
there on IG
I started it every day one year ago
today and replaced coffee with it I had
a lesion on my leg that was going to get
taken off whoa and it disappeared
completely in about a
month whoa that's incredible