talking about neurological problems
brain issues because let's face it I
don't know if you guys are seeing it but
everybody's brains are going to out
there there's no doubt about it you can
see it out there you can talk to people
out there you can see how things
function or work and everybody's getting
tripped up people's brains are not
functioning like they should I want to
make an announcement before I head into
that I'm also going to talk about Foods
a little bit right Troublemaker Foods
foods that are problematic why they're
problematic you'll see I got assorted
amounts of foods right here in front of
me but I want to make an announcement
the Cafe Gratitude medical medium
collaboration popup dinners for October
22nd October 23rd are sold out they were
sold out before I can even get them out
there the link out there to even make
the announcement so so what happened was
the link leaked out somehow somebody
found it maybe they sleuthed it maybe
they found it somewhere but the link got
out it leaked out because tomorrow I was
going to make the announcement so that
everybody knew about it I Was preparing
everybody look it's going to be tomorrow
and you might want to actually be there
because it's going to be a meet and
greet with me it's going to be an
intimate setting it's just in the
restaurant Cafe Gratitude and I'm going
to be there and it's going to be really
cool it's going to be a lot of great
stuff happening
but I didn't even get a chance to even
go into any of it the link was thrown
around or spread around it got into some
groups or somewhere else and that was it
the tickets were all sold in literally
uh two or 3 minutes or something
ridiculous like that so I just I mean
it's crazy it's actually crazy but it
happened I can't do anything about it
and I feel bad for anybody who is
waiting tomorrow or anybody who's on the
other side of the world and they're
asleep right now so that another thing
too I was a little worried about is that
there's a whole bunch of people that uh
probably would have come that are on the
other side of the world all in bed you
know snoozing and snuggling and they're
going to wake up in the morning their
morning their morning and they're going
to see what happened it's not even being
launched there's no launch or anything
like that lra over there YouTube says no
this is so sad we had we had a launch
link that was going to be used for
tomorrow all these things and it didn't
happen someone got the link and passed
it around and so we had to then release
whatever we had to release that we had
that was for tomorrow but we had to do
it today so anyway that was just what I
wanted to tell you by the way anybody
who did get a ticket for the Cafe
Gratitude medical medium pop-up dinner
is going to be stoked is going to be
totally totally psyched for October 22nd
October 23rd you can join the wait list
though there are weit lists for both
restaurants because it's October 22nd is
one restaurant October 23rd is another
restaurant so it's Cafe Gratitude so
there is a waiting list that's there so
you can hop on that wait list you never
know you might be able to get boom you
might get your your lucky number called
and you're there so it's going to be
really cool there like that but anyway
that's what happened it's shocking
totally shocking I'm I'm in shock
because it happened in seconds like in
seconds like 3 minutes it was just
seconds basically I don't know what it
was like 240 seconds or something like
that and it was all gone that's what it
that's what it seemed like October 15th
though I do want to say this before we
go into brain problems and neurological
issues and everything in foods and stuff
like that as you guys could see we're
going to talk about and I got the brains
saer books right here so this is really
cool before we go into that I just want
to say that this that at Cafe Gratitude
October 15th the medical medium recipes
will be available on the menu at Cafe
Gratitude now that's like you know
that's that's a week or a little bit
more before I'm there for the night for
October 22nd the meet and greet it's
going to be really cool cuz I'm going to
be there in the restaurant with you guys
so anybody who did get a ticket look I
look I hope Cafe Gratitude and medical
medium we do more more of these
collaborations so you'll get your chance
but it's going to be really fun I'm
going to be in in the restaurant with
you in there and
eating and also talking and doing some
other things too and meeting you so it's
really exciting this is really exciting
it's something that I I couldn't wait to
release and launch and I was doing it
tomorrow but like I said before if
you're you know wondering what's going
on or what happened the link escaped
somehow or somebody got the link somehow
they found it and they passed it around
and it was sold out just in a literally
in a second not literally in a second
but three minutes anyway all right so I
want to talk a little bit about
neurological brain and everything and
then I'll just remind everybody in case
somebody comes on and goes what happened
yeah it's it's it's crazy it's
crazy so I'm going to talk about Foods a
little bit but I'm also going to talk
about brain problems because I don't
know if you guys are seeing it out there
right uh um anyway Spirit of compassion
told me back what was it five years ago
four and a half years ago or something
like that that there was going to be
this onslaught of just
deterioration um people getting
chronically ill in so many ways
neurologically and so forth and it was
going to be just quite a ride and that's
where it's heading and it is heading
that way and you'll see me like there's
studies out there like scientist say
that 40% of the people now are have this
or 60% of the people are getting sick
with this this and that they've never
seen anything like it's
unprecedented yeah so you'll see that
you'll see that out there and at the
same time really the reality is it's
more it's more it's more it's more
people are getting sick they're getting
brain sick it is
disturbing it is disturbing a lot of on
a lot of levels because when someone's
brain is getting messed up for some
reason or another we're going to cover
some of those
things it can open the door for anything
all kinds of different problems so it's
toxic heavy metals are really elevating
like nobody's business in people's
brains these days it's a whole another
level right all that and what you'll see
out there is this you'll see this now
right this got popular forever chemicals
forever chemicals pfas or whatever
forever forever you know chemicals
you'll see this whole thing out there
about forever chemicals and you'll see
article after article and people be
talking about it but forever
chemicals yeah it's not something
medical medium information talked a lot
about because that's compared
to what's really in people's brains
that's compared to what people
are really up against and that's
compared to what's really going
on like the reality and real problems
okay so forever chemicals sure that's
not a good thing but you'll see it's the
buzz right now but it's a great
distraction for what's really causing
harm to people's neurological systems
and their brain and their organs and
everything else their other organs and
that's the sad thing but there's always
some kind of hip trendy BS thing going
on and forever chemicals avoid these
foods with forever chemicals avoid these
foods that have this and that in it and
that you know you'll hear that out there
it's like okay great great glad you got
that figured out you're not supposed to
spray crap that's you know on pans and
you know cook your food you know aerosol
cans filled with all kinds of crazy
stuff sure I get it duh but really it's
much bigger than that it's a viral
explosion I've always said it's Plastics
right that's another thing that's been a
problem out there I've always said it's
radiation that's another thing out there
so life-changing Foods I talked about
the viral explosion and the metals and
the radiation right the pesticides like
DDT and everything that are still out
there and they're still using DDT by the
way they're still using it all around
the globe that stuff is like still
backlogged I mean they they have like
warehouses and warehouses filled the DDT
from the 1950s and the
1940s and the 1960s they have so much to
use that they're still unloading it
they're unloading barrels of DBT with
dates on the barrels like 1951 1952 and
they're unloading these and selling them
to you know on the black market to
people they're using it all around the
world they're using it as a pesticide
and insectic side they're using As for
apartment buildings around the world
they're using DDT still and that's how
insane things are so it's like yeah
forever
chemicals yeah blah blah blah I hear
that all the time now it's like you
don't worry about those how about
worrying about all the Mercury and the
lead and the cadmium and the copper
that's going into people's brains and
building up like crazy right now how
about worrying about other things how
about worrying about everybody's zinc
deficiency how about that there zinc
deficiencies are just out totally
outrageous on the level people have zinc
deficiencies and then you know worry
about the viral explosion that's taking
off where people are getting
neurologically sick because of viruses
viral explosion and boom Metals right
those are the two big ones and then of
course there's all these solvents and
all these pesticides and herbicides and
fungicides which are high in metals and
there's all these other different things
that get in people's systems solvents
are a big one right there that's an
antagonist and then Pharmaceuticals
right Pharmaceuticals in water
Pharmaceuticals in food Pharmaceuticals
in everything basically it's in the air
it's in pole water if you go swimming
it's in the beach Pharmaceuticals are
floating everywhere now and that's
another thing on its own but either way
there's a lot of different different
things that are getting into us and
creating that dirty blood syndrome which
creates a dirty liver which creates a
you know a dirty brain which creates all
of this and we end up in trouble so
there's lots to talk about here um you
know as far as the hip stuff that's out
there which they're trying to shove down
people's throats forever chemicals is
one of them the other one is HPV they're
trying to actually say basic basically
with HPV they're trying to say well HPV
that's a cancer-causing virus that
creates cancer it's interesting because
they're using medical Med information
that I put out there about epine bar and
so forth creating cancer and they're
using that information but they don't
have the science to back it up so this
is pretty crazy so it's like oh HPV
causes all kinds of throat cancer causes
all kinds of cancers because it gets
into it invades the tissue creating you
know de demented C
uh really because it's medical medium
information that's all about viruses
creating damaged cells which in turn
creates cancerous cells I published
articles about it I put it in the books
I lectured about it before the books but
now science all of a sudden what they
just went to Medical medium again they
just took well let's just pluck this out
now this sounds great let's just start
saying how HPV creates cancer it's like
where's your science though when you
really dig into it they don't have it
they've never seen HPV even create a
cancer can saw that's how sick that is
but they take the information and
they're now applying my Epstein bar
information about Epstein bar and other
viruses creating cancer cells and now
they take that and they now take it put
it to HPV even though they have no signs
to show it it's actually disturbing but
that's how it works out there so
um but yes if you talk to people enough
or you look into things or you're just
looking for help somewhere some services
or you You' got errands to run or you
didn't you talk to somebody here or you
talk to somebody there you'll notice
that things aren't working like they
used to preco era pre right four years
ago pre five years ago you'll notice
things aren't the same you'll notice
people making mistakes like a ton of
mistakes that's what people do they're
making lots of mistakes because their
brains aren't working good have you
noticed it have you noticed it yet a
whole bit their brains aren't working
like they should some mistakes are
happening all the time
and people are not functioning like they
should and that's happening right there
yep Dr fa they take medical Med
information warp it to fit their agenda
very
true very correct right there so I'm
going to read just a couple of things
first of all I'm talking about chronic
illness as well you know chronic fatigue
syndrome neurological fatigue that's a
big one right there you know for years
and years and years it was all about
people being tired you know yeah you're
tired you just you're depressed that's
why you're tired tired you're depressed
that's why you're tired it's like no I'm
not depressed I don't want yeah I am
depressed because I'm T I'm not
depressed no I'm depressed now because
I'm tired I can't function for 6 months
but I wasn't depressed before I got
tired but now I'm tired every day and I
can't function so now I am depressed so
the confusion is there that happens all
the time to people it's like no you're
depressed you need an anti-depressant
need anti-anxiety meds and
anti-depressants that's why you're tired
but really what's happening is people
have so many problems in their brain
their brain stem problems in their brain
stem problems with their cranial nerves
they're inflamed they're inflamed
because of metals and viruses those are
the two big boys right there JS says yes
I work in Bakery and it's a Biz it's
bizarre how much brain fog there is not
only that but there's also a lot of
arrogance and entitlement coupled with
it
entitlement entitlement that's a fun one
right there enti entitlement is
definitely out there there's no question
about that I've talked about entitlement
a little bit you know there's in people
who have gone after medical medium with
lies and all kinds of other stuff they
were highly entitled so many people are
that entitlement thing is just crazy I
know I know it's true though it's a
level of like brain fog but it's a level
of entitlement with it crispy
perspective they repeat the wrong
numbers can't remember things oh my God
it pre
2019 pre-2020 it wasn't like that they
repeat the wrong numbers can't remember
things can't read info correctly can't
spell get brain fog Etc crispy
perspective that's exactly what's
happening out there sure there was
always a little bit about that little
bit of that out there okay keep that in
mind there's always a little bit of that
out there pre 2019 pre-2020 there was
there just was there brain fog out there
of course I mean there's sick brains
there's people that aren't well but it
exploded exploded Parkinson boom on the
rise right Ms On The Rise Parkinson's On
The Rise all the different you know
memory loss Alzheimer's dementia all on
the rise but it's even more than that
it's like this person doesn't have
Alzheimer's but this person just got the
numbers wrong right there and then they
put it in the computer and boom they
just ruined your life and now you're
calling that you know blah blah blah hey
that's not that's not what happened
identity theft or this and it whatever
it is you know the craziest stuff's
happening because people are misplacing
numbers and information that you're you
know you need services for whatever
you're doing and they're you're using
private information and you're giving it
to them and they just put it in the
wrong category or the wrong place and
then it gets out there it's crazy what's
happening um it really is Katie over
here on YouTube Says Yes actually now
that he says that people do do seem to
make a lot of mistakes oh like it's
unbelievable to the degree like things
don't go smoothly anywhere sometimes I
wonder how the world is still
functioning seriously Katie that is
exactly what's happening now it is
getting worse it was worse it was bad a
year ago it was bad two years ago now
it's absurdly insanely bad like it is so
bad now but what are we going to do
about it probably nothing it's just
getting worse and worse and worse but I
want you to be able to protect yourself
so you're not falling into that category
of people where mistakes are being made
and everything else is happening like
that so yeah so you you live a good life
and you can think clear and you can
function and you can you know you can
see other people messing up left and
right because their brain isn't working
but at Le at least yours is working and
you see it I'd rather have you on that
end I want to be on that end I want to
be on the end of like my brain's working
yeah and that is good end to be on and
then I want to be there and then I want
to be on the end where you know I'm
seeing everybody mess up it sucks I
don't want to see people mess up but I'd
rather be where I am now like you guys
and then see other people just screwing
up every second because their brain
isn't working I don't want to be
somebody who's losing their mind and
that's what's happening out there um
because it's
true the medical medum heavy metal detox
is critical to protect people it just is
that's a fact it just is it's critical
to help people and protect them it's in
the it's in the medical medium brains
saer books right here okay it's in there
and you know it's important to take care
of your brain so let's talk about Foods
a little bit before we get into some
illnesses let's do that okay
so what you see in front of me is just
some foods okay you got a cheeseburger
right here you got a pizza right there
you got I think a meatball wedge
meatball wedge you got a steak and
cheese right there steak and cheese got
some eggs over here if you see that got
a nice big hero right here a big hogy
big wedge grinder whatever you call it
whatever you want to call it or whatever
it's called somewhere right so you got
that there too but what you're seeing in
here sure our foods that you might not
eat you might not be out there eating
these Foods tomorrow you might not be
eating maybe you never even you you like
the hero right there and so you may not
be eating these okay but there's things
in these foods that you may be eating
though in some other food keep that in
mind you might be like I haven't had a
meatball wedge in 20 years so this
excludes me aw oh it's not really about
the meatball wedge it's about the egg in
the meatball it's about the cheese on
the meatball wedge it's about these
things right it's about the
oil that was used in that meatball wedge
it's about the gluten in the bread
crumbs that were were used in the
meatballs cuz you know a lot of people
do meatballs they put there's
breadcrumbs put into the meatballs right
and there's eggs put into the meatballs
and so forth but there's eggs and gluten
and then there's Dairy and it's these
Foods right here that are problematic
for so many reasons one big reason is
those Foods feed feed bugs bugs that eat
people alive over time so bugs love
things like Dairy and they love the
proteins and eggs and they love the
gluten they love the feed off of gluten
bugs love these kinds of foods and so
it's key to actually know hey look these
aren't good foods and it's not good to
get canola oil in your system do you
know I started talking about canola oil
being bad for people in the 80s how
crazy is that in the80s canola oil is
bad everybody thought I was crazy to say
canola oil is bad it was like what are
you talking about canola oil and then
now you need got to worry about the
canola oil and olive oil mixes out there
that's a big deal is the mix of canola
oil and olive oil it's everywhere so
what we're allowed to do here is we're
allowed to take uh olive oil mix it with
a little bit of canola oil and call it
just olive oil that's how it works here
now so that's the rules and that's a
scary place to be and but it's the rules
now as long as the percentage of canola
oil is less than the olive oil maybe
even a lot less than the olive oil and
you make a mix right there predominantly
as long as you know you got the olive
oil there and the majority is the olive
oil you can call it olive oil not Olive
and canola you don't have to put canola
on the ingredient list on the bottle
canola oil is
damaging damaging to the intestinal
tract to the liver it's not a good oil
to have people eat that all the time and
don't even know it's in all these salad
dressings it's in lots of condiments
canola oil is infiltrated in all of
these condiments out there you got to
worry about it something to keep in mind
right these things matter these little
things matter I know people want to live
their lives they want to be in Bliss
they don't want any rules they don't
want any concerns they don't want to get
depressed about food or about what
they're eating they don't want to be sad
or anything like that and feel like
they're being restrictive I get it I get
it but if you're sick you got to do
something about it bottom line before
the medical medium books the health
movement thought canola oil was good
even though aw was out there screaming
how bad it was the health movement
thought canol oil was not just good but
freaking great the health movement
believed it was great not just great
excellent for you that's what the health
movement believed before medical medium
books medical medium books got out there
put the information out there even
stronger and much more aggressive in
this sense where it got around the world
because thank God I got a publisher to
to stand behind medical medium
information and to stand behind the
medical medium book books an amazing
publisher at that Hay House I don't know
if you guys know about Hay House
phenomenal best publisher I believe at
the world hands down and they backed the
medical medium they took the they took
the medical media manuscripts and they
put it out there
worldwide millions of man millions of
copies of the books got out there in
people's hands thanks to the publisher
changed the world of Health all the way
around
that's these babies right here okay and
people then the health movement shifted
and canola oil was now bad so in the
health movement canola oil became a bad
thing all right I want to read a couple
cool things I want to read this little
section right here page
93 uh brain saver right there it's
called toxin clouded emotions
interesting right so's information
everyday toxins and poisons inside the
brain are a large part of the brain
limitations we experience brain
limitations from toxins and poisons in
the brain did you know the health
movement didn't really even like I mean
the conventional Health movement didn't
even use the word toxin it was
ridiculous most of the health movement
didn't even touch the word toxin it was
crazy everyday toxins and poisons inside
the brain are a large part of the brain
limitations we experience including
emotional limitations so emotional
limitations so someone could be seeing
their psychiatrist they can be seeing
their therapists they could be seeing
their coaches and they're just they're
just like unloading so much so much just
suffering and pain and confusion and
depression and anxiety issues and
everything else are unloading unloading
unloading but really what's happening is
there's limitations emotionally because
the brain is so overburdened with junk
and garbage in there and lotss of
different you know things in there if an
area of the brain is clouded with an
abundant level of poisons and toxins
ranging from toxic heavy metals to
solvents to Plastics and other
petrochemicals to Pharmaceuticals to air
fresheners fragrances scented candles
and Beyond CTIC candles you everybody's
freaking out about vaping out there
they're freaking out all the time now
you see horror stories about vaping
people know vaping is just terrifying
it's so bad for so many people people
know this out there you know
they know it's gotten bad The Vaping
thing destroys your lungs causes
problems people get injured by it and
everything else scented candles are
vaping that's a level of vaping it's
scented candles I remember when I first
started hitting the whole fragrances
really hard and the scented candles
everybody was just screaming at me like
all you care about is scented candles
and fragrances what's wrong with you
medical medium putting fear at us about
scented candles
yeah it's that bad scent to candles are
that bad and then people are taking it
now right taking that information you'll
see somebody pop up on Tik Tok like Tik
Tok like fragrances the sending candles
are bad mhm yeah sure yep they
are so people have all that stuff the
area of the brain that gets clouded up
with these brain betrayers like sended
candles and air fresheners clones and
perfumes and metals which sit inside of
all those things I just said the bra
brain the emotional Center of that of
your brain gets actually all kind of
clogged up with that we're going to have
a trouble and we're going to be in big
trouble when emotional centers of the
brain become filled up and clouded with
toxins and poisons we become more
reliant on other parts of our brain so
it's another thing that happens so as
the emotional you ever run into somebody
that's just like so numb emotionally
though they're emotional in some ways
but they're so numb they're just numb
with seeing like somebody else's
emotions are what they're going through
they're just numb in general they seem
like they're really really self-absorbed
and they're wallowing in their own
suffering and pain and everything but
really they're just like they're numbed
out and numb that means the emotional
centers of the brain got so clogged up
and so clouded up with toxins and
poisons to such a degree that they're
now using other parts of their brain
they're using other parts of the brain
which means that they just they're not
connecting at all to that person in any
way it's not possible instead they're
just you know off here
instead so um we'll go into a little bit
more of this
right we can become Limited in getting
in touch with our own emotional state
and that's another thing
depersonalization so let's go into
depersonalization a little bit I mean
you guys know anybody who suffered with
depersonalization or maybe are suffering
with
depersonalization that's a big one out
there that's getting worse too every
single condition that I can say is like
this now up there versus down here
depersonalization boom that's how many
more people are actually suffering with
that it's incredible what's happening so
the personalization is a big one so when
the emotional centers of the brain are
getting clouded up with poisons and
toxins and metals and all of that then
we get disconnected toxins and poisons
clogging the emotional centers of brain
can also mean that we become extremely
emotional without understanding why so
then we're having a burst or an episode
or we get triggered easy how many people
you know get triggered easy because the
emotional centers of the brain are so
poisoned up they're so clogged up with
so much different stuff right how many
people you know get triggered so easily
emotionally and it's like boom they're
in an episode they're triggered boom and
they're there like easily there how many
people do you know so many people go
through that because there's that much
junk and garbage inside the emotional
centers of the brain causing somebody to
be like this is Lightning Fast triggered
in the moment an episode can hit out of
nowhere or they're just completely
numbed out disconnected with
depersonalization but even people with
depersonalization you guys end up boom
into sometimes like the deep end with a
trigger then now they're just oh
everything's just coming out
everything's just rolling out right you
guys it's just unbelievable what's
happening there's people out there like
that where they're numb they're numb
they're numb they're numb and then all
of a sudden they're off the deep end and
everything is just dumping out and
they're just in such a place they're in
such a place with it all so that's
something to to think about right there
too on IG right there okay every day
okay so let's see loving healing says
I'm a medical doctor I'm me sure a
medical
coder read notes every day and most
people have memory issues mental health
problems Barkin in it's terrible yeah
most people do and it's getting worse
and worse and worse
oh my God it's just it's sad what's
happening out there um thank you for
that comment by the way all right formed
by Nature over there in IG says why did
they release the tickets a day early the
email said tomorrow to register what
happened okay here's what happened okay
we were all set to launch the Cafe
Gratitude medical medium collaboration
tomorrow we were all set to launch it
tomorrow had my whole team working on it
they were killing themselves I kid you
not like like working hard on it right
they have been all week and so forth and
then what happened was we were all set
to do it for tomorrow and we were
mentioning CA gratitude collaboration
and all of it I mean you know a big part
of my team was doing it and then out of
nowhere someone somehow got a hold of
the link that was supposed to be put in
the email and released tomorrow they got
a hold of it today and then they passed
it around in all the groups and
everywhere and then things just went
haywire and it went crazy I mean it's
mindblowing really how it happened and
what happened but it's also going to
upset some people let's just be honest
there it's going to upset a few people
that were waiting for tomorrow looking
out for tomorrow like I said before
there are people sleeping on the other
side of the world right now asleep and
they're going to wake up tomorrow and
they're going to be like what happened
what happened and so the link basically
got out someone somehow sleuthed it and
they found it or they found it somewhere
yeah it's it's something like
that making peace with our healing
timeline I want to talk about healing
timelines right here too a little bit
because neurological problems and brain
problems don't go away fast for a lot of
people they don't Parkinson's does not
go away in a day for people people who
do medical M information can get rid of
their Parkinson how many people reverse
their Parkinson with medical medum
information a lot of people okay so um
but does it happen in a day no it
doesn't you can see results in a day
believe it or not just by bringing in
some of the tools but getting rid of it
completely in a day will never
happen
so conditions like
Parkinson's or any kind of neurological
condition and that's another problem too
on all on its own you may not be
diagnosed with Parkinson's
you may not be diagnosed as um dementia
Alzheimer's you may not be di diagnosed
to something like that but you got all
these other different symptoms and you
didn't even know they're neurological
people out there have so many
neurological symptoms like aches and
pains tingles and numbness dizziness and
vertigo and floaters in the eyes
neurological migraines
neurological gum pain that's
unexplainable jaw pain unex explainable
neological PL this in the chest okay a
funny feeling of butterflies all the
time in the stomach anxiety depression
bipolar depersonalization OCD tourettes
neurological so many people have
different forms and versions of all of
this ADHD add and they have all of this
neurological stuff fatigue debilitating
fatigue okay weak arms weak limbs weak
fingers numb fingers numb toes
restless leg syndrome insomnia all
neurological the list goes on and on and
on so I want to talk about U making
peace with our healing timeline I want
people to know you can heal and you will
heal you got to stay on track okay doing
the best you can and you can move
forward and adopt these tools bring them
into your life get them into your
Consciousness use your free will to
apply them and heal and move forward and
heal so I want to talk about making
peace with our healing timeline a little
bit when we get sick we start to track
the timeline did you ever run into
anybody who tracks the timeline did you
track the timeline I talked about this
before but it's really important it's
pertinent right now to talk about for a
lot of reasons because that many more
people are getting sick every day when
we get sick we start to track the
timeline everybody okay we count the
days we've been sick maybe even the
hours a lot of people will count hours
believe it or not we count the weeks the
months and eventually if it lasts that
long and we're sick that long we count
the years that's something we do when
we're sick that is definitely something
people do when they're sick it's like
instantly it's like I got sick on this
date I got sick that week I got sick
that month and I've been sick for 5
years people do
it okayy
over there on YouTube aw what tea are
you drinking I'm drinking a lemon bomb
tea right here but it's not just a lemon
bomb tea it also has a shot of a couple
of things in there it's got a shot of
guess what it's got a shot shot of the
vigy propolis I put in my lemon bomm tea
as you can see right there it's The Vig
propolis one of the most profound
profound I mean right there is that prop
is cure it's incredible anyway you guys
know you guys know that it fully endorse
mgy but anyway I have that in there but
this is my lemon balm tea with propolis
in
there I love the way that tastes by the
way something happens to us emotionally
when remember when we remember the month
we got sick the time of
year something that connects with that
and it sticks with us so if you were
sick a year ago in September it sticks
with you and then When September Comes
Around again it's like boom right
there's this connection that happens
okay the beautiful thing about ever all
of this is when you start healing you
remember when you started to heal and
you remember the month you started to
heal and you start remembering and then
that starts to wash over so many
emotions so many different references
and memories of when you got sick right
it starts to take over that healing
process starts to just be this bright
light it's such a beautiful thing many
of us remember the people we were around
when we first got
sick that's a big one right there some
of you like well I was with my
ex-boyfriend I was with my ex-girlfriend
I was with my ex-wife I was with my
husband I was with my friend I was on a
trip I was on a vacation I went and took
a trip to India I took a trip to you
know the UK whatever it is people
remember many of us remember the people
we were around when we first got sick
the places we were the jobs we were
doing the commitments do you remember
the job you were doing when you got sick
do you remember if there was a job you
had when you got sick that happens all
the time too especially when people lose
their jobs and lose their careers when
they get sick they remember that the
commitments we had on our plate time
plays a large role in our emotional
brain it's as if our emot emotional
brain is directly connected to time sure
we worry about time on a daily basis
even when we're not sick or struggling
our responsibilities and plans are based
around time everything's based around
time yet something changes when we're
sick we see time differently we start
saying it's time to get better you get
sick it's time to get better and you can
get better I want to tell you that right
now this is really important to know you
can get better remember that hold on to
that keep that in your heart and keep
that in your soul you can get better
don't forget that that's Inc so
important right I want to just go
through this a little bit and I want to
talk about shock therapies and in some
other incredible
tools something changes when we get sick
we see time differently we start saying
it's time to get better or it's about
time I'm feeling better or we hear it's
due time time you'll get better it's due
time I get better it's about time I get
better it's time right now to get better
keep that in mind time is such a large
aspect of illness because if we're sick
we feel like we lost time we're losing
out okay so if you guys know if you've
been sick and I know a lot of you have
been sick and struggling you've risen
out of the ashes you
know you know that it feels like it's
lost time when you're sick so many
things you could have done so many
places you could have gone right and so
many people have healed and they have
gone to the medical medium events right
they've done that recently there's
people there that were sick for years
couldn't travel couldn't do anything and
now all of a sudden you're traveling and
they were there which is mindblowing all
on its
own right time feels like it passes by
us at the start it doesn't feel us
threatening emotionally yeah I've been
sick for a week I've been sick for 2
weeks the hands of time start to feel
heavy when it goes on too long you're
not quite better you're not you're even
getting worse and now time becomes
doctor appointments and your care
schedule time is about how much energy
you have how much space you have around
your illness to do what you need to do
life can change when you're sick causing
restrictions making us feel everything
is so difficult we have to slow
down and when you heal and when you
start healing
everything just speeds
up everything just moves forward it's as
if you're bypassing time is as if you're
moving past time and moving ahead of
time as you're healing it's an
incredible experience incredible feeling
healing the feeling of healing itself
you know what that feels like you know
when wait a minute I'm actually better
than I was wait a minute that symptoms
calming down wait a minute it's
intermittent now instead of being all
the time wait a minute something's
changing something's happening I'm
healing I'm moving forward that's a
feeling that's an experience that is so
beautiful so amazing all on its own and
you can feel that experience if you
haven't yet you will feel that
experience if you haven't yet keep that
in mind you'll get in touch with that
experience and that feeling of I am
healing and I am moving on medical Med
information does that it heals people
that could have never gotten healed
anywhere else it heals people that were
so wounded and so bad off from years of
being sick and had no options anymore
and they lost hope and it healed them
medical meme information moves people
forward gets people out of wheelchairs
gets them walking again gets them
exercising and working out again even in
the gym or whever they want to work out
or taking hikes and walks it gets them
back into life you could be in that
position and get there you can
our emotional brain puts due dates on
things just like past due dates on our
recovery I have to heal before this date
I have to heal before next week I have
to heal before my next birthday I have
to heal before my pet's next birthday I
have to heal before you know something
or some event or something happen so we
put timelines and we put dates on it and
there's nothing wrong with that we can
do that okay
okay Tina says what page are you on on
Facebook page 94 of brains saver do you
have brain saver I'm on page 94 it's an
incredible
book if you have this you know like what
this book is
definitely our emotional brain wants us
to be healed by a certain time be
healed on a certain
time our emotional brain
wants us to be
healed it does it
does and it will shout it in the middle
of the night when we're sleeping our
emotional brain will get us into a dream
where we feel like we're healing in the
dream or we think we're healed in the
dream a lot of people
dream different ways when they're sick
when they're really sick they dream of
being sick sick and how difficult it is
but they also dream of moments when they
weren't sick and they were strong and
they felt good and they have dreams
where they felt good and they were
living their life and they wake up from
the dream and they're like I'm not there
yet that was in the past that was it
that's not now so so many people dream
the feelings of like where they were L
over there on YouTube can neurological
symptoms get worse as soon as getting on
an anti viral protocol with propolis and
cats
claw keep in mind right get a journal
out what did I do did I push it too hard
as I was trying to heal you got to look
at all these things did I get some
gluten in my system while I was trying
to heal did I get some Dairy did I get
some eggs in something that I ate
recently did I get corn in something
that I ate recently did I get soy in
something that I ate recently kind of
kind of Journal these things up right
get a little bit of a of a journal
together and put it together what did I
eat yesterday what did I eat the day
before what did I eat tomorrow what's
happening emotionally am I under a lot
of emotional stress am I getting support
from my family or is my family against
me am I getting support from my friends
or my friends against me did something
happen with my boyfriend did something
happen with my girlfriend keep in mind
that there's so many things that can
happen emotionally that can kick us down
a notch we're like boom so we're trying
to get up and we're getting kicked down
did I catch C you know did I catch like
you know what I mean did I catch the flu
did I catch something and I was sick for
a few weeks ago and now my neurological
problems are worse but really it's
because you're recovering from Co or
you're recovering from the flu three
weeks ago or a month ago because what
happens when people get a flu they get a
cold whatever you want to call it and
you're you're you're blowing out snot
and you're you're coughing and
everything else and now you're
recovering you're recovering there's
this weird lag time response that
happens there's this wake that happens
and now your neurological problems a
month later are down here a little bit
could have been when you started some
cats claw around that area you started
some cats claw do your due diligence
make sure you're looking at everything
you can a lot of people are so sick
right now from pathogens going around
right now they are bed RDS keep that in
mind right
now people are bedridden because of the
flu and the cids that are actually going
around right now it's bad right now like
today and next month the month after
that there's some bugs go it around
right so people can actually kind of
hold on to those they catch it they hold
on to it they're coughing they're just
you know doing their thing and then they
get dragged down a little bit with
neurological problems it becomes a
trigger so check that out too like in
your life and your references and go
back into your journal and look and then
Foods that's important too okay Foods
matter if you're feeding something
that's creating your neurological
problem what are you feeding your
neurological problem which is meaning
like neurological viruses neurological
pathogens what are you feeding you know
those pathogens is it the foods that are
creating more trouble creating more
neurotoxins or anything like that what
are you doing did you stop your celery
juice have you even drank your celery
juice what's you know all these things
play a role while you're trying to heal
so you might be doing some propis and
then you're having a down cycle but
propolis can't create a down cycle
that's how it works cats Cola can't
create a a down cycle propolis can't
create a down cycle so what's happening
in your life examine it take a look and
see what's going on or were you already
getting sick and thank God you're doing
the propolis or whatever you're doing
you know and did you have a medical
treatment did you have something else
out there did you have an x-ray did you
have radiation exposure didn't know it
did you get a pesticide drift hit hits
you from the apartment building next
door from somebody spraying it guy had a
mask on he was just spraying it like
this all in the yard you got to look at
everything but you got to also have
faith and trust in the tools but you got
to look at everything else you have to
it's important to look at everything
else but no propolis does not cause a
down cycle propolis is one of well wait
a minute well what kind of propolis
who's propolis that all stuff is there
alcohol in it is there junk in it what
kind of that's a whole whole another
game all on its own you know a lot of
people don't know about a good propolis
they don't know about like say vimer
propolis or something else they just
they have no
idea but it's a good question and keep
the questions coming
in if you have hyper
sensitivities your nerves become hyper
sensitive keep that in mind anything can
also rock the boat a chemtrail can rock
the boat one day anything can the heat
index can rock the boat exercising one
day you know you're doing a sweat and
everything you're a little dehydrated
that can rock the boat maybe you're not
hydrating enough so many people don't do
enough for themselves are you drinking
coconut water you drinking celery juice
listen to the chemical sensitivity and
food sensitivity podcasts on medical
mean podcast at Apple podcast everybody
wants to heal can I read this little
spot for you guys everybody wants to
heal nobody does doesn't want to
heal no one wants to be sick or suffer
emotionally no one is afraid of healing
no one has a fear of healing that's
secretly holding on that's secretly
holding them back from getting better
nobody is being held back because they
have a fear of healing keep that in mind
because I'm seeing it more and more
about manifestation out there and you
know look I'm I'm not out there to just
rip into people I've been I've you know
it's not my thing to just rip into
people like that where like manif if I
don't like you know
manifestation or something like that
it's not that I don't like manifestation
it's just
that it's
like if someone's sitting there and they
got a virus and the virus is creating
chronic fatigue syndrome and the brain
is swelling and they got Amy you know
CFS and they can't even driving a car
and they're just falling apart it's like
manifestation is not something I'm
worried about I'm worried worried about
getting that virus killed off killing
that
virus getting the body would it needs to
fight that virus getting them recovered
and if you want to play in manifestation
land after that you can play in
manifestation land all you want I just
want you better you know what I mean
it's like and that's the problem when
manifestation kind of crawls into crawls
into the chronic illness world it's a
tricky tricky blend you know the
manifestation movement was really
originally about people that weren't
sick at all they just weren't sick there
was lesser numbers of people being sick
it was for people who were just you know
they wanted more in their life and they
wanted good things to happen and it's
fun right and people can believe in it
and work with that right but the
manifestation thing flung into the
chronically ill world and then made
everybody in the chronic illness World
think they manifested their sickness
that's where the problem went it's not
that I personally
you know can't tolerate or disagree or
hate manifestation that's not it at all
manifestation mixed into the chronic Leo
world like a big bag of nuts mixed up
and what happened was it was like a lot
of leaders and manifestation that would
say you're the reason why you're sick
you created it you did this to yourself
you wish this upon yourself you
manifested this now you got to manifest
out of this sickness and a lot of people
who chronic leil and sick are trying to
manifest out out of the sickness but
they're not getting better how come
they're trying to manifest them then
they all of a sudden hate themselves
they all of a sudden doubt themselves
and they hate themselves because they're
like wait a minute I can't even manifest
properly here I am bedridden on couch
Island and and Mattress Island and
obviously I must have created this
because everybody else who's manifesting
such good things are doing great things
out there and they're fine I'm bedridden
so I'm trying to manifest myself out of
this but I can't seem to so I'm a
failure even more not only did I create
my sickness and illness manifesting the
wrong way or whatever it was that
created this I am now a failure because
I can't get out of it and I'm sick and I
must have done this to myself and I
created it for myself that's demented
and that's sick not the person who
thinks that but the manifestation laws
that have been thrown upon the
chronically ill in the last five six
years seven years and just eight years
and I've watched that happened where it
was like a storm coming over The Chronic
leil
like the manifestation
storm and the chronically old people
these poor people suffering and
struggling sick for 10 15 years and it's
just like mixed just you know boom piled
on top of them everybody was like I must
have created this I must be sick because
I must have manifested it I must have
made this happen and it's sad no you got
sick because of other reasons you got
sick because of yeah epine bar shingles
cyega virus you got sick because hhb6
you got sick because herpes simplex one
and two you got sick because of strep
you got sick because of toxic heavy
metals you got sick because of all these
solvents and pharmaceutical poisons and
all this other stuff that got into your
body and yeah you didn't help yourself
out by not knowing what to eat and you
were eating things that you probably
should have been eating and you're
seeing some of that right here right and
you're seeing that here sure sure but
you you know you didn't know you're just
eating to survive you're just eating to
try to just get through another day it's
not your fault but either
way you got sick along the way because
of all these other reasons and maybe it
was emotional stress adding to it maybe
it was emotional abuse adding to it and
maybe you got injured in many ways
emotionally and abused emotionally and
that packed on to the mercury poisoning
and all the other vital issues and now
you're really sick and now you got every
symptom in the book and then
manifestation comes along like we got
the answers for everything you just have
to manifest it and get yourself out
that's all it really is you know and
then and then whoa you're sick because
that you caused that that's your problem
20 doctors you saw that they didn't they
don't know you know why you're sick you
don't have the answer so you must have
manifested this or it's all in your
head and that's that's what I don't
like there's also a trusting wire within
us that's been taking advantage of by
Industries this has created a
brainwashing within us a me mechanism
inside us that wants permission to do
harmful things to
ourselves people want permission to do
harmful things to themselves this the
desire for health is so strong inside us
that we'll try to look for answers about
why anything that's harmful could be
good for us I just saw an article that
somebody sent me a friend sent me there
an article about once again red wine red
red wine is good for
you red wine is good for you that I just
saw that again the red wine is good for
you it was unbelievable once again I saw
this again chocolate is good for
you chocolate is good for you black tea
is good for you green tea is good for
you sure you know you believe that when
you're chronic Leo with a neurological
problem you're just going to go like
this black tea chocolate coffee red
wine you're going to be down there is
where you're going to be yeah it's
amazing but you'll see that right you'll
see it just saw another like somebody
sent me that article and it's like here
it is this is good for you that's good
for you this is good for you it's like
no if you're sick with chronic illness
bad for you bad for you bad for you bad
for you will destroy your life bad for
you especially if you do too much of it
like too much of it too much of it
medical medum information out there only
only used chocolate for a couple of
things one is to get people off of
heroin it was a tool to get people off
of
of cigarettes to use chocolate like a
really high quality cacao to get you off
of cigarettes so medical me information
throughout the years and I used to try
to help people they used to come to my
office throughout the
decades and and spirit of compassion
said chocolate's not good for somebody
who's chronically ill chocolate will not
help their adrenals chocolate will
destroy their adrenals CH chocolate will
do all these things if they regularly
eat it but Spirit of compassion said
it's either that or the heroin kills
them it's either that or the other drug
kills them it's either that or they
can't get off of smokes it's either that
or if they can't get now they can't get
off of vape and you there's a way to use
it as a leverage until they can get off
of something that's literally killing
them fast to get them all of a sudden on
something that you know is you know much
less
aggressive theah says over there in
YouTube he has a podcast about using
chocolate for
addiction I forgot about that
everybody wants to
heal everybody wants to
heal so I'm talking about the trusting
wire so I want to go a little bit more
into this is really good okay right here
all right the desire for health is so
strong inside of us that we'll try to
look for answers about why anything
that's harmful could be good for us like
wine red wine my God if I see that one
more time one more
time it's almost like
that's almost like a demon in the
industry it's like haaha another three
years went by people forget let's put it
out there one more time red wine is good
for you three years go by four years go
by it gives permission to people
permission to drink more red wine and
kill their liver or whatever they're
going to do right it's not helping them
out and then a demon comes out again and
puts it out the industry and it's just a
demon industry says red wine is good for
you again and does it all over again so
people in their are like you know after
they've destroyed their health you know
in universities and college and drank
themselves practically to death and
they're trying to recover all of a
sudden they hear a demon out there in
the industry say red wine is good for
you so they go back to drinking red wine
and they think it's good for them they
drink it when they're pregnant they
drink it when they're two weeks pregnant
three weeks pregnant they just whatever
they're drinking it and they're just
back to you know doing something stupid
again and then when they get past it and
they realize the red wine is making them
bloated and sick and not good and
they're getting sick a demon in the
industry comes out again and puts out
another article and says red wine is
good for you it it's almost like a
massive trick that's it's
unbelievable we want validation that
hurting ourselves is actually good for
us this can make it seem as if
self-sabotage is part of our innate
emotional nature as if we want to harm
ourselves when we really don't we don't
want to harm ourselves we don't and our
soul is saying don't harm me don't harm
me we don't self-sabotage because we
want to make ourselves sick we
definitely don't want to do it to make
ourselves sick that's for sure we
self-sabotage because we're taught to
self-sabotage we're conditioned to
self-sabotage we're practically bred to
self-sabotage do you know anybody who
self- sabotages throughout the years you
guys know anybody who self- sabotages
we're actually conditioned we're taught
we're bred to self- sabotage you guys
know this this book is insanely
incredible by the way I have not read
the Brain saer book in a while and I'm
reading through it right now I have not
like read through this so's information
just blows me
away check out this little part here
alternative medicine Cults interesting
alternative medicine Cults as well as
top feeders and Bottom Feeders of the
health industry are always catering to
the self-sabotage
brainwashing you'll see it with all the
shock and all out there oh Tik Tock
restricted me again I must be saying
something so
terrible and they're of often using
their credentials to manipulate our
trust I see that out there they create
their own social media channels and give
their five tips in 15 minutes in those
five tips you always you'll always find
at least one recommendation that
provides validation and reassurance for
self- sabotage remember that in all the
Articles just like I was just saying
just now someone sent me that you always
see those five tips or 15 tips or 10
tips or eight tips and you always find a
couple in there that are like feeding to
people's self- sabotage coffee's now
good for you right espresso now good for
you four espresso a day good for you now
says
scientists you know whatever it is
right a big part of the self-sabotage
brainwashing is that we become
programmed to seek validation at doing a
harmful thing and moderation is
perfectly fine which leads us into the
moderation game all on its
own moderation is a big one you guys
it's always like oh how a little this
and a little that moderation is always
good you'll see moderation come and go
and come and go over and over and over
again um I want to go into a couple
different protocols in here by the way
good information in here I want to show
you the protocols all right incredible
information in here so in this book
Brain saver right here you have a whole
bunch of different neurological diseases
and conditions and symptoms and it talks
about what the causes are to that
neurological disease condition or
symptom which is incredible all on its
own I want to go to page 20 you guys
have this book right here brainsaver
protocols
okay one thing about s so is answers to
move people forward and heal
them moving people forward to Healing
it's not just about the information that
we can learn to heal with that's one big
piece of it then it's the tools that's
another one so if you got your book
let's go to page
20 on page 20 this is incredible
information all on its own right here
and I love this part of the book medical
medium shock therapies from Spirit of
compassion incredible right here in page
20 it says you'll find that some of the
supplement protocols in the next chapter
call for optional shock
therapies medical medium zinc shock
therapy medical medium vitamin C shock
therapy medical medium lemon bomb shock
therapy I'm doing lemon balm
tea that's so
good medical medium golden seal shock
therapy always check with your doctor
take your take your book to the doctor I
always tell people you know take your
medical medium protocols book to the
doctor and say what do you think about
this get your doctor's permission get
your doctor's
thoughts medical medium golden seal
shock therapy I can't tell you how many
uh friends of family members and so
forth that have done medical medium
golden seal shock therapy for acne or
for you know congestion or for sinusitis
what that has done for them medical
medium time t-shock therapy never
underestimate that one bit medical
medium prop shock therapy oh wow medical
medium aloe vera shock therapy medical
medium B12 shock therapy medical medium
California poppy shock therapy pretty
amazing right here okay these are
powerful healing tools to rebuild your
immune system by fueling it with what it
needs to fight an infection support your
brain and body through an emotional
challenge calm and restore your nervous
system strengthen and heal your
digestive system and Purge rebuild and
fortify your lymphatic system whether
you're dealing with a condition that's
occurring for the first time or you're
experiencing a
relapse that's incredible so the medical
medium shock
therapies medical medium shock therapies
have a profound record of helping people
overcome Health obstacles these
supplement therapies can be useful for
almost anything you're ailing with
medical medium shock therapies are
powerful whether you're up against
intense stress or need a shift from from
a long-standing chronic illness or
roller coaster Rod which everybody ends
up on when they're sick they're
chronically sick for a long time medical
mem shock therapies are critical to this
day and age because that's what's
happened here the reason I'm going to
the medical meme shock therapies is
things have gotten so bad out there like
I said how I opened up this episode with
about people aren't thinking right
people aren't feeling good the amount of
sickness and illness is going crazy
people are dying left and right just
dropping out there there are protocols
in this book for neurological symptoms
and conditions I'm just talking about
medical M shock therapies but there's
full protocols in here in this book for
neurological symptoms and so forth as
Darkness tries to destroy all that's
good and if that doesn't sound right to
you if it
doesn't then you're in a really really
mighty fine
bubble you're in a mighty fine bubble if
that's if that line right there doesn't
resonate as Darkness tries to destroy
all that's good we Rise Against Darkness
using light created Health weapons to
regain empowerment and that's what s so
is and that's what s so has done right
there Spirit of compassion has put in
these books those
weapons light created Health weapons to
regain gain empowerment yeah because it
matters when you're sick gaining Health
empowerment is
critical as The Changing Times bring did
I just say Changing
Times we talking about ending times what
kind of times are we talking about
because a lot of people are are feeling
like ending times are coming A lot of
people are feeling something's coming
Spirit of compassion always called it
the quickening in these 40 years I've
been trying to get the word out since I
was a kid and spirit of compassion has
been calling it The
quickening Spirit of compassion has be
you know calling it Changing Times as
these Changing
Times okay bring additional stress Upon
Us humankind goes into a deeper Health
deficit if you don't think humankind is
going into a deeper Health deficit then
I got news for
you it is and the funny thing is too A
lot of those stats are just all being
buried there are more sicker people out
there than anybody knows and sure you
might be around people that aren't quite
sick yet but they got something going on
you know but whoa is it getting worse
and
worse humankind goes into a deeper
Health deficit than during previous
decades this is the decade right here
that we're in where it's all shifting
right now in spirit of compassion saw
that coming 5 years ago and forewarn me
to forewarn everybody that we're going
to see a level of sickness that we've
never seen before before and guess what
it's going there we're in it and we're
in that decade right now wait till we
get to
2030 Spirit of compassion tells me that
2030 isn't a landmark of time because it
lands on 3
0 or 2030 because it's the end of the
decade Spirit of compassion says it's a
year that's going to sum up a lot of
what this decade really really was about
for a lot of reasons and it's going to
be extremely visible for so many people
at that point of what's going on in the
chronic illness
World sickness now dominates the lives
of billions of people medical medium
shock therapies from s so above and take
the book to your doctor see what's right
for you from your doctor medical meme
shock therapies are here to help level
the playing field where chemical and
medical Industries are playing dirty
against humankind and that's a big piece
of it the industries are playing dirty
with humankind cuz you're just a number
is what you
are and everybody has a number assigned
to them that they're not even aware of
on planet Earth because in the end
you're just literally a number to the
evildoers there's some great notes in
here about the medical meme shock
therapies you'll find suggestions for
the best applications for various
ailments all through this book It's
amazing And like I said before there are
incredible protocols not just the
recipes which are amazing all on its own
but the protocols are really um amazing
too and then the brain shot therapies as
well I haven't talked about brain shot
Therapies in two years I think was it
two years or a year and a half now or
year and 3/4s don't quote me on that
exactly please out therapies they are
change they are changing people's lives
every day they're in the brain saver
protocols want to remind people that
these books are here because I don't
talk about them enough I barely talk
about these books I barely utter them I
think that it's important to let people
know they
exist uh Lory Star on YouTube says great
book so yeah I'm going to look through
the some some of these protocols
migraines an amazing protocol for
migraines menitis people don't even know
they have that maners disease memory
loss
memory
issues
melasma um Mind Body
syndrome mitochondrial uh myopathy
mononucleosis mood changes mood swings
motor skill disorders people have motor
skill disorders that aren't even
diagnosed as motor skill
disorders they just they're they're it's
it's crazy like the way the systems
built multiple sclerosis protocol for
multiple sclerosis right here and you
can look at symptoms for multiple
sceris and you know or take the symptoms
individually don't even just take a
symptom individually that's also the
best way to do it too I tell friends and
family out
there tell doctors to tell their
patients muscle weakness okay
um my God myin nerve sheet damage people
don't know they have of course they just
don't know there's just so many mystery
hunger mystery fears narcolepsy
neurological fatigue
neurological gastroparesis people don't
know that their intestinal tract
problems are on the borderline of
gastroparesis and they don't know
they're not getting a gastro prus
diagnosis from their doctor they're not
getting that quite yet or they may never
get that but they have this variety of a
neurological vagus nerves you know
gastroparesis that they don't even know
they have these books are critical for
people to learn about this so they can
get out of you know out of the way of
sickness into the light of healing
nausea neck pain neuralgia neuritis
protocols neuropathy Neurosis
neurological lime of course neurological
fatigue like I said before numbness
that's another one right there OCD is
obsessive compulsive disorder optic
neuritis
orthorexia overeating protocol for
overeating I mean how insane is it pain
in back of the head pain inside or
around the ears people have so much pain
around their ears and they have no idea
why pancreatitis autoimmune pancreatitis
all of it parasites Parkinson's disease
it goes on and on I'm just saying
pressure in the in the chest
pots even post polio syndrome I know
there's not a lot of people out there
but they have like the new polio nobody
knows about that's another thing all on
its own so many people have neurological
problems that just getting different
diagnoses with meanwhile they have
basically polio they don't even know it
no one's not giving them po the polio
diagnosis because it's not hip it's not
really in the system as being like uh a
trend in the medical establishment right
now but people walk around with polio
like new polio they don't even know it
how crazy is it new polio symptoms is
what I
mean Pika eating disorder personality
disorders popping in the ears I can go
on and on the protocols in here are
insane Sandy over there on IG took my
brain saor book to my doctor doctor was
impressed with my lab work that she
wanted to borrow the brain saver books
oh tell your doctor I'm actually Beyond
honored and that and I'm so proud of you
I'm proud of you for all that you're
doing that's that's
amazing so psychosis I mean psyched
psychedelic mushroom
withdrawal like who has that in what
book can you tell me where that is I
mean find me a book out there maybe
there is one and I don't even know but
who has an actual protocol like a real
protocol something that works for
psychedelic mushroom
withdrawal sciatica sad you know
Seasonal effective disorder sadness
sarcoidosis roving pain ringing in the
ears pulsating Sensations in the head
and around the head recreational drug
withdrawal it's a protocol in here
restless leg syndrome restlessness ra I
mean it goes on and on and on shingles
everything else I'm just going through
the protocols right here there's
protocols for these symptoms conditions
and it keeps on going on there's no book
out there like this and if there is or
getting one out there I guarantee you
information's been poached or stolen
from this
book anyway you guys so much good stuff
anyway back to the Cafe Gratitude
medical medium
collaboration before I go I just want to
let you guys know that I'm sorry I don't
know you know someone got their hands on
the link and spread it around and you
know how computers are and you know how
things are it just happens and and they
spread the link around and it was sold
out in minutes and so October 22nd
October 3D I'm going to be in person at
Cafe Gratitude with you if you if you
got a ticket
it's a four course medical medium meal
the Cathy gratitude is putting on the
menu October
15th that is so awesome so Kathy
gratitude My Heroes you guys putting the
medical
medium um recipes on the menu October
15th I hope you guys go in there and
enjoy them if you guys are in the area
right to their restaurants and I'm going
to be there I'm going to I'm going to be
in I'm going to be in the restaurant
periodically I'll be in there a lot cuz
I'm going to go in there and order the
recipe because I want to sit down and
eat the medical meum recipe in there so
and it's incredible really because Chef
Drew he took the medical me recipes and
in that collaboration process with me he
elevated the flavor
profile October 22nd 23rd it's a meat
greet personally it's an intimate meet
and
greet I will say just because I'm going
to be right there in your
face right there and I'm going to be
shaking your hand I'm going to be
standing there and it's going to be
really really cool cuz there's only so
many people in the restaurant I'm going
to be there eating I'll probably do a
little talk or something but it's going
to be really fun and like true medical
medium fashion you don't know what's
going to happen
so anyway um just letting everybody know
and unfortunately there's going to be
some people that are just finding out
about this now and they knew it was
going to be tomorrow but like I said it
wasn't our
fault don't know what to
say so we we had to immediately put out
some information so people can get a
chance at least to get a ticket maybe
some people got a ticket and I hope so
all right you guys
okay beasy on these Foods right here
that you see in the
front I know I know it's might might be
something you're not eating that's fine
of course but you might be eating a
little something that's in these Foods
in another food keep that in mind too
gluten dairy eggs look out for that
canola oil corn look out for that if
you're sick you got chronic illness you
got chronic illness got to look out
Dairy cheese Che butter milk a lot of
people go kefir kefir kefir it's like uh
kefir no good if you got chronic
sickness no good if you are chronically
sick Kefir is not a good thing yogurt
yogurt yogurt you know Cow yogurt cow
sheep yogurt you know not good if you
are struggling with some kind of
sickness you're struggling with some
kind of chronic illness not good
okay and I'll spill it out butter milk
cheese yogurt kefir Dairy just
Dairy will feed a bug that's hungry that
sits inside of your liver and your body
and your lymphatic system and your gut
and everything else and that bug will
just your liver like I said and your
spleen and your pancreas wherever that
bug is and it's going to feed on those
things watch out for gluten too you got
to look out for the troublemaker foods
which I have written about extensively
in the medical medium
books okay we got a question right there
on
YouTube sick boy on YouTube says will
the events be
broadcasted get ready for this answer
okay we are looking into this to see if
we can live
stream so people who couldn't make it to
this these events could see it because
of the limited space in the restaurants
and they can't be there because there
was only 200 tickets it's 120 for one
restaurant 80 for another
restaurant because of that we're going
to see if we can live stream it and
we're going to fight for it in the sense
where we're going to try to get the
right people with the right equipment
and right everything and we're going to
do everything we can to try to live
stream this if we can I can't make
promises I can't make promises on that
but like true medical median fashion I
will will do my best my team will do
their best to try to live stream this
with everything we have and you never
know we might be able to do it unless
there's some massive glitch and we can't
or something falls through we're going
to give it a shot
and if we can do the it's expensive to
Li live stream live stream how about
that that's pretty funny it's expensive
to live stream in the way we like to do
it which is like the professional Pro
high quality High Tech way that's really
expensive so and um we're going to try
to pull it off it's right anyway you
guys I this this concludes some of our
chronic illness talk which I want to
talk more about as we go along I'll try
to do another live and then go through
symptoms and see what's going on with
you guys and everything take the medical
medium books to your doctor if you'd
like show them the the shock therapies
or anything else okay and it will be
free to you if we live stream it but not
free to us not free to me but it'll be
free to you if we live stream it that's
what we want all right you guys
incredible and
um love you guys take one day at a time
you know I'm proud of all of
you I'm going to have some tea with some
propolis in there