geminal neuralgia tentis vertigo brain
fog so many people have these the thing
is an epidemic happening because
everybody everybody and their mother
everybody and their grandmother
everybody and their grandpa everybody in
their cousin is getting one of those
things two of those things three four
five 10 15 20 35 50 50 symptoms
literally people are getting symptoms
that's what's happening right now these
days so what's going on people are
getting sick and you know it's all fun
in games until you're sick it's all fun
in games until you don't feel good it's
all great until it's not it's all
perfect until it ain't anymore and
everything's just going great going good
until it's going terrible and awful and
that's how it works with sickness and
then you're Doctor shopping and Doctor
shopping and then Doctor
shopping and if you got guys you guys
are probably getting all booted off IG
right now I see it so just go to Medical
medium.com I'm streaming live off of
medicalmedium.com
so you can go right there and you can
watch the show before you get booted off
so I'm just saying because you're going
to see this thing on your screen that
says oh bad connection or whatever so
just get to medicalmedium.com over there
in IG just letting you
know
so yeah and there's a new podcast out
medical medium podcast at Apple podcast
check it out blood brain barrier gets
penetrated because yeah that's what
happens to everybody's blood brain
barrier they think it is great you know
what happens with medical research and
science is they make everybody feel so
comfy and so good and so safe don't
worry your bloodb brain barrier will
protect you that's not going to cross
your blood brain barrier that can't hurt
you there's no way that's going to cross
your bloodb brain
barrier and guess guess what everything
crosses the blood brain bar pretty much
almost
everything gets through the blood brain
barrier into the brain and that's what
happens so check out that
podcast so meic Me podcast Apple podcast
right bloodb brain barrier check it out
it is really a good episode it's packed
with information it's
concentrated seriously concentrated with
info so so um you guys go to medical.com
I could already see you're probably only
going to have 3 minutes on IG before
Boop you're shipped off into Never Never
Land all right so let's go into it how
many people got tontis who's got the
ringing in the ears when decibal damage
has been ruled out I'm reading right out
of here a little bit just so you know
when deciel damage you know what I mean
by that like decible damage where you
around loud
Machinery every single person back 20
years ago 30 years ago whatever every
single person who had ringing in the ear
or some kind of like sound going off in
the a or some kind of buzzing were told
they were like deciel damaged by
something were you around Machinery were
you around this did did a baseball were
you at a baseball park and a baseball
flew and hit you in the head did it hit
you in the ear ma'am that's how it was
people have no idea about this how it
worked the medical industry and you go
to the doctor's office back boom years
ago and you had ringing in the years it
was always a diagnosis of well you have
a damaged ear because you must have
listen to loud music way too much loud
music before and so people are always
told that it's like loud music gave me
the the ringing the year gave me the t9s
and you know not only that the New Age
movement really really spelled out the
whole ringing in the a as as something's
talking to you or somebody's talking to
you or it's a message right and that
happened all the time too it's these
people would suffer from the worst ttis
and then they would go to like a psychic
and then the psychic would be like well
that's because you know things are
talking to you that's because fairies
are talking to you that's be you're
ringing in the ears because something's
talking to you or somebody's talking
about you and that happened too so it
was all this confus you went to the
regular doctor with ttis and you were
told you just have a damaged Year from
loud music and then you're trying to
think about when did I listen to of loud
music well when I was in college I
listened to loud music maybe uh I worked
around Machinery did I what's going on
and then when you went to like the new
age kind of situation you were just told
a your head was chopped off in England
in 1607 or you know your head was put on
a pike or something in you know the Dark
Age ages in the 800s ad and whatever it
was that's why you had the ringing in
the ear okay or you got fairies talking
about you or someone's talking about you
somewhere else and that was the answers
you got that was
it honest to God that was the answers
you got back 20 years ago 30 years ago
when you had ringing the ears and
tonight so let's go into it a little bit
okay when decibel damage has been ruled
out like you really didn't have an
injury like there wasn't a serious car
accident and your head was smashed
against you know the car
door right and you haven't worked around
heavy machinery for many years how many
of you guys got tonight is how many of
you guys got ring in the ears whooing in
the ears buzzing in the ears humming in
the ears vibration in the ears
right and um or you didn't work in the
like work in the music industry that's
another one too or were you at a lot of
live concerts like lots of live concerts
like heavy metal or had a physical
injury right if none of that happened on
a regular basis then when you Reed the
tentis diagnosis because of the humming
and everything
else people would be like what is it but
what it is is viral inflammation mystery
ttis is viral
inflammation
viruses inflaming the Labyrinth
inflaming different areas of the ear the
inner ear okay so that that is what it
is tonius doesn't have to be ringing in
the ear it could be humming buzzing how
many of you guys got like buzzing or
humming right pounding tontis whoa
Restless Soul you got that yeah that's
awful when it's like that where it's
pounding that's terrible em then Nicole
says that sounds like me but I never
have been around machines nor loud music
yeah and you know to this day they still
say that they'll be like were you around
loud music were you around machines you
know um Mrs Jones were you listening to
loud music cuz I think that's what it is
everything else checks out fine so
fluttering in the air crackling
fluttering check this out vibrating
popping crazy
popping okay how about that I'm not
talking about where you just had the flu
and all that mucus is going through you
know what I'm talking talking about when
someone gets a flu and all that mucus is
kind of moving through and they're just
so sick they feel like they're congested
their whole head is congested they're
their face is congested just everything
is like every sinus cavity sinuses
everywhere completely clogged up and as
the stuff's moving in the middle of the
night you might hear a pop you can't
hear good and then you hear a pop right
that happens because you're sick right
you're sick with that flu or C or
something like
that Reena Robinson say says I healed my
tenius Because of You explanation point
Thank you thank you for being here thank
you for your comment that's
awesome but if you don't have like the
flu and you know and c and whatever if
you don't have any of that and you're
getting popping or ringing or fluttering
or crackling or whoosing whoosing I
never heard whoosing described until the
medical medium books were published
never heard that and I heard somebody
running an ad recently on
IG and they were just like whoosing in
the a I'm like
really never heard that one before out
there when someone has the high pitch
ringing in the ear it can change alter
and dance about this is one thing that
that's really hard on tonight's
sufferers When someone tells me aw I got
ttis okay look if first thing that comes
to my mind is the whole
dancing that whole dancing sound okay
because when you have tenius and that
ringing is going on all you need is
background noise like a fan going or the
refrigerator starts running do you know
about this or your laundry is running in
the back there something you got your
laundry running and it changes the tone
of the ringing now not for everybody but
there's a lot of cases where people and
it's changing their tone it's going like
instead of
like it's going
like it's doing this thing where it's
going crazy all over the place if some
Fan's going and air conditioning is
running if something's like happening if
there's some wind or something or you
got a window open and there's a plane
flying by it Alters the
tentis and if you're just laying there
in bed or laying there on the couch or
trying to fall asleep at night with the
ttis and the ringing what happens is
that any noise can alter the ringing and
and shift it up to the point where it
makes it so you can't go to sleep so you
actually have a difficult time falling
asleep or going to sleep that's really
hard it's like the first thing comes to
my mind is are you tortured by that
because so many people get tortured by
that oh my God James says oh my God yes
right and here's one right here that you
might not even have heard and maybe you
experienced this right Denise said that
is exact my problem yes I have that too
Vanessa whoa whoa and here's the thing
though you guys check this out this is a
big deal right here and and maybe you
experienced this maybe you didn't
experience this all right but tonius
there's a variety of
ttis okay that when the sound is going
right
that that if there is a fan
running or an A running or something
blowing air or some noise it can alter
the ringing and turn into songs so you
actually can recognize some of the
ringing where the ringing starts to
fluctuate so much you hear music in the
ringing but yet there's no music you're
not there's no music playing nobody's
playing music but you're hearing music
within it so as it's doing that right so
I I don't know if you've ever
experienced that but that's a hard one
for a lot of people where they hear
songs within their ttis but there's no
music playing but they hear Melodies
going up and down these Melodies these
chains of Melodies going up and down and
songs they can recognize through the
ringing in the ear that's being altered
by a fan but yet it's not no song that's
playing there's no song that's going on
no one has the music on but you're
hearing it and that that's just really
really bizarre how it does that Molly
says Rell says over there on YouTube I'm
healing my ttis with your information aw
I rarely have ringing my ears now so you
really have rarely have ringing in your
ears now so much healing has happened
thank you aw and so s so so appreciates
that Janessa says what about air candle
burning along with the ringing okay good
question right there okay um not into
the the air you know air Canal I see
that okay not the air candle I want to
tell you about air candles too okay
that's something that's important was on
my mind the other day too is that makes
tonight's
worse so ear
candles actually make tenius worse I'm
forewarning people right there because a
lot of people do that well they'll
they'll burn the the candle they'll
stick it in their ear and they'll do
that practice PR practice has been
around for a long time it worsens
tenius aggravates it because the
Labyrinth if the inner ear is so
inflamed that when you're doing that it
aggravates that inflammation that's
already hot wire don't do the air the
ear candle burning thing that's
something I wanted to you know
say um Kelly says this is mind-blowing
information I'm honored I'm glad you're
here so on the music front I want to
just cover that for another second okay
um that's a difficult tonight is for a
lot of people because as they're trying
to sleep or rest they're catching those
songs and those rhythms and The Melody
of that rigging going into all these
songs and tunes that they actually can
recognize and sometimes recognize or not
sure but yet there's no music playing
and that one right there is difficult
for a lot of people I don't know if
you've ever had that before you know um
see all right let's go let's move into
it a little
bit okay all right when someone has the
high pitch ringing in the ear it can
change alter and dance about when a fan
or air conditioner is on and music is
playing some people experience what
sounds like air rushing through their
ear air rushing through their ear
like
then it backs down or it stays there
permanently it's a ttis without the
ringing so I want to cover that for a
second do you guys know of that like do
do some of you have the ttis without the
ringing how about that well there's no
ringing but there's a
constant that's there all the time okay
all right some people experiencing
popping like they're popping pop popcorn
in the ear pop tonight us can vary from
mild to extreme some people get small
moments when they hear a ringing in the
ear and it goes away this has been
pasted office someone's speaking about
you that's what everybody said and the
problem is with that one where someone
is speaking about you and you got a ring
in the ear and it's like someone's
talking about you the problem is with
that is that
early early sufferers of tontis in their
very early
stages who get just a
quick and it goes away it's like someone
must be talking about
me and it goes away well those people
end up hearing it more a year later like
there a little more it's like whoa
someone's talking about me again but a
lot more today another year later
someone's talking about me a lot this
week like twice this
week a year goes by another year goes by
someone's talking about me like once a
day wow what's going on and then boom
they got ttis and now they're ringing
all the time it was just basically early
warnings and then finally it went into
chronic ttis and now they're like I
guess nobody was talking about me darn
it it was tonius all these
years what most of okay so here's
another thing too all right let's see
sometimes it takes years of intermittent
ringing in the ears to be diagnosed with
ttis like okay here's another thing too
you go to the doctor like I got a ring
in the ears it doesn't mean you're going
to get a
ttis diagnosis at all you know I'm
reading out of the brain someone asked
just now um I'm reading out of the brain
saver book it's an Incredible
Book it'll blow your mind this book be
prepared when you get it it's so packed
with
information um such a great book
life-saving life saving tool seriously
Epstein bar is the number one reason why
people have mystery tontis Epstein
bar yes EBV is the number one
reason why most people have tentis it's
epine bar getting into the ear working
its way on the nerve root hairs so the
nerve rout here so let's go into that a
little bit another way it does it
through neur toxins look it here I got a
quick
board all
right so that nerve channel in the ear
okay what happens is when a virus gets
to that nerve
Channel and it
does so when that virus gets to the
nerve Channel there you are the Epstein
bar
EBV right when it finally gets to that
nerve Channel Channel and it gets into
those nerves and gets into the
Labyrinth right
there it clings on to it but it only
clings on to it if you got root hair
sticking out a lot of people have frayed
nerves in their ear channels Fray nerves
little root hairs popping out you see
these root hairs and as you get older
and you're not taking care of yourself
and all the stuff's happening you get
more Fray on that nerve and that Fray
that's on that nerve right see the
little Fray stuff what happens is the
viruses look for that the Epstein bar
looks for that it goes and it finds that
root hair coming off the
nerve sticks on there camps out makes a
home and then when it makes a home you
get a whole bunch of
inflammation in that area
now that nerve is inflamed just like
that and the whole nerve can get
inflamed it's
inflamed it ends up making noise yes it
vibrates what you're hearing are bugs in
the ear you're actually physically
hearing bugs on the nerve vibrating
because it's such a sensitive area where
you can hear the inflamed nerve because
of the bugs so that's what happens right
there move this
over
okay A lot of times too if the bug
doesn't get in there yet and it's
releasing a lot of neurotoxins that's
Epstein bar feeding off of mercury
aluminum copper herbicides fungicides
and whatever and fragrances when the
epine bar is feeding off of that and
that's releasing all this
poison that poison can get in there and
inflame both ears and you got tentis in
both ears just ringing ringing ringing
once
neurotoxins released from the
virus they have an injuring effect on
the canal nerves nerves of the inner ear
so clear nerve that one these nerves can
swell from the neurotoxins constantly
saturating them so neurotoxins from the
viruses saturate the neres so that takes
us to this right
here okay so you got a nerve right here
nice new nerve right there it gets
inflamed
okay and neurotoxins from the viruses
that get released out of the viruses all
that poo that comes out of the viruses
right
there it ends up getting on the nerves
and it just inflames it so neurotoxins
as well all
right see guys I'll show you that right
there all right let's move on so when it
comes down to you know healing ttis
killing off the viruses is
critical that is important killing off
the viruses is critical so there's
different protocols right here so I have
protocols for that in the protocols book
here got them also in medical Med M book
one New Edition there are protocols in
here to adhere to if you adhere to them
and work with them um you can be like
thousands of others that got rid of
their tenius like gone like bye Gone
With the Wind just that's it moved on
with their lives out of that tontis
problem okay over there on YouTube My
vertigo is gone with medical medium
vertigo let's talk about vertigo for a
little bit too so all right most cases
of vertigo are caused by viral infection
unless you have a serious physical
injury or you've had a concussion and so
forth like a injury exactly so most
cases of vertigo are caused by viral
infections some are caused by physical
injury or a growth or a tumor right but
if you're all cleared you went to the
doctor and you're all cleared of a
growth or a tumor and so forth okay and
you're all good there you did not get
into accident you didn't get to a car
accident you didn't something didn't
somebody didn't hit you you weren't you
know seriously injured then that
vertigo is
viral it's important to
know um unless you're having some crazy
side effect from a
medication something like that you know
like some crazy side effects but even
then you have to have a sensitive Vegas
nerve or set of veg nerve that have to
be you know
sensitive um if no such thing exists you
weren't injured and so forth and someone
is dealing with mysterious vertigo
mystery balance problems you feel like
you're on a boat you feel dizzy you
don't feel stable or you're getting the
whole bed spins where you're laying on
the couch or bed and it's going like
this constantly so you got that vertigo
where it's your you feel like your
head's moving like this you shut your
eyes and everything's moving moving
around you know like that kind of
vertigo which is brutal so many people
suffer from that it's
awful the theory goes that if you move
your neck or head a certain way it
disrupts the crystals and triggers a
bout of vertigo so the medical industry
believes vertigo get this important to
know the medical industry believes
vertigo is some kind of inner ear
problem that may involve crystals and
particles or stones inside the inner ear
I called BS on that many many years ago
and the industry is starting to shift
oo published First Medical meme
information but now they're saying
maners which is
vertigo man's disease may not be the
stones that were in everybody's ears
decade after decade after decade the
stones that nobody saw that science
never saw nobody saw them under a
microscope they didn't exist the stones
in their ears might not be it ooh viral
inflammation looks like that might be
what it is and so now it's changing
they're taking medical meme info
published first now they're saying like
maners could be
viral it is viral Theory goes on that if
you move your neck right like you go get
some help somebody works on you you move
your neck and your head just right they
try to adjust you maybe a chiropract
doors adjusting you maybe you're going
to massage therapist maybe you're going
to a clinic where they actually have a
system where you lay on the table they
lock your head in and they they try to
give you a jolt and they try to move
your head in a certain way hopes that
your vertigo goes
away that's
scary then the the the whole theory
behind it was the crystals would
actually move so the stones in your ears
would move they try to move your head
around a certain way shake your head
around and everything they hope that the
stones
move but they don't move because they
never existed there are no stones and
crystals that get in the way that create
vertigo the real
cause
Indiana says YouTube in the podcast you
mentioned global cooling but the ice is
melting in the ocean temperature is
rising please explain
and much love well that's a good
question right there okay but yeah in
the podcast global cooling is what's
happening because what's going on is the
atmosphere and this is important to know
first of all caps are melting from the
hole in the ozone okay because that's
the whole thing the ozone layer right
the atmosphere is basically dissolved on
on the opposite spectrums of the planet
okay so it's the one reason why and the
the Chemtrails aren't saturating up
there they're not D they're not dumping
chemtrail after chemtrail after
chemtrail over the Bergs that's really
important to know right listen to the
podcast and I'll go into more about that
too sometime so check out the podcast
episode in in medical mean podcast at
Apple
podcast but it's important to know
what's happening with that okay but yes
we're getting global cooling we're
getting poorer
crops because it is getting cooler
because the sky is filled with so much
metal that they're dropping out of
PLS the atmosphere is filled with so
much
metal that it's reflecting the
Sun and the Earth is getting cooler
because it's one of the reasons right
there and yeah the Caps are melting
because they're not dumping those Trails
on the Caps they're not dumping them
there
number one plus that's where that that
hole is that's why the burgs are melting
faster All By Design anyway we'll go
into like a deeper understanding and
I'll go into details on that but I love
talking about that it's just
depressing all
right the real cause of most case of
vertigo is the epsteam bar virus because
epine bar creates ttis and vertigo and a
lot of people get
both they get get both they get the
tenius and the vertigo they get them
both
together yes and if they don't have them
together in that moment they get them
later together could start out with a
vertigo Boop end up with tenius 5 years
later start out with tenius Boop end up
10 years later with a vertigo or a year
later they end up having both most
people end up having both because epine
bar creates a crap load of symptoms and
has disrupted people's lives in so many
ways what a really really annoying
virus
okay which area of the Vegas nerve is
inflamed affects the variety of vertigo
okay let's go into that a little bit
we'll go into Vegas nerve talk a little
bit about Vegas nerves okay
whoa
see well the best we can get for now now
that's what happens when you use a wet
sponge
okay all right so you got your Vegas
nerves yes Vegas
nerves
okay all right see what we got here your
Vegas nerves you got your viruses epin
bar
virus Epstein bar virus loves the Vegas
nerves typ in the chest tightness in the
throat all kinds of different ver
versions of
gastroparesis yes Vegas
nerves that's right so you got a A lot
of people are just loaded with Epstein
bar they're loaded with different
varieties of Epstein bar they might have
two varieties of Epstein bar here's one
variety of Epstein bar here's a second
variety of Epstein bar different strain
then they might pick up a third
one a lot of people have more than that
okay different varieties of epine bar
they release different varieties of
poisons the poisons come out of the
virus and as the poisons come out of the
virus the poisons end up touching the
vagus
nerve okay the vagus nerves the poison
ends up touching the nerves the nerves
get inflamed and start to sweat
when they start to swell vertigo
occurs the higher the inflammation on
the vagus nerves
are brain
stem cranial nerves the higher they
are more problems with your
vertigo the lower they are the vertigo
can change and be different and
shift so a lot of people might be
swelling
their Vegas nerves are
swelling up
higher creating a real crappy vertigo
just downright ugly vertigo where
they're throwing up they're puking their
guts out because the vertigo is so bad
okay some people the viral poison that
comes out will inflame a lower section
of their Vegas nerves
and so their their dizziness and their
balance issues are going to be different
it's going to be a different type of
vertigo so I want to kind of run that
critical information I find it's
critical I find it's critical in
information I mean I do I can't say
everybody thinks it is but I think it is
when you're suffering from vertigo and
it's like driving you crazy you can't
drive anymore you can't do anything you
got to like you you can't live your life
the way you want to and you're living
with this constant vertigo this
dizziness this balance issue problem
it's devastating it's
devastating all right some rare cases of
vertigo can be inflammation to the brain
the brain stem higher okay mild
undiagnosed incilius or even brain
inflammation caused by a viral infection
predominantly
EBV vertigo symptoms can range from
feeling like you're on a
boat to not feeling balanced when you're
walking to feel like you're falling
forward that's another one too you're
falling forward right that that falling
forward
thing and or you're walking sideways and
you're like walking like this
right and you're just gosh there's so
many versions that just throw
people it could become so severe that
you get what I call the bed
spins as you lie in bed the room is
spinning or rocking back and forth when
you shut your eyes you close your eyes
and the room is literally
spinning that is brutal some people live
with that every day every waking day and
sleeping day of their life it's awful
some cases of ver or severe where you're
vomiting where you get the vertigo
attack and you're like
vomiting
awful it's a rough one and there's and
okay so these are more acute viral
infections where someone's immune system
strength dropped and the EBV took over
fast and now you're throwing up because
you're really tripped up you're
triggered so now you're really triggered
into the vomiting one you're triggered
into the bed spins it's when the viruses
all of a sudden kind of explode and they
proliferated to such a degree and so
fast and they lit that Vagas nerve
Channel up boom open the heel says I got
hospitalized for vertigo several years
back they had nothing for it they seem
to never do Margie said falling forward
yes and to the right so you got the
falling to the right thing so it's
falling forward into to the right yeah
that's brutal that's that's really
difficult and I'm sorry you actually
have that that's brutal
Susie Sunshine says it makes me want to
die I've heard that I've heard that
before because that's how bad it can be
where it just takes away your quality of
life and and you just feel like okay
wait a minute I'm stuck with this it's
just such a painful
situation
um okay in many cases it's not just EBV
neurotoxins inflaming the Vegas nerve
it's EBV itself so I showed you on the
on the Whiteboard right there that it
was toxins coming from the virus
inflaming the Vegas nerves but it can
also be the EP scene bar some cases
there's different varieties of EP bar so
if you take a look at this board really
quick for a second you see one variety
of EP bar right here the red little
right red is the virus you see two
variety of of the virus right there it's
another variety you see three varieties
right here it's another variety right
there and so what happens is you can
have one variety just infl
the channel the veg nerves inflame it
another variety of epine bar actually
going on the nerve and that's an
entirely different situation so you get
another type okay so maybe you get
another version of epine bar it's a
different strain of evv okay and that
one actually
heads to the nerves and it clings on to
the nerves and it inflames them directly
and it takes time to heal it takes time
to heal these you know it takes dis some
dis
discipline right some
compliance it takes a little time but
you can heal the one thing about medical
medum information is people have healed
it's not this whole thing does it work
does it
not no it works and that's the thing
with medical Med information this book
right here millions of people all around
the globe everywhere who have this copy
who turn their lives around over the
decade who moved out of chronic illness
who healed the vertigo and their ttis
and so much more that we're talking
about trigeminal neuralgia and brain fog
and everything else they healed it
healed I mean healed gone boom symptoms
out of the way out of here carola
says over there on x minus so
life-altering so few people understand
what we go through and it goes back to
that unless you experience it yourself
you won't know what the other person is
going through you think they're crazy or
you think there you don't even know what
they're talking about it's like what do
you mean you're dizzy go to the doctor
that's what they'll say people will do
that they'll say to somebody so you know
you're telling me about this vertigo
thing you got I don't understand it I
don't know why you're so dizzy all the
time go to IT doctor isn't it fixed
already no it's not like that it's not
easy the protocols in this book can be
customized because it's not one siiz
fits all keep that in mind but you can
find your way through these books and I
got the Brain book right here find your
way through there and you can heal so so
critical Kim Miller says your info is
the only thing that has helped me it's
fantastic and I'm honored you're here
Kim thank you for leaving a comment yes
so it's important information all right
let's keep on rolling along
yes indeed my migraines have finally
stopped after 33 years on medical medium
the nerve shifter shot combined with
three years of medical medium almost 5
months without migraines
woo yeah I'm proud of you too proud of
you too because you've been doing it
long enough you stuck with it you
know that's what you
did it's
amazing I will say right here that you
know it's hard because um when you're on
you're you're working on healing you're
on the trajectory of healing you're
moving
forward and you stayed with the
information you diligent you stayed with
it disciplined you worked hard 5 months
without migraines and that's how it's
done you just got to just you got to
keep on forging ahead with the
information tune out the like tune out
the
competitors that are coming into the
community everywhere pretending celer is
bad or whatever is bad and everything
else tune them out because they're
literally
sharks absolute sharks trying to build
their Empires tune them out tune out the
haters with the false stories and the
fake stories tune out all of them okay
and just focus on your healing process
is what you do okay stick with it boom
move forward amazing all right let's
talk about brain fog a little
bit let's go there severe cases of brain
fog can be
devastating
man I mean that line doesn't cut it
doesn't cut it at
all severe cases of brain fog can be
devastating nope doesn't cut it
terrifyingly
devastating I should have put
devastating because I've seen brain fog
cases where you can't make yourself
something to eat you can't walk
somewhere you can't drive a car you're
it just it creates Madness you just feel
like you're losing yourself and you're
losing hope brain fog can be oh I'm a
little foggy I'm a little foggy I need
my coffee you know use coffee to mask
your problem you're living with brain
fog you're struggling with brain fog you
don't even really know it you have no
idea but you need coffee because you
can't function without the coffee
without the caffeine taking over and
running your adrenals and exploding your
adrenals cuz that happens so brain
Foggers are huge huge caffeine
consumers huge caffeine consumers that's
what they are and University student
brain Foggers are Aderall consumers
right they're they're medication
consumers right 80% of the colleges it's
everybody's on adol right so that's how
it works that's how brain fog is masked
brain fog is an epidemic all on its own
out there big time I mean millions
billions have brain fog
billions 50 billion people on this
planet have brain fog anybody catch that
one yet did I contradict myself at all
50 billion people have brain fog on on
planet Earth did you catch that one
anybody going to put that one out there
see I told you he's bad look he said 50
billion people are on this planet no
it's 8 point something said
whatever um Deborah says my brain fog is
gone with medical medium
incredible the thing the thing is is
that coffee will
mask the
illness and chocolate will mask the
illness and matcha tea and green tea
will mask and black tea the
illness
right and there we go Tom just said 50
billion question mark and there it
starts yeah so anyway so so many people
have brain fog and they have to hide it
by using the caffeine but what happens
is when you do that you're creating
future brain
fog and that really things Victoria
Rising said but what do you mean by 50
billion I am curious is it a joke or
something else could be something else
it's a joke though all
right when your adrenals are sitting
there every single day getting beaten
down by the
Aderall right and and in the prescribed
amphetamines and they're just the
adrenals are getting clobbered because
they're squeezing every last bit of gold
out of them so that the brain can
override because what adrenaline is it's
like basically fuel for the brain to
override a problem and so the brain then
kind of shakes out of the brain fog so
whatever those metals that are in there
creating brain fog toxic heavy metals
Mercury aluminum copper lead cadmium
arsenic right all those toxic heavy
metals that are in the
brain they're creating a problem in the
brain and then you do the
caffeine and you do the amphetamines
prescribed
amphetamines and then the adrenals just
explode right every single day like boom
I need my adrenaline fixed and then the
adrenaline shoots out and that
adrenaline is strong stuff it's
corrosive and it goes shoots right to
the brain and when it gets into the
brain it lights everything on fire the
electrical grid gets lit right up boom
and then it overrides the toxic heavy
metal inflammation the to the viral
inflammation the heavy load of toxins
and poisons that are in the brain the
fragrances and everything else that
we're Poisoned With and then it moves
that over in a way and it lights the
grit up so you can start shaking out of
that brain fog but you can get brain fog
so bad that that doesn't work anymore
and the amphetam means and the caffeine
doesn't shake you out of it and then
you're just in the pit you're just
really in the pit struggling and
suffering and then later
on later
on it gets
worse 10 years later so you were 20 and
you're in you're in you know college and
you're 20 years old and you're using all
the amphetamin in the caffeine and
you're pushing through pushing through
and you're robbing Peter to pay hey
Paul and then 10 years later now you're
30 years old and you're Doctor shopping
everywhere for every functional medicine
doctor you can find on the planet or
whatever conventional doctor because you
got brain fog that's so bad and you want
your medications to be like adjusted and
you want your amphetamines to be
adjusted and you want all
that and it just gets worse worse from
there and no one no one you know was
going to be like let me help you and get
you out of that and people just get
stuck talking about brain
fog are there other planets that have 50
billion people on
them certainly there are bigger
planets
okay all right I want to go into this a
little bit one major factor behind brain
fog is a liver that's saturated with
toxic heavy
metals Ed candles air fresheners
fragrances
pesticides herbicides other toxins and
so forth so a
liver that's saturated and soaked up
clogged stagnant sluggish
overheated burnt out
fatty fatty liver all burnt up and then
boom you can have brain fog just from
that when Epstein bar feeds on these
poisons neurotoxins get released and
they go to the brain so what happens
is when viruses such as epine bar feed
off
of right feed off of these poisons and
the fragrances and all the different
chemicals and the
herbicides and everything else right and
the metals and they feed off of them
those chemicals those neurotoxins now
being released from the viruses get into
the neurons and now you're just fogged
up and your grit's
going it's
happening P Robinson over there on
YouTube I have been off caffeine for
three years my sister is quitting now
with help from medical medium but she
didn't want to but knew it had to be
done it's really hard my mother would be
on a couch would be on couch Island
without Aderall and
coffee yeah it's
brutal so many people would be on couch
Island and only there without Aderall
and coffee I know it's not their fault
it's not the person's fault always
remember that always remember that it's
not and it's not easy out there
neurotoxins have the ability to diminish
neurotransmitter activity and
neurotransmitter chemicals themselves
meaning that when an electrical impulse
tries to run down a neuron the
electrical impulse can misfire as it's
approaching any kind of contamination
and inconsistent uh inconsistency see so
what happens is that your electrical
Grid in your brain right all that
electricity spinning around and going
through neurons all of a sudden hits all
those toxins and poisons and all that
garbage and then boom diminishes and
when it diminishes you your brain fog
gets worse and by 9:00 in the morning
you slept a good night by 9:00 in the
morning you're brain fogged again you
woke up and were less brain fogged for a
half an hour in the morning you got up
at 7:30 8:00 in the morning you were up
for half an hour your brain fog was not
as bad by 10:00 in the morning it came
on worse and worse electrical grid is
circulating it's hitting more toxins and
poisons after you had a good night's
sleep it takes a few hours and then
you're back in the saddle again into
brain fog Nightmare and
troubles another factor in brain fog is
the heavy metal load inside the brain
brain itself Metals that's why the
hmds and the medical medium heavy metal
detox and the the advanced and the
regular and all of that in the medical
medium books is critical heavy metal
detox is critical for so many people you
can't get out of the brain fog until you
get the metals out until you get them
out easily and safely without any
problems that's how you heal you get
through brain fog and you get through
other conditions when you take those
Metals out you move forward you get your
life back that is critical
critical
indeed
indeed another factor in brain fog was
the
metals and here's the problem like in
the brain right here's the problem okay
you can have Metals in one part of the
brain tissue and then they move Metals
actually
move they leech and they discard and
they corrode and they out gas and they
basically push out more
metal like methyl metal off of the
original metal itself and that metal
leeches like a leech field into other
neurons and other Leo cells and then the
brain fog gets worse and worse and if
it's not bought and cleaned up and no
one's working on it and getting it out
and getting the metals out and it ends
up into a bigger problem down the road
and then down the road a bigger problem
and a bigger
problem and that's how it
rolls there's so much information in
these books you guys you should get them
if you can get them free at the library
or go to amazon.com us or wherever you
are they're on sale right now and
there's protocols in these books so I
have the
protocol Brain book right here with all
the protocols you want to get both of
these it was one book two big the
publisher wouldn't publish it two big
books it became it was one massive
book okay it's one massive
book and then how to be
turn into two
books there you go customize a protocol
for yourself take control over your
health I know a lot of people they think
okay what I'll go listen this person
I'll go Len that person this person's
selling this this person's doing that
and it's like you get this like little
fix here and a little fix here and a
little fix there and then you just still
you're still sick three years from now
learn the information become your own
expert become your own own
expert that's what people need to do and
take the book to your doctor or to your
healthare provider and be like look can
you help me with
this all
right trigeminal neuralgia one of my
favorites one of my favorites because
when you heal somebody with brutal
trigeminal
neuralgia it is it the ultimate blessing
it feels so good anybody struggling with
trinal neurology long term do not lose
Faith do not lose
hope there is a way to
heal important words you need to live by
and have in your database your
subconsciousness your Consciousness that
there is a way to heal when it comes
down to trigeminal neuralgia timeline
right in time some people heal it fast
some people need a few years when it's
brutal and they've had it too me too
long okay trinal neuralgia is one of
those annoying annoying conditions very
annoying
because
because when those nerves get inflamed
they're in a really really sensitive
spot real sensitive spot when they get
inflamed
okay so let's let's set up a set of
nerves here trigeminal
nerves get a set of trigeminal nerves
here okay here we go looks like a
heart indeed it
is all
right okay trigeminal
neuralgia the
shingles definitely interferes with
these nerves greatly herpes simplex one
definitely interferes with these nerves
greatly leeching out poisons and
toxins shingles virus a lot of people
have different varieties I did I did a
shingle live the other
day okay here's little viruses
everywhere all
right some are
shingles some are it's just be one
herpy
simplex and both these viruses have the
ability to cling to the root hairs of
the nerves so root
hairs okay trinal nerves they root hair
out very
easily they do they Fray so keep that in
mind it's why people suffer long
term that's why they can have it so bad
where they're getting you know they're
getting injections in the back of their
neck they're getting
injections in their jaw I mean they're
getting all kinds of different things
all kinds of different
therapies and what happens is the reason
why they suffer from it long term is
because the root hairs coming off of
these
nerves seem to be a little bit more than
a lot of other nerves it frays easier
that's what the trigeminal nerves do
they Fray easier there's a lot of
reasons for that but um when the viruses
get on the trigeminal
nerve they usually
hit the molar
areas
molers those areas down in there in the
jaw and that
nerve so people end up getting tons of
rot
canals rot canals without needing a r
Canal you need a rot Canal you need a
rot Canal but people get a lot of of
root
canals when they don't need a root canal
they get a lot of teeth drilled because
their trigal neurologist so bad and back
20 years ago 30 years ago was huge huge
mess a huge mess dentists always just
pulled teeth or drilled teeth with any
kind of pain it didn't matter if what
what it looked you know like in the
digital x-rays or the pre-digital X-ray
era the pre-digital X-ray
where is just like
radiation supersonic amounts of
radiation not just like the digital
where it was a little bit more it was
it's a little bit more pinpointed and a
little
less
radiation but either way what would
happen is if you had pain and even
though the teeth checked out okay they
drilled them and the 80s the 19s 90s and
the first decade of the
2000s people they just were literally
drilled drilled drilled to
death it's not happening as much because
right now dentists are actually
understanding that wait a minute and you
know they're like wait a minute
something else is happening
here but so these nerves get highly
inflamed they get inflamed
easy
by the way subscribe to the medical
medium podcast at Apple
podcast or on Spotify there will be a
new episode every single week big
announcement coming next week I just
want to give everybody for warning make
sure you are on the medical medium
newsletter please to be the first to
know follow medical medium on telegram
for exclusive audio messages but I'm
making a big announcement next week and
I don't know you might be interested
okay but you got to be on the medical
meme newsletter to get the announcement
because I'm going to be announcing it on
the medical mem newsletter if that makes
any sense because that's what I'm going
to be
doing all
right trino neural just really annoying
shingles fires many many times probably
the
majority and then the herpes simplex one
a big one there too
some people can have both they could
they could have the herpes virus simplex
one and shingles inflaming their jaws or
their nerves but trial trigeminal nerves
aren't just in the jaw cranial nerves
and they can be inflamed all the way to
the brain stem and it can be brutal
giving people pain that is beyond
pain like
just terrifying pain and and so with
that we want to heal and people do heal
they rid their trigeminal neurologia
when they do medical mum information
they learn it they learn how to heal and
they do the
information if I had it I would be
killing off the viruses with medical be
protocol I would be getting the metals
out so they're not being fed because a
lot of times herpes simplex one and the
shingles will feed off of those
Metals so let's talk about Auto immune
for a little
bit so what you're going to hear out
there is so many people being diagnosed
of autoimmune you probably already had
an autoimmune
diagnosis
and pretty much everybody's going to be
handed some form of autoimmune diagnosis
in the coming years we're at a place now
where everybody is getting sick even
when they look fine they seem fine five
years from now they're sick it's there's
not going to be a person left on this
planet that is in struggling with a
symptom at some point so autoimmune is
going to be the big overhanging umbrella
and I talk about that in the books so
the first thing I just want to tell you
about autoimmune is it's not your body's
immune system attacking itself so it's
not your body's immune system going
after your organs and glands so if you
get Hashimoto thyroiditis you get a
thyroid
condition and they say it's autoimmune
it's not your body attacking the thyroid
keep that in mind because it doesn't
help your immune system when you believe
it has turned against you so if there's
anything I can tell you with autoimmune
is you have to support your immune
system subconsciously consciously from
your
soul with your spirit with everything
wholeheartedly have to support your
immune system and know that it's working
for you and it hasn't turned against you
and it's not giving you
autoimmune because the system is rigged
so that you think your immune system has
failed you and yes you're out there
working with somebody or a doctor or
somebody and you're trying to get your
immune system more balanced and you're
doing things and you're eating better
and you're doing keto or you're doing
something else or whatever it is out
there and sure but if you think in the
back of your mind somewhere and you
think somewhere in your Consciousness
subconsciousness that your immune system
is causing this and you're now just
battling your immune
system not a way to win the
healing it's not the way to win over the
Beast the system is
actually set up so we have these pot
holes that chip away at us and try to
bring us down one of them is the
autoimmune Theory telling you that your
body is attacking itself it's faulty
it's destroying itself and when that
happens it does not support your immune
system your your immune system needs to
know you're on board because your immune
system can
actually understand you it knows what
you want it works with you it's
connected to you like none other it's
it's a supernatural Force so your immune
system is a
supernatural
force that
can understand what you're
thinking what you're
saying and what you're
hearing
yep you always thought autoimmune made
no sense whoa rest of Soul said I have
learned more from you tonight than all
my years combined in nursing I am blown
away and I am honored truly thank you
lant says trigeminal neuralgia you
describe me to a te I will be getting
your book for geminal neuralgia make
sure you get the new edition right
here get the brain books if you don't
want to get them on sale at amazon.com
us go to the library and tell that
Library you want them if they don't
already have
them yep you guys it's been fun and um
but I am making an announcement pretty
soon probably this week but check out
the medical beam podcast at Apple
podcast bloodb brain
barrier okay now you guys I'm delivering
this information the information's from
above that's what's in the medical
medium
books and you know I droke around a
little bit and I don't
know and um and sometimes I get serious
right I'm serious too but I need you to
know something
that like
I know that so many of you guys are
really suffering and struggling because
the medical meme
Community is the PE is is the place
where the most sick come because they've
tried everything else out there and they
they didn't just come into the medical
medium community and buy a book or
whatever and or take a book out of the
library they didn't just come in because
that's the first place they wanted to
go millions of people people that have
the books around the world they tried
everything everything and they exhausted
themselves
financially emotionally and physically
and couldn't find the answers and so the
people in this community really do
struggle and they really do suffer and I
don't lose sight of that even though I'm
sitting here reading or talking to you
guys or you know kidding around about
something or whatever for a moment you
need to know that I know your struggles
and I know you're suffering and it
matters to me greatly because so many of
you have been through so
much like your stories and what you've
gone through people just don't even
understand because unless they know what
it's like and been in your shoes I want
I want you to know that I know many of
you guys have it hard and have had it
hard and uh I just want to say that keep
the faith keep the Hope going take one
day at a time one hour at a time
actually CU when you're sick with
chronic illness it's like 1 hour at a
time each day and I I know that I know
what that's like anyway I love you guys
and I will I will see you
again all right