we're here and we made it
praise our therapy brain shot therapy
yes therapy for the brain so we can fix
our brains anyway I'm exciting you guys
this is the 20-day brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge that's a mouthful I'm
excited this is day one day one of 20
days
am I crazy did I lose my mind
possibly I have I'm wondering because
why in God's name on this Earth would I
ever do 20-day challenge for free for
free anyway 20 days I'm committed and
I'm in that's the whole point I'm
committed are you guys committed are you
in
and let me just say this for the
dabblers
the dabblers out there if you only want
to do one of the 20 days you're welcome
there's no rules
no way
if you want to do one day you do one day
you want to do three days you do three
days I'm doing 20. but the bottom line
is you can pick a day if you want we're
on board we're all in it together either
way hang out even if you don't want to
do it hang out it's okay either way
we're gonna have a lot of fun sign up
for your free
grocery list
important go to medicalmedium.com and
sign up seriously seriously we're
talking about eating disorders a little
bit today by the way I'm gonna read a
little bit about eating disorders
that's going to be fun oh sign up to get
your free grocery shopping list and look
out for daily emails you have to sign up
to get the daily emails with a challenge
you have to sign up to do that anyway 20
day brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
we're going to do the robot during the
halftime by the way I forgot to do the
robot we're gonna do it during the
halftime
you guys I can't wait I'm really excited
about this let's get into a little bit
what's this
what is this
whoa right there the food fear shifter
that's the first thing we're doing food
for your shifter
let me read about it for a second too
okay if you guys don't mind
food fear can take different shapes
and forms for example apply this shot on
a regular basis if you're living with an
eating disorder
the food fear shifter is also a useful
tool when someone is pressuring you not
to eat healthily
did you ever have that did you ever have
that or someone is pressuring you not to
eat good someone's pressuring you not to
eat healthy and healthily
right hey check this out use the food
for your shifter if you guys just got on
here this is day one and we're doing the
food fear shifter as day one
use the food for your shifter if you're
upset about what you've been eating
lately are you upset about what you've
been eating lately then you should be
making this food for your shifter right
here if you're upset get ready for this
use this food for your shifter
if you're feeling locked up about food
in general did you ever feel locked up
about food in general like you just feel
stuck about food in general
okay
and check this out too afraid to eat
because you're having trouble figuring
out what foods you can eat comfortably
without flaring up symptoms or a
digestive discomfort too that's
interesting so let's keep on moving
forward I'm going to read more about
this what I want to move through a
little bit more let's get into it so
we're talking about eating disorders I'm
going to read a little bit out of brain
saver right here so
I forgot do you have your brain saver
this is a brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge brain saver it's all in here
so I'm excited so let's go there now
let's read a little bit about that
so I'm going to go to page
here we are page 272 page 273
I'm in the eating disorder chapter in
brain saver
so let's roll into it a little bit
we all
we can all become consumed by what we're
eating is that true
can we all become consumed about what
we're eating if you ever hear someone
say I don't think about food ever
I don't think about food it's not even
on my radar I eat when I want to eat
I'm not you know what I'm not really I'm
not
I'm not like stuck with the whole food
thing I could eat when I want eat what I
want whatever right no they're thinking
about food all the time that's the whole
point if you're a human being on this
planet do not get tricked by that if
you're a human being on this planet
you're thinking about food
you are no matter what kind of situation
is going on I'm reading a little bit of
the eating disorder chapter right here
and this chapter is huge and there's a
lot of information in it but I'm
scratching the surface a little bit
are we eating too much
has anybody been concerned about are we
eating too much
that's something I think a lot of people
are concerned about
are we eating too little have you ever
heard that before where there's people
that are concerned they're eating too
little
it's either you're eating too much or
you're eating too little what is it
right
I mean are we eating when we're not
hungry have you heard that one before
have you felt that like I'm eating when
I'm really not even hungry and I'm
eating right you hear that one a lot out
there do we eat so much we make
ourselves sick
has that happened to you do you know
somebody where it's like they eat so
much they make themselves sick
Phyllis said absolutely
are we into portion control have you
seen that before have you been in that
world where you're worried about portion
control this book is so incredible when
I just read when I just start reading a
paragraph in this brain saver book my
mind is blown like
so are we into portion control have you
done that whole thing like the portion
control thing
are we micromanaging our eating on a
daily basis it's another thing people
are worried about micromanaging
our food on a daily basis
do we convince ourselves that we're
eating in moderation or eating balanced
have you heard that one where people
they convince themselves I'm eating in
moderation is what I'm doing or I'm
eating balanced
I'm doing balance eating medical mediums
not balanced eating I'm going to do I
like balanced eating well what is that
balance eating then
do we tell ourselves we don't need much
food
are we eating the wrong things
I don't know are we eating the wrong
things
what are we eating
we could be eating the wrong things have
you read the medical medium book series
maybe you're eating the wrong things
do we punish ourselves for eating the
wrong things how many people punish
themselves for eating that chocolate
cake
and then they want permission to eat the
chocolate cake and I totally get it like
people want permission to eat that
chocolate cake right do you want
permission
it's like yeah no I only had a slice of
that chocolate cake don't worry about it
cacao's good for you you can have a
slice of the chocolate cake okay I feel
I feel I feel better about it now
permission to have a chocolate cake now
I feel better about it all
do we eat the wrong things to reward
ourselves I'm gonna get a reward I'm
gonna reward myself right now I'm gonna
eat that chocolate cake because I want
to reward myself that's what it is I
need a reward
what constitutes the wrong things
who's right who's wrong
this is incredible I'm reading out a
brain saver right now do you have the
book please say you do because the books
are really powerful they're filled with
information it's books you need both
right brain saver and brain saver
protocols
[Music]
I'm reading out of
where day one of the brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge we're doing food fear
shifter
I have this excitement welling up inside
of me because I know what's going to
happen
When anybody participates in this and
they do the 20 days with me and they're
doing the brain shot therapies every
single day and rewiring their brain I
know what's going to happen I know the
results they're going to get I have an
excitement I can't even explain
nicolinus as an IG I've had people make
me feel bad about food saying you don't
need to eat that or you know what to do
to lose weight I've always had a bad
relationship with food since I was
younger
let's keep on reading a little bit
Eating Disorders are rampant
yeah someone's like no they're not yeah
they are eating disorders are rampant
they can exist in every one of us yes
it wouldn't make sense okay here check
this out
we're all consumed about food if we
weren't it wouldn't make sense because
we have to be concerned about food when
people say I'm not concerned about food
that's not me I have no concerns about
food b s
capital b capital s
everybody's concerned about food or
they're an alien and they're not you
know aliens are concerned about food
everybody's concerned about food
or you cease to exist it's just an uh
you know on our radar
if we weren't it wouldn't make sense
because we have to be concerned about
food it's how we live work play function
you want to function you got to be
concerned about food
loving healing says I used to be I used
to stress so much about food always so
much Obsession and guilt two years on
medical medium protocols and I feel so
free food makes me happy now no more
guilt that's what I love about the
medical medium
food protocols in the medical medium
cleanses in the medical medium words of
wisdom from above because it frees us
from that
it really does
that's always been a part of our history
as humans we are focused on food right
what makes it a food disorder in today's
modern world is the amount of unhealthy
conditioning all around us combined with
contaminants in our brains so
food disorders can happen from our
brains being saturated with all kinds of
contaminations and all kinds of
different stuff that I talk about in the
medical medium book series our brains
get filled with it and that could make
things a lot more difficult
and so what we have to do is learn how
to eat in order and not have an eating
disorder it's more of like what can I
eat to heal myself what can I eat that's
going to change my life and turn my life
around there's nothing wrong with having
that sense of understanding and that
sense of knowing there's nothing wrong
with being like what can I eat to get
myself better what can I eat to heal
what can I eat to turn my life around
what's wrong with that nothing nothing's
wrong with that that's eating in order
that's putting things in perspective
that's putting things in order that's
putting things in the right situation
for your body it's like no I want to eat
to heal right
thank you
eating in order can have a few meanings
eating in order to heal
in order to heal
I gotta eat a certain way right now
okay eating in order to live
if I want to live
I'm gonna be eating eating in order to
survive if I want to survive eating in
order to thrive I want to thrive
these brain shot therapies after 20 days
of these brains out there after today
it just starts to happen the the power
of these brain shot therapies just blows
me away eating in order to function I
want to eat to function
eating in order to succeed I want to
succeed I want to be productive I want
to heal I want to
I want to be successful in anything I do
doesn't matter what it is even if it's
just cleaning my kitchen I want to be
successful at it
by the way I clean the kitchen yes I do
someone said to me the other day you
don't clean up stuff you don't do that
you don't vacuum clean yeah I do
I do all that stuff why those are
beneath me no they're not
you better believe
so yeah
so why Colin says I need to download
that Mantra in my brain what can I eat
to heal what can I eat to heal
a focus on food is not on its own
unhealthy
do not let anybody convince you that
focusing on food is unhealthy don't let
someone convince you of that that's a
bad convincing I'm serious that is not a
good thing
often when we're trying to take care of
ourselves holistically and heal from
symptoms and conditions buying the right
Foods consuming fruits vegetables eating
less processed foods looking after
ourselves in general we can feel like
we're trapped and we're alone and
worried about food in a bubble of our
own world unless we find our others like
us right so that's another thing once
you have to start healing and start
eating better we can feel like lonely
and lost and we're like stuck in this
bubble
foreign
alone and worried about food in a bubble
of our own world unless we find others
like us even when we're doing it right
life becomes all about what to eat how
healthy it is where to find it we can
get lost wondering does anyone else have
to worry about this so here's what I'm
talking about right here okay as you
Embark in healing and you're using food
to fix your brain and you're using food
to fix yourself and heal
physically emotionally right mentally
spiritually you're you're using food to
heal
it's gonna feel weird because it's going
to look like nobody else is you guys
it's going to look like no one else out
there is using food to heal no one else
is out there is focused on food you see
people in the streets you see people
driving by you see people whatever and
you're gonna think they're not like you
they don't have to worry about anything
but they're still worried to some degree
even if they're not eating healthy
they're still worried about what they're
eating everybody is worried about what
they're eating whether they say it or
not or tell you or not
yes every single person on this planet
has to worry about food it's natural
when you're trying to heal particular
illnesses and diseases and conditions
and symptoms it's especially natural to
worry about what you're eating if you're
trying to heal something if you're
trying to fix something in here if
you're trying to fix something in here
something's wrong you got those
autoimmune diagnoses you got all kinds
of anxiety and depression you guys got
all kinds of problems people have right
that everybody has you guys if any
things like that is happening you're
working on trying to heal it that's what
you're doing
you do have to be extra mindful about
what you eat if that mindfulness about
food is done the wrong way it can
contribute to an eating disorder
if it's done the right way
this is important this is when the
details matter right here it's one of
the places it matters it can correct an
eating disorder and teach you how to eat
properly
the traps out there and the potholes out
there make it so if you're trying to eat
to heal
it can create an eating disorder in a
lot of people if it's not done the right
way
I've seen this over and over again
what I love about the information from
above right SOC and the info from above
about how to heal it's not about
creating Eating Disorders it's about
reversing them and healing the brain and
healing the body
it's incredible information right here
it's all important you guys just so you
know if you just got on here I see a lot
more people coming on here we're just
just quickly we're day one of the brain
shot therapy cleanse challenge
so and it's a 20-day Branch out therapy
challenge it's going to be mind-blowing
of letting you know download your free
your free grocery shopping list go to
medicalmedium.com okay
make sure you have your books it's a
brain saver protocols
right in the brain saver book download
this right here we're doing 20
days of this brain shot therapy cleanse
Challenge and before I get lost in the
Eating Disorders chapter I just want you
to know where you where to get the
information when you sign up you'll then
get be able to get those daily emails
only if you sign up
great information
let's see medical media Army says I've
had every single eating disorder there
is
overeat check portion control check
moderation check no food check
intermittent fasting check nothing
worked for me nothing worked to make me
that thing worked for me
incredible credible information you guys
we're doing it
let's see cold White Springs says
McDonald's is an eating disorder
interesting
only medical medium protocol work to
heal me
that's in that last uh IG comment
okay all this is important information
let's get down to it right now
okay
eating the right items at the right time
can still feel as if you have an eating
disorder because of how others view it
others view it
one of the problems when you're trying
to heal is what others are viewing of
what you're doing
that's one of the problems
when you're trying to heal is what
others are viewing
other people are judging other people
got their eyes on you right how many
people have their eyes there's eyes on
them
keep that in mind because that can then
Propel someone to feel like they're
doing it wrong that they're in an eating
disorder
when you're trying to eat healthy others
often see it as too rigid
what do you do in your celery juice
again you're doing your celery juice one
more time what do you do in your brain
shot therapy one more time is it a
little too much
they may even even label it orthorexia
orthorexic right
when someone scoffs down a cheese pizza
right
in a Coca-Cola
and they're calling you orthorexic
because you're trying to heal yourself
let's just insane
Erica Alex says and that mm protocols
healed my worsening bulimia whoa that I
suffered with for years
oh God said I'm just happier here and
healing so many people have been through
that and it's it's just so hard I tried
doctors and therapists and nothing
worked when all hope was lost the
medical medium healed me completely with
no relapses incredible
so when someone names somebody
orthorexic which you'll read about later
in this chapter I have an orthorexia
section in this chapter you've got to
read this book brand saver Michelle L
says the bullying about what I eat has
been unbelievable capitalized
okay
they may even label it orthorexia which
you'll read about later this chapter you
can get blamed for too much fruit
how many of you been blamed for too much
fruit first of all fruit wasn't allowed
in any of the eat better diets out there
medical medium
spent the last 30 plus years bringing
fruit into the health world because it
wasn't allowed
the only place fruit was allowed was
believe it or not the the food pyramid
where they said you still should have
some servings of fruit meanwhile in all
of the health realm Alternative Health
fruit was never allowed it was demonized
and I spent decades trying to bring it
in right and then medical medium info
with the millions of books around the
world and all of the people seeing that
fruit and the wild blueberries now all
the eat better guys that were like
they're chameleons they're lizards man
because they change their colors every
second they're lizards and now like yes
we let in wild blueberries yes we let in
fruit fruits good for you and our eat
better diet it's like unbelievable it's
like
foreign
but fruit is is critical but how many
people were blamed for eating fruit
Laura Robinson says mm has healed me and
my hair is thicker and stronger amazing
hey have you heard this before not
enough protein
you're not eating enough protein where's
your protein protein robot we'll do that
half time
too many carbs whoa that's too many
carbs don't eat that banana first of all
it's a fruit and it's way too many carbs
how about that one how many people are
said to that lizards is right I saw that
on IG you like that one lizards it's
endless bringing your own food to
holidays is difficult not eating at
events where the menu doesn't work for
you always packing snacks orientating
your life around the farmers markets or
making special requests at restaurants
none of this should be considered an
eating disorder when what you're doing
is eating in order to truly heal did you
guys hear that how many people get
punished for actually picking and
choosing at the restaurant packing
snacks making sure you're taking care of
yourself having like your fruit with you
okay all of that how many people are
punished for making special requests in
restaurants or punished for like
bringing their food to an event or not
so many people are punished in that way
now don't we want to feel normal
to go out and eat a pizza or some fried
food or cheesy pasta or a grass-fed
burger or maybe some sushi
to go over to a friend's house and eat
whatever they're serving have ice cream
afterwards
to eat whatever's on the table at a
family holiday without worrying about
how it's going to affect your bloating
your stomach your cramps your gastritis
your diarrhea your constipation your
heartburn your acid reflux your
indigestion and acne
we all want to feel normal right we all
want to scoff down that cheese pizza no
problem and eat whatever we want to do
the irony is that all the people who
seem normal
actually
normalize dysfunctional eating and have
Eating Disorders themselves
I mean seriously
so that's what's happening out there
right everybody wants to be normal but
the whole thing is that normal our
Eating Disorders that's the whole point
let's see rolanki says yes the
functional doctors did all cat good
sensitivity Foods food sensitivity tests
and I couldn't eat this and many veggies
were out too it was horrible that's
another thing the food sensitivity test
that I've watched people go through hell
with for years
and what happened to their food eating
I always say this okay
so functional doctors said don't eat
fruits and certain vegetables and that
whole thing right so then you you're
stuck with this food sensitivity test
where you were just eating what meat and
meat only right red Rosia says or eat
this burger and eat this pork rib you
need to gain weight as if that's the
only way to gain weight I could eat
clean and Gain
I think what people don't realize
really is that how many people are
ostracized and made fun of for trying to
eat
healthy for real healthy right
Hillary said
my eating disorder was completely
obliterated when I learned and applied
these protocols and I don't apply it as
often as I want but I am still healed
from that incredible
look you know you can always come back
as well come back to the medical medium
information too you can always come back
and then here's what I've noticed some
people in their life when they get a
medical medium book and they read it
they're at a different point in their
life and they need to come back to it
years later and then they read it and
they see it in a whole different light
they're like why didn't I see it that
way what happened why did I just lose
two more years
all right so we all want to feel normal
the irony is that with all the people
who seem normal actually normalize
dysfunctional eating and have Eating
Disorders themselves they don't eat
correctly no one has ever been taught
what our brain and body need what foods
our organs need what foods to eat for a
physical spiritual emotional and mental
health
were left to our own demise here on
planet Earth no one has taught the right
things it's painstaking and here's a
point I just want to be clear about you
tell me if this point is or not
you tell me go ahead judge me I need you
guys to judge me on this point right
you got all these eat betters you know
things out there books and programs you
got all these exactly all cat tests and
food sensitivity tests
but what do you think about this
all those professionals don't know why
we're sick science and research doesn't
know why we're sick they don't they
don't have the answers but yet they're
right about what you should be eating I
guess
am I wrong to say that
so they're right about what you should
be eating when they don't know why
you're even sick the true cause
and what's bringing you down in your
life
and why you're suffering if they don't
know why why why then why are they right
and what they're telling you to eat
when I think about that I'm like okay
in order to heal you have to get your
Foods figured out
you have to understand your foods and
get them in order
that's what we're doing right now we're
doing the brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge right 20 days of it that alone
is a powerful tool and that's what we're
doing right now you have to understand
your foods and get them in order when
your foods are in disorder that's when
you get an eating disorder when you
don't know what the hell we eat when the
hell to eat it well you don't know what
you're doing
The Whole World's all scrambled up as to
what's good for you eggs are good for
you you need your protein make sure
you're on your eggs you need a good hard
cheese don't do the American soft cheese
you need a good hard cheese as if that's
the answer you need to eat good butter
grass-fed butter that's the answer you
need to be a vegan you need to be a
plant-based person you need to be eating
lots of nut Butters only like the amount
of stuff you need to be carnivore you
need to be this
like it's Insanity out there and that
Insanity alone can create Eating
Disorders already
many times
all right
you have to understand your foods and
get them in order when your foods are in
disorder that's when you can get an
eating disorder everyone has has been
there wondering what to eat and everyone
is guessing
guessing that's what I was trying to say
all right you guys read a little bit
more but I'm just telling you right now
we're day one
we're doing 20 days call me crazy
because that's one killer long cleanse
and I'm excited about it so I'm on page
273 in Eating Disorders chapters where I
am I got more to go
so let's go a little bit more many times
food contributes to not feeling well
eating foods that are not appropriate
for healing can contribute to developing
a condition illness or disease
contributing
not the cause
but contributing keep that in mind so
what seemed to be normal eating normal
acting normal being normal with food
wasn't a good normal because it was
contributing to someone getting sick
eating normal acting normal being normal
with food wasn't a good normal it's it
might have seemed like a good normal
because you were with family and friends
it might have seemed like a good normal
because the food seemed tasty and
satiating it might have seemed like a
good normal because it was convenient is
your mind blowing right now like sure am
I just blowing up it might have seemed
like a good normal because it offered
comforting Sensations that connected you
with past memories in life
it wasn't good for other reasons though
people who try to use food to heal
especially young people will frequently
be blamed for disordered eating in the
older days it was even more common
particularly if it was a young adult
trying to heal from chronic illness by
eating fruits and vegetables they could
be taken to a clinic and force-fed
prompted by well-meaning family members
who were actually the ones with the
Eating Disorders did that ever happen to
any of you guys
a lot of you guys you got you know you
got you're seasoned you got some years
under your belt you're not like 18 years
old or 20 years old right maybe you've
had this happen to you a long time ago
where a family just basically said we're
just taking you out of here because
you're trying to heal and you're trying
to eat carrots and we're just we gotta
just take you out of here and put you in
a clinic somewhere
radioactive heart says yeah it's
exhausting I feel like everybody jumps
up and down in joy I eat badly and I
made fun of for being sick
I think it's moving up and down so hold
on so you're saying let me read it again
radioactive heart yeah it's exhausting I
feel like everybody jumps up and down
enjoy if I eat badly and I made fun of
got you got you being being sick and
Bones I feel ostracized trying to figure
out my health problems totally
understand I feel for you and I get it I
do I do
we're in a better safer place now with
food than we were just two decades ago
people can be dragged out of their
houses
by guys in white coats putting you in
straight jackets years ago it was done
it's just terrifying
bring in more plant Foods is more
accepted not fully accept it believe it
or not but more accepted just becoming
more upset accepted a lot of confusion
around eating disorders and healthy
eating remains and rightfully so there
are many Trends in the health field that
aren't right for the body and they can
rain on the parade of better approaches
and holistic health
medical meme information has healed so
many people around the world
but there's
Trends out there that ruin it
because they're so scrambled up with
misinformation
some health professionals become
Reckless and it ends up looking bad for
everyone in the natural health field
people venturing into certain cleanses
certain detox programs and certain diets
already have eating disorders and when
they do these Reckless diets and
cleanses it worsens their eating
disorders
creating more confusion fear and
frustration this is critical right here
this could give Healthy eating a bad
name and even start a new eating
disorder because the makers of these
diets and programs out there have no
idea why anyone is sick to begin with
that's the point right there you guys
it's a huge point they have no idea why
anybody is sick to begin with why should
I trust medical mediums protocols
because you finally have answers why
you're sick
why should I track why should I trust
medical medium food protocols and his
lenses
because you know why you got sick to
begin with why shouldn't I trust those
out there they don't know why anyone got
sick because the makers of the diets and
programs have no idea why anyone is sick
to begin with so the information they
are giving others to use
is not in a good order for the body
all right you guys let's get moving on
we got a half time coming up
too so keep that in mind we're in day
one of the medical medium brain shot
therapy challenge
this chapter is so mind-blowing can I
just tell you if you got one second
right now I'm scratching the surface of
the Eating Disorders chapter wait till
you crack it open
wait till you crack it open it's in
brain saver right there don't miss out
get that book get its companion book
Brain saver protocols right do not miss
out on that so let's go to page 445
if you guys don't mind medical medium
brain shot therapy so what are we doing
what is the medical medium brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge what is this I
see before me
medical medium brain shot therapy is
what we're doing here's a brain
here's a brain here's a brain well I
don't have it well I got a bunch of
jelly beans in here is what I have but
anyway it's about healing up the brains
okay medical me and brain shot therapy
offers instant relief because it's
configurations of synergistically
combined Foods right wild food herbs
leafy greens fruit vegetables but in a
way
that helps to crack what's happening
inside our heads
this therapy is miraculous
I can say that
it's miraculous what I've seen the brain
shot therapy do and the branch out there
be cleanses you out there is mind
blowing I'm just saying if you just got
here and you don't even know what we're
doing
so anyway you guys I would love to also
see what you guys are experiencing have
you guys tried the brain shot have you
tried food fear shifter we're doing it
today what did you feel what was your
results did what did you experience
please share
a story a real
um a post okay tag at Medical medium
hashtag at Medical medium so I can see
it I can't see it unless both of that
happened tag at Medical medium and
hashtag would love to know how you guys
are feeling the healing shots of medical
media brain shot therapy are tools that
come from above then that's the
difference right there this isn't just
hey I'm trying to make something taste
good oh let me try to make a really good
feel-good shot a tasty shot let me just
put this together oh let me put that in
there oh it tastes pretty good people
will like it delicious it's a cool juice
that's not what this is
these brain shots are composed of
specific combinations of ingredients
working together systematically to heal
the brain
so I'm going to go to page 515 now in
the brain saver book we're in the
shifter shots okay actually we're gonna
go we are in the shifter shots
that's where we are
here we are medical medium brain shot
Therapies
so what's really cool about this we're
doing entry level keep that in mind
John zuk says your book looks like an
encyclopedia where can I buy it
amazon.com us if you're here in the US
or on YouTube
there are two books so don't just get
one make sure you get protocols as well
it was one big book yes they are like
encyclopedias your mind will be blown
John zuk if your mind isn't blown
then I don't know what to say because
wait till you read these it's nothing
like anyone has ever seen
hands down these books okay are like
history makers
okay when it comes down to brain shot
therapy cleanses because that's what
we're doing we're doing an entry level
20-day brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge
these cleanses are imperative for what's
to come in the world
have you been noticing how crazy how
how
crazy
the world has become
and how many people are falling ill
it's unbelievable I mean it was
predicted by a spirit of compassion but
still unbelievable what's happening
right now
this is actually sad
and unbelievable
the onslaught of domestic chemical
warfare in our homes right you know our
schools our institutions and our society
today has reached catechismic
proportions when you embark on these
cleanse options
you're using your free will
right and your intention to clean and
protect the organ that Harbors the
knowledge
of your past
keep that in mind right here this is the
organ that harbors
Harbors your memories
the information that's here
and this is the organ you're protecting
with the brain shot therapy cleanse
the brain shot
oh this is really cool right here
okay
when you embark on these cleanse options
you're using your free will and your
intention to clean to protect the organ
that Harbors the knowledge of the past
present and soon to be your future and
your future life it Harbors your soul so
what you're doing is you're protecting
the organ that Harbors your soul right
here there's no better organ to protect
and that's what we're doing
it just blows my mind when I even think
about it
all right we're in the entry level
that's where we are brain shot therapy
cleanse levels right there
we're doing the 20-day
we're at the entry level okay entry
level is really cool you could drink one
brain shot per per day right you can
have your choice 10 20 30 days we're
doing 20.
I still think I'm crazy for doing 20.
because this
it's a lot but we're gonna do 20.
what better crazy
your choice of which brain shot option
is day to day you can choose what brain
shot you want the 20 I'm doing is right
here so go to medicalmean.com and get
the information you need right
the books have all the details in here
too but everything you need as well
there are two books for people
two books it's the protocols and the
Brain saver book get them both these
books have all the details so you can
customize your unique needs
so I'm excited we're doing entry level
right here
so like I said your choice at which
brain shot option from day to day
incorporate as many other medical medium
tools you desire if you're doing
something medical medium right now if
you're actually in a mono eating cleanse
or you're in something else or you're in
a morning cleanse or whatever you're
doing you can still do this if you're
curious if that's what you want to do
try to drink a minimum of 50 ounces of
water throughout the day
and that can include even coconut water
be mindful not to drink the water too
close to your shot so when we make our
brain shot
I'm not going to go and all of a sudden
drink
a gallon of water a second after I
consumed the brain shot therapy keep
that in mind too right
customizing
you can do it one you can do one shot a
day you can do three shots a day you can
do two shots a day of the same shot
I'm gonna do three shots
a day for the next 20 days I'm
customizing it to myself
you can do it that way too you can do
one shot
you can do it that way as well okay
so keep that in mind
we're in the shifter shots
we're doing the food fear shifter shot
there it is
and the food fair shifter shot
I'm gonna go right back to it
let me go find the food for your shifter
shot here it is this is the shot we're
doing right now
Emma read a little bit about it
food fair shifter shot
you can use it if someone's pressuring
you not to eat healthily
you can use this food food for your
shifter shot if you're upset about what
you've been eating lately
you can use this shot if you're feeling
locked up about food in general afraid
to eat because you're having trouble
figuring out what foods to eat
and what foods make you comfortable
you can use this shot if you're
experiencing other symptoms and
conditions and you're afraid of changing
your diet to heal
life coaching nurse Kim says as a nurse
I'll say this info is the only truth out
there listen up folks thank you so much
aw and SOC
incredible
you can use a shot if someone wants you
to eat healthily yet you're afraid of
fruit herbs
leafy greens wild Foods vegetables
maybe you can use this if you have an
unexplained dislike or fear of certain
foods that are healthy so if you got
like fear about food this is the one to
use
you can use this shot if you're having a
hard time letting go of a comfort food
that's harming you Mildred says Anthony
can you please mention them the page
number page 482
food fair shifter
right there
all right
see a little half time and then we're
gonna do the shot
you guys want to do the robot
I'm actually missing the robot already
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's go
foreign
[Music]
guys the bot is back
it's back
[Music]
all right
20 day breaks out there be Glenn
challenge
day one
food fair ship there
let's go let's do it
getting the juicer out
nice
let's go you guys let's do it let's get
this done
have you ever tried this shot
because I love this one it's incredible
let's roll half cup
tightly packed fresh dill
I hope you like Dill
because this is a very
potent herb
very potent herb
okay
we got that in there
half cup tightly packed spinach
that's next try to do it in order if you
can like as it directs in the book
Drake Clark
what are the rules for doing three
different shots in one day how many
hours apart
if you read the book it says space them
four hours apart
if you read the book
okay guys
food for your shifter are you doing it
with me right now
are we doing it together so that's about
tightly packed because I'm talking about
tightly packed right there let's move
into the next one
three quarters of a cup of
sword mango
Frozen mango works or you can do fresh
mango I don't have a fresh mango right
now but I love love love love
Frozen mango too okay there we go
nice
and then we're gonna go with some celery
right a quarter of a stock
let's get some celery down in there
incredible
now the amazing thing about these shots
is they're so potent you can feel it as
it's entering you so keep that in mind
okay
now what I have on here I have the if
you have this juicer I have the celery
end cap the high compression
right and what that does is it squeezes
every last drop practically out of the
food
so this is the Omega mm 1500 if you're
curious right
and you can just you can just juice with
this all day if you wanted to juice and
stuff but what's powerful about this
is what you're going to see is you're
not going to see
all this wet sloppy stuff come out of
this end if that's the case you're going
to need like a lot of other juicers
you're going to need instead of a half
cup of spinach or a half cup of Dill
you're going to need that much still
probably that much spinach because it's
all going to come out the pulp's going
to come out flying sloppy it's just
going to be sloppy mushy you know wet
right
okay there we go
so I have a screen on here so I'm just
moving some of it through the screen
okay there we go
and if you want to
all right I'm gonna take my screen off
for the second here that's my shot right
there
didn't even need that it was incredible
didn't even need this
all right
let me show you this right up close
maybe we'll even
that's it
you guys have your shot ready
I'm gonna take a little sip
[Music]
there's a feeling I get
and there you guys do these shots so you
know what I'm talking about right where
it just starts to come over you
because it's about the combination the
amounts and what it's for
that's my second little step
I'm nursing this one for the moment
but I could feel it
[Music]
I get like a charge
right now I'm feeling like I'm getting
charged up all here
right from the brain stem really it
feels like the brain stem is getting
charged so I feel energy moving through
the brain stem right now I don't feel it
on the top I feel it in the brain stem
area right now for me
I'm going to send the whole thing down
[Music]
bartender
give me another
and I'm feeling all through my body
right now
it's incredible
you guys have you tried this one you
if you want to make all three and make
them all at once
seal them in an air type container if
you can
put them in the fridge in an airtight
container if you want to do that Monica
M says can you freeze the shots aw yes
you can if you want to freeze them you
can for some reason if you need to yes
you can
incredible have you guys done this one
what do you feel right now let me know
how you you know tag on medical medium
medical medium you know when you do your
post whatever your real estate stores I
would love to see them I'd love to
repost them if I can that would be
incredible
and it's best to fresh and not frozen
and not sitting all day but it's but you
still if you had to do it that way then
I understand
Emily Marshall says we don't need to
strain the shot then you don't have to
if you don't want to I I do a little bit
of a straining
it's really potent
it's really powerful
I love the food for your one
I get like
the sensations haven't gone away from me
they're still there after sending that
down and I still feel it around the
brain stem for that one which is really
incredible
I had a strainer for my shot
amazing Pamela Miller says I felt it
instantly as going down the hatch
like I the thing is is the brain shot
therapies that's how I feel it too
and it puts me in a whole different mode
a whole different mood it's really
incredible
if the be sure says is one brain shot
enough like a single glass shot it is
enough indeed because depending on
ingredients some rain shots created up
to five glass shots that's okay
you can use what's left over too and
make another shot absolutely what's
going to happen is variations of how
much how much juice content is in each
thing you're using is going to kind of
vary sometimes you get mangoes that are
not as juicy sometimes you'll get
spinach just a little bit more drier
sometimes you'll get an herb that's a
you know drier with a not a lot of water
content in its stems and all of that
plays a role when you're making it and
that was all accounted for when Spirit
of compassion was designing the brain
shot Therapies
Lisa boxes mm School
indeed 20 days of it I hope you guys are
excited as excited as I am and what's to
come
Stevie Bella says while doing the shot
challenge do you recommend that this be
done at a particular time for instance
someone has done 20 to 40 ounces of
lemon water 16 to 20 ounces of celery
juice is that shot next the book gives
exact details to that particular
question that you have it'll it'll spell
it out for you which is incredible
but great question
you guys
I'm jacked up from that food fear
shifter
like
I'm not afraid to eat a whole cheese
pizza with sausage on it now and I'm
kidding I'm not gonna eat that anyway
but seriously
it's actually kind of like lightened by
heart
I feel it's like it's working my brain
stem right now
it's what it's doing I feel like it's in
here it's radiating around here and then
I feel a cooling sensation happen from
here on down which is so weird that's
how I'm feeling that's what I'm
experiencing right now
so that's the experiences I'm having in
the moment just letting you know you
guys
all right got the book in front of me
right now going to page 272.
eating disorder chapter actually I'm
gonna go to page 277 is what I'm gonna
do
let's go there
these are big books
just keep that in mind
okay 277 food fear section in the Eating
Disorders chapter in brain saver
oftentimes an eating disorder develops
because of a symptom
I wanted to ask you guys a question how
many
how many of you experienced and I'm on
page 277 right now how many people
experienced
where
a symptom came over you
you got your first symptom or you got
sick and then eating disorders what
feels like eating disorders came
afterwards
how many people experience that because
I know a lot of people experience that
a symptom related to not being able to
swallow correctly may be choking nausea
pain in the stomach a feeling of
tightness in the throat or chest
how many people got like
anxiety disorders
right a condition where symptoms of
anxiety and then that
followed up and eating disorder because
of the anxiety did that ever happen to
you I'm saying you're saying I did
you're saying yes so it's like you got
it your first symptoms you got your
first anxiety attacks you got your first
panic attacks
and then
what came with that
was all of a sudden eating problems
because you had anxiety it started with
that or what about a tightness of the
throat what about a tightness
of the chest right so maybe you got this
symptom where it's the tightness of the
chest tightness of the throat or maybe
you got a stomach symptom
did you guys ever have your first
stomach symptoms where you're like
serious bloating serious stomach
symptoms going on
and then that actually created an eating
disorder now you don't know what to eat
because your stomach's all wonky things
are all strange with your stomach you
don't know what to eat
and so then an eating disorder followed
after the symptom of having stomach
problems having a throat tightness
having chest tightness having anxiety
yes too what about like
OCD as well and then that follows into
an eating disorder because of OCD you're
suffering from or struggling from
a symptom related to not being able to
swallow correctly choking nausea pain in
the stomach or feeling of tightness in
the throat or chest right and instead of
the Rope kindness in the chest
we're losing the sense of taste or smell
that's another thing that throws people
into Eating Disorders it's the losing
the taste or the smell
this is where someone is living their
life and they're eating just as anybody
else would be eating and then these
symptoms start to develop you're going
through life you feel like you're just
normally doing what you're doing
you're eating what you're eating you're
eating what everybody else is eating
everything seems fine and dandy and then
the symptoms happen
and now an eating disorder starts
in some cases if it's a chronic nausea
for example then Foods become pick and
choose
chronic nausea that's a huge one right
there
that's a big one actually
so many people have gone through that
where it's like you got the chronic
nausea and then you're in trouble it's a
game of what's going to help ease my
nausea what's going to help my nausea
right Amy has a question over there on
YouTube or wait just Selena's question
so grateful so much of my OCD is gone
thanks to Medical medium
Amy has a question there on YouTube can
we do the shots on the 369 cleanse yes
you can
yes yes yes question here on YouTube
Angela
I feel more energy when I do these brain
shots and the pathogen exposure shots
start staved off covet when I sat
next to co-workers
got covet at the Holiday party whoa so
you staved it off incredible the
pathogen exposure shot that's amazing
so what happens is when people get
nausea that really triggers often to
Boom a Cascade of
Eating Disorders right
what's not helping this nausea what's
helping this nausea what foods do I eat
because I'm nauseous do any of these
Foods I'm eating contribute to my aunt
nausea weight that food made me nauseous
but it made me nauseous the other day
it's not making me nauseous today wait
that food is making me nauseous again
what is it and that creates the Eating
Disorders because it's like
that food was working for me last week
it was working for me yesterday how come
it's not working for me today
what's not helping with this nausea do
any of these Foods I'm eating contribute
to it how come when I'm not eating I
still have the nausea then that's
another thing too
then our mind Consciousness starts to
pick up patterns and habits because of
small bursts of PTSD developing how many
guys
how many people you know
have PTSD around food
post-traumatic stress around food and
eating right
because at PTSD around food and eating
can be like in tens
you eat something and you're nauseous so
you identify that food is being the
problem
she learned to avoid that food
just as you get comfortable eating
another food thinking you're safe and
good you get nauseous again
so then that's another food you're
uncomfortable eating suspecting it's
contributing to your problem this can
carry on into other Foods as well nausea
doesn't usually receive a diagnosis
besides nausea but then we end up with
an eating disorder
nausea doesn't usually receive a
diagnosis besides nausea or maybe
nervousness or anxiety if everything
checks out okay in the abdomen it's
usually passed off as someone being too
sensitive but then we get the PTSD
and with that PTSD we end up getting the
Eating Disorders with that PTSD
happens to so many people
you guys I'll see you tomorrow
for day two
of the brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge make sure if you haven't
signed up you sign up at
medicalmedium.com download your free
grocery shopping list and if you don't
sign up
you won't get daily emails letting you
know what's going on with the brain shot
therapy challenge including tools and
other things that you might need so make
sure you're ready for it today was food
fair shifter what do I see on the list
right here
tomorrow pathogen exposure
Gonna Knock those pathogens out is what
we're gonna do that's what tomorrow is
day two of the brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge
are we really gonna do this
are we gonna do it 20 days of the bridge
out therapy challenge are we
are we unbelievable
come on
unbelievable
[Music]
seriously
that's a bad robot I gotta practice up
my robot now
that's not a good robot either
moonwalk
hey guys
I'm serious
day two's tomorrow don't miss it
come on
we're gonna take care of ourselves
follow the medical medium on Instagram
follow it on telegram follow it on
Rumble follow it
everywhere if you can including Twitter
right fall Medical medium I'm doing
telegram messages exclusive to telegram
by the way
all right you guys
and make sure you got your books I'll
see you guys