right now episode 10 released
do you know what the show's about have
you listened to it
um tingles numbness
burning skin jaw pain
back pain ticks spasms
twitches body pain
feeling of being on a boat dizziness
where it gets so bad where you're kind
of feeling like you're gonna fall to the
ground
or you're gonna just topple over yes you
guessed it
neurological symptoms that's what we're
talking about episode 10.
did you catch it and it is out
i explain and talk about all the
different symptoms
including what comes along with it like
the anxiety
tightness in the chest how about that
do you ever experience that too you get
tightness in the chest you don't know
what's going on you don't know why
have you caught this episode because it
is mind-blowing
and it's a apple podcast so it's medical
medium podcast at apple podcast
that's where the episode is so make sure
you go there that's the uncensored
platform uncensored episode if you hear
it i know that a lot of you guys here
none of the platforms are trying to or
meaning like or you're used to but
that's different this isn't the old
radio show this is the medical medium
podcast at apple podcast
and it's uncensored at apple podcast so
i'm just letting you know that's the
place to really
listen to it to make sure there isn't
little pieces missing but neurological
symptoms i go into
depth about it and hey you know have you
gotten to a point with your neurological
symptoms where
people don't understand what you're
going through because i hear that all
the time
i have people come to me and say look i
have all these symptoms
and they're really in my way and they're
really hard on me but people think i
look
fine from the outside so they're like
you're okay
no big deal they pat you on the back
like you're all right
just don't worry about it you look good
you look
fine and meanwhile you're struggling
with the tightness of chest or
tightness and tightness in the chest or
you're struggling with tingles and
numbness or
dizziness feeling feeling like you're on
the boat of some kind
feeling like your body hurts your jaw
pain your neck pain
your lower back hurts got restless legs
you can't sleep good at night your feet
hurt you feel numbness on your
extremities and your fingers and toes
and you know these are just some of the
symptoms plus anxiety
it's great to see you guys come on here
it's so awesome and
so you've got to catch this episode it's
really packed
in each other just says eachother is
healing oh my goodness this
episode was so packed with information i
am listening again to catch it all
this one is packed so you're gonna have
to guys are gonna have to check it out
um medical medium podcast at apple
podcast neurological symptoms
that's something so many people deal
with they deal with the panic attacks
with it they deal with
their body goes numb they get kind of
spacey and disconnected
they get the brain fog with it right did
you check out that brain fog episode you
might want to check out that brain fog
episode the last one
that's a powerful episode
and undiagnosed dizziness people get
exactly the link is in the description
you don't want to miss this episode
it is packed lynnette says great episode
incredible so you caught that i'm so
excited that you caught that episode
amazing walla green hello i'm on the
third i'm on my third listen right now
this was fantastic i felt heard and
validated
all the feelings i hadn't explained so
wireless listening to it for three three
times you're listening to the episode
for three times
uh regina says the podcast is amazing
um hey soc says hi back
so you guys i'm just really proud of you
for all the hard work you're doing on
your symptoms and conditions and your
healing
but you know it's so hard for people and
it's so hard when you have these
symptoms when you have
the tightness in the throat tightness in
the chest the dizziness the tingles on
your face the jaw pain
the neck pain the back pain and then
your feet hurt and your knees hurt and
you can't walk that great or
you can't do those big exercises yet or
however you're going through your life
or you feel dizziness or you feel like
you're on a boat
all of that so i understand that there's
so many different
neurological symptoms and a lot of times
nobody knows
those are the neurological symptoms
sandy says just listen to the podcast
and it's on point great info for all can
you guys
share it at all can you just share it
with whoever you think needs it
share this episode uh episode 10
it's the neurological symptom episode
okay it's body pain
dizziness tingles uh oh boy
oh crap um oh shoot so it's a real
serious episode and it's packed with
information
share it with people that you think need
it that you think people can use it
because it'd be really helpful um anya
said
great great episode thank you so much
i'm on my healing journey incredible
so proud of you guys really and and it's
really that
packed with information just so you know
and
the thing is is what people don't
understand
what they don't get is that when you
start getting neurological symptoms
when you start getting the aches and
pains and the fatigue and you feel like
you feel like you got sandbags on your
your feet you feel like you have
sandbags on your legs you feel like you
have sandbags
just you know like holding your arms
down and you feel weakness in the limbs
and you feel
uh a little dry in the throat you feel
weakness in the limbs and you feel like
your fingers hurt and you feel your
pinkies are hurting and tingles and
numbness
all through your body and you know what
i find is that people don't get it
unless they've been in your shoes
they don't understand unless they've
been there with you you know and it's
hard
for a lot of people who don't know what
this feels like they don't know about
the tightness in the chest and
the panic attacks and your arms go numb
and your
pinkies start to hurt and you get the
trigger thumbs and the ticks and the
spasms all through the body
and different kinds of symptoms or the
eye floaters what about that where
you're getting the eye floaters
and all the different snow the snow in
the eyes all of that that syndrome
and a lot of people are also in pain
their jaw hurts
back of their head hurts their ears hurt
they feel kind of like
numb all of that so it's really
important to know that
it's it's there are answers out there
there are
reasons why we have these symptoms and i
cover in great
detail in this neurological episode so
episode 10
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
that's where it is
sarah says sarah burton says wow best
podcast ever
had me in tears boat dizziness
you're the only one who described this
so well re renewed my faith in healing
so sarah you got the whole boat thing
and the whole dizziness
where you feel like you're on a boat
does it ever happen where when you're
walking along and it's just you feel
like you're gonna topple over
or you feel like you're you're you're
you're gonna topple to the left or
topple to the right
it's really hard it's it really is arjun
says hi anthony blessings from the
netherlands
whoa netherlands i'm i'm healing from
parkinson's
applying your information amazing
amazing i'm so proud of you just so you
know i really am
it matters to have answers it
matters to have answers to neurological
symptoms these symptoms
plague people you guys know how it works
you guys
know you know what it's like when you're
seeing your third neurologist your first
neurologist your second neurologist
you start out at your doctor's first
your your normal doctor
if some people even have a doctor
because it's some people can't even
afford a doctor and they're living with
these symptoms
go to your first doctor and you go to
your second doctor
and then now it's like hey off to a
neurologist and now to another
neurologist and it's really difficult
for so many people lorraine l hey
lorraine
just listened amazing the end is
powerful
and it got me a bit choked up um can
sense your passion and drive the key is
how do we help people how do we help
people
find their way to healing how do we let
them know lorraine that
there are answers because i know i know
lorraine you've dealt with a lot of
stuff with your health you're really
seasoned you've been there you've done
that
you you know how it works and i just
want people to actually know that there
are answers and there is a way to heal
and the first step
is to know what's wrong and and even
with that
to understand the symptoms like why do i
have tingles
why am i numb why is my limb not like
one of my limbs not feeling strong
how come my my legs feel like they have
sandbags attached to them how come i
have fatigue
how come i'm struggling in some way how
come
things just aren't feeling good and i
can't find my way
through this and and what about things
like burning tongue
and like you know and and and vibrations
like laying in bed and feeling
vibrations all through your body
feeling them through your legs and
feeling them through your body in your
chest like you feel like something's
humming
and buzzing inside of you and what about
ringing in the ears
what about ringing in the ears ringing
in the eardrums
buzzing in the ears popping in the ears
you guys
have you had any of this and what about
anxiety with all of this and
these symptoms are serious they could
really hold people down the neurological
episode
episode 10 you got to catch this episode
please
share it with others please and think
about leaving a review if you enjoyed
the episode
this medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast
that's the place link is in the
description
please share and listen to it more than
once because it's packed
with information and you can't just get
all that information i listen to it
again because after i finish it
i listen to it again right away before
right before i
send it out and i listen and i'm like oh
my god
there's so much information about
symptoms there's so much information
about the causes
there's so much information about what
to do it's like oh
it's in quids packed stella says i am
amazed
that this came at the exact time i
needed to see it
i love cell i love when it happens when
there's this divine
timing that occurs when something like
this happens this didn't divine
timing it's just it's just so special
i'm so happy that this happened like
that for you it means the world
to me it really does um
so vegan sabina says that podcast
episode was such an
a powerful one so many people have these
types of symptoms
especially my mom so vegan sabina your
mom has these symptoms oh my god
and thank you for helping and to help
her get back
or back into her health you know what it
means the world to me knowing that your
mom
has some answers at least can listen to
this episode
and can hear what's going on with people
how they struggle and you know what
unless someone's been in their shoes
it's different with a family member
because
you can have a family member that has
this and that maybe you don't need to be
in their shoes because you feel it and
you're like oh my god
but there's a lot of people out there
that they don't they don't know what
this is like to have the tingles the
numbness the burning pain the burning
jaw the gums the
pain in the jaw pain in the neck pain in
the back of the head migraines with it
nausea what about nauseousness too what
about
the dizziness feeling like you're on a
boat and weak limbs and feeling like you
have sandbags attached to your legs and
back pain and and you're buzzing and
vibrating and humming and got ringing in
the ears
this is serious and people deal with
this and you're on your third
neurologist and then you're on another
doctor
then another doctor but what's causing
this um barbara
cabone says this podcast is out now
question mark gotta watch
medical medium podcast at apple podcasts
the link is in the description don't
miss this it's
free free free free free free i mean
you know what medical media information
free free
it and and just because it's free don't
mean it doesn't work
because it has a track record of healing
millions worldwide
the results are in medical medium
information has healed more people
worldwide
than any other information in
alternative health dimensional health
when it comes down to mystery things and
mystery illness and overall everything
um so anyway and if you don't have an
apple device
and you can just go to medicalmedium.com
okay
go to the menu podcast in the menu and
just figure it out you can easily
listen to it there michelle l how are
you only a higher source
can be this accurate i'm honored truly
honored
because it's helped that many people
michelle you know you've seen this out
there
like you've seen what's going on out
there with what people go through and
you see the medical medium information
help a lot of people out there and i
just really appreciate all that you're
doing michelle
it's so important it's so important it
truly is
grace says wish your podcasts were
captioned too
this is why not podcast this is
captioned right
totally totally i can look into that i
will look into that
um because i just want the experience to
be the best for you guys in any way i
possibly can
right now i'm doing double time triple
time trying to get these episodes done
and ready and out to you guys have you
checked out the other episodes the brain
fog
episode how about the air freshener
cologne perfume scented candle episode
how about the the egg episode tanya says
does the podcast go into how to help
with it
i have so many of those symptoms um
tanya
yes it does it talks about the different
tools
different things that you can get help
from by using even if you apply
some of them it's so helpful and if
you're dealing with that
boat thing where you're on a boat you're
dizzy you don't feel good you get the
headaches the nausea
you don't feel the buzzing the tails and
numbness on the body the aches the achy
jaw the neck
the snowness in the eyes the eye
floaters
and there's healing tools on this
episode like you guys
i woke up this morning i was so excited
about this episode going out there so i
know you guys get help
like i was giddy i was giddy about all
the episodes coming out i know that but
this one
i i knew that this one will really
just really resonate so we can help more
people
rob says thank god for anthony and
spirit of compassion tremendous gift
the caffeine podcast blew me away
go celery go go go okay the caffeine
podcast blows me away
i heard that one again because even
though i'm busy doing all this i
listened to that one and it blew me away
again because i was like oh my god i
even said
i almost said oh my god i can't believe
i put this information out there because
yes it's all information that's people
haven't heard
so you when people haven't heard that
information before they're gonna get
mind blown and you don't know who's
gonna get mad
who's gonna get upset because yeah when
you tell the truth and you put truth out
there like that you're
gonna topple over that topple over the
apple cart a little bit
maria says great episode you described
everything i went through until i found
you
thank you thank you for for being there
thank you for actually
being here now thank you for listening
so happy you guys are listening
you know it's someone says oh uh randy
uh where do i watch the episode okay
it's medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast
it's for free just listen to the episode
listen to all the episodes
that this is episode 10. so listen to
the 10 episodes
listen to the 10 episodes haven't
listened uh
zero says haven't listened yet does the
episode offer a solution
yes it offers lots of solutions tools to
start the journey to say
how do i start getting rid of some of
these symptoms how do i start
getting some of these symptoms to back
down and here's here's an important part
knowing what's causing these symptoms
and the trigger so i want to go into
that if you guys got a minute i want to
cover triggers
very important it's a lot of different
triggers out there i talk about the
trigger
foods foods that trigger
these symptoms more and more so i talk
about that
so i talk about foods triggering these
symptoms
i talk about different things also like
chemicals and pesticides and herbicides
they can trigger these symptoms
i talk about a lot of things that can
and that's important also emotional
hardships
i talk about betrayal and broken trust
and different struggles emotionally and
how that can trigger
our neurological symptoms a little bit
but it's not the cause but it can
definitely
trigger mold that's one right there so
mold can actually
trigger the the nervous system it can
trigger the nervous system because it
weakens the immune system so really
really intense mold problems can trigger
the immune system by
weakening it and then the neurological
symptoms could get worse i talk about
all these things but that's just some
stuff
i describe the symptoms all of that
tonya says where do i find this episode
it the link is in the description
that's where you find it so just look
there link is in the description
okay so you'll see that you know and
um and you can listen to it so it's not
it's not a video it is a podcast
audio so yes medical meeting podcast at
apple podcast link is in the description
that's the uncensored platform if you
find it at another platform it's going
to be missing little pieces even if it
doesn't look like it it just is
um so medicalmedium.com you could go
there too
if you don't have an apple device and
you can just look at the menu
see podcast in the menu and and you can
listen to it it's about
about free information but powerful
information
life changing information because i know
how many of you guys are dealing with
the tingles
numbness weakness in the limbs the
sandbags on the feet you feel like you
can't move you feel like you got fatigue
you're not sleeping good you got the
restless legs the ticks and spasms the
burning skin
the jaw pain the neck pain the dizziness
the the nauseousness i mean i could go
on and on and on
and and it's so and so important so
and then i talk about conditions too
talking about all different kinds of
conditions as well like
multiple sclerosis and lupus and all
these other conditions where we get
labels for that for these symptoms i
talk about that
share this episode please with anybody
you can
so we can help as many people
every day i say the same thing how many
people can i help
i need to help as many as i can in this
lifetime
and i need them to find answers i put
out the medical medium books
like you're looking at one right now
behind me because i could see it you're
looking at the medical medium cleanse
the heal book it's a medical textbook
it's saved already a lot of lives and
it's saving lives now
and it's right there so if you want to
get that free at the library or
amazon sell that has a sale on that book
right now okay in the u.s
it's got a sales 51 off at 16.99 but i
look for
and if you you know you don't have to
buy it you can go to library but i look
for ways to
how can we heal as many people as we can
and in my lifetime
i need to do that i have to and and
i want people to not get lost in their
symptoms where they're suffering so bad
and struggling so bad that even if
they're getting help from their doctors
which is great
it doesn't mean it's gone or that it's
not troublesome or that it's not causing
more trouble or problems
and like roberta just said eye floaters
yeah
eye floaters exactly so medical medium
podcast at apple podcast that's the
uncensored platform that's the official
launch
platform for the medical medium podcast
you could see
neurological symptoms and and you can
see that
so and i talk about anxiety too so
remember that anxiety what people go
through
casey shellman says hey casey the poem
at the end really spoke to my heart
oh that's incredible that's incredible
the poem at the end
are words from spirit of compassion and
i make sure that they're there in this
for you guys
and they really speak to me too they
speak to me too
i'm so happy about that it matters um
mary says episode was so informative it
makes so much sense
it really is informative like really
powerfully informative
life changing and share it if you can
to help others too because i look at it
this way if someone's got the panic
attacks
tightness in the chest their tingles and
numbness they feel like they're on a
boat
they got the eye floaters they got the
ringing in the ears
they're not feeling good they got the
jaw pain the back
pain the neck pain how can i help them
how can i help them that's what i think
like what can i do
this episode incredible way to do it
it really is alina hilina the podcast
just keeps getting better and better
that's that's a compliment again that
blows me away
okay i can't wait to listen to this one
i have so many neurological symptoms and
more and i know this will comfort me and
of course
will help heal me i'm honored that the
podcast keeps on getting better and
better
the episodes you guys if you get a
chance listen to all the episodes if you
can
listen to you know michelle l says so
done with doctors that means you must
must have been through a lot of them you
must have seen a lot of doctors and not
had
enough answers i respect that you're
amazing michelle you're doing so much
good work and you're helping so many
people out there i actually see
you helping a lot of people out there
it's incredible um
so i cover healing tools so that's what
i do in this episode healing tools
and um and i'm pro doctor just like
everybody is we're all pro doctor
all of us and you know and but what
happens is i
i also know that so many people they
have a lot of symptoms and they've gone
to their tenth doctor and they're like
okay
i'm done with doctors right now i have a
friend that tells me that every day
i'm done with doctors my friend would
tell me and and you know and and i got
another
person i know and what happens is that
it's what happens is when you
have these symptoms and you have them
too long like michelle knows like what
you know friends of mine knowing
everything and they know that hey
you know what i gotta heal i gotta heal
this i need the tools
i gotta heal this myself i gotta figure
out how to do this and heal this myself
and where are the tools where are the
answers how can i do this
and it all matters because yeah that
merry-go-round
it's really hard and it's so hard to get
through it and and all of that
so in the end you know you can take this
information from this podcast
from this episode from neurological
symptoms you can take this information
and take it to your doctor too you can
do that be like look
here's this information what do i do you
can do that if you want
silk hey silk how you doing we got your
newest book
now in germany yeah incredible
that's the newest one right there
cleanse the heel it's a medical textbook
it's a mind-blowing book and
sure and elizabeth in is apple podcast
an app have all these symptoms yes it's
an app
totally an app that's what it is hello
and blessings from an
uh nfl so yeah definitely
so it's an app and the the link is in
the description
please check that out so you can have
the option there
sherry how do i find the podcast medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast
the the link is in the description and
you can find it
and listen to it for free catch this
neurological symptoms episode
it is mind-blowing filled with
information
about all of our symptoms but not just
that tools to help
heal it it's and it's free i'm not
sitting here trying to sell you guys
something
i'm not i'm sitting here trying to get
you guys
to listen to something for free okay
and because the bottom line it's like
this
this is the bottom line right here when
someone's got that dizziness
and they got that fatigue and they got
the eye floaters
and the ringing in the ears and the
buzzing and humming all over the body
and the ticks and the spasms and the
neck pain and the jaw pain
and all of that it's no joke it's no
joke that is hard for so many
and gotta have respect for people going
through it gotta have respect and when
you have anxiety with it
when you're struggling with it when
you're suffering with it you gotta have
respect for people going through this
it's critical unless you've been in
their shoes
gotta have some respect and we need
answers
debbie mcclain been following you for
three years debbie three years
incredible
no longer rocking on a boat so you got
rid of the rocking on a boat
a symptom vertigo is gone
incredible incredible
um heather says what about trigeminal
neuralgia
yeah what about it exactly
i talk about it in this episode it's in
here all the different
all the different i talk about the
trigeminal nerve in this episode
so check this out here's how it works i
talk about the vagus nerve in this
episode
i talk about the trigeminal nerve in
this episode i talk about
the phrenic nerves in this episode what
are phrygic nerves they run through your
chest here the vagus nerve runs from
your brain down
on through okay i talk about the
trigeminal nerve woo
and all the nerves it connects to and
the different pain and all
all of this so yes somebody said what
are you talking about
medical media podcast at apple podcast
neurological symptoms
that show body pain dizziness tingles
oh boy episode 10
don't miss it clara you did a great job
on this podcast thank you
i'm honored because i'm working hard i'm
i'm not gonna lie
i'm busting my butt on this podcast
meaning like meaning like in a good way
because i know
i'm helping heal more people and get
them answers
but i'm glad that you think i did a good
job because it makes me go phew
because i'm trying really hard to make
sure you get the information
i'm trying really hard to make sure you
can heal and so when you say that
it makes me feel better because i just
need you guys getting better it's what
it's all about
lisa says just finished listening and it
made me cry at the end
oh it was so so powerful the tears come
with that ending i get choked up when i
hear the ending
but i get choked up when i hear the
beginning
too when i hear the beginning i get
choked up
a vet hey is this on youtube no it's
actually
a medical meeting podcast is that apple
podcast the link is in the description
that's where it is and um so yeah it's
it's
in but look it's medicalmedium.com you
can go there
medicalmedium.com you can see in the
menu podcast in the menu
and you can listen that way too so you
can do that as well
um okay here's lorraine says
um how can i listen if i have an android
if you have an android okay
you want to listen to the uncensored
version which is what you want to listen
to
go to medicalmedium.com go to menu
see podcast in the menu and you can
listen to it there
okay trinity says it is such an awesome
episode going to listen to it multiple
times thank you so much
that's music to my ears because you're
gonna listen to all the info then
because one time
when you listen to this neurological
symptoms episode one time
it's so packed with information
so jammed with information that you
might miss something
listening to it multiple times just it
warms my heart because i know you're
going to do some healing
deanna says doctors tell them tell me it
because i'm getting old so they tell you
that
you're getting these symptoms because
you're getting old
well that's not it it's not because
you're getting old listen to the episode
if you can the link is in the
description don't
miss out on it lisa says i was saying
yes to 90
of your list of symptoms when you were
listing them on the podcast
whoa whoa ninety percent of those
symptoms
just don't my heart pours out to you
that means you had a hard journey
that means you haven't had it easy that
means you know you've gone through a lot
um and you're seasoned and you
understand
and you understand denise says i can
relate to all your podcasts
and have got your books i'm honored you
even have to have the cleanse the heel
book behind me
you hit the nail on the head with
everything you say can i really have all
these things wrong with me
different or at the same time people
call me a hypochondriac
that breaks my heart breaks my heart
when people call people hypochondriac
that breaks my heart because you're not
a hyper contract you're not a hyper
contract
you're not these are real symptoms
people don't understand
they just don't get it and unless
they've been in your shoes they just
don't get it
some people get it because they have
family members and some family members
like they feel it and like okay but a
lot of people don't
presley prince you're one amazing human
i'm glad you're here
pressing prince you're here again
incredible
um you're amazing too and just i'm
really proud of you guys i really am so
neurological symptoms body pain
dizziness okay
fatigue tingles all that stuff this is
the episode 10th
episode uh please share please share if
you can
share with someone share with anyone you
know get the information out there get
it to go around so we keep the
grassroots movement movement healing
because i think about it all the time
how many people are suffering and
struggling
and how do we help them this episode
really powerful
and same with the other episodes did you
do the brain meditation
did you do the moon meditation did you
do free as a bird meditation i
guide you through these meditations
don't miss
out on this please share leave a review
it's so
helpful if you guys can leave a review
at apple podcast medical medium podcast
at apple podcast
if you guys can figure out how to leave
a review there and when you get a chance
if you're feeling up to it how that can
help people please do that
the meditations deanna says the
meditations are awesome and helping me
so much
thank you with all my heart um and
listen to the other episodes
uh there's some serious episodes going
on there there's the fruit fear one
the air freshener one sent the candle
one clones perfume that episode
there's the egg episode um that one you
have to listen to
okay so there's there's the brain fog
episode there's the chemtrail episode
which is scary there's so many
episodes already ten episodes now and
they're packed with
information jody says your podcasts are
incredible
they helped so much i felt you were
talking directly to me on the dizzy
episode
so yeah the disney episode because
you guys you guys you just need to know
like
i know you're struggling with these
symptoms when you have these symptoms
my heart pours out to you like but not
only do i know you're dealing with those
i also know there's a way to heal and
and you have to get the support you need
in between that point of healing
and how you know that point of having
the symptoms and healing
it's about making sure you guys get a
chance and there's a way
there's a way up from this there's a way
up from this so important
braun says this is a huge relief finding
out what what it is i've been suffering
from for the last
past three years after my accident i had
all that you described plus hashimoto's
anxiety ptsd so important um
make sure you subscribe so you get the
notifications subscribe to medical mean
podcast at apple podcast
you can hear the uncensored version get
the notifications so important
so make sure you do that if you can and
in a newsletter sign up to the
newsletter at medicalmedium.com
so that yeah so you can get notified
when the
because that's what happened i sent out
the newsletter this morning so everybody
can get notified so they can get the
episode and listen to it
so yeah all this is important you guys
i'm so proud of you
um barbara says i'm behind on these
podcasts
i think i'll binge on mm tonight i'm
honored that you're going to take time
out
to binge on mm tonight honored honored
honor you guys
i love you guys greatly i stand with you
i believe in you
you know i know you can heal just just
know
that i'm really really there with you on
this
because i know you guys suffer and
struggle have compassion for yourself
and uh keep a light heart keep a light
heart okay
and bless your heart take care