okay we're live
we're live on rumble
we're live on youtube we're live on
facebook we're live on tick tock it's
the pre anti-buzz cleanse it's the
preliminary day okay starting tomorrow
is the first day out of three days we're
doing the anti-bug cleanse so this is
really a special time i'm excited by the
way you see a pot right here you see
apples i'm gonna make some apple
cider or apple juice hot spiced apple
juice is really what i'm gonna make and
i'm actually excited about that so we're
gonna do that i got all my spices here i
got my apples so i'm gonna do that a
little later on do you have a copy of
the cleanse the heel this has the
anti-bug cleanse in it an important book
it's critical and right now it's on sale
amazon.comus
incredible 51 percent off go to the
library you can get it for free if you
don't have the 16.99 for the sale
the sale that the book's on right now if
you don't have that you can do
um try to try to get a copy at the
library for free and that's perfectly
fine now
i'm doing this cleanse right and this is
a free
free
cleanse
and we're doing it for basically four
days so today's the first day it's the
pre-day and we're doing three days after
it okay now this is free so this isn't
the kind of thing where you gotta pay
three thousand dollars or twenty five
hundred dollars because i'm gonna give a
tremendous amount of information out
we're not taking this to a private
platform somewhere where you actually
have to sign up and you actually have to
you know you have to buy a ticket and
spend all that money that's not what
we're doing here okay this is a free
resource that's how i like to do it i
don't want to charge everybody two
thousand dollars three thousand dollars
for
you know to do this and in fact you can
go to the library and get the book for
free if you don't want to get the 16
book at amazon.com us but it's on sale
at amazon.com for 16 and it's on sale in
other places too so check out wherever
you are go into your bookstore whatever
barnes noble's you can pick up a copy so
but the book's important because the
anti-bug cleanse is in the book and
we're going gonna do it listen another
thing too if you guys are here to just
view this to just watch it just chill
out
perfectly fine okay so if you don't want
to partake or have fun or make recipes
or get the book and you just want to
hang out have fun with them we do that
too
but the point is there's a lot to learn
we're going to cover a lot there's a lot
to cover it's exciting
so it's great to have the book it's
important so this is pre pre-anti-bug
cleanse day
so this is not day one but it's about
preparation it's about being prepared
it's about getting ready for it and why
why are we doing an anti-bug cleanse
what does that mean
so
now just for preparation wise important
to know okay
and
day one
okay
so day one
we're going to be doing the potato salad
now if you guys want to prepare today
and get ready for tomorrow and make the
meal with me that would be fun that
would be awesome because i would love
that if you guys want to make the meals
with me so day one tomorrow
we're doing the potato salad okay and i
know the book's just flipping around
right here but the potato salad so
being prepared having the ingredients
would be awesome we can make it together
i mean how cool is that right
day two
all right
is the portabello there it is the
portobello stew okay i'm making the
recipes i want to make it make it with
you as each day goes on and that would
be so great
make them together right how fun is that
so
there's the portabella stew that's um
[Music]
okay and then there's the
day three
the stuffed peppers so potato and herb
stuffed peppers right there so i'm gonna
make that recipe too so how amazing is
that today i'm just making the hot
spiced apple juice but i'm just showing
you guys right there telegram can you
guys see that you guys on rumble can you
see that
incredible right
so
making the recipes together throughout
this anti-bug cleanse is going to be fun
i hope you guys do that i hope you guys
have the book i hope you get a copy as
soon as you can or a good library get it
for free
the cleanse is free
really important to know because someone
left a comment i think it was today
and it was a comment of something like
you know how much are you charging for
this cleanse how much is it gonna be is
it gonna be like everybody else fifteen
hundred dollars or two thousand dollars
it was something like that and i'm like
whoa whoa
chill chill chill man it's free
it's free so i'm excited
incredible so you guys um so let's go
into this let's talk about this a little
bit why anti bug plants what does it
even mean like
how does it work we got bugs that live
inside of us everybody is loaded with
bugs some people load it with more bugs
some people little less
and
there's four
actually yep four categories okay to
think about all right one category is
bug fuel
so we're eliminating
bug
fuel so we're eliminating a category of
foods
that feed the bugs so we're eliminating
bug fuel so that's one part that we're
gonna do
we're also eliminating blood thickeners
foods that thicken the blood when you
use foods that thicken the blood you
never cleanse you never detox you just
slowly kill your liver
you slowly kill yourself along the way
throughout your life
all those blood thickeners we're getting
rid of another category
dehydrator
not food dehydrators meaning like if you
got a dehydrator something like that you
want to make some crackers no no no
we're getting rid of a category of foods
that dehydrate the body dehydrate the
brain dehydrate the blood dehydrate the
organs right
and then we're getting rid of another
category of foods which are toxin
contributors
we're getting rid of the toxin
contributors so we're getting rid of the
bug fuel that's one right there we're
getting rid of blood thickeners that's
another one right there we're getting
rid of dehydrators it's another category
of foods we're getting rid of toxic
contributors another category of foods
that's how exciting this is we're
getting rid of four
categories
that end up keeping us from healing
keeping us from cleaning out toxins
keeping us from killing the bugs that
live inside of us and you may say hey aw
i don't have any bugs i don't know what
you're talking about i just have a
little acid reflux i get a little
fatigue here and there i got a little
bit of eczema that gets scratchy on my
skin i got a little bit of anxiety it's
like bugs
that's what you have if you got the
eczema then you got the epstein barr
or you might be like hey aw i don't have
any bugs um do you get any cold sores
ever you ever get a fever blister that's
simplex herpes one it sits in the
trigeminal nerve it sits in throughout
the body on different nerves it sits in
the brain stem and it sits there and
then it breaks out every now and then
you get your cold sore right you get
your cold sore well that is a bug we're
not going to want to feed that bug
anymore
aw i only get some chronic sinusitis
once in a while and i got like some
mucus in my head streptococcus
that's a bug
hey aw i had a uti last year but i don't
got no bugs that bug is still in you
it's still there streptococcus you know
hey w i got some acne but i don't have
any bugs streptococcus you've got acne
utis chronic sinusitis styes
anything like that that's what you're
dealing with say you've got chronic
fatigue you're dealing with bugs
chronic fatigue
is the epstein-barr
rheumatoid arthritis is the epstein-barr
hashimoto's thyroiditis hyperthyroidism
hypothyroidism
cysts and nodules on your thyroid
is the epstein-barr
long-haul
pandemic stuff
is
viruses tripped up from getting your
immune system dropped and slammed down
from catching
that plague going around right
so then the epstein-barr creeps up and
the shingles creep up sciatic pain so
back pain you can't explain where it
runs down your butt and runs down your
leg down to your foot and but yet your
back seems okay and you're at the
chiropractor and you're still having the
problem it's the shingles virus right
there jaw pain that's mysterious so
you're at the dentist and they don't
know what to do they do the x-rays
everything looks okay a lot of people
still get their teeth drilled for no
reason
trigeminal neuralgia
right bugs that's the shingle bug
shingles so
we all got these bugs and they all keep
us sick do you have another diagnosis
multiple sclerosis lupus right
what else do you have neurological lyme
we're talking about bugs this is the
anti-bug cleanse so i'm giving you guys
kind of a little prep about it like what
is it what are we doing like why are we
even doing this and i want to read a
little something too in a second about
the cleanse
but if you guys just got on here it's
critical
to have the cleanse to heal book
right
you guys are like hey he's just trying
to sell a book well that's funny because
i could turn this into a cleanse and
sell it for three thousand dollars a
ticket take it to a private platform
sell it to fifty thousand people or
twenty thousand people at three thousand
dollars a piece do the math how much can
i make but i don't and i'm not going to
i'm not gonna do it go to the library
get it for free we're getting on sale on
amazon 51 off but make sure you have the
cleanse the heel book it's got the
anti-book cleanse in there and when you
read the rest of the book your mind will
be blown because it's got a lot more in
there than that it's got over 200
symptoms and conditions it's got 75
recipes it's got the causes of chronic
illness it's got other cleanses this
thing is already saving lives all over
the world make sure you have a copy and
we're doing this cleanse together
doing it for free how cool is this so
what i love about the anti-bug cleanse
is it makes more room for healing foods
it makes more room for healing foods
right
so when you're making more room for
healing foods
you're taking away other foods that may
not be healing does that look like
healing foods to you i'm kind of
wondering does that look like healing
foods is that going to get rid of all
the bugs it's not and i'll talk to talk
to you guys why later right the eggs and
the butter on that gluten bread the
bacon is that gonna get rid of the bugs
okay so
when you take away
these other foods or choose not to use
them and then choose to use foods that
help heal you
like the recipes we're going to do
together
your life changes
like you get empowered
you take control over your life
that's what happens
now ain't nothing going to take you down
nothing's going to run you and rule your
life
no way
you're taking control over your life
you're really becoming in power it's not
just using the word like empowerment
everybody throws it out there left and
right hey take control of your life go
do this
take control of your life go do this
medical treatment hey take control of
your life go do this uh no take control
go do this
that's not taking control of your life
okay a lot of people say yeah yeah you
can do this
you know what how about really taking
control let's knock out the bugs the
bugs that sit in us wreak havoc as our
life goes on you go along you go along
and then all of a sudden
whoa why am i sick it's because you had
some bugs in you all these years and
we're working on knocking them out so
this is really important you guys
so
i want to read a little something to you
real quick okay that's that's i think
it's important to know
all right so let's go there
okay first of all i want to make a quick
announcement
later on today okay
right i'm doing an exclusive
15 minute live on rumble
6 15 eastern 315 pacific
so just letting you know so it's going
to be on rumble right
and so rubble.com slash medical medium
so make sure you're there it's not going
to be about the anti-bug cleanse it's
not going to be about what we're doing
in this cleanse for the next four days
the next three days after you know after
tomorrow it's not gonna be about that
link is in the description
it's just an exclusive talk
a little private talk
on rumble okay it's gonna be 15 minutes
or maybe a little bit more depending on
what's happening depends on how many
zingers i throw out or not could even be
longer but it's going to be on rumble
later on 6 15 eastern 3 15 pacific make
sure you subscribe to rumble and you
know and you're and you're there don't
miss that exclusive live that's coming
up later on we're not going to be
talking about the antibiotic cleanse
we're going to be talking about other
stuff so it'll be fun okay just be you
guys and and spirit compassion and i so
i want to read a little something in
here
and if you guys just came on here i want
you to watch this from the beginning
okay
later on watch it from the beginning and
and because i talked about other stuff
getting ready preparation getting ready
for the cleanse tomorrow's day one of
the anti-bug cleanse gonna make some hot
spice
apple juice i'm totally pumped about it
so i want to read a little bit too okay
okay on the troublemaker foods list
because that's what's in here's
troublemaker foods list right that i'm
gonna have you guys
choose not to do you'll see that the
foods are divided up by level with level
one being the most important to remove
if you want to make progress with your
health which level you try is up to you
guys so there's a variety of different
levels okay so there's levels one
through five
level one is going to be the easiest but
it's still going to be helpful and it's
still gonna be eliminating bugs you're
still gonna be starving bugs without
starving yourself okay
so then the level two gets a little bit
more intense not much more but a little
bit more intense level three of the
anti-bug cleanse a little bit more
level four even more and level five is
the bonus level i'm going all the way to
level five that's what i'm doing
i'm not gonna do level one level one's
great you can do level one you can
choose to do level one and i'm pumped
i'm excited okay
i'm doing level five which means i'm
doing all levels
including bonus that's what i'm doing
okay
but i got a couple things i want to read
to you a little bit real quick if you
have a negative association
with removing foods from your diet
because of past diet protocols where
food was eliminated do any any of you
guys run into that do you have like a
negative association with removing foods
because of some kind of elimination diet
out there or some other kind of diet out
there right
where your food was eliminated for
example like food allergy diets or food
allergy testing
please know
that those were man made programs
gonna say it again
if you have a negative association with
removing foods from your diet
because of ptsd
from past
diets you've done
and cleanses
and food elimination
right please know that those were
man-made programs
man-made programs so important to know
their makers
their makers the men who made the
programs
their makers are unaware
of what causes chronic illnesses such as
autoimmune
okay and how food plays a role they were
unaware of that going all the way back
35 years of doing this that's any time
i've ever seen any kind of diet or
cleanse or anything
nobody was aware of what caused chronic
illness why somebody was sick with
autoimmune or chronic fatigue or
anything else but yet they were creating
these diets okay
so that's important to know
those are guessing games that we don't
play here so we don't play guessing
games
this is about knowing why you're
eliminating a food
what happens when you do
what bugs you're starving because of it
and how to heal like so many have healed
this is important so those are guessing
games out there that we don't play here
only here
only here will you find food empowerment
and the ability to take control of your
healing
take control of your healing process
using real knowledge okay i recommend
that you consider shifting your thinking
it's not that you're not allowed
to eat something i'm not gonna see and
actually you're not allowed to eat
something you're not allowed to eat
something okay you're allowed to eat
anything you want you you want to eat
something
yeah
look if you want to do this cleanse with
me and this is what you want to eat for
four days because that's what your free
will wants to do
and that's for some reason of what you
want to do
don't let me get in the way
the only i'm still going to do the
anti-bug cleanse and i'm not going to
have pizza this week
but but i'm not saying you're not
allowed to do anything you could do
anything you want okay but i'm hoping
you choose
choose not to eat the foods that will
feed the bugs like the cheese and gluten
pizza or anything i'm hoping that you
choose to do the cleanse
[Music]
if you're up for it if you're up for it
so i'm excited about that okay
so as i always say i'm not the food
police nope
never been the food police
ever ever ever i've been the bug police
that i have been i've been the bug
police the bug police that gives you
your fibromyalgia the bug police that
gives you your lupus and multiple
sclerosis the bug police that gives you
anything else you've been dealing with
your eczema your psoriasis your vitiligo
i've been the bug police
that gives you your utis
i bend the bug please that's what i bet
okay i'm on page 172. i'm going to
cleanse the heel i'm reading out of it
right now we're in the anti-book cleanse
we're doing the preliminary stuff this
is the prep you guys
this is the prep we're prepping getting
ready tomorrow starts three days
anti-book lens i'm doing all five levels
you can pick the level you guys want to
do
it's gonna be fun right
so
this lit this is a list here so you can
make informed decisions
so the list is in this book you can make
for informed decisions on what foods
that are getting in the way of your life
right
let's also be clear that none of the
foods here are listed as problematic out
of prejudiced
against a dietary belief system such as
veganism
plant-based
vegetarianism paleo philosophy or
ketogenic
theory
okay so this isn't about being biased to
ketogenic being biased to paleo being
biased to veganism being biased to
plant-based being bias to vegetarian
this isn't about that at all
okay
nor is this cleanse about
self-deprivation you guys
you're gonna be drinking hot spiced
apple juice
you're gonna be eating
delicious recipes
this is not a cleanse about
self-deprivation
starvation
or shame
this isn't about shame either i told you
before if you're not ready to do the
anti-bug cleanse hang out
if you're hanging out and you're eating
pizza i still want you here and i'm not
shaming you it's a hard world
some people are just like man i just
need a slice of pizza
but i want you to be able to learn
though you can learn so hang out
maybe get the book someday
right
the foods are listed solely because they
pose the risk
that you will not succeed with your
cleansing or healing process
that's what it is
so it's important
give you a quick
rundown on the medical medium
books here in this book
they got the street cred
millions around the world have gotten
their lives back they're healing
everywhere
it's the thing that moves the needle or
the medical medium books medical medium
book series when people use it and apply
it properly they move the needle and
they get their lives back
and that's already happened so this
isn't this thing where i came out with a
book for the first time and it's an
experiment and i'm hoping to get one or
two people better and maybe i will
someday and hey maybe i can get my book
known or something no
he's number one new york times
best-selling books they're saving lives
they already have it's happened around
the world and before the books came out
people came from all over the world to
my office got the information they
needed and got their lives back for over
35 years so this is exciting this is the
anti-bug cleanse it's a free
deal nothing better than that get the
book free at the library
hit a library and see if they got a copy
kicking around so you don't have to pay
the 16 if you don't want to
51 off amazon.com
16.99 amazon.com us it's an unbelievable
51 off it's an angelic price i say that
because
it costs more to print the book
it's costing more to print the book
it's incredible you guys want to say
that quick announcement once again for
everybody just came on everybody knew
i came on
later on on rumble okay i'm doing an
exclusive talk later on
okay it's at 6 15 eastern 3 15 pacific
so i'm gonna be on rumble it's gonna be
you guys and us i'm not gonna be on any
other platform and it's not going to be
talking about the anti-bug plans that's
separate we're going to be just chilling
and we're going to talk your book
arrived yesterday jennifer fields
incredible
incredible okay
so let's talk about the cleanse a little
bit
why not
16 ounces of celery juice now if you're
somebody that's already doing 32 ounces
and that's what you're doing every
single day these 32 ounces of celery
juice but 16 ounces to celery juice
every single morning okay
keep out the troublemaker foods that
you're picking the level you're picking
whether it's level one level two level
three level four right
drink at least 32 ounces or a liter of
water every day
you can sip coconut water make sure your
coconut water if you like coconut water
you don't have to sip or use coconut
water but if you are
make sure your coconut water is not red
make sure it's not pink
okay that's toxic coconut water
i know a trend passed around because the
coconut water industry didn't want to
lose millions and millions and millions
hundreds of millions of dollars over the
years so they convinced everybody they
lied
a zinger alert zinger alert
they lied
and they said that the pink red to pink
to darker red and the darker the color
of the coconut water going red
is actually good for you and that's the
best coconut water
that was a gross disgusting lie
the coconut water industry
i mean it's oxidated it's shot the
coconut water went bad
and that's what happens when it goes red
singer alert that's all that's what
happens when it goes red keep that in
mind
and what happens is when they're getting
all that coconut water shipped overseas
and it turned red
or it's turning red because it's getting
old they don't want to lose their shirts
so that red pink that pink to red
coconut water
is oxidative and gone bad and then they
sell it in the health food stores
pretending that that's the best stuff
that's how many tricks are out there of
the trade anyway use coconut water
that's not like that
keep that in mind so
zinger alert you're being screwed over
like
so many things happen in the alternative
movement non-stop
and uh and i love making no friends
because of it because then i'll piss
somebody else off because
man once you get that word out there and
stuff people start getting you know mad
again it's like what are you gonna do
it's like if i don't have your back what
what am i supposed to be not be be
afraid i can't make any friends out
there and i'll turn movement i don't
want to play that game i just got to
have your back people who are
chronically ill don't have time to waste
and they have to heal and that's what
it's about at medical medium okay
so all right
so the recipes in the book if you want
to choose other recipes in the book say
you don't want to make the recipe that
i'm going to be making tomorrow
right the potato salad
so you don't want to make that recipe
say you want to make a different recipe
you don't want to make the potato salad
tomorrow because i'm making that
tomorrow that's okay if you want to do a
different recipe totally on board okay
and say you don't want to do your
portobello stew
because you don't like portobello
mushrooms that's okay
maybe keep the portobello mushrooms out
or something make it the way you want to
make it right that's perfectly fine
so this is not a restricted diet you can
eat all day that's the cool thing you
want to make a big portobello stew and
you want to eat that all day long and
you can do that that's what's awesome
about that
and there's the portobello herb stuffed
peppers i'm making on the third day i
think i'm making that on the third day
yeah third day
right
so if for some reason you don't like
peppers you want to pick another recipe
inside the book pick another recipe in
the book but i'm hoping you make the fun
stuff with me right
so
let's talk about the levels that's the
next part so let's cover levels for a
little bit so this is fun
level one you want to keep out certain
foods okay
so let's bring in some foods in level
one level one
right
you want to keep these out
this is critical
this is bug fuel
i'm not ranking on eggs
eggs were a good survival food for years
and years and years out there
i was never anti-egg
but what happened was
classified medical research in science
before 1920
took the egg
and they learned they can grow pathogens
inside there because the eggs can eat
undeveloped protein from the egg so that
i mean the bugs can eat under
protein from the egg so they they
learned
that eggs feed all the bugs
and so they raised all the pathogens
the plague that everybody's freaking out
about right now
came from
eggs
meaning they were raised in eggs in the
labs
right so it's important to know so every
bug you deal with your simplex fever
blister
or your simplex 2
genital herpes or whatever you got going
on in your life that you want to clean
up and heal
or your mono or whatever it is
came originally grown out of eggs
from classified medical research in
science and then was released into the
public hiv
was grown out of eggs
and then released into the public person
purposely
so that people would get hiv
that's how classified medical research
and science does it
public medical research science doesn't
know this
so
you eat the eggs and every single bug in
your body
has a field day
and starts to eat
so we're taking away the eggs
that's on level one
so can you do it can you break away from
the eggs
can you break away from the bug feeders
right there so that's one
another thing too now level one in level
one right here says dairy products
so
can you get rid of the stick of butter
can you get rid of the cheese
can you get rid of the cheese sticks
right can you get rid of any kind of
cheese
cheese will feed the bugs too
can you get rid of the milk cheese and
the butter so that's one thing right
there to get rid of
okay
gluten that's the next one so let's get
rid of gluten right so we've got a slice
of bread right here
got a slice of bread can you get rid of
the bread
now that's not like straight white
processed flour bread but still
this was and it was toasted up with some
cheese inside right so can you get rid
of like the bread and the cheese
so this is level one level one also says
no soft drinks
no soft drinks on level one
so no soft drinks
right
that's important to know
no gluten which was the bread right the
wheat gluten so you can read the book
for more details but that's level one
and that's what i'm in right here
cleanse the heel
now maybe you're somebody that you just
wanna do level one
totally cool
totally cool happy you're here if you're
somebody that doesn't wanna do level one
and you just you just to have some
buttered toast and watch the gig i'm
happy you're here okay maybe you'll
learn some stuff it'll be fun right
let's go into level two so can you guys
do level two level two
is the same as level one you you get rid
of those first you get rid of the eggs
the milk the cheese the butter
gone but level two has additional foods
like pork
so that's when you get rid of the pork
so
you get the pork out of there that's a
big one too so that means like the bacon
the pork so i got some bacon on this
dish right here right so that's the
bacon so level two is getting rid of
pork now that's what we need to do
it's level two
okay
pork is a blood thickener i just showed
you
bug fuel right which is the eggs the
dairy the milk the cheese the butter
that's bug fuel
now i'm showing you blood thickeners
pork right
let's move to another one too so we're
in level two right the next one is tuna
so now we're talking about tuna so this
is sushi
so whether you open a can of tuna fish
or you open a pack of tuna
keeping tuna out is critical we're in
level two level two is not just eggs
dairy gluten milk cheese butter gluten
right and soft drinks level two
is pork
tuna
right
and corn
pork tuna and corn
that's level two
keeping those out so what happens if
you're gonna have corn tortillas
taco shells
made of corn
right
any kind of popcorn how many of you guys
are still like
cooking up and popping popcorn thinking
you guys are like in the safe zone
you're popping organic popcorn every
single night or on the weekends right
and you think you're in the safe zone oh
those feed bugs corn will feed the bugs
because it's it's all contaminated it's
all gmo and they use corn
right in the pharmaceutical world that's
how they make your drugs they use corn
to make all your drugs gmo corn they use
corn now also to still feed bugs in the
labs
okay
so we're level two
we will go into levels more tomorrow i'm
gonna make some hot apple juice so
there's level three there's level four
there's level five
right so let me make some hot spiced
apple juice so make sure you're ready
this is the pre-cleanse day so this is
the preliminary to the cleanse it starts
tomorrow i'm really pumped out i'm
really excited right
so that was you my god doing all the
corn even organic corn even organic corn
it'll feed the bugs now what i've always
said with corn like organic corn if you
wanted to use it sparingly and carefully
throughout the summer or something
because you wanted you know to put some
corn in a dish you want to have that
roasted corn on the cob keep keep it
under control where you're just doing a
little here and there but if you're sick
with chronic illness like really sick
you've got something going on and you're
really struggling i would keep the corn
out all together because it could feed
the bugs even organic corn can so keep
that in mind i'm gonna make some
hot apple
spice juice right got two options okay
so i got apple i'm gonna i got the apple
juice itself so you can go and pick up
an apple juice and organic apple juice
right you go pick one up you can um use
that if you need to it's perfectly fine
right as long as it does as long as it's
not like some apple juice it's got all
the citric acid in there or all these
natural flavors in there if it's just
pure straight
apple juice
you can use it if you want you can pour
it into your pot
you can make you can make your hot
spiced apple juice pour it into the pot
in the whole bit that's one option you
can also juice fresh apples too
so you can do that so i'm going to juice
a little bit of some fresh apples right
here
so i'm going to do that
and this is an option too you guys can
do which is perfectly fine
you just run some apples to the juicer
if you'd like
that's an option
just going to cut up some apple slices
right now
what i love about the anti-bug cleanse
is that it gets rid of bugs that control
your life
because if you're sick and going to the
doctor all the time and you're doing
your doctor visits all the time and
that's that's a big part of your life
where you have to you have to make your
doctor appointments okay i gotta go see
this doctor about this skin problem now
i have to see the doctor because i don't
feel good now the doctors you know
drawing all your blood and knocking down
your immune system by drawing too much
blood out of you you become like a slave
to the industry a slave to
what the bugs are doing inside of you
you know like you're becoming a slave to
to basically the world of bugs and the
medical industry
and
that's not a like a great place to be
that's not a fun place to be like i
don't want to be um controlled by bugs
and then controlled by big pharma too
like who wants to be controlled by bugs
and big pharma and here's the crazy
thing big pharma the classified medical
research and science part of big pharma
is what made all the bugs so that's why
you're sick to begin with you're sick
because they made you sick and then they
exposed you just like the hiv right
you know the hiv they stuck all that hiv
and all that blood that tainted blood
and then they pumped it into people
right that was one thing right there i
mean
you know they've actually spread hiv in
a lot of different ways throughout the
years purposely so that people would
actually get sick right and they're
doing they're doing it with every single
thing with
with the epstein bars
i said once again i said in the past
woodstock isn't is it how simplex and
herpes got around it wasn't because of
free sex and woodstock
they put those bugs out there
and
they they put them out into the system
they contaminated the system
they actually infected people purposely
that's what medical research and science
did so keep that in mind of how it works
so any reason why you're sick
is because of that and then people yes
people spread them of course but they
knew that they knew people would spread
the bugs they actually knew people would
spread the bugs
so it's like if you're if you're
somebody who's living with a condition
of any kind
you're living with the bugs and if
you're living with the bugs
[Music]
they're controlling a part of your life
they're they're actually pushing you
into
they're pushing you into the doctor's
offices you have to get prescriptions
all the time right you got a thyroid
problem and you have to live on thyroid
medication well the bugs are doing that
because the epstein bars is the whole
reason for the thyroid problem you got
hypothyroidism that's epstein-barr so
why are we doing the anti-bug plants
i think about it we're doing it so we
can start knocking back the epscene bar
knocking back the simplexes knocking
back that shingles people think they
skate free
people think they skate free and they're
going to be fine and then they have
if you can like fast forward someone
into the future like a healthy seemingly
healthy 20 year old who's feels
indestructible who has no problems if
you can fast forward them to when
they're 60 years old and they get a
shingles breakout all through their
mouth and throat and then want to kill
themselves commit suicide
it's happened you don't think the 60
year olds or the 55 year olds to get
shingles all through their mouth and
their throat and the roof of their mouth
you don't think they weren't they were
20 at one point and weren't like
exercising and playing sports and
feeling indestructible and now they're
54 years old shingles all down their
throat and they want to die and they're
on morphine in the hospital
these bugs are in everybody and they
come out and they come out in the most
crazy ways
[Music]
so
medical medium information is
reactivated epstein-barr if you heard of
epstein-barr reactivated
if you've heard that
public medical research and science
didn't know epstein-barr caused
neurological symptoms and reactivated
that's medical medium information so if
you hear that from a podcast doctor it
was taken from medical medium
information
because that's where it was first no one
knew and it's years of teaching this and
years of teaching doctors nobody knew
any of that they didn't know that that's
how it worked they didn't know
uh epstein-barr reactivated they didn't
know epstein barr
had a second or third fourth life and
reactivated over and over again
they didn't know that epstein-barr
[Music]
is long haul
uh play
that's all that's that's that's all uh
that all that i've seen bar information
is medical medium information originally
so if you're here doubting why am i
listening to this guy and his anti-bug
cleanse well
that information is originally medical
medium just so you know so
what i'm doing is i'm juicing a fresh
apple juice right now
if you guys are interested in the mm-900
hds wait for the sale
wait for a sale
i'm just saying because i know i'm going
to get a billion questions about
juicing so i'm trying to head it off at
the pass
so i'm what i'm doing is i'm making some
fresh apple juice right now
i'm going to put it in there
in the pot so i'm going to make that
fresh hot spiced apple juice
[Music]
which i'm excited about now there's
honey crisps out there right now you
guys
and like i said you can do bottle juice
if you want to do an organic clean
bottle juice
you can do that like you know without
citric acid put in there without natural
flavors put in there so that's important
to know what i like about the spicy hot
apple juice it tastes so good it's
insane
you can use any kind of apples right
you may not want to use green apples
though so you may not want to use green
apples green apples don't usually come
out that great
they don't they don't come out that
tasty they don't come out that great
[Music]
what i love about
you can use any juicer you have what i
love about this juicer is with food
costs going up all it does is save you
money which is incredible and really
really
like puts the pressure on whatever
you're juicing so that you squeeze every
last juice like drop a juice and that's
what i love about it
i'm gonna cut up some more apples real
quick you guys
i might have enough and then i could
also add some too which is great
i mean i could juice but
and i'm gonna make it again during the
cleanse too probably in the whole bit
i'm gonna pop this right in
i'm excited so that's incredible
and move the juicer over
get the book here
all right so i got this heating up i'm
gonna throw some spices in here too
so i got some cinnamon sticks now you
don't have to use cinnamon sticks so you
can just use some cinnamon if you really
want to but i'm gonna use the cinnamon
sticks okay so i'm going to pop i'm
going to break one all right
pop that in there okay
i'm going to add also a little bit of
the bottle stuff because i want you guys
to know that that's an option
so
it's a clean apple juice which you
really like it's got no natural flavors
got no you know citric acid always check
is whatever apple juice you find make
sure it's you know you do the organic
apple juice and make sure it doesn't
have that citric acid or anything so i
just put some cinnamon sticks in there i
could put one more
too
[Music]
let that do its thing this tastes so
good it's insane
i'm gonna pop some cloves in here
too
i'm gonna pop a few of those
right and you know what the weather and
everything this is just such a great
thing oh my god a little bit of nutmeg
put a little bit of that in there and i
i'm gonna take a little bit of ginger
pop a little bit of ginger in there so
you can use fresh ginger
perfectly fine
okay i got this simmering
so
everybody has a bug in them
whether they know it or they don't
hepatitis c when you see people getting
hepatitis c
that's epstein-barr gone wrong so that's
epsilon sitting in somebody's liver for
so many years that they eventually get
the hepatitis c diagnosis see
so and if you got a reproductive system
problem if you have endometriosis
those are bugs if you have pcos that's
the epstein bar which creates pcos
so keep that in mind so can i use
essential oils of clove cinnamon and
ginger etc no kathleen don't do that
that's not food like that's not food
it's essential oils
and and i'm not against essential oils
but don't don't use that as a food okay
use the food
use the cinnamon stick don't use the
essential oil
use
use the ginger the fresh ginger or the
ginger spice don't use the ginger
essential oil no they're not the same
they're not the same i know people think
they are but they're not okay
and i never recommend essential oils
internally
i never recommend them internally it's
great to smell them you can put them in
infusers your diffusers or whatever you
want to put them in you can put a little
on your skin you can make your own
concoctions you can add it to some hemp
oil or coconut oil make your little
concoction you can play with essential
oils absolutely
but never
take them internally
never
eat them don't internalize
those essential oils they aggravate
the intestinal tract the central nervous
system and when you're sensitive it
could wreak such havoc i've seen people
just in such bad shape from it so don't
do that some people are so sensitive
they're sensitive to even the smell of
essential oils they're too strong for
certain people to even smell them
without getting headaches from it or
getting aggravated by with anxiety
problems getting worse essential oils
are for people who
have a very strong constitution who
don't mind about strong smells they're
their nerves aren't that sensitive or
not sensitive at all
and they can you know they can burn and
they can diffuse them they can do they
can do what they want with them but i
still don't recommend taking them
internally important on the central oil
note really important information
okay guys right now i'm just doing some
hot apple cider
actually it's hot apple juice and this
is really amazing i got this in here
i did some fresh apple juice in here i
also want to show you that you can use
the bottled apple juice too so i don't
want you feeling stuck like you can't
use the bottle you can all right
so
so i want you to make sure you're doing
32 ounces of water or up to a liter of
water a day i want that water intake
herbal tea doesn't replace the water
intake so if you're doing herbal tea
right so if you're doing your herbal tea
it doesn't replace the water intake
keep that in mind during this cleanse
right
this cleanses in a deprivation cleanse
so it's not about holding food back and
starving
it's not about going hungry
really important to know okay
so
what you'll notice if you have questions
like wait a minute what can i eat what
can i eat what can i eat what can i what
can't i eat
when you look at the levels
you'll instantly know
because the levels tell you what you
should choose to stay away from what you
shouldn't eat right
so you can actually see whoa i'm not
supposed to eat the pork okay well
that's not enough i'm not supposed to
eat the tuna okay that's not on the list
i'm not supposed to have a corn i'm not
supposed to have eggs dairy products
cheese milk butter gluten i'm not
supposed to have soy and then it goes on
i'm not supposed to have soy
or lamb if it's
level three if it's level four it
includes vinegar fermented foods right
i'm not supposed to be doing kombucha
not supposed to be doing sauerkraut not
supposed to be doing so the levels get
more intense but you'll know
that what you can eat
are the recipes you find in cleanse the
heel so you know all the recipes are
here you can eat all this incredible
food by the way that's potato salad that
i'm making tomorrow on the first day of
the anti-bug cleanse right
so and then read
the book like read the troublemaker
foods chapter when you get your book
so you can learn
so make sure the book is on its way or
go to the library and get a copy
okay so it's important to know all right
read the anti bug cleanse so you can
learn it's not hard this this cleanse is
so easy because whatever level you pick
if you can do it it's actually easy to
do whatever level you pick
it's really it's really easy to do see
guys i'm gonna actually take this out
this is ready
okay so i'm gonna make a nice cup of it
right here so what you do is you take a
strainer whatever kind of strainer that
you have
right
you put that over it like this
and i'm straining this because i'm
straining
the cloves
i'm straining out the cinnamon
i'm straining out
that see so
we're just making sure
we're doing some straining
so i'm making a nice hot
cup
of spicy apple juice
see the cinnamon sticks in there right
this is so good i mean you can drink
this
all day if you want during this
cleanse
you can combine this cleanse with any
other medical medium cleanse that you
could be doing you can combine it with
any other medical medium cleanser tools
that you're doing okay you don't have to
stop your medical medium tools you don't
have to stop your medical medium
cleanses if you're doing them okay or
you can you can combine them if you'd
like and that's perfectly fine
right
so that's the hot spiced apple juice
that is so insanely good
can't wait for you guys to have that sip
it during the cleanse
i'm gonna have some more
so good really good
you guys
want to make that announcement one last
time
later on at 6 15 eastern
right 3 15 pacific
i'm going live on rumble
and we're not going to be talking about
the cleanse
we're just going to talk about some
other stuff it's just exclusive a little
private time exclusive it's going to be
intimate it's going to be like just
whoever comes there it's going to be us
going to be probably a small crowd but
we're going to talk about stuff so it's
cool
and i'm going now to instagram i'm going
to turn telegram back on
i'm going to turn tick tock back on i'm
heading there in just a little while so
i'll see you guys there i can't wait i'm
excited about the anti-bug cleanse i
can't even tell you guys
i'll see you soon
and the answer bug one starts tomorrow
remember that day one we're just doing
the pre stuff
all right i'll see you guys on the next
platform we're heading over there on ig
or just stay stay on telegram just click
telegram back on i'll be back on there
live so pumped and tick-tock too alright
love you guys