syndrome and the Brain saver books
comprehensive detailed information about
restless legs so let's get into it
restless leg syndrome often when
addressing restless legs medical
communities start with the legs first
are you cramping
what's going on with your legs do you
need leg massage do you need to lift
your legs up maybe your problems in your
legs but it's not right they'll ask
could that be the problem it's just a
leg problem try putting a pillow between
your legs when you sleep that'll fix it
how about that or the last how's your
bed and your mattress go out and buy
another 500 mattress or 300 400 whatever
it is dollar mattress and replace your
mattress that'll fix your restless legs
or your legs comfortable are they
supporting your lower back when you lie
down that's the problem you know experts
will be like maybe you just need a
little bit more support when you're in
bed maybe you could put your leg up
maybe you got your pillows between your
knees or right there a whole bit okay
how are your feet maybe your restless
leg syndrome is just your feet maybe you
got a feet problem you need to go and
try on some new shoes supportive shoes
do the shoes fit right do they have
enough padding are they the problem or
is one leg shorter than the other and
everybody says hey my leg is an inch
shorter than the other leg my legs I
have been shorter than the other leg
that must be my restless legs and then
so on so on if looking at the place
where the symptoms are felt doesn't
yield results then the doctor may move
on is it in your mind is your mind too
active at night are you giving
yourselves restless leg syndrome so then
you go through that whole thing is your
mind too active when you're trying to
sleep read a book read a book before you
go to bed right you might hear that
maybe light a candle and take a bath
listen to some calming music you'll hear
as advice consider taking magnesium for
your legs if none of this helps often
patients are told it's time for an MRI
on their lower back to investigate for
degenerative disc problems or a bulging
disc and if this all checks out even if
there is something like a bulging disc
doesn't mean that's a restless legs if
this doesn't check out or checks out no
signs of structural spine issue the
restless legs will be considered a
medical mystery and that's the whole
point with restless legs it becomes a
medical mystery everybody thinks science
research is really advanced but they
don't even know the cause of restless
legs even here it's detailed
comprehensive information let's go on a
little further if looking at the place
where the symptoms are felt does it
yield those results instantly now we're
at the medical Mystery World and that's
really interesting so and here's the
other point that's interesting too
if there's no signs of anything wrong
your feet your legs you tried everything
you tried the pillows you tried the
shoes you went to the doctor you got
massage therapy it's not a mystery when
you look at the brain saver books it's a
medical mystery out there but detailed
information in here of what's really
going on is really incredible here there
are some neural neurologists these days
who will start looking into the brain a
little bit now I've seen that out there
because of the medical medium books
being out now for eight years they're
starting to look at the brain a little
bit right but even if the MRI and the
brain look normal there's nothing
abnormal there then where do they go
from there the true cause of restless
legs wouldn't it would not appear on the
MRI so let's go into that if you get an
MRI you're getting the restless legs for
like a year and it's bothering you you
tried everything you go to the doctor
the neurologist says let's look in the
brain they do an MRI they look for your
brain it looks pretty good nothing
really is terribly wrong in here okay
everything is checking out the brain
looks good nothing abnormal then
they're going to be like okay let's try
to go a different route let's go with
sleep medications let's start going with
different Pharmaceuticals they start
heading to that that place the true
cause of restless legs won't show up so
then they'll offer hey here's some sleep
aid here's a sleep drug have you tried
this have you tried that so then it's
going on to different places maybe you
got anxiety a lot of people with
restless legs are blamed on anxiety so
they're like well I don't know if it's
anxiety but maybe it is and now they're
taking anti-anxiety it's true you know
as well even if the scan showed a brain
tumor it wouldn't mean that that's the
cause and I run into that every now and
then throughout like talking to doctors
a doctor would be like hey aw there's a
brain tumor in my patient you know is
that causing the restless legs and well
first of all let's try to get rid of the
restless legs they get rid of the
restless legs and it turns out the brain
tumor wasn't causing the restless legs
so
so even if someone has a lower back
issue
it doesn't mean the lower back issue is
the problem too someone could have a
bulging disc they could have a spine
issue they can have a sciatic nerve
problem they can have a degenerative
disc issue something can be wrong in
their lower spine right here and it
doesn't mean that that's actually
causing their restless legs so that's
another problem on its own so now you're
at the chiropractor and the chiropractor
is trying to do all kinds of stuff
saying well man
you know well sir your restless legs
probably because we're seeing there's an
inconsistency right here in your lower
spine in your lumbar or your thoracic
area that must be where your restless
legs are so they start searching in
those areas but even with that visiting
your chiropractor over and over again
visiting your massage therapist you've
been to the doctor you've had your MRIs
you've had a lot of things done and
looked at and you're still suffering
with restless legs let's go into now the
nitty-gritty and some details right here
so we're in brand saver talk about
restless legs you guys restless legs can
come from two places ah
first is the shingles virus releasing
neurotoxins that affect the lower spine
so let's head there
shingles virus likes to sit around the
lower spine for a lot of people it's
likes to Harbor in this area the
shingles virus can Nest itself in
connective tissue around the lower spine
then release neurotoxins these
neurotoxins can then inflame the sciatic
nerve other nerves too so the shingles
virus without having the pustules like
the rash can cause those restless legs
this is one of the Undiscovered
mysteries of restless legs which is the
neurotoxins created by the shingles
virus produced by the shingles virus
sitting inside the liver is is another
problem so the shingles virus doesn't
just harbor around the lower spine the
shingles virus likes to sit around the
liver too so not just the lower spine
liver as well inside the liver producing
neurotoxins and those neurotoxins start
to gum up and fill up the liver so when
that liver gets filled with neurotoxins
we have another problem
so the liver can settle in different
places the neurotoxins can settle in
different places inside the liver
depending on what those neurotoxins are
filled with so here's the incredible
piece of information too right here in
brain saver so we're in the details you
guys
higher amounts of lead and copper being
consumed by the shingles virus will
result in a heavier neurotoxin so check
this out if the virus is feeding off of
different Metals it can actually create
a heavier neurotoxin so if the virus is
sitting here feeding off of different
Metals it could then produce a waste
that comes out of the shingles virus but
a waste that's heavier and when that
waste is heavier check this out this is
incredible really this is how you become
your own expert right here
if higher amounts of lead and copper
being consumed by the shingles virus are
happening then those heavier neurotoxins
tend to settle in lower areas
they'll often drop into the lower back
legs and feet irritating the nerves and
creating subtle spasms so if you have
certain toxic heavy metals and the
shingles virus is feeding off of those
Metals those metals neurotoxins are
being released they settle in lower
areas of the body
feet the legs the lower back irritating
the nerves creating nerve spasms giving
somebody restless legs signs of research
is probably 50 60 years from knowing
this information maybe even a hundred
years some varieties of Epstein-Barr can
also create these heavier types of
neurotoxins as well so Epstein-Barr can
create heavy neurotoxins people can have
restless legs all day long while
standing and working or sitting and not
realize it until they're still or lying
down for the night so let's talk about
that are you somebody with restless leg
syndrome when it's at night and you're
trying to sleep but during the day when
you're working moving around working in
the kitchen maybe doing your job it's
not bothering you like where's your
restless leg syndrome so here you are
you're living your life it's during the
day you're working you're in the kitchen
washing stuff you're doing things you're
doing the laundry you're walking around
the house where's your restless legs is
it there or is it not but then when you
lay down and it's sleep time you get the
restless legs
so people can have the restless legs all
day long while standing working or
sitting and not realize it until they're
still are laying down for the night
here's the other way restless legs can
occur viral neurotoxins filled the same
methylated metals can enter the brain so
then we can get
a restless leg syndrome some viral
neurotoxins entering the brain
that's a whole nother level of
neurotoxins you guys there's so much
information in here I'm just cutting
into some of some it's you know
scratching the surface restless legs
protocol is in this book right here
so there are two books two big books
couldn't be published as one big book it
was too big too much comprehensive
information
seven heavy metal detox cleanses over
300 symptoms conditions and protocols
brain shot therapies and I'm just
scratching the surface of these books I
mean there's meditations in these books
there's so much information it's so
comprehensive your mind will be blown
when you get into this but I will tell
you right now be prepared to become an
expert so nobody owns you you're not
controlled by anybody you become
empowered because you have the answers
you have the details your mind's going
to be blown are you ready for it