hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now and as
I've always said who has had 10 or 20 30
years to wait or waste away or lose or
four years to lose or 5 years to lose I
know I say this a lot but it's that
serious where when we're sick and we're
not feeling good waiting for answers
could feel like it's
forever and most importantly waiting for
real information to what's causing our
problems to what's causing our Agony you
know real information on what's wrong
and and that's a big part of it you know
I run into people all the time you guys
that they just want to know what's
what's the deal you know what's really
going on in their body cuzz when you
don't know what's going on in your body
you you can be lost you can feel really
lost so when you think about that that's
serious stuff we're talking about that's
really serious not knowing what's wrong
inside or inside our body makes things a
lot harder with healing it makes things
really difficult in healing it makes
things complicated it makes things a
little bit more you know challenging in
many different Avenues emotionally
physically mentally um for both families
and for someone's own you know being too
but the families around them they're
friends and you know what happens is
when we get sick and maybe you've
experienced this
before maybe you've you've you've had
this happen before but you have some
friends and you get sick and you you'll
lose a couple of friends meaning meaning
they just kind of don't really want to
be friends much more because they're
kind of tired of everybody being sick or
they're tired of you being sick or
they're tired they're having troubles
with that they're it's not easy for
them and you know friends we thought
were our friends are not our friends
anymore but then we find new friends we
find new friends along the way you know
we do find new friends that actually you
know see a different you know
understanding and under you know see
things differently and um and you know
one of the reasons why it's so so hard
on also with having sicknesses and
illnesses and having friends and family
and and you know because when we don't
know what's wrong or what's causing the
symptom and then you know I've seen
people they I've seen people come to me
and say look my friend doesn't even
believe me anymore um I saw something on
a television show just recently too um
where you know this person had
rheumatoid arthritis and was running to
doctor to doctor
but then she was also um you know she
was also kind of looking healthy she
looked healthy she looked fine and her
friends were starting to say Hey you
know I I don't even get it anymore you
look fine everything looks good are you
just kind of like is this kind of a game
and it really hurt the person's feelings
with ra with rheumatoid arthritis and
you know to be kind of insulted to that
level
and look maybe you've look maybe you've
known somebody maybe you've done this to
someone where someone was years ago and
somebody was sick and you know and that
happened and you and you and you you
know thought somebody was kind of Faking
It faking it um so you know it it's It
Maybe not maybe somebody did it to you
I've seen it happen over the years I've
talked to a lot of people and a big part
of this is the no answers just there's
no answers
and they're really not out there we get
some diagnoses we get some labels but
the answers really aren't there and
that's what makes it so hard for for
everybody that's sick and then knowing
what connects to what like what's
causing those symptoms what's causing
those problems and then if you can't see
the illness you really can't see it if
it's not blatantly in front of you then
you know people say well you look fine
well you look good maybe you're just you
know looking for attention oh maybe
that's Sally just looking for attention
maybe that's um you know maybe you're
just maybe you're overreacting you know
I've had people say to people I got
aches and pains too I got problems too I
got this you don't see me complaining
you know there's there's so much going
on out there but but here's the deal
when you know what's causing your
problems when you learn what's behind
your illness and what's connecting the
dots and the pieces of the puzzle and
you know what they really are are and
you're not lost on the internet and
you're not lost out there looking for
things and when you when you find these
answers it makes a world of a diff
difference and that's what the medical
medium shows about who's got 10 years
who's got 20 years to wait for this
these answers no we want to we want to
get down to it and we want it we want
those answers now and it's important for
our children it's important for our
grandchildren it's important for the
loved ones that we've lost you know it's
important for the you know four four
fathers and four mothers of the
past it it's in it's important for all
of these reasons and so we're on it
Today's show today's show is about the
brain about the brain okay and you know
how to keep our brains healthy in a
world where we're having brain problems
and lots of brain problems how to keep
our brains from
shrinking how to keep our brains from
shrinking ining how about that one huh
yeah our brains shrink and when they
shrink we lose brain cells we lose brain
mass we lose you know we lose our brains
and then how about this one how to keep
our brains from
swelling okay how to keep our brains
from swelling that's another thing
that's a big deal that's called brain
inflammation all right that's called
brain
inflammation so we got two problems in
the world we're getting inflamed brains
causing lots of
symptoms and we're getting brains that
are shrinking so we're going into this
heavy there's no question about it you
guys check out my life changing Foods
book I know I probably sound like a
broken record but I'm not going to let
you down if you're disappointed with
this book I'll be I'll be probably
banging my head against the wall if you
are because I won't I won't cuz cuz I'm
my my mind would be blown that you'd be
disappointed it's it's packed it's
packed and and when I mean packed I mean
packed I mean um you know what's funny
on Facebook I saw recently on Facebook
someone like well wait a minute what
does this book what is this
life-changing Foods book have in it that
the first medical medium Bible doesn't
have in it you know how can what is this
going to be is this a throwaway recipe
book is this a a cute little add-on book
no this thing is passed
and it's when I'm talking about over 700
illnesses and and symptoms and diseases
okay how to connect the dots what foods
help information that doesn't exist
anywhere else on wild Foods herbs and
spices on vegetables on fruits how to
protect yourself from the unforgiving
for the unforgiving for that everybody
ignores that's destroying our lives
making us sick that's making us decline
everybody's ignoring it the trends and
the fads are ignoring it you know all
the fads and different Trends they're
you know they're all the you know the
hip you know books out there hip
information hip internet information all
ignoring it because they don't know
about the unforgiving for it's in this
book I can't say it enough try to try to
lo you know try to grab yourself a copy
Lo meaning get your name on a copy
before it even comes out so you don't
have to wait forever and it's out of
stock and all that stuff like what
happened with the medical medium
original book and this one I think will
be worse in that in that department so
anyway listen let's talk about the brain
I'm I'm here I'm I'm with you now I just
want you to fast in the seat bels for
this this ride and um because and we're
we're hitting a rocket ship on this one
well I mean we're in a rocket ship on
this one um so you know take a deep
breath and relax and uh take another
deep breath after that and then relax
cuz we're about to take off and you want
to be slightly Calm before we take off
so brain shrinking what the heck am I
talking about with brain shrinking what
am I talking about okay well brain
shrinking is the
loss of carbohydrates in the brain the
loss of carbohydrates in the
brain yes yeah the loss of glycogen in
your brain and we get older we lose
glycogen storage in our brain what is
that what is glycogen sto do you know
what glycogen storage is you probably
somebody probably does out there what is
glycogen storage and glycogen storage is
sugar the loss of
sugar imagine that the loss of sugar in
our brain okay so why is that important
like why why should we care sugar
Sugar's bad Sugar's bad for you wait a
minute it's all about fat now no lots of
fat no protein it's all about protein
protein protein which is basically lots
of fat protein and that's all that we
care about
nowadays well all that does is Fast
Track us to to a brain that shrinks more
and to a more unhealthier brain and to
brain diseases and Alzheimer's and
Dementia and everything around brain
diseases we know today so the brain is
made out of this dense amount of
carbohydrates that have like that have t
it's a carbohydrate ball of it basically
because carbohydrates is one of the keys
to conducting
electricity it's one of the keys of
cooling down the
engine see our brains get hot they get
hot and you have to have sugar to cool
them down you got to have carbohydrates
to cool down the brain now I'm sure some
of you are out there saying okay this is
this is bull
crap this is bull because he's talking
about sugar Sugar's bad for you what's
he talking about I'm not talking about
corn syrup I'm not talking about I'm not
talking about table sugar I'm not
talking about chocolate cake I'm not
talking about chocolate donuts I'm not
talking about powdered Donuts here's the
deal okay we're not talking about that
we're not talking about that kind of
sugar and you got to know this I just
got to make sure that that gets across
because I know a few of you are going to
be already peed
off you're going to be already upset and
frustrated but the brain is made out of
sugar and there's a little bit of fat in
the brain not a lot the brain doesn't
have a lot of fat at all in it very
little micro micro micro
small micro
small
literally like we're talking like less
than
10% and the fat that's in the brain is
just highly highly rare rare oils that
the body practically
produces and we receive from Foods rare
oils it's not what runs the brain it's
just a fraction of brain health so right
now you're going to hear about Omega-3s
you're going to hear about Omas fish
oils oh it's for the brain it's all the
brain outdated outdated outdated go to
the Antique sh shop I've been saying
that too many times lately someone told
me the other day I think my assistant
said to me said you got to stop throwing
the antique thing out at
everybody I can't help it because you're
shopping for antiques with the
information that's brand new off the
press right now and brain health and
everything else around it I don't care
what came out two years ago what came
out one year ago what's coming out next
year if it doesn't say your brain is
made out of 90% carbohydrates that's
part of it we're going to cover some of
the rest of it and then a small
percentage a small
percentage of things like squalene and
things like omegas re you know DHA EPA
but on a small
fraction okay
and that that very little fat and then
the rest the rest is
minerals
minerals and of course there's cells and
neurons and they're there too you got
your gal cells you got your neurons
those are there too they're all wrapped
in and around lots of stored glycogen
that was built up when you were a baby
in the womb from your
mommy eating anything that had sugar in
it anything that had sugar in it when a
mom goes carb free
pregnant the baby the baby's brain
suffers when a mom goes carb-free
pregnant and one of the one of the
greatest mistakes in the world is
lowering carbs with a
pregnancy okay so we got to make sure
your carbs are up it's very important
because that initial storage you're not
hear you're not hear this from anywhere
this isn't good you're not going to hear
this stuff from anywhere this is why
we're here at the medical Medium show
this is why Spirits giving us this
information so we can protect ourselves
and our family and move forward and heal
I don't want anybody in the dark anymore
and you know what happens is those
critical storage bins of carbohydrates
that mommy's eating while pregnant
becomes the backbone to brain
tissue becomes reserves car carbohydrate
reserves glycogen storages to make the
brain grow and
become and so we start with that and we
keep that it's it's
imperative so our brain is mostly
comprised of a sugar and runs on sugar
it runs on sugar you know what you know
how I pick on medical research and
medical science a lot and you know and I
don't mean in um heart transplants and I
don't mean in broken legs and I don't
mean when you need a great surgeon
surgeons are you know gifted incredible
gifted men and women on the planet um
and and you know when we need them we
need them when things happen to us we
need them when we go through all
different kinds of crises like your
gallbladder explodes because you weren't
taking care of your gallbladder for 30
years um you know that kind of thing um
aneurysm in the brain you know we need a
brain we need a brain surgeon with Rob
you know with robots with a robot that
go in there and literally remove an
aneurysm and
and I got tremendous respect for doctors
and practitioners I'm talking about
medical re research it's science that
doesn't understand chronic illness one
bit on any
level and what happens here is that um
with medical research and medical
science there was a great discovery and
you know I'm always picking on research
and science but there was a great
discovery that the brain ran on
sugar you focus on just protein and fats
and you starve your body of
carbohydrates your brain will shrink and
it'll shrink faster sure you may not
notice it when you're 30 years old and
your your low carb and you're exercising
you're low carb and you're 30 years old
you're not going to notice it you'll
notice it when it hits you when you're
60 for what you did when you were 30
it's that imperative that we have
carbohydrates and before anybody else
gets upset at me hold back your rotten
tomatoes and your potatoes and the rocks
that you want to probably Stone me to
death with for for people who just don't
like this topic because it's it's
controversial uh and I'm on your side
without I get it contral stuff can just
you know get anybody upset but before
you you know before you throw a Stone
you know you you have to understand that
I'm also not talking about bad
carbohydrates I'm not talking about you
know wheat I'm not talking about wheat
gluten I you know well glutens are
proteins but I'm not talking about wheat
I'm not talking about bad bad
carbohydrates okay I'm not talking about
corn and um so so basically the first
understanding is what the brain's made
out of because if you don't know what
you're made out of then guess what
you're not going to do the right things
and guess what we're not going to take
care of our brain and guess what we're
totally going to be you know messed up
from it or we're going to cheat
ourselves out of something we're going
to lose out we're going to lose out I
don't want anybody losing out so um so
we got to get into this a little bit so
electricity runs hot our brains run hot
when we go through trouble when we have
problems in our lives our brains heat up
anxiety heats up the brain stress heats
up the
brain you can't be carb free while under
stress you will dissolve I've seen
people do it they dissolve they're like
a puddle they just dissolve and they
melt you carbs are critical for the
brain to keep the brain cool and
calm now it is true that there are some
essential oils that I'm talking about
not essential oils but essential omegas
that are critical for the brain and
brain health you know like pumpkin seed
oil okay hemp seed oil um you know that
kind of thing it is important because it
does comprise of part of the brain but
but that isn't what runs the whole
machine that's what I'm talking
about so to keep our brains from
shrinking as we get older so we don't
get all kinds of diseases and brain
diseases and memory loss and everything
else we got to make sure we have
glycogen storage banks in the brain
keeping that tissue good so that's the
first thing to understand so what that
means is sweet potatoes it means regular
potato it means and at wait and before
you pick on me about potato being a
white food it's not a white food it's
not a white food you guys it's not I
know everybody's not saying anything I'm
just saying I I I feel someone's out
there saying he's talking about a white
food now someone new on listening in is
saying he's talking about a white food
now hang on hang on okay
the skin of the food determines if it's
a white food or not you got a red
skinned potato you got a red food you
got a purple skinned potato you got a
purple food you got a brown skinned
potato you got a brown
food you you have a you know a gold
skinned potato you got a gold
food okay you cut it open and you got
white inside but that's not processed
that's a whole food loaded with minerals
and vitamins lyine to stop viruses and
diseases that's what's in a potato okay
okay you take a cultivated blueberry
which I don't like by the way I don't
like cultivated blueberries I mean they
they got Health to them they're healthy
but it's the Frozen wild blueberry that
holds all the power but just let's move
over the the Frozen wild blueberry
because when you open up a FL Frozen
wild blueberry it's blue
inside it's
blue like blue like real blue like real
blue you open up a big cultivated round
uh cultivated blueberry in the clamshell
you pick up the fresh blueberries in the
clam shell you open that up it's white
inside want to call that a white food
let's call that a white food if you're
going to call a potato a white food
you're your blueberry that you're
probably throwing in your smoothie let's
call that a white food it's not a white
food it's a blue food even the
cultivated blueberry is a blue food
let's talk about a radish let's cut open
a radish it's white inside it's a red
food and purple food depending if it's a
purple radish or red radish and the
potato is the same way it's not a white
food this is another mistake I'm
clearing up as we run into these as we
need food foods for ourselves I have to
clear up some of these trendy mistakes
and
misconceptions for you guys because
there's so many of them they're like
landmines that poison our ground they're
like like landmines that are there to De
you know to literally you know basically
detonate and knock us off our tracks and
this is part of why people don't heal
every one of these counts it's why we're
that's why spirit and I when I say we're
spirit and I are loading these things up
in our books this book coming out life
Chang ing Foods we need to have the
information the medical meaning book we
need to have it out here we can't be
doing this anymore we got to make sure
everybody has that so brain shrinking is
when we lose our carbohydrate reserves
our brain squee you know they squeeze
down and they shrink all right brain
swelling brain swelling is mild en
sephtis that's not
diagnosed from viruses that's what
people with Lyme disease get people with
multiple SC osis get people with ala get
I mean ALS get people with um all these
different problems and their brains they
get swelling in different parts of their
brain it's hard to pick up on CAT scans
you can't pick it up on MRIs and you get
brain
inflammation and so that's something
that's caused by
viruses viruses such as um you know hhv6
viruses such as shingles different
varieties of shingles um even different
varieties of Epstein bar can do it you
know V is actually in cause inflammation
in the brain because the nervous system
is inflamed from neurotoxins so
neurotoxins neurotoxins are pro produced
by viruses they float around in the
bloodstream they get into the brain and
they give us brain fog memory loss all
kinds of problems they give us migraines
they make us susceptible they give us
SES and pains they hurt our eyes they
give us all kinds of weird stuff in the
brain and those are neurotoxins from
viral debris and stuff and then we have
heavy metals lots of heavy metals in our
brains and we got to get the heavy
metals out we got to get the viral
toxins out that are floating around in
the body we got to get that out of the
brain got to get the heavy metals out so
listen you know because we we don't have
a a ton of time today you just make sure
you know you do the heavy metal detox
that I talk about um check that out the
heavy metal detox it's in the first
medical medium book and you get the
metals at of your brain and we'll talk
about some foods you know to kind of
help that along as a little later on uh
today with this with this um Talk um so
we want to make sure we get those Metals
out of our brain too so it's a whole
another thing Mercury lead cadmium
arsenic copper our brains are filled
with copper a lot of times you know
that's a whole another thing there's
copper everywhere which reminds me if
you're somebody that is afraid to take
zinc because you're going to lose your
copper storage that's another trendy
mistake that's it's another
misconception that's out there first of
all we're loaded with hard copper all of
us are loaded with hard copper okay it's
in our livers it's in our brains people
with examen psoriasis have way more in
their liver with Co copper but it's in
us and the only way to get it out is to
do things to take out heavy metals like
like in the book I talk about the barley
grass the wild blueberries the spirulina
the cilantro and the dols and that helps
get it out but understand that when you
take zinc zinc won't remove the mineral
copper that we have the precious mineral
copper that we have in our body that we
use the zinc a high quality zinc only
removes if at best hard copper the stuff
we're loaded with and food is has tons
of copper in it both the mineral
itself you know the trace mineral itself
copper and both the bad copper you know
on different foods if it's or if it's
conventional produce bad copper is going
to be on it if it's um not not
traditional produce if it's conventional
produce if it's organic it'll still have
the mineral copper in it because it's
it's plentiful in our soils zinc doesn't
exist
anymore it doesn't it doesn't exist
anymore it's not even in pumpkin seeds
barely anymore so we need our zinc
supplements it helps us with the brain
health it helps us with everything
it helps it helps keate bad metals like
the copper out of us the bad copper so
don't be afraid to taking a little bit
of zinc so you just want to clear that
up so our
brains okay let me tell you something
about it and I talked about this before
in in a in um in another podcast in
another radio show I talked about it and
our brains
actually if there are people out there
that eat brain they eat sheep brain cow
brain brain goat brain lamb brain
there's people out there eating brains
out there I don't recommend it I don't
at all I I don't like the brain eating
thing I just can't get I can't wrap my I
can't wrap my head around it I can't
wrap my head around that all right no uh
no pun intended and you know and the
bottom line is is that when people do
eat brains in different countries
including here and you know like rabbit
brain that's that's pretty common here
rabbit brain that there's a lot of
people eating in the US they're eating
you know they eat the the brain out of
the rabbit they have the rabbit stewing
in a stew you know afterwards you just
you know kind of crack the head open a
little bit and they take the rabbit
brain I'm just I'm just telling you guys
it's very common in the US it's it's a
staple in a lot of different communities
here's the
deal um the brain is sweet it's sweet
like a sugar pudding it's sweet because
it's got so much carbohydrate in there
so so let's go into the carbohydrate
thing carbohydrate is a conductor for
mineral salts conductor for mineral
salts mineral salts sodium chloride you
know potassium magnesium all these
different mineral salts and um and and
those sugars in the brain the glycogen
that's a conductor so that these mineral
salts become a neuron a neurotransmitter
sorry so they become a
neurotransmitter and that
neurotransmitter is a chemical that sits
on a neuron so we can think and function
and get stressed out and work hard and
play hard and do whatever we got to
do and so that's just so you know the
background a little bit when you have
heavy metals in the brain they interfere
with electrical impulses running down in
neurons so you got you have to
understand you have this neuron and you
got electrical impulse that needs to get
to one end to the neuron to the other so
we can communicate so we can talk so we
can function and as that electrical
impulse is driving down that neuron it
needs that neurochemical that
neurotransmitter chemical potassium
sodium chloride magnesium it needs those
to run and be and just to run that
electrical impulse across the neuron and
then if you're loaded with heavy metals
Mercury cadmiun lead if you you know
where Mercury for sure aluminum they
deflect they get in the way they they
they D down the flame of of the uh the
neurotransmitter they die down the flame
of the electrical impulse running you
know running running down the neuron
using the neurotransmitter to do so and
it just it dieses out the flame so we
got to get the heavy metals out of there
and heavy metals oxidize into the brain
and they end up bleeding into the brain
meaning that they oxidize and run off
like a river polluting the
brain and so we have to clean out the
metals out of the brain that's number
one got to clean out the old the old
glutamate not glutamine glutamate the
MSG um lots of MSG in the brain we have
in many different people pockets of it
in different places we need to clear
that out as well aspiran got to get the
aspiran out of the
brain and that's important and all this
is critical and then we got to make sure
our brain is healthy with enough
glycogen so we need the right foods and
I'm going to talk about that and we need
to get rid of the wrong foods to get our
brains healthy
healthier see all this is important and
we're going to cover some supplements
too about how you know what's good for
the brain so the goal is that under
stress we need a carbohydrate if we're
under
stress the carbohydrate and eating when
we're under stress stops our adrenaline
from dissolving our
brains what happens is adrenaline
becomes
one of the most toxic substances to us
that destroys our brain health so this
shows about brain health and I'm going
to tell you one of the one of the most
toxic substances is our own adrenaline
being triggered off by crap happening in
our lives you know like bad news and you
know you name it and the shock of bad
news why do you think we say Hey you
have to sit down for this list listen
listen Mack I think you're gonna have to
sit down because I got to tell you
something I gotta break break some news
to you because if you're standing up
you're going to have an electrical shock
so hard in the brain that you might pass
out or you might just fall backwards so
we might have to just have you sit
down I always find it doesn't work to
get bad news delivered to you sitting
down I I I would rather
Pace with bad news coming to me I'd
rather be moving a little bit um but
there's a reason why we tell people to
sit down there's an electrical shock
it's magnified when it gets handed to us
like this when we get stressed or bad
news or we're under the gun and then our
adrenaline floods if you're not eating
enough carbohydrate during that day or
every hour and a half or two hours your
adrenaline will just go into the brain
and start saturating it and pickling it
pickling it like it was in
vinegar and and this is what we're up
against it's
basically a technique it's a way we you
know we we survive it's fight or flight
but when we're under fight or flight so
much we have to be cautious and Cal it
down and make sure we have enough of
those good carbohydrates to stop us from
fight or flight meaning it stops the
Damage Done by the adrenaline it Shields
the
adrenaline and it's also why naturally
you know you go look you know you take
your child to the doctor's office and
they got lollipop sitting there after
after your child had you know um you
know a look after the doctor looked down
your child's throat and told your your
child to say ah it was kind of a scary
experience so then you know your child
you know it's you need a lollipop at the
end or or Mom will take the child to to
get some ice cream afterwards after a
doctor's visit that happens a lot
because those are not good forms of
sugar but it's to kind of take that
shock of whatever adrenaline was kind of
running from being
scared and so
glucose is what we need to protect
ourselves in a stressful world that we
live in today but it's not just
protecting ourselves it's protecting our
brains and the 21st century we're
getting some serious brain rot it is
evident it is rampant it is out of
control protein does not keep our brain
healthy and protein does
not make our brain stay
strong um that that's very important to
understand just so you know I'm not
anti-protein we need our protein from
lots of fruits and vegetables you know
there's other protein sources people get
it from you know high quality animal
products but the goal is the goal is is
that we can't do the carb free thing we
can't go that route we have to have a
lot of fresh fruits in our diet and I
want to go into that now
antioxidants stops your brain from dying
it's antioxidants so phytochemicals it's
the phytochemical antioxidant family and
especially the one that's not even
discovered by science that I talk about
in life-changing Foods they keep your
brain from dying that's what
antioxidants do they stop the dying
process highest forms of antioxidants
are in the fruit group so don't be
afraid of eating an apple an apple is
anti-inflammatory for the
brain TI in antioxidants but it's ant
anti-inflammatory and it's not a white
food just because the skin is remember
the skin is red you open an apple it's
white inside that's where the people who
pick on potatoes got it all wrong okay
then maybe call an apple a white food
then you you see what I'm saying you
guys another piece of you know you can
you can really do your own you know your
breakdown on some of these Trends and
some of these fads you could even just
you know learn how to break them apart
yourself because they're that
ridiculous so anyway an Apple's not a
white food yes it's powerful and that's
what we need to be helping that's a
brain
food so the goal is lots of antioxidants
for the brain you do the heavy metal
detox for the brain the
spirulina the cilantro the barley grass
juice powder and you guys know my
favorite I have it listed on my um you
know it's on my website if you want to
look I mean there's one there and
that'll take you to a place to get it
and so the barley grass juice powder and
the dols the cilantro it's that whole
team to get the metals out of the brain
and and that team also does have
phytochemicals in it that that that help
with mineral salts help with
neurotransmitters but that's the team
there and then you want lots of fresh
fruit in your diet I'm not talking about
you don't have to eat just just fruit if
you don't want to that's fine you just
have to have it in there you can't H not
have your berries got to have your
blackberries your raspberries when's the
last time you had blackberries I want to
know I want to know the last time you
had
blackberries and so you know we need
these you got your apples oranges
calcium from oranges supports the brain
supports the nervous system supports the
brain so
calcium that's that's a that's another
one that's actually a neurotransmitter
chemical believe it or not it's not
listed as one but it is it's in the
family meaning it helps support that so
get that from oranges best source of
calorie you know best source of of you
know calcium and it's also a great
caloric food for the brain um so these
are some of the things we're talking
about what we can do to protect our
brain in every way
possible let's go into some different
stuff we'll go into some foods wild
blueberries most powerful antioxidant
there is for the brain for keeping your
brain healthy so it doesn't shrink and
it doesn't swell
and celery juice the mineral salts and
celery juice you guys doing the celery
juice there's people healing all over
the world right now you can see it on
the Instagram page go check it out I
mean and and there's people healing on
Facebook doing their celery juice it is
really helping people and and spirit
brought that to the world's attention
and you know and I'm not talking about
one stick of celery in a green juice
with other you know greens I do like
green juices of all kinds but those are
for those are for kind of Maintenance
celeries a
medicine medicine especially for in the
world of brain health today in the world
of brain problems and what's happening
in in with with what's going on with our
brains celery has undiscovered mineral
salt
compositions and and a type of mineral
salt that science hasn't even touched
upon yet because there no one's even
looking there and I talk about it in
life-changing Foods celery juice is
amazing for brain health you can't get
away from it it's that good cucumber and
cucumber juices they help with DDT heavy
metals pesticides radiation in the brain
you know cucumbers tend to help calm the
brain down and make it kind of an Avenue
so things can leave the brain easier so
when you're doing your heavy metal detox
you got your cucumber juice and you got
or your cucumbers and your salads every
day now here's the deal if there's
something you think you got going on
and you think you got a problem and you
think you got something and you think
you got your handle on it and you you
know what food to use you got to use a
decent amount of the food you can't just
have a cucumber once a week if if you
think you got something you know
happening and you want to eat some wild
blueberries you can't just eat them once
a month although it will still help you
and will still protect you but for
getting better you want those wild
blueberries every day you want a celery
juice every day if you're really
thinking you got something that you're
challenged with something that's in your
way something that you're having a
difficulty with with your health you
want to make sure you got these things
going on leafy
greens leafy greens
incredible for the
brain spinach lettuces butterleaf
lettuce has a
rare aega oil in it that goes to the
brain remember I told you there's still
a percentage I'm not saying that the
Omega-3s and I'm not saying the DHA
Omega-3s and and and fats aren't in the
brain I just told you it's a smaller
percentage it's much smaller it's not as
important as the carbo carbohydrate
factor that it's not as important okay
that means that we do need that Omega-3
for the brain but it's not a deal
breaker people can live long enough
without it you take away the
carbohydrates out of the brain people
die pretty fast it's a deal breaker you
see the difference that's what I'm
trying to say all right um so and you
can search for all the brain books you
want out there and you're just like
antiquate it antiquate it antiquate it
antiquate it you're just going to you
can go through all the ones you want if
it doesn't have this information in it
and uh I'm just saying that so you're
not wasting time on every day of your
life for getting healthy someone said to
me the other day well you've been
picking on you know other Avenues out
they're saying it's you know it's it's
Antiquated and stuff like do you want to
waste time you want to waste another day
of your life no you got to you got a
health problem get on it get H healing
get working there's no time for debating
there's no time for you know whatever we
just got to get the right information
now because it's that important it it
matters it so matters Arta chokes Arta
chokes incredible for the liver which
helps the brain cuz the liver gets
clogged up with Epstein bar toxins gets
clogged up with heavy metal it gets
clogged up and when the liver gets
clogged up and we're in trouble because
it's just just it just releases it all
in the bloodstream everywhere it
releases it all in the bloodstream and
when it does it gets to the brain and it
cause causes brain fog memory loss all
those neurotoxins from Epstein bar and
different viruses and different bugs it
all gets into the brain causes brain fog
confusion so you want to get your arch
chokes it helps with that helps with the
liver parsley another great one parsley
helps remove toxins like MSG and other
types of toxins and pesticides and and
you know the whole bit it helps remove
that so we like partially for the brain
it's what it is is it hitches a ride to
the the Fab Five you know it hitches a
ride to the sparina cilantro to the
barley grass to the DOL to um you know
the wild blueberries partially kind of
you know what it helps it helps walnuts
now try not to get thrown by that whole
thing where the Walnut shaped like a
brain so then it's good for your brain
try not to kind of get thrown by that
because there's better things for your
brain and they're not shaped like a
brain the wild blueberry is the most
powerful food on the planet for the
brain is it shaped like a brain no it's
not shaped like a brain it's shaped like
a wild blueberry all right so I I I
realize that there's information out
there that we kind of get we could get
sucked into like oh yeah wait a minute
the walnuts looks like a braak brain
okay that's a brain the Tomato looks
like a heart that's a heart doesn't work
like that the most powerful brain food
there is in existence right now is the
wild blueberry hands down can't touch it
it's not shaped like a brain okay just
you know I know I'm being sarcastic but
it's because you got to make sure you
know what's best it's so important right
now in our life in our world today I
can't express it enough and I like to
joke around a little bit too I know I
know so
but the wild blueberry seriously but
walnuts are good for the brain they
really are they are because they do have
that omega-3 that is that one little
part that one little portion that does
help the brain and help protect us like
I said though it's not a deal breaker
but I want some walnuts in your diet hem
seeds same reason is a hem seed first of
all hem seeds are better for your brain
than Walnut are hem seeds shaped like a
brain I want to know all right so you
know hemp seeds are really good so
that's a great one tum turmeric that's
good for the brain helps the body
cleanse helps the body detox supports
the liver supports the pancreas a little
bit of turmeric is wonderful
coconut
coconut coconut water coconut water
coconut that's great you know coconut
meat young coconut meat you know you
know coconut butter okay it it it's
actually good for the brain one reason
why it's good for the brain is because
it's it actually knocks down viral loads
so it knocks down um Epstein bar in the
liver knocks it down a little bit so
coconut should be in the diet one way or
another it knocks down that and that's
why people start feeling a little bit
better with brain problems it's not the
coconut going to the brain it's the
coconut knocking down the viral load
that's clogging up their bloodstream and
getting to the blood brain barrier and
poisoning the person's brain giving them
brain fog and brain confusion so coconut
that's really good aloe
vera fantastic it's just a great food
all all around for the brain cleans up
the liver cleans up the digestive tract
gets a lot of heavy metals out of there
um gets viral debris out of there aloe
vera is fantastic sea vegetables amazing
sea vegetables helps remove everything
under the Sun out of her bodies
pesticides radiation DDT heavy metals
you name it sea vegetables dolls kelp
very important
okay so make sure they're in the diet
make sure you're using them they support
the brain they protect us and and uh
keep them in there bananas yeah bananas
don't throw away your bananas I heard
years ago and I couldn't believe this
when the banana was becoming a a hated
uh you item in the world I heard there
was some huge conference somewhere and
some of the practitioners on the stage
had a they they open up the entire
conference holding a banana and throwing
it against the wall as the
opening because it was because it had
sugar in
it yeah let me tell you something about
banana it's the only thing on the planet
the only thing we have today that kills
HIV AIDS the virus itself the retrovirus
when put together in a Petri dish with
it nothing else has killed HIV
retrovirus I mean killed killed it just
Banana by itself it's one of the most
powerful antiviral Foods we have it's
got also it has neurotransmitter
chemicals to get us to sleep to Pro
protect us our brains it massages the
intestinal tract kills CBO kills strep
in the intestinal tract kills everything
out of the intestinal tract knocks out
fungus just clears out mold and that's
what banana does but it was thrown
against the wall at a contract at a at a
at a a conference it was thrown against
the
wall and you know so I'm just giving you
the rundown and that's how banana the
whole banana move it anti- banana
movement started I don't know if it was
seven years ago six years ago five years
ago but it it started and just has been
blossoming from there make sure you get
some bananas in there okay we'll talk
about you know we talked about let's do
a recap really quick we talked about the
brain eaing sugar it runs on sugar cools
down the engine and it's also made out
of carbohydrates the brain I was like I
was telling you before not bad sugar
good sugar like some fruits and some
sweet potatoes some butternut squash and
fats are okay too avocado hem seeds
walnuts coconut you know and other fats
too if you if you're eating really good
healthy lean meats and you like that
it's going to be better off than than
bad Meats stay away from pork because
pork fat doesn't help the brain um if
you're into you know if you're into uh
fish make sure it's salmon or hbit or
hack those are actually decent if you're
into fish um if you're you're into
proteins animal proteins just minimize
them a little bit each day if you have a
brain issue if you have a brain issue or
a brain problem just lower the animal
proteins I'm not telling you you have to
quit and you know and some people they
can if they want some people they don't
have to they could just lower them but
just lower them make it moderate so you
can get room for the things that help
your brain the room for the things that
help fix your brain very important
supplements melatonin incredible brain
supplement and you don't get addicted to
it that's misin out there it's not
addictive and it doesn't hurt the body
I'm telling you right now we should do a
whole show on melatonin spirina barley
grass um vitamin C curcumin which is you
know pulled out from turmeric curcumin
vitamin C incredible for the brain
berock root go get yourself some berock
root tea or fresh berock root juice some
fresh berock root in your juicer if you
want with your celery you can add
cucumber you can do a different kind of
juice that's not just celery and add
beroch if you're into different juices
add berock um magnesium magnesium
glycinate that's a good one good for the
brain magnesium uh is really helpful
l38 like from that company um jaro they
got magm or the other company life
extension they have neuromag so
lonate that's actually good for the El
glutamine is good for the brain too Gaba
Gab a you could always try that it's
helpful for the brain and um can calm
down anxiety in some people um you know
and so that's where we're going so we
talked about oxidation talked about the
heavy metals we talked about the brains
made out of you guys know now and we're
getting rid of toxins out of the brain
we're boosting up
neurotransmitters so this was this was a
big ride today you guys are you guys are
literally becoming the experts you're
becoming the experts I'm just telling
you that right now you guys are going to
be be teaching me every day you're going
to be teaching me something now I mean
literally you guys are becoming the
experts and I'm proud of you I stand
behind you 100% And I am absolutely
proud of you you could you can unlock
the seat belt right now and you know
relax for a little bit take a deep
breath because we're we got through this
check out the lifechanging foods book
we're you know if you can you know lock
down a copy if you can um I gave it my
all I gave that thing my all all I mean
you know late nights uh lost sleep um
you name it under the sun I made sure
it's in there and it matters it it's
it's in there not to mention you guys
there's 50 powerful healing recipes in
that book and that's just that was just
the fun part that's not even the heavy
duty information so um make sure you
check that out you know the other night
you know I was praying I was praying to
the angels I was praying to God and I
and I said that that you know you know I
love everybody for what they're doing
and taking care of themselves and it
means everything to me and I told spirit
I said spirit I said listen you got to
be quiet for a second because I got to I
got to talk to God and I told Spirit
just just just hold hold your horses I
got to talk to God I got to talk the
angels and I just got to thank God the
angels for all that is happening right
now with everybody's hard work and what
you're doing you're all a blessing in my
life and I thank God and I thank the
angels for that and I love you and I
stand behind you you're not a bad person
you didn't make yourself sick you're a
good person pat yourself on the back
have compassion for yourself I love you
bless you I'll see you next time