[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else in is decades
ahead of what's out there now and I mean
that the information we talk about on
the show the information that spirit and
I have been delivering for years and the
information that we have and we're
writing about right now so that you get
this information is unfiltered it's
unskewed it's untampered with it's
unchanged and it's
unaltered and what does that mean you
know you know how Food Works you guys
know cuz you guys are like becoming like
experts like Beyond experts you know how
Food Works where hey you grow your own
food or say food came from a farmer's
market or say you know whatever say even
conventional farming food grew and at
that State it's that whole food right
you guys it's like a whole food it's not
processed it's not tampered with it's
not unaltered it's not unchanged it's
not it's not UNF it's not unfiltered or
it's not filtered sorry about that and
it's just in that whole source that
whole food source you know so when you
have a carrot when you have a sweet
potato that's a sweet potato that's what
it is and even if you make a recipe
still you know it's the Whole Foods it's
that lettuce leaf it's that Cal Leaf
it's that mango it's that kiwi right hey
I'm talking about fruit a little bit hey
remember those are bad words fruit all
those names of fruits are bad words now
today I'm seeing it more and more out
there it's unbelievable
and so it with all these Whole Foods
nothing's nothing's tampered with when
they're like that they're whole and
that's the information here that's the
information on the medical Medium show
right there hasn't gone through process
processing hasn't been turned into a
potato chip hasn't been turned into a
cookie hasn't been turned into a donut
whatever it is hasn't been turned into a
a blueberry muffin with fake blueberries
in there hasn't been processed and
altered and the information here is 10
20 years ahead of what's out there now
and I mean that and life is precious and
there's no time to spare because you
don't have 10 years to wait for answers
unless you do unless you think you got
10 more years 15 more years meaning just
to wait around for answers I mean I
don't have that there's no way I need
the spirit I need the spirit information
now you guys need it now and you know
what I'm seeing out there right now
which is really disheartening I got to
tell you I would have thought by now
2016 I would have thought by now at 2016
where we are today we still weren't
going to be
recycling uh nonsense information that's
been around for 30 years 20 years the
same information but
recycling back into brand new literature
and selling it with a bow on it I never
thought that would happen it just makes
no sense and it tells me something it
tells me why we're still backwards and
why we're still not healing and why
we're still where we are today without
getting the answers and it just tells me
and and know I'm like okay okay you know
what okay now I know now I know here it
is 2016 so listen we're here we're tuned
in because we need that information we
need to move forward there's no question
stick around for today's show because
you know why Today's Show is about
rising out of the ashes you heard me I
said it rising out of the ashes okay
okay you know what that means right you
know what that means that means we go
through stuff we go through struggles we
go through trials we go through hard
times maybe we're not well maybe a loved
one's not well maybe we lose a loved one
maybe we we lost something in our lives
whatever that may be maybe you know
we're trying to change maybe we're
trying to make up for it maybe we're
trying to move ahead move forward but
sometimes we get stuck in the mud and
it's time to rise out of the ashes for
real and move forward and today we're
talking about that we're talking about
all the different little things to help
us rise out of the Ashes to help us
boost forward to move forward do you
need that because you know I can't get
enough of that because I I want that
there's no question I want to keep on
moving forward I want to be able to rise
out of the ashes anytime no matter what
hits no matter what comes and I want to
do that with you we we need to do it
together we need to go go and rise out
of the ashes together I'm with you let's
do it we're going to talk all about that
and you know in many times in our lives
we can rise out of the ashes at
different times in different ways
meaning in different different types of
rising out of the ashes that's a whole
another thing different types you know
I'm not just just talking about being
really ill and then rising out of that
Ash because we're going to talk about
that today but I'm talking about when
you need change in your life you need
change in your life and you need a
different direction or a new thought to
really help you pick your speed up and
move and just rise out of whatever
that's going on around in your life in
that moment so get a fresh start fresh
perspective you name it it's all about
that with rising out of the ashes
there's no question so that's today
check out the book lifechanging Foods
coming out really soon get a copy get a
copy if you can because this thing is
packed it is it is completely packed
with information what I mean that over
50 foods and this is just a fraction of
what's in there I couldn't even talk
about what's in there because there's so
much um 50 Foods in there what they
really do for you emotionally what they
do for you spiritually spiritually and
emotionally and how they help us in
every way diseases conditions symptoms
and information about the food that
doesn't exist anywhere else but in that
book from Spirit so make sure you get a
copy when you can that book is
life-changing I'll tell you why it's
changed my life just putting it together
and writing it one way is I had to after
writing that book you had to you had to
sweep me up off the floor I had to rise
rise out of what's called like you know
what's called like aftermath of getting
information like that from Spirit into
that book I was like okay I need I need
some recharging time for a week that's
how powerful this book is and what's
packed in there I mean literally I would
say A Part of my soul sitting inside
that book so I want you guys to get that
information and and you know and utilize
it and move forward with it because it's
going to be great you know check out my
events you know the LA event um coming
up uh it's coming up right around the
corner uh make sure you try to you know
if you're if you're around if you're in
the mood for getting a light blast to
ignite the healing and that light blast
that I talk about that started when I
was a child because what happened was
back a long time ago there wasn't a lot
of options for people to heal what I
mean by that is the grocery store had
nothing in it I'm going to be honest the
grocery store had nothing in it and I'm
sure you know there's there's people
that are listening you guys are
listening people out there that remember
that you go around your Corner
Supermarket and there was iceberg
lettuce okay and if you're lucky some
broccoli so I'm not going to be
completely completely saying there's
nothing in there but there was some
broccoli okay there was yes there was
some iceberg lettuce at least in my
store that's what we had and we had some
apples and some oranges okay those were
there and we had some bananas so I'm not
saying there wasn't some food but it was
really Bleak there wasn't cilantro there
wasn't you know berock rote okay there
wasn't Alo there wasn't just not even
just that there weren't even radishes
not in my neck of the woods back a long
long time ago there weren't the food for
healing and guess what the supplements
there weren't supplements they barely
existed at best they were really
gruesome I mean it was really gruesome
it was the Dark Ages back then so
options for people to heal weren't that
easy for people I remember when I was
about 13 years old and I was talking to
a client on the phone yes a client on
the phone at age 13 and in another state
and it was so Bleak yeah they had had
potatoes and they had iceberg lettuce
it's the two things they had and you
know for for medicinal Foods is what I'm
saying and I remember saying to Spirit
is there something else I can do is
there something else we can do because
they can't get they were in Idaho they
can't get anything but those two things
and no supplementation really when it
was in the dead of winter there was no
there was no foraging for wild food
because that's the first thing Spirit
would have said is we're going to look
for wild food for them that's what we're
going to do so there were a couple of
tees I remember that so I said to Spirit
what can we get and I and I asked the
people you know can you find this tea do
you know who could have this tea and
they had to go and just basically rans
sack an entire town for a little bit of
an herbal tea that's how bad it was so I
said to Spirit what do I do what do I do
we're not there yet and spirit said to
me there's going to in the future we're
going to have we're going to be packed
with different foods in the grocery
stores including even wild Foods in the
grocery stores to help us and I said
well you know what you know I I know
that but that's decades from now decades
from Spirit said there's going to be
supplements in the future too lots of
different supplements from Geniuses
Geniuses and Alternative Health I'm not
talking about the cookie cutter crap you
know the the the the conventional um
nutritional supplement that's just
garbage that I see on TV every day and I
look at it you know when I whenever I
get a chance and I watch TV for a couple
minutes or I see a commercial somewhere
when I'm over a family member's house
and they got the TV on all the time is
that's usually when I'll see it is going
over a family member's house and when I
look and I see a commercial come on and
it's for a junk junk junk fish oil like
something that's just not even a good
fish oil and you guys know how I stand
about fish oil where it's not really
good and or I see some kind of
conventional supplement and I'm not
talking about even those I mean I'm
talking about right now in this day we
have all kinds of ingenious supplements
coming from incredible places I
recommend them on my site uh all the
time um I don't sell them on there but
if you if you go to Medical mean.com
you'll see I have the supplement
registry it's a supplement kind of
directory of the best stuff from genius
people out there and that didn't exist
back then that didn't that did not exist
and I said to Spirit what do we do and
spirit says let's do the light
blast and and I said okay I like the
light blast and spirit showed me the
light blast you know even even a couple
years before then when I was even
younger and spirit had to remind let's
do the light blast again okay I'm ready
and then I would help and get that light
blast of the person Spirit would send
light from above down hitting the crown
of the person rushing through their body
and igniting their healing process and
that's what we do at the events and that
I don't care what it takes and I said
this before in some of the other shows I
don't care after that light blast that
I'm like a jellyfish on the ground okay
that I've been that I've been literally
neutralized and I'm on the ground like a
like a pull of sweat I make sure
everybody gets that blast of light and
then then I recharge later it's it's
it's it's fine you I don't want you guys
scared by it but I make sure that light
blast runs through everybody and starts
to ignite the healing process remove
start removing some old injuries some
Old Wounds we have hundreds and hundreds
of people that have had benefits coming
out of that and and and I and I still
I'm still willing to do it while I'm
here while I'm alive and breathing I'm
still willing to do it and that's just
the bottom line and I'm going to going
to keep on trying to do it so hey so
that's at the event we do the light
blast also we talk about things that we
don't talk about anywhere not even not
even here on the radio show and we do
the live readings right on right on
stage so right there spirit's with me by
my side never lets me down and and tells
me what's going on with someone so check
that out so you know if this is your
first time here we're going to get we're
going to get into it today we're going
to get into the show if this is your
first time here today it all started for
me at age four and I heard Spirit a
voice perfectly clear perfectly clear in
my right ear without anything in the way
just right there from the outside just
hearing spirit I went to my window and
looked out there thinking there was a
radio playing and there was nothing
going on there was nobody out there I
went
downstairs and saw my family and try to
shake it off and it would not shake off
that
evening sitting at the dinner table
Spirit appeared for the first of two
times Spirit has ever shown itself to me
so I hear spirit all the time in my ear
but this the first of two times that
I've ever seen Spirit ever
standing behind my
grandmother standing there and I was
sitting in my chair at the dinner table
and Spirits it spirit said to me and
waved me over and said come over and I
got out of my chair and I walked over to
my grandmother and he said pronounce
grandma has lung
cancer and I did after a couple of times
to get the words out just right and
later on we found out she did because we
had to take her in because a 4-year-old
just said Grandma has lung cancer and so
it all started there and I've dedicated
my life helping people helping tens of
thousands of people get answers and
that's what this show is about you guys
it's about getting the answers so that
we can move forward and heal and that's
what it's about so let's let's talk
about let's talk about rising out of the
ashes what does that mean what does that
mean well you know about the whole
Phoenix thing of course you know you got
the whole Phoenix thing and that's yeah
that that's that's a whole part of it
but we're not we're not talking about
that part of it we're talking we're
talking about the part of it about you
know literally when just everything
burns down on us that's what it feels
like and I'm not talking about Mercury
retrograde stuff where things get a
little hard I'm talking about when we're
we're struggling we're trying to push
through we're dealing with problems
we're dealing with sickness we're
dealing with illness we got all kinds of
different things going on in our life
and we and we have to get through
somehow you know spirit said to me
spirit said to me okay spirit said to me
all all storms
pass okay all storms pass and it is
sunny on the other side nothing stays
the same and all things change one thing
that people have told me over the years
has theyve been sick so long or not
feeling good so long or they've been
having a string long string of B bad
luck and they say to me it's not going
to
change it can't change it's been going
on too long and that's what they say to
me and it breaks my heart to hear that
to hear that come out of somebody's
mouth and I respect it I honor
it but one thing that like I said Spirit
has told me is nothing stays the same
and all things change no matter what so
nothing stays the same so if you've been
sick for a long time it's not going to
stay that
way it's going to change you have to
know that this is so important because
if you're in a storm and that Storm's a
long time and you've been experiencing
that storm for a long time and not well
and you're unwell and you've been sick
and not feeling good and you've been
experiencing that storm for a long time
it's not going to stay the same
it's not it's going to change and the
blue sky is going to come and the Sun is
going to come out so you need to know
that whether it's small whether it's big
whether it's something small where you
just have some symptoms you're dealing
with okay and the symptoms are doing
weird things and you're not sure what
they are cuz you've been to every doctor
and you've been searching and you don't
have answers but you have answers but
they're really not real answers but
you're looking for more
answers and it's you know it's not so
bad because you look
fine on the outside or maybe it's bad
and you still look fine on the outside
by the way did you guys ever have any of
that did you ever have that happen where
you know you're you're going through a
whole bunch you're going through a whole
bunch of stuff you're going through a
whole bunch of symptoms you're going
through a whole bunch of
conditions and people on the outside
they think you look fine like there's
nothing wrong with you Sally there's
nothing wrong with you Susan there's
nothing wrong with you you know Jennifer
there's nothing wrong with you you look
fine you're pushing through you look
fine you know no matter how many doctors
you went to and you said hey I'm not
feeling good people around you they're
like you look good you look good I mean
and that's really hard right there and
then people you know people are kind of
tired of hearing about it too did you
ever run into that I run I I hear about
that all the time then people are you
know they're tired they're they don't
want to hear it anymore they don't want
to here oh that's right yeah you're sick
well you look okay oh but that's right
you're tired um yeah I forgot you I you
know or I know I heard it a million
times and so we have to we have to hold
on to these things when we shouldn't
have to hold on to them but we have to
we have to be quiet about them sometimes
you guys ever you've ever run into that
because I talk to people and then I've
seen it happen and I've seen people go
through that and it's really hard but if
you're not feeling well and you've been
through something and you're going
through something like that it can
change it can change there's no question
about it it can change and you can move
forward so all storms pass Spirit told
me nothing stays the same and all things
change you got to remember that because
when you know that it helps make it
happen it helps make it happen faster
and
sooner and it helps build up the spirit
it helps build up your spirit okay so
it's something I wanted to tell you so
rising out of the
ashes you know if anyone who's ever been
sick or has been sick too long they
could get to a point of saying something
and I was kind of talking about this a
little bit they get to the point where
they're like can I heal that's what they
say is it possible to
heal is it ever going to happen can I
heal because when you've been sick too
long and you get and you're going
through it too long you lose even the
the feeling that you can heal you lose
it I've seen people lose it after 6
months so they get sick with something
they're going to doctor they're going to
the doctor medical clinics you know here
across the country famous medical
clinics um you know the whole
which are just starting to get just you
know a little bit of new information on
health a little bit but they but they're
not there yet so you go to all the fancy
medical clinics that still think the
body's attacking itself they still think
autoimmune is the body attacking itself
so this is if this is your first show
and you've haven't you know read any of
the books or anything else like that and
or looked into um our information the
body doesn't attack itself and
autoimmune is a great mistake and um we
talk about it more and more so you're
going to have to tune into some of that
so you know when when we're when we're
going around and we're looking for help
and even after 6 months we can get to
the point where I can't heal I I just
can't or can I is it even possible
anymore and all the doubts file in and
then there's some people that are like
okay no no and they got a little bit of
jevity in this and they just they fight
they got a little bit more fight and
they go for another year of looking
around and they're still not feeling
well and they go for two years then they
get their Lyme disease diagnosis and
then they don't get their Lyme disease
diagnosis and then nothing seems right
and they never got bit by a tick or
whatever it is and then you know or they
get their Ms diagnosis or they get no
diagnosis and they're still tired or
they get told it's all in their head and
they're creating it whatever it is you
know it can last and it can go on a
little bit and and eventually we get hit
with I I don't even know if I could heal
anymore and and that's that happens to
so many people and I'm sure you guys
probably even know a little bit about
that I'm sure it's happened to you
somebody I mean I know it's happened to
somebody cuz I hear it all the time and
I mean right have you heard it too have
you seen it in any loved ones or any
friends have you heard that that way too
I mean there's no
question the um you know if you're
here's the thing you know you got
there's one thing that's important to
know that if you were feeling good at
one time in your life this is for
anybody who's sick this is for anybody
who's not feeling good this is for
anybody who's struggling with hardships
even if it's not sickness or disease or
illness or
symptoms if you were in a better place
before in your
life whether that be at the beginning of
your life whether it be in the earlier
part or in a different part of your life
and you were feeling good and you were
well okay and you you felt great before
you got
sick you got to go back to that in your
mind you got to go back to that in your
memory or if it was before you had all
these trials and these you know these
hardships and struggles that are that
are not even sickness in your own life
but there's something else in your
family's life or something else around
you or whatever it might be whatever
kind of
struggle if you weren't in that position
at one time of your life you got to go
back to that and you got to be thinking
this is where present moment moment does
not help us
whatsoever this is where present moment
the whole present moment concept sh is
shattered being in the present moment
because because one thing Spirit told me
that if you're in the present moment
when you're really
sick then you're just going to be in
your present moment of being so sick and
if you're in the present moment of your
hardship you're going to be in the
present moment of your hardship this is
where looking into the future and
looking into the past past can save your
life and Present Moment present moment
doesn't now I believe in living in the
present moment I do I'm not I'm not you
know I'm not anti- presentes moment
believing um that's not it at all it's
just that present moment the whole
concept of present moment the whole
entire movement of the present moment
and the spiritual movement of it is for
people that aren't sick that's for
people that are healthy and fine and got
a lot of good things in their life and
they're just not they're just not being
the present moment during it
all and so that's what that's for okay
I'm just going to be honest but when you
got struggles like I've seen like I I've
I I even you know hey I've seen it in
all kinds of ways I've seen it in family
I've seen it out there I've seen it in
friends I've seen it you know all kinds
of struggles if you got all kinds of
struggles and you're sick and you're
going through Hellen back yeah I said it
hell and back you know you're going
through all this present moment doesn't
cut it I just going to I'm going to be
straightforward it doesn't cut it all it
does is put you right okay I'm okay yeah
I'm sick I know it I'm in I'm you know
being in the present moment how do I
enjoy this moment when I'm suffering how
do I enjoy this present moment when I
see someone suffering like they do how
do I enjoy this present moment when I'm
going through Hellen back with some kind
of trial that may not even be a
sickness and what what matters then when
you're in that position is you have to
go in the
past if you have to live in the past you
live in the past for a little
bit and that means if you were feeling
good and you weren't in a struggle or
you weren't in a trial and you weren't
in a battle and that was in the past and
you had freedom for that moment like
really good
Freedom that you feel like you might
have lost of being sick you got to go
back there in your mind you got to get
that sensation you got to touch it you
got to feel it because you own that
sensation it's
yours and you can't let the present
moment concept take that away from you
and then when you're better and you
recover and you get past it all you can
be in the present moment meaning you can
you can utilize the present moment of
what it has to offer but right now you
need to use what the past has to offer
that is critical I've seen it save lives
because when you're sick for 10 years
like you guys know you're feeling you
know not good you've been through so
much and you knew there was a time when
you were at your best feeling at your
best not sick and you were healthy you
got grab on to that you got to grab on
to that you got to go back there and say
I was healthy that means I still am
somewhere inside of me healthy you get
where I'm going with this now you got to
tap into the
past to realize Health still resides in
you somewhere you're not entirely
sick okay that you can get better it is
real inside of you what you have in you
cuz you were feeling good you had it
going on you were feeling great you're
living your life you were doing this or
you were going through school or you
were working or whatever it is and maybe
you didn't feel the 100% grip but you
felt good enough to function whatever it
is and that that was in your past better
grab on to that because that tells you
you got Health inside of you now in the
present you got Health inside of you now
in the present that you're you know that
you got attack
into and also it brings you back when
you go back to the past of that when you
go back to the past of
that you're you're capturing that you're
basically planting seeds instantly by
pulling from what you had in the past a
garden you grew a long time ago forget
the present moment Garden forget that
one right now you want to go to the past
and you want to pluck things out of that
Garden you want to pull fruits and
vegetables out of that Garden from the
past that's going to ignite something
inside of your soul and start rebuilding
your soul and your spirit start
strengthening your spirit strengthening
your spirit is what it does strengthens
your
spirit in the moment in the present
moment it strengthens your spirit you
got to go to the past and here's the
thing you got to go to the
Future you got to go to the Future you
have to know you're going to get better
remember what I said all storms pass so
what's in the future you guys what's in
the
future right you're thinking about it
right I'm with you what's in the future
Blue Sky Sun okay you feeling good you
over the storm you are healed you are
better you got your life life back you
feel great you're functioning the way
you always knew you could and had and
will and would all of that is there in
the
future so we got to forget the present
moment when we go through Tri trials and
we go through hardships and we go
through struggles we got to we got to
dump it just push that aside just just
it's about the future and it is about
the past you strengthen your spirit and
you build up your soul with from Gardens
you planted in your
past those fruits and vegetables those
herbs you planted those flowers you
planted in the past and that reminds me
I had one person one client say to me a
long time ago they said you know what
thank God you told me this I said why
and she said because I planted a lot of
flowers a lot of flowers in the the past
when I used to feel good and I could get
in my garden and I could dig and I could
plant bulbs and different flowers and
annuals and perennials and all this kind
of thing and I remember doing that and
getting in the dirt and I love my flower
garden I would put you know all the
different mulch down around my flowers
and then I would go out there with the
hose and I would water it with the
hose and she said
Anthony I've been sitting here trying to
meditate in the present moment sick as a
dog knowing I'm
suffering and you just you just brought
back something that I had in my life
that I've been latching on to now and
I'm nurturing now in the past and
bringing back and I'm
healing and I'm
healing an I said yeah well you're going
to think about your future too and she
goes but the future isn't the present
moment you can't we can't we're not
allowed to be in the future right I said
no no no no no no no no no no no no
don't don't worry there's things in the
present moment that you have that are
good that we can hold on to it's not all
anti-rent moment that's not it at all
there are things there are things that
we have that are in our present moment
good good things you know when we a
Friend helps us and and we are you know
moving forward taking our supplement or
eating the food we need there are things
in the present moment I'm going to talk
about in a minute I'm just trying to
make sure you guys know the point I'm
trying to get
across and it's so serious to Healing it
means everything to rising out of the
ashes and you got to think about the
future right told her and she goes well
I don't I don't really like thinking
about the future too much I said well
what are you afraid of and she goes I'm
afraid of I'm not going to heal cuz I've
been sick so long I said no no no you
got to think about the future you got to
know you're going to heal and you're
going to get better because remember
what I said that Spirit told me one of
the most powerful things ever and it
seems simplistic and it's not a lot of
words but I'm going to tell you what it
is again is all storms pass and nothing
stays the same and all things
change and I and and that right there is
a rising out of the ashes phrase quote
from
Spirit which reminds me somebody said to
me well you got a lot of quotes I said I
don't have any quotes they're all from
Spirit they're all from Spirit I'm not
smart enough to come out with a
quote they're all from
Spirit okay because I get all my words
from Spirit sure you know exactly I'm
not the smartest guy then because I
never went to school so I'm not the
smartest guy it all comes from Spirit
every last bit of it I got to use from
Spirit spirit's the smart one spirit's
the one that knows everything and I told
you that story a long time ago you guys
I told you that I I had you know this
ego built up inside of me when I was
when I was in my late teens and early
20s because I felt Invincible because
every single thing that came from from
Spirit was always
right and I remember helping out a
neighbor okay and I was in the garden I
was pulling out onions in the garden you
guys know the story I know I can't help
but to tell you I was pulling onions out
of the garden my neighbor was came over
and he was standing there in the garden
and he said to me I don't know how you
do it I said what said I don't know how
you knew what was wrong with my wife she
couldn't walk for years she was in a
wheelchair and you knew what was wrong
and how to fix it and we went to every
doctor and every clinic and to every
place possible we even went overseas we
went to Germany we went everywhere and
it couldn't be fixed and she was
worsening and he said and I was positive
she was going to die I lost all hope and
said you knew what was wrong you knew
she had arsenic poisoning how did you
know she had arsenic poisoning it wasn't
even testable but you knew and you knew
how to get it out of her brain I said
and I looked up as I was holding the
onions and I said that's because I'm
never wrong never forget the I'm always
right I'm going to be right I'm never
never going to be wrong you never forget
it everybody else in the world never
forget it I'm right I'm always going to
be right you better believe it you
better know it it's the way it's going
to be and I'm never going to be wrong I
stood up cuz I was feeling Invincible
because Spirit since age four just you
know built me up pretty good I was
getting pretty pretty pumped up and I
got up and I walked over I took a few
steps and I Ste stepped on a rake kind
of like a hoe that was in the garden
stepped on it it came back at my face
knocked me out I was unconscious when I
mean unconscious I was completely gone
and as I was laying there on the ground
and I came out of it I saw my neighbor
standing up looking over me and then at
the same time spirit said to me you
remember this Anthony I'm the one that's
right you're wrong I'm the one that's
right and never forget it and so what I
mean by that is when spirit's saying
all storms pass nothing stays the same
and all things change it's
true and so I was telling this client I
said you got to think about the future
what is it let's get the dream going
we're not going to kill the dream we're
going to bring it to life I want to know
where you see yourself at the
future I want to know and she say you
know what I see myself doing my flowers
again I see myself in the garden and
feeling good and my knees aren't
swollen and I see myself feeling better
I said I do too I see it
too and and I said you're going to take
what you have in the past that's yours
it's yours and you're going to bring it
in your mind now and bringing into your
soul now and you're going to recover
while you're doing your herbs and your
things that you need to do for your
health and you're doing the things
Spirit recommended and you're doing the
foods and you're doing all this great
stuff that Spirit recommends while
you're doing all of that in the present
moment that part's in the present moment
you're going to be thinking about the
past and you're going to be thinking
about the future and you're going to be
healing and she got better and she's on
the other side of that now in her life
she's on the other side of the storm and
let me tell you anybody who looked at
her at that time was like no no there's
no way no we just just she's she's she's
disabled there's no way she's disabled
she's not going anywhere that's what the
doctors would say that's what the
medical authorities also would say she's
not going anywhere that's it but no
she's better so it's important to
know you know when you're recovering and
you get the first sensations of
healing you got to hold on to those too
because it's a roller coaster ride for a
lot of people who've been sick for a
long time you guys it's a roller coaster
ride for a lot of people who have been
sick so if you guys have been sick or or
anything like that or anything going on
your life forget the sick thing too I
mean I I'm sure some of you out there
are like well I'm not sick I'm just
going through Hell
and Hell and everything plus and I got
all this stress and I got everything and
it hasn't changed and it's not
changing and um well then you know you
need to know you need to know when
something starts feeling better then no
matter what it is you got to hold on to
that even if it's for a moment that's
another thing I would tell people I
would tell people and I'm telling you
guys now so you start recovering and
you're doing your celery juice that
Spirit brought to us cuz celery juice
didn't exist prior to this and you bring
your celery juice
okay and you start drinking it you start
getting a little bit better and you
haven't you you haven't gotten a little
bit better yet with all the things
you're doing better hold on to
it build up that Spirit hold on to it
take it and use it for strength so even
if it takes a little time some people
have had Epstein Bar for a long time you
know I finally brought Epstein bar
information to Life For The First Time
in the World matching up the symptoms to
the illness meaning symptoms to Epstein
bar what symptoms cause and I see I
what's really amazing as I see people
actually talking about it now and
they're and they're saying hey look I I
heard this from Anthony William and and
they're just I've see just good people
doing that and and which is great
because then it could lead people to
getting more information also that maybe
someone might have forgotten or not you
know written down exactly so we can all
help together it's like we're all
working together as a team but then a
doctor friend just let me know that
there's a couple of people that you know
are taking the information kind of
altering it not saying where it came
from making it look like it's theirs and
the problem is with
that is it loses its auth authenticity
because it's not the the source of where
it came from is not being mentioned and
uh and that can lead people into a
direction that ends up just endlessly
just you know swimming around once again
back into the circle of sickness and
when I see that it's so disheartening
it's not even funny so we got to all
stay together we all got to stay strong
together and we got to stay in this
together and um and all heal together
using spirit's information using the
information that comes through so what
I'm telling you now if you get those
sensations of healing and you had your
celery juice and it's
helping and you're doing some of the
things that that we that we all talk
about here on the show and on all the
other shows and and you're healing
remember three steps up two steps back
three steps up two steps back remember
that three steps up two steps
back that's how healing
works and some sometimes it takes a
little longer for some people they've
had a viral infection for 20 years might
take take extra months to get some
results and then they get the results
and you hold on to that you hold on to
those results what I mean by holding on
to them you
remember you have
them
because that right there is a key it's a
key to healing and rising out of the
ashes you hold on to that and more of
it's going to come and more it's going
to come even if you went two steps back
then you're going to have three steps
forward and more of it's going to come
neurological problems there a lot of
neurological symptoms brain fog memory
loss those are neurological depression
that's
neurological uh anxiety that's
neurological aches and pains that's
neurological okay all right migraines
that's
neurological tingles and numbness that's
neurological ringing in the ears that's
neurological vertigo
neurological and it keep keeps in going
balance issues neurological planter
fasciitis
neurological all of it is and they take
a little time to heal all of those by
the way are Epstein bar
caused and and they take a little time
to heal so you got to grab onto that
healing when it happens you grab on to
it you move forward I don't care what
disease or illness or diagnosis you had
or whatever it is you got to grab on to
the healing and we move forward together
it's one of the keys now say you're one
of those people that was sick all along
and don't have a past you can pull from
and we just we hold on to the Future
it's okay if you don't have that past
and you never felt good one day you
never had a good day it's okay it's all
right that don't matter you hold on to
the Future and we do what we need to do
to rise out of the
ashes because I got to tell you
something it doesn't mean that you're
not healthy here's something to know
that's so critical so just buckle your
seat bels this is so important to know
you need to know this okay just because
you're sick just because you're not
feeling good just because you got
struggles just because you're suffering
doesn't mean you're not
healthy doesn't mean you're not healthy
and that you don't have healthy organs
and that you're not healthy
inside it doesn't mean you don't have
health so just so you know doesn't
matter if you have the symptoms all the
time you have the anxiety you have the
depression you hurt you're fatigued you
got the chronic fatigue you got all
these different diagnoses you whatever
it is whether you got Ms you got you
lime disease or whether whatever it is
that you've been told or you're
struggling or trying to recover from it
doesn't mean you're not healthy and
there aren't healthy Parts in you like
lots of healthy Parts like all healthy
Parts in you like all your organs all
the different things going on it doesn't
mean they're not working for you it
doesn't mean they're not standing by
your side helping you heal your body's
working for you it's not letting you
down it's your best friend it's your
best friend it is when someone says
who's your best friend you say oh my my
my internal body my internal body is my
best friend and it's helping me recover
and it's helping me rejuvenate and it's
helping me come back that's what my best
friend
is it's my internal
body that's my best friend it's not
letting me down I trust it you sure I
got this neurological symptoms now and I
got this that I had I got sick years ago
or whatever it is but you got to trust
your body it's working for you and it's
helping you heal and it stands behind
you
100% And just so you know just in case
you got chronic fatigue syndrome just in
case you got Hashim modus thyroiditis
just in casee which we know the answers
to we know the answers too here okay we
know where the source and the answers
are for all that you know when you got
the Hashimoto whatever it is just no it
doesn't mean you're not healthy doesn't
mean your pancreas isn't healthy it
doesn't even mean your thyroid is not
even healthy your thyroid still healthy
in multitude levels multitude levels
doesn't mean your liver is not healthy
doesn't mean your intestinal tract's not
healthy if someone's got seabone and
they got that that small intestinal
growth of overgrowth of bacteria which
is still unexplainable by doctors by the
way it's it's anti antibiotic resistance
strep a cacus is what that is and that's
from taking you know antibiotics when
you're a child and and and all kinds of
different stuff and later on you get a
little bacteria overgrowth it's from not
eating good you end up eating eggs and
dairy products milk cheese and butter
and that's what that's from and you know
and wheat uh cuz wheat feeds strepa
cacus so when you're when you're doing
that it's growing in you it doesn't mean
your intestinal tract is not
healthy so you need to know that so if
you got digestive problems and you got
digestive sicknesses or digestive issues
it doesn't
mean that hey that it's not healthy that
your digestive system is not healthy
your colon is not healthy absolutely you
got to know that all these things matter
to rising out of the
ashes all of these things matter I want
to talk to you about my favorite food on
the planet can you guess what that is
can you guess what my favorite food
is uh you probably know right you got to
know is it
celery no even though that's one of my
favorite foods on the planet it's you
know but it's not celery so what do you
guys think it is you know what it is
it's blue it's the wild blueberry you
guessed it right it's the wild blueberry
I'm not talking about blueberries
cultivated blueberries they're weak
they're still help they offer health
benefits don't get me wrong they offer
health benefits if you have them you eat
them you you have them you better eat
those blueberries those cultivated
blueberries but if you can get a hold of
wild blueberries that's what you want
I'll tell you why because and I talk
about this in life-changing Foods in my
life-changing Foods book that you guys
are going to be happy when you open it I
don't think you're going to be
disappointed I don't I'm giddy inside
about it I'm giddy inside about I'm
excited actually I got a smile on my
face cuz I know when you open that book
you're going to be like all right he did
us right the guy did us
right cuz I got your back all right so
here's the deal the wild
blueberry is the most powerful heavy
metal detoxifying food there is and we
deal with heavy metals heavy metals work
side by side with epsin bar along with
shingles and as along with other
illnesses and viruses heavy metals work
side by side causing nothing but harm
wreaking havoc and they sit in our brain
and they become like Alloys they sit
there with copper and lead and aluminum
in our brain and guess what removes them
out removes that alloy out of our brain
so we can free up our brain and heal
it's the wild
blueberry this is the food you want in
your life when you've been through the
unthinkable and need the support to ride
up again this is the rising out of the
ashes food of all time I promise you is
the Frozen wild
blueberry it's for anyone who needs a
physical boost or or even someone who's
feel good they feel good in their
athletic wild blueberries in their
system can mean the difference between
life or death for a rock climber I'm
going to tell you right now if a rock
climber was going to miss his
point by 2
millimet where his finger slips and he
doesn't get and he doesn't have the Rope
latched yet or anything like that and
he's in this weird position where it's
it's
treacherous and he's about to slip if he
had wild blueberries in him or she had
wild blueberries in him could have meant
the difference between slipping or not
that's the power
of the wild
blueberry I'm serious and it's literally
a holy food when I mean holy food it's
the resurrection food of all time it's
the Jesus Christ food of all time it's
that
Resurrection which is the ultimate
rising out of the
ashes that ever existed so it's that
Resurrection so I'm telling you how it
works with wild blueberry wild
blueberries have information in them
information that's tens of thousands of
years
old hundred thousand years old of
survival of literally existence and
survival when you eat those that's what
transforms into you that's what meaning
transpires that's what actually moves
into your body and enters into your
heart and
soul and they're good for every illness
possible you think about it every Cancer
possible they're good for every single
disease they're good for every symptom
they're good for for they are the rising
out of the ashes food of all
time and they help us they're the best
motivation speaker there is the Frozen
wild blueberry on the planet it's the
wild blueberry if you're into motivative
speakers are you into motivation
speakers and all that because there's a
lot of them out there now are you into
them and you go you go see them or you
you know you buy their tapes or CDs or
whatever it is now and you do whatever
and you're you know downloading their
their their talks and all that well the
the wild blueberry is better than any
motivational speaker there is on the
planet is the wild blueberry it's the
motivational speaker inside the body
inside the body and if you've been
through scorn humiliation rejection
here's what it does on emotional level
you guys on an emotional level and I
talk about this in the life-changing
Foods book and more okay if you've been
into if you've been rejected felt like
you have humiliation has ever happened
devastation being degraded rejection
like I said scorned punishment whatever
it is criticized or just criticized or
depreciated or discredited or mistreated
or neglected if any of that's ever
happened in your life and it plays into
you being even hurt along the way this
is the holy food that helps us rise out
of the
ashes it's the wild blueberry and that's
what it can do emotionally help pick you
up from that and help clear that out of
the body and that's what we try to do
too at the events and spirit sends the
light down in everybody and hits the
crown of their head and rushes through
the body we try to do that there too and
it does lift people up thank
God and then if you have your Frozen
wild blueberries in you too and you're
getting the light blast it's a whole
another story but still the wild
blueberries and if you can't get the
light blast don't worry you get the
light wild blueberries and then you put
them in you every day every day and the
spiritual lesson the wild blueberry
offers
and this is what I have here also in the
book The life-changing Foods book is a
spiritual
lesson wild blueberries understand what
youve been through they know what you've
been through there's an intelligence in
the wild blueberry that connects to your
internal body and your cells in your
body that knows what you've been
through they know who you are wild
blueberries Frozen wild blueberry je
they know who you are as a person they
know the damage you've dealt with
and they know how to help you rise out
again rise out of the ashes rise up and
they know they
know that's
how and so
listen it's all about you getting better
and that's what it's about and you're
going to get better and people already
are getting better with spirit's
information but you're going to get
better too you're going to get better
too and you're going to do some healing
and you're going to move through this
you're going to get through this because
you remember what I said and don't
forget what I said whatever you do don't
forget it and you know what it is now
because I said it a few times remember
this that all storms pass nothing stays
the same and all things
change what that means is you're going
to be healing you're going to get to the
other side you're going to get to the
Blue Sky you're going to get to the sun
you're going to get to the light all
that that's going to be there going to
pull you out of the darkness no matter
what's going on your life or a friend or
whoever it is what's happening or a
loved one we're going to help you move
forward and that is so important to know
that alone right there is so critical to
know know that I stand by you I'm by
your side through all of
this okay and now listen you know if
you're if you're doing all the different
things get the celery juice in you don't
forget I don't want you guys to forget
about that try to get some celery if you
you can't handle a lot of it try to do 1
oz of it 2 ounces of it try mix it with
something if you have to but try to
build yourself up so you get 16 ounces
of celery juice by itself by itself in a
glass 16 ounces once a day you get that
in you okay make sure you're getting a
little bit of kale in you when you can
make sure you're bringing a lot of
spinach into your diet too lots of
spinach make sure you're bringing in
lots of different lettuces when you can
that's important don't forget that
cucumbers make sure you got some
cucumber juice going on too at different
times but make sure that celery juice is
there as well don't forget about all of
these things all right don't forget
about all the things we talk about and
everything and try to get that B12 in
you the one I talk about you know the
B12 I'm talking about you can find it
also at my website as far as where to
look for it we don't sell it there but
you can you can at least get the name of
it know that I stand behind you I love
you guys take one day at a time we're
going to rise out of the ashes together
okay and we're going to keep on getting
healthy and for those who have risen out
of the ashes already I'm with you still
and we move forward together we're all
doing it I love you I believe in you
stay healthy move forward let's heal
together blessings love you take care