talking about natural flavors
how toxic natural flavors are even
dangerous
natural flavors are and how everybody's
tricked
duped fooled about natural flavoring
so we're going to cover that that's an
important topic because guess what
you're eating it and you're drinking it
every day
probably it's on the top chart of
most eaten food group is natural
flavoring that's right
so um we got that to cover and we'll
probably cover some other stuff too
hey elena came on good to see you
um everybody's coming on great you guys
so i'm gonna make the banana salad for
you it's
in this book right here now i even have
a section in the medical medium new
edition about natural flavoring you
might want to know
link is in the description check this
out on amazon this book will blow your
mind
it's so packed with information about
chronic illness and how to heal
um and it's already has the track record
the older version the original version
has a track record appealing millions
worldwide and then i put a whole entire
book into it you don't want to miss this
out
go to amazon.com or wait until it comes
out and then go to library get it for
free at the library
if you want to um so anyway let's go
good to see everybody coming on so the
banana salad by the way
is a way to get leafy greens in you
healthy nutritious life
saving leafy greens because leafy greens
are antiviral
antibacterial foods they have properties
in them that
actually inhibit viruses
inhibit bacteria and banana does too
so when you think about it you got
banana and you got a salad and you got
your banana salad what you're doing for
yourself
is really important and there's no fats
in this recipe because i know
most everybody they're inundated with
fats in their diet so i'd like to get a
recipe in your diet once in a while that
doesn't
have all the fats and isn't packed with
all the fats
and talk about why that's not good
either to have all the fats
so um talk about the banana salad start
making it
let's see i got some teas here i'm going
to talk about a little bit too
josh is it okay to put a clean protein
powder in the detox smoothie
would alter the effectiveness of the
smoothie josh
99.99
of protein powders have natural
flavoring in it if you see
berry flavor that's a natural flavor and
i'm going to talk about what natural
flavoring really is
if you see natural flavoring natural
flavor
organic flavor flavoring on its own
whatever the term if you see the word
flavor
flavor you're in trouble so i'm just
letting you know if that's in the
ingredient list and so you be careful
because you can be dumping a protein
powder that's got natural flavorings in
it
and what does that have msg
is msg bad dangerous we're going to talk
about what it does to the brain what msg
does to the mind
why natural flavoring should not be in
supplements
you know for example the vimergy
never had and never will have natural
flavoring
i noticed that traditional medicinal
teas that's a tea i drink and not
sponsored by these guys
doesn't have natural flavoring in it but
most teas do now
natural flavors of all different kinds
whether it's raspberry flavor
some other kind of flavor dr fans on md
great doctor glad you're here um
so giselle says what if you can't eat
carbs
well you're getting sugar somewhere so
if you give you you you must be getting
sugar somewhere so
certainly you're not carb free because
say you're on a carnivore diet
and you're doing all meat the meat has
sugar
in the blood and packed with sugar
because
the cow's blood sugar is really high
so all that blood sugar is in all that
blood is in the meat so that when you're
broiling the meat
you know cooking baking frying whatever
it is you do with meat
you're actually caramelizing the blood
sugar
is what's going on and that's why people
can survive on eating meat
because there's so much sugar in it and
that's why it's almost sweet i've hear
heard that over and over again i like a
good steak people say
it's just it's just it's sweet and zesty
it's just got some kind
of meaty sweet flavor yeah it doesn't
taste like apple pie
but they don't measure the blood sugar
and meat they keep that part out
so they'll tell you there's no carbs in
your meat so you're getting carbs so
you're actually doing carbs
so so it's like you just is it you don't
want to do a different carb you don't
want to do an
uh another carb or a healthier carb
that's all that is
but if you don't want to do the banana
and
you don't want to do anything like that
we can figure something out and have a
salad
maybe tomatoes lunell said i had a b12
supplement with natural flavorings
before getting the vimergy one
loon thanks for reminding me because
that's exactly it the vimergy
b12 doesn't have natural flavoring but
there's a
20 other reasons why the b12 for vimergy
is better than anybody out there but
there yeah there's no natural flavoring
and everybody had natural flavorings in
their b12s
and the couple of companies that might
be out there without natural flavorings
in their b12
their copycats off vimergy because
everybody had natural flavorings they
had msg in their b12
so that's what's happening so hey let me
go take my b12 and get poisoned by msg
that's what it is oh i got a migraine
now i feel sick oh my god i just got a
dizzy spell
because of that msg those natural
flavors that are in everybody else's b12
and that's why it was critical that you
you shouldn't have that in a supplement
that's why i trust the vimergy
but i got to go into what msg does
how it works and when what they say
about natural flavors out there to trick
you
you guys just got on here making a
banana salad and just show you real
quick because i see a bunch of people
coming on it's gonna
be like that after i'm done with it and
it's a great recipe
it's in medical medium new edition
yeah loon it's crazy right totally
you had your i see uh sonya said i had
my vemma gb12 today incredible
that's one i can trust and um the
dinosaur kovaleman methylcobalamin
so let's talk about it if there is
natural flavoring in a supplement out
there and the supplement
company is trying to defend it
you got a major problem you got a
supplement company
you can't trust because that supplement
company
doesn't even know or they do know and
they're not going to say it
or they don't know that there's msg in
that natural flavoring
now a company will say this there's no
natural there's no msg in our natural
flavors we talked to the manufacturing
plant of those natural flavors
you know we talked to the manufacturer
of natural flavors and they said there's
no msg in there so the msg is all
organic and pure and it goes in our
supplement
but that's not the truth not the truth
at all
see years ago before natural flavoring
was developed there were artificial
flavoring
artificial flavoring but when artificial
flavoring was out there
artificial flavoring didn't have msg
in it okay so it had chemicals
like different kinds of chemicals in it
that's what artificial flavoring had
right and sometimes now artificial
flavoring will have msg
but in the past years ago it didn't
here's what happened
get ready here's where you guys all been
suckered all been tricked
all been duped the wolves been pulled
over your eyes
right here i'm gonna drop it on you okay
a deal was made
okay that msg can hide now
behind a veil the veil was natural
flavoring
that was a deal that was made in the
food and drug world
so here's how it goes everybody was
figuring out msg was toxic
everybody was figuring out msg was
dangerous
too many people got sick disturbed
hurt by it okay and so msg
would have to be labeled in the past so
everybody's products on the store
shelves
all said msg in the ingredient list m s
g in the ingredient list on all the
shelves
and then all of a sudden it disappeared
gone
right when natural flavors was birthed
all of a sudden msg's not on any
products anymore
every single product in the condiment
aisle and anywhere else
in the store cans condiments you name it
had msg in the ingredient list years and
years ago
you walk down the grocery store and you
just grab something you read what it is
it's a can of whatever beans
msg oh here's a can of hot sauce a
bottle of hot source
msg you see msg and right when natural
flavors was born
msg disappeared off of everybody's label
every single food product food company
out there
the word the letters msg
gone disappeared overnight
overnight so um has he ever said not
sponsored by vimergy
he is not answering me i am cat i am i'm
not sponsored by vimergy
okay so letting you know i'm not
sponsored by
traditional medicinals i'm not sponsored
by
dozens of other companies that you see
on my directory
i'm not sponsored not sponsored not
sponsored okay
the omega juicer though uh i am
connected to mega juicer
i licensed my name to them i tell you
guys all the time they have the best
juicer i've ever seen ever made
and i just said you know what if if
that's gonna save people thousands of
dollars
then then i'm in as far as i license my
name i said you guys could use my name
but as far as sponsored by vimergy no
sponsored by
traditional medicinals no so anyway the
bottom line is
when they did that switch over all these
other products msg disappeared
but it showed up as natural flavoring
without the word
so what they did was natural flavors
flavoring
raspberry flavor strawberry flavor any
kind of flavor
not vanilla extract don't get that
confused
extract is different than flavors
flavorings or flavor so our flavors
flavoring flavor okay
so natural so extract
is different so vanilla extract
is different than vanilla flavoring
really important to know all right so
so when you're going through all your
products you'll see natural flavors
everywhere you go go in yourselves
go through all your shelves check them
out
go through every single product on your
shelves tonight
go through all the food stuff in your
pantries
go into your fridge check out all the
food stuff in your fridge
and read every single label and you're
going to be
somewhere swimming in msg which is
natural flavor somewhere natural
flavoring
and any product company that defends
themselves
a supplement company says no our stuff
is pure
um we talk to the manufacturing of that
natural flavor and it is fine
they don't have to disclose it the
manufacturers
of natural flavorings are not there they
don't
have to disclose the msg anymore it they
got a free ride
when the deal was made to hide msg
because
think about it thousands and thousands
and thousands
hundreds of thousands millions of
products years ago all had to put msg on
the bottle okay
and then it disappeared so you're
telling me the msg
plant factories manufacturing facilities
all stopped when they didn't have to
you mean to tell me they just dropped
hundreds of millions of dollars
and just got rid of it and closed all
their factories down
for no reason no they kept it running
but they were allowed to get the free
ride and not have msg on the label
see how it works but it was switched
into natural flavoring
and it's in every food almost every
single
bottle can different foods all the
different packaged foods
go through all your stuff go through
anything you eat you're gonna find it
and that right there is a way to get msg
in your brain and that's when you become
brain damaged
in a different way msg builds up in
pockets inside the brain causes damage
to the neurotransmitters electrical
impulses to the neurons
msg is a neuroantagonist
it does damage to brain tissue
and you guys all become suckered into it
not your fault at all on any level but
when what really really gets my goat
right
because i'm about protecting you guys
i'm about looking out for you guys what
really gets me
is supplement companies that get
question on the msg on the natural
flavors they get questioned by people
like you guys who have learned because
when medical medium
the first edition of this book came out
right i talked about natural flavoring
in here and it being msg
and so that started a movement so people
can look out
but for supplement companies that have
followed
medical medium or i've spoken to over
the years
ignore the warning that natural flavors
is msg
and they purposely put it in all their
products and then
tell all their mm fans followers
users they tell them their natural
flavors comes from a company that isn't
msg which is not possible
they're all msg and then tells them that
is negligence and i know i see it all
out there
all over the place and it's like you
know what
you knew about it in here all the
companies knew about it in here all the
supplement companies all read the
medical medium books especially this one
and i've talked to all the supplement
companies out there
and they knew about the natural flavors
so to still have them in their products
is
just it's just disgusting really so
back to protecting you guys because
that's what it's about let's start
making a banana salad i'll talk a little
bit more about this
i got some romaine here i don't know if
you guys are doing romaine at all
hello from romania cool romaine lettuce
so i got it i'm going to chop it up
msg cedaria says msg was created for
pharmaceutical companies
very interesting very interesting the
msg factories
didn't just throw their hands in the air
and give up so i'm chopping up this
romaine it's going to go
i'm not going to leave it in really big
pieces i'm chopping the salad a little
bit
okay guys the msg companies didn't just
give up
and they were done the day natural
flavors arrived
and every single bottle stopped saying
msg on it
they actually morphed it into natural
flavors
organic flavors yep
organic flavoring look
why should i care why should i care why
should i like
work this hard to like let you guys know
because i'm thinking about that baby
somewhere
and i'm thinking about that two-year-old
somewhere that doesn't need natural
flavoring msg
and the little two-year-old's brain
which is going to then support
adhd support problems with toxic heavy
metals make problems with toxic heavy
metals worse
i'm thinking about that child that's
five year old five years old
and the mom thinks that that organic
natural flavoring is perfectly healthy
and doesn't know i'm thinking about that
little one that's taking supplements
because mom wants a little one to take
supplements
and it's a crappy supplement because
it's got msg in it
and no one's telling that mom like you
know
what do i do stay quiet
and i get crap for all this stuff but
i mean i don't get it am i supposed to
just kick back and be like you know what
let
everybody just do their thing everybody
just
you know let them do their thing that's
their business well is it
or is it the business of a two-year-old
a five-year-old a mommy
you know and the whole bit so that's
important to know you guys
i just put some romaine in here so i got
that it's really beautiful that
romaine lettuce is a leafy green but
it's not as powerful it's powerful in a
different way
lettuces got their own source of
nutrient power okay
photochemical compounds and alkaloids
and stuff but
um but you know i love other leafy
greens so like using herbs as leafy
greens like cilantro it's medical medium
information no one's used cilantro like
leafy green
and i say this because i've taught so
many people now to use it as a leafy
green where you got all this cilantro so
i tell people the same thing you do
romaine lettuce do a
cilantro salad with that much let's try
that one day
bananas on that kimberly miller says
your info healed my alcoholism
incredible it really is
um and i'm really proud of you seriously
that is not easy
that is not easy to break i'm really
proud of you on that one
i'm gonna chop up some cucumber some
slices
okay i'm gonna peel back the cucumber a
little bit you guys
it's cutting off the ends right here so
look i don't want companies out there
having problems i want them to live
their life and sell their stuff
but i want them to fix what they know is
wrong
or if they don't know what's wrong i
want them to fix it anyway
right because in the end it's just going
to hurt everybody
it's people that get all kinds of
neurological symptoms
from msg because msg
um really kind of makes things worse if
you're viral if you've got low grade
viral infections like ebv
if you got toxic heavy metals and you're
dealing with anxiety and depression
natural flavoring can really add into
that depression that anxiety
it's kind of like another cut
death by a thousand cuts all these
different cuts
can you eat the skin on all cucumbers
yes you can i
conventional cucumbers um i would
probably peel them back a little bit
but all cucumbers in general organic
ones you can i would still wash the
cucumber
like i washed this is what i did i leave
the skin on
most dishes i kind of do this because it
gives it a look
too there's a look i was going for by
having like
taking the skin back a little bit you
see i was going for this kind of look um
but yeah you can keep the skin on them
just that if they're conventional i
wouldn't
on cucumbers i'd probably peel them back
at least a little bit
so i'm going to peel this one back now
too
that's what i'm doing probably only need
one
this is a really big cucumber right here
so i'm probably gonna only need one here
so that's what i'll do i'll use this one
that i'm cutting now
so all these things matter the details
matter when
you're getting better every single
break you can get in your body can get
is a big deal
so people say well why do you support
traditional medicinals so much there's
there's hundreds of tea companies out
there now
it's because i can't trust them they got
a track record of not putting natural
flavors in all these years
unless they change that track record but
they haven't so that's the natalie tea
right
traditional medicinals and so it's it's
it's like why i don't want to jump to
another tea company unless they can
really promise me
or show me a track record because teas
are all
getting natural flavors now natural
flavorings of different kinds
you go to a restaurant hey can i have a
chamomile tea
it's going to have natural flavoring in
it you go can i have peppermint tea
you just had a nice dinner you're with a
friend and
you want some herbal tea even though
everybody's like have matcha tea
afterwards so they get jacked up on
caffeine and their adrenals are like
oh my god help right but you can order
some say or order some herbal tea
it's gonna have natural flavoring in it
so
traditional medicinals doesn't that's
why i like that one the vimergy products
don't and never did and that's one
reason why i like them it's one out of
many
so it's important
b12 is infamous for having natural
flavoring of some kind in there
truly is so i'm gonna cut this right
here
so the first of all i'm gonna cut the
cucumber in half
like that okay and then i'm going to cut
these like
half moons is going to do and i'm not
going to cut them too big but yet
just about the right size here a little
a little bit more than a quarter inch
by almost a half inch each one that's
what i'm doing right here
you guys there's something that's really
important with cutting boards just
letting you know no matter what kind of
cutting board you use
this is a real i use wooden ones right
but
this is this is not the wooden one you
can see right it's the plastic
and the reason why i do that is because
i have it arched
out it's halfway off the counter and if
i use the wooden one it would just fall
down in
i use it because it's part of the studio
i set up in here right so i'm putting
these cucumber slices
on top of the salad i see people when
they're cutting
what they do is they scrape their boards
with the sharp part of their knife
so after they they cut something they
they scrape their board whether it's
wood or something you don't want to do
that
all you're doing is scraping tiny fibers
of wood off your board
tiny fibers of plastic tiny fibers of
glass
so you don't want to do that with your
knife you want to flip your knife around
and use this side which is not the sharp
side
to actually do this on your board i see
it all the time and i want to let you
guys know too
uh b senior says is that way some
so-called herbal teas
made me feel sick it's very possible
it's very possible
because there's there there's also a lot
of heavy metals and herbs
out there a lot a lot of heavy metals
and herbs letting you guys know that's
one thing
that slips the the radar not every
company
there's very few companies that do
independent testing very
it's very few if any and what i like
about vimergy to do independent testing
but herbs out there
they're notorious um
chinese medicine chinese herbs highest
in heavy metals
um there's just it always oh
always had heavy metals known for it
known for it for decades known for it in
the 90s known for in the 2000s
you want the lowest metals that's what
it is the lowest metals because there's
metals in every single thing you eat
every herb you take there's the metals
and it
falls out of the sky it's in the water
that feeds everything but
um and natural flavorings have metals
in there they have more than just msg so
natural flavoring isn't just
monosodium glutamate it's not just that
it's
it's msg is also a
like a combination some toxic heavy
metals
aluminum that's a big one in natural
flavors
so when you have a package and it says
organic natural flavors boom you just
got a heavy metal dose
boom you just got an msg dose symbols up
like that
so wouldn't you like to know or am i
wasting your time
hopefully i'm not wasting your time got
some bananas
you know i'd want to know
right i mean
so let's get some bananas in the salad
and we're going to put some other things
in here too
you guys i think four bananas should
work
when it comes down to healing knowledge
is power but if you're not
informed on something that's under the
wire that's hidden
that's secret i remember doing a lecture
in 2014 was before book one came out
there's a thousand people in the crowd
i was doing a lecture and i opened up
the lecture
with how if we don't know
something's happening so we can't make a
choice to protect yourself
what if we're not told what if it's
hidden what if it's secret what if
you've been
tricked what if you've been duped
and that's the case with natural flavors
right there every single
package now of food almost that we'll
you'll see a natural flavoring somewhere
in there
go down the aisle look you'll be in the
natural food store the health food store
you'll see it so
why should we worry about msg
msg pockets it pockets inside the brain
it collects on neurotransmitters
it lowers your battery charge in your
brain
it reduces electricity in your brain
it does some short circuiting similar to
toxic heavy metals
so if you're already was struggling with
depersonalization
adhd autism
you got anxiety you're just getting your
anxieties through the roof you got a
nervousness
you got you know some depression that's
really really hard on you i'm putting
some banana pieces and cut them in like
these half moons right here
msg can make or break
make or break your healing process
just like caffeine can you want to heal
but you can't get quite to the finish
line but you don't know why but nobody's
telling you it's the caffeine you're
doing whether it's matcha tea chocolate
or coffee
or espresso or green tea or some kind
you don't know that that's what's
holding you back it's
make or break to the finish line
i mean do you want to get to the finish
line of healing or do you want to kind
of wafer around
and stay sick and then kind of try
something else and hit some fads
hit some trend go listen to some podcast
person or
hell in health and now you're like doing
something else
and you're really not going to the
finish line you're not going all the way
meanwhile you might not even know that
medical media put out information about
msg about natural flavoring a long time
ago
and people forget or people might not
have read that chapter or something in
the book that i was showing you earlier
then you just kind of stay
sick you get the migraines you stay up
all night you got insomnia
msg can create some wicked insomnia
i'm not talking about the night you use
msg
not talking about that
i'm talking about the fact that it
builds up in the brain
becomes a neuroantagonist stays there
for a long time
pockets of msg do some brain damage
where eventually gets seen on an mri
years and years and years down the road
but they don't know that's msg causing a
crystallization
so let's go into that a little bit msg
crystallizes in your brain tissue
natural flavoring as harmful and
harmless as it sounds
will eventually become a problem as
you're using in your diet for years and
years and years
you get an mri down the road when you're
70 years old and they see some white
spots
crystallizing because
msg is
is a compound that doesn't wash away
stays in tissue builds up as the years
go on
and um i think you guys might want to
save
some money right now and maybe not have
to go through all that medical
testing in hell and back situations
because msg is building up in your brain
causing pockets i figured you guys might
want to
have a chance to not go there and at
least check that one off the list right
that would be great so
putting some banana pieces in here
let's thinly slice up some onion msg is
manufactured
just letting you know it's it's messed
it's messed with
something to know right there i don't
care what anybody says out there
it's in it's it's it's in these massive
massive centrifuges that are just i mean
we're talking about
20 tons of msg liquid sitting in
gigantic centrifuge in the middle of a
chemical factory
siphoning around what of the packages
say raspberry flavor it's msg
but doesn't have the word natural
raspberry flavor
strawberry flavor raspberry flavor ring
raspberry flavors um vanilla flavoring
um chicken flavoring
chicken flavor i've seen that one too
chicken flavoring
i've seen that one too it's msg
that's that is the scary thing
that's a scary thing
i'm gonna thinly slice an onion right
here really good question and exactly
what's happening out there
felicia says natch flavors they put that
on everything yeah i know they really do
you're spot on do real thin sliced onion
for this
guys i'm making this out right here i
got the banana
banana's already cut in pieces i'll put
on top of the romaine lettuce
i got some cucumber slices in here too
let's do some really thin slices of
onion
i'm actually paper like paper thin right
here on these onion slices
i don't i don't like big hunks of onion
inside this banana salad
so i like just having these really thin
slices you don't have to have a lot if
you don't want to you can have a little
bit this is an anti-pathogen food right
here
when you're eating onions if you can if
you can stand onion
the smell of onion onion on food
you're already like using you're using
an antiviral medicine
that's what you're doing think about it
right a sulfur and onion
that's a viral killer bacterial killer
so i'm just cutting in this half and
just going down here like that there you
go paper thin
my eyes are going to run now your
central nervous system
is highly sensitive
msg is an irritant
an antagonist troublemaker
causes a lot of trouble
but you guys aren't on any msg no way
you're just unnatural flavors which is
msg
what about when it says citric acid
yeah stay away from citric acid it's
another reason why i like the vimergy
products
it's another reason why i like say um
traditional medicinals right here
like with the vimergy you take a lid of
energy you get the lemon balm you're not
gonna see citric acid in here
there's a couple of companies that are
like prided in their vegan
supplements vim is for anybody who's
vegan not vegan
whatever right animal protein whatever
but there's a couple like vegan
companies
they put they put products out there and
they got citric acid in it
and they think they got the best stuff
they got
casey a gum in there they got citric
acid in there they got alcohol in there
and
and meanwhile they're on this hoo-ha you
know rant
that this stuff's the best and vegan
vegan vegan and all that and it's like
what
you got citric acid in there that's corn
citric acid is corn
that's another trick happening right now
citric acid is really bad citric acid
isn't from a lemon it's not from an
orange
so i've got some slices thinly slices on
top here
that's not the citric acid you see in
supplements
so important to know okay got that
optional is the onion but i like the
onion so that's why i put it in this
salad
and optional is celery
so i'm going to chop up some celery real
thin slices of celery i'm going to put
on top here
carolina says i can't eat onion anymore
you know there's phases you can go
through in your life
i've heard people say that absolutely
and then they're back on in a few years
they introduce it back so i'm going to
put little pieces of celery on top
it's going to look nice that way too i
gotta make the dressing and i still have
some dolls to go
showing you what it looks like right now
tina says can you speak more about
adrenals i can so i got some little
celery pieces on here i got the banana
pieces this is the banana salad okay
what's in this salad actually supports
and feeds adrenals keep that in mind
when it comes down to the celery pieces
really good for your adrenals romaine
lettuce great for the adrenals mineral
salts critical for your adrenals
right onion i'm gonna do the dolls
cucumber which is really good for
adrenals
um so this is atlantic dulce right here
you see guys i'm just showing you what i
got here
so you can moisten it and put it on you
can put it on dry i'm going to moisten
it for this recipe so
what i do is
i'll leave it in a bowl like this and
add a little touch of water
real quick i just added a little bit of
water
not a lot just mixing it up a little bit
just get it kind of moist
you don't want to soak it because then
you start losing some of its flavor
if you soak it soak it so
keep that in mind it's a great way to
keep your dolls just so flavorful
right just mixing that up so i'm going
to put some strips
on the cutting board and cut it
pop that on top there we go
do that now when it comes down to
adrenals you don't want to intermittent
fast unless
you're doing like the medical medium
morning cleanse which is
your lemon water 16 to 30 ounces lemon
water in the morning then you go to 16
to 32 ounces half an hour later of
celery juice
you do that next then you do like a
smoothie medical medium smoothie heavy
metal detox smoothie is a great option
and then you can have a little bit of
fruit with some fruit snacks or
something
or some celery sticks and fruit all the
way up until lunch
lunch and after you can bring in a fat
if you want
or you can bring in some oatmeal you can
bring in some millet but the point is
is that if you're intermittent fasting
and you got adrenal issues
you're hurting your adrenals you got to
be really careful especially if you're
intermittent fasting and dropping the
caffeine in someone's telling you to do
calf
someone's telling you that caffeine is
really healthy for you meanwhile you're
killing your adrenals and
and no one no one's teaching you that i
talked about that in the last couple of
of lives chocolate it's another one
they'll tell you chocolate's so good for
you but you kill your adrenals
you can't get adrenal fatigue better if
you're doing chocolate
just letting you know
caffeine there's caffeine in chocolate
gotta be concerned about that matcha tea
green tea
you can't get adrenals better if you
have an adrenal issue on any level
you can't get adrenals better if you're
doing
any kind of chocolate espresso coffee
matcha tea
and then the same thing with high fat
diets you gotta be careful how much
fat's in your diet
are you doing chicken twice a day you're
doing it you're doing um
you're doing bacon you're doing chicken
are you doing too much nut butters tons
of peanut butter uh
you know chocolate what are you doing
how many fats are you doing you do an
avocado toast and then for lunch you
have chicken on your salad
then later in the afternoon you eat a
chocolate bar then at night you have
more chicken or you have something else
right
and then you have oil somewhere on all
the stuff so there's so much fat in
there
you then then you you also kill the
adrenals over time the adrenals can't
keep up with that because
your adrenals have to spill out all this
epinephrine to thin out your blood
because your heart
is like oh my god if you keep on putting
fat inside my bloodstream
all day long every day i'm going to give
out on you that's that's the whole point
the heart and the brain they work
together and they're saying stop the
fats stop the fats
and a way to bring your adrenals back is
to actually eat every hour
hour and a half to two hours depending
on how bad your adrenals are
have an apple and some celery have some
dates and some celery sticks
have a couple of oranges have a banana
and some celery banana and some lettuce
so
there's all these different combinations
i call them adrenal snacks
and it what it does is it replaces your
blood sugar so adrenaline doesn't have
to replace your blood sugar so i'll just
run this by you real quick
so when you don't eat and too many hours
go by
you you drop your blood sugar blood
sugar drops right
and then your poor adrenals they have to
pour out
all this adrenaline just dump out all
this adrenaline
because adrenaline takes place of blood
sugar when blood sugar is missing
adrenaline have the adrenals try to
become blood sugar
and then you wear them out you wear them
out you wear them out and no one teaches
you how to knot and then you're just
adrenal fatigue later on and then
then you lose the hair for women they
all lose their hair their hair thins
their their skin ages they get the
wrinkles they get the hard childbirths
they get
they get the um you know they get
difficult they can even get miscarriages
they can get the adrenals just start
getting all beat up
um you get the hormone imbalances
constantly
and all these things happen then you get
all the sun spots the skin ages you
gotta
then everybody's running to get botox
and all these other problems
and there's a whole adrenal section in
medical medium
the new addition so make sure you get
that and you check it out
when dulce gets wet it makes a mess
what causes high cortisol
high fat diet is one thing right there
so
too many fats in the diet every single
day high cortisol caffeine is the
biggest
high cortisol causer there is chocolate
biggest high cortisol causer there is is
caffeine
when you do caffeine you annihilate your
adrenal glands
annihilate them and no one wants to talk
about it
everybody wants to pretend it's fine and
good i notice that the podcast doctors
want to pretend it's fine and good
because they don't want to
they don't want to stop their caffeine
addiction they love it and
i noticed that um men in health
they don't know women's health is
different they just don't
they don't they think women should be
following the lead of men
that's what they believe so all the
health gurus that are men they just
think women should be following whatever
they're doing you know what i mean
and they don't know that women's
adrenals are designed differently
because women's adrenals produce all the
progesterone i'll produce all the
the estrogen produce reproductive system
hormones right men's adrenals don't do
that
so you know and and men don't have to
have babies
they don't have babies so what happens
is that men's adrenals are entirely
different than women's adrenals and
it also covers all of women's health
entirely different than men's health
but men will actually promote things
that destroy women's health so men gurus
and men podcast
heroes and doctors and other people and
health enthusiasts and trainers and
and and health coaches they just promote
things that hurt women's health in
natural health
conventional health too not everything
but a lot of stuff
i just just don't know i'm gonna give
them some credit they have some stuff
right here and there
anyway so let's make let's make this
let's make the dressing
let's go there let me grab a bowl
so let's make a dressing i'm gonna half
a cup of orange
juice got some oranges here probably do
a little bit more
when you go long hours
of no food you're gonna get high
cortisol
long hours of no food now if you go long
hours and in between those long hours is
celery juice
maybe a heavy metal detox smoothie maybe
another smoothie
maybe some lemon water maybe an apple
that's different when you go long hours
without food
and then the food you choose is caffeine
even if you don't choose caffeine or not
you just kill your adrenals the cortisol
that's how
you literally get the high cortisol
that's how you eventually high cortisol
is a cry
for help it's your adrenals crying for
help
it's saying stop whatever it is you're
doing
stop destroying me stop hurting me
because
you're going to have a shortened life
because of it and that's what high
cortisol is it's a warning sign
for you to adhere and listen and
hear not just adhere and it's like and
you know it's really important
so and that you know so much information
i'm gonna squeeze some oranges by hand
aren't oranges high in sugar mary meets
high in sugar
everything's high in sugar everything's
um the blood in meat
is glucose so the cow's blood
is sweet cow blood is sweet
chicken blood is sweet it's actually
really sweet
it's all sugar so meat's filled every
blood vessel
in that meat is filled with sugar it's
called glucose blood sugar
so when you fry up that meat have that
burger you're having a sugar bomb and
fat bomb combined
it's just that they chose not to tell
you that part they chose not to measure
that part
your blood sugar is filled with sugar
your blood is filled with sugar
so everything has sugar in it
but an orange has vitamin c in it
phytochemical compounds calcium to stop
your
teeth from falling apart so you're not
getting root canals and veneers and
implants
and getting drilled at the dentist all
the time that's what
oranges have meat doesn't have that and
i'm not anti-meat if you want to eat
meat
meat at least doesn't feed bugs dairy
does
eggs feed bugs they feed bugs if you're
like bugs what's he talking about i'm
talking about the bugs inside your body
that cause every single illness and
aches and pains that you have
eggs milk cheese dairy that will feed it
but um
making a little bit more orange juice
here
but yeah and
and and it's not that there's too much
sugar in in fruit that's not at all
fruit's got
living water in it phytochemical
compounds it's got minerals trace
minerals it's got nutrients it's got
vitamins it's got all that in there
pulp fiber
fasting promotes longevity is that true
fasting during a crisis can be very
healing
to allow your body to heal while in that
crisis
but short fasts one day two day three
day
you get food poisoning you can't eat the
next day
you'll just go downhill it's almost like
best you can do is just sip a little
something right
so you're fasting so your body can fight
whatever that foodborne pathogen and
enter your body
when you've got food poisoning see how
it works short fast
are healing in many ways i've talked
about that but long
long fasts where there's nothing but
water starts to just drain you
it starts to drain your trace minerals
it starts to take minerals out of the
bones over time
it all depends on the person in the
situation
i noticed that if you got chronic
illness you're suffering from chronic
illness a long water fast is not
ideal no
and
so that's something to think about just
so you know anyway i got some orange
juice here
so when you do long time water fast long
you know do long water fasts you do
week 10 days 14 days 21 days no one
knows what's happening inside of you
they can't tell what's happening so i
mean nobody
nobody's going to know and how to
measure anything in there it's not like
how do you measure
anything in there like how can you
measure what happened to your adrenals
during that water fast how can you
measure anything and then you've got to
recoup from that water fast and recoup
from that water fast
it's it i don't recommend the long water
fasts i don't i don't because
it's it's i recommend knowing why you're
sick and not having to go that route
that's something that hits
when you're desperate and you don't
really have anywhere to go
and you don't know why you're sexy end
up doing a long water fast
but i recommend finding out why you're
sick how about that so you don't have to
do a water fast
so let's do a little bit of honey in
this dressing i'm gonna mix this up
do about two teaspoons could do a
tablespoon if you really want to in this
dressing
but i'm gonna like two teaspoons
trina said i helped i felt so sick after
two days of celery juice
what else is going on in your life are
you what foods are you doing
what foods were you doing in those two
days are you doing nutritional yeast are
you doing vinegars
so your vinegar free your apple cider
vinegar free your vinegar's free of all
kinds your nutritional yeast free
you're you're caffeine free completely
caffeine free so you don't do caffeine
at all
these are some of the things to think
about here also
celery juice were you doing it without
lemon were you doing it by itself
how many ounces of celery juice did you
do that's another thing too
did you buy it in a store did you juice
it yourself was it hpp
did you buy it in the store and it was
high pressure pasteurization because
that'll make you sick
um you never had a symptom before that
celery juice
so you've never been sick so you're
drinking celery juice because you're a
healthy person with no problems and
you're drinking celery juice because
you just want to drink it or you
actually have symptoms and you felt sick
before like
last week or two months ago or six
months ago and you've been to all these
different doctors
it's just these are all questions to ask
yourself to see where you stand
and then kind of see if you can be your
own detective and maybe you can try
celery juice again someday you never
know
so i just put raw honey in here and i
mixed it up with the orange juice
are you really toxic really toxic
did the celery juice hit the liver how
much did you drink
celery just gets into the liver and
fleshes out all this stuff
so here's the salad right here it's
really pretty like this
um so you see the little slight the thin
sliced onions i got the little dolls on
top
pieces of dolls i got the banana all
intermixed with the little celery
and everything else heavy ass is
nutritional yeast bad it's terrible it's
got msg
now this whole thing we're talking about
msg every this whole thing about it
nutritional yeast they say nutritional
yeast will have b12 in it
and wrong they add it
and they add a really bad one they add a
really bad one to
the nutritional yeast um
jane says intermittent fasting is
supposed to be good for type 1
type 2 diabetes sorry type 2 diabetes i
stopped doing it
and then gained a few pounds i don't
want to go back
fasting but it did help me maintain my
weight
which is 57 is more um
which at 57 is more important than me um
you don't have to intermittent fast to
get your weight down why don't you once
you um
learn how to lower your fats that's one
thing right there that's that's the
whole thing there too
what happens is the reason why i was
helping you is because you got rid of
your fats in the morning
that's what it did the worst thing for
diabetics
hear me out everybody here i mean this
is good for if you know somebody who's a
diabetic this is really good emphasis
you might want to hear this
um when it comes down to diabetes the
worst thing you could ever do is eat a
fat in the morning so bacon
and egg cheese butter milk avocado
nuts seed oils any of that in the
morning
is the worst thing you can do as a
diabetic
because all that does is it keeps on
compiling on that insulin resistance and
keeps on
creating that insulin resistance and
insulin it's the fats
fats first thing in the morning or mid
morning it's all those fats that
actually cause the reason why you were
getting a little better and dropping
some weights is because you gave your
liver a break
and you stopped eating fats in the
morning that's all that was it's not
like intermittent fasting is this
is this this incredible thing
oh my god i found the holy grail
intermittent fasting no
all it is is you stopped your fats in
the morning that's all it was
i mean you don't have to intermittent
fast you'd be like wake up one morning
but like you know what
i'm gonna do medical medium stuff and
stop my fats in the morning i'm not
gonna down all this
milk cheese butter bacon eggs oils
peanut butter peanut butter in the
morning peanut butter and oatmeal in the
morning
even oatmeal is high in fat oatmeal
itself so imagine putting fat on it
so what happens is you guys is that that
just gives you insulin resistance so
when you get rid of that
as a diabetic you're going to be like
whoa i'm losing some weight because your
liver is recouping it's starting to
survive again you're not
killing it with fats you're not
bombarding it with fats
if you did this banana salad like mid
mid morning
and did some celery juice early morning
and some lemon water and then you
decided to do the banana salad somewhere
around mid-morning
you already would be losing the weight
because you're not bombarding your liver
with fats
and all my books talk about diabetes so
medical medium new addition there's a
diabetes
section in here type 2 diabetes section
in medical medium
new edition i mean you should have this
link is in the description so i just
made the dressing
and i'm going to put it on top of salad
that's where we're going now and you
guys i'm heading over
pretty soon to ig and tiktok at the same
time
i'm gonna drop some of this dressing
right down in here like this
it's beautiful so right here i have the
banana salad
it looks beautiful it's got the dressing
on top
and um it's just a gorgeous salad it
really is
see guys i'm heading over to ig i'm
heading over to tiktok at the same time
simultaneously going to do those you
guys want to come over going to talk
more
about everything keep in mind about the
natural flavors whatever you do protect
yourself
look out it's important
if you're looking for teas without
natural flavoring boom you got the
traditional medicinals
not sponsored looking for supplements
without natural flavoring
that's critical like the curcumin or
anything from memorgy
no natural flavors keep that in mind
they're actually smart enough to know
that
and that right there says everything
because companies all
use natural flavors they got msg and all
their stuff out there look out
it's a trick and all it does is just
take you down the wrong path
i love you guys and i'll see you over at
igantik.com