weak adrenals and sodium levels that's a
question that comes up all the time just
because you have weak adrenals doesn't
mean that you're not going to have any
sodium levels but if you're hitting your
body with the quick hit the wrong sodium
is not going to help your adrenals you
can also cook your adrenals and salt you
can pickle them your adrenals need salts
your adrenals need salt you know
trainers out there now health coaches
out there dude you can pickle your
adrenals you can dry them up like little
prunes if you overs salt and then it
gets worse need more salt for my
adrenals but your adrenals are being
pickled and they're shriveling up and
dying more salt for my adrenals ma'am
your adrenals aren't doing good so you
need more salt and you're addicted to
the Salt so you're misreading all the
signs and when you're sick and
chronically ill it's the Wild West it's
really bad