hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 or 20 30 years to
wait for answers to their illnesses life
is precious and there's no time to spare
so let's get to the healing now Today's
Show
is about Seasonal effective disorder
sad are you guys experiencing any of
that do you know anybody in your family
do you have any friends that say they
get so you know emotional or or
depressed or anxiety ridden throughout
the
winter do do you know anybody who's
dealing with that or they feel low
energy and they just there feel listless
and no motivation and when fall comes
around and we go into winter and you
just don't want to function and aches
and pains and all this other stuff that
comes along with it there is some
serious things going on with this whole
thing and people suffer and they
struggle and and they fight through this
and you know fighting to survive
fighting to get through the day fighting
to just push through and persevere you
know when that sad comes popping around
and but it's it's much more than this
it's much more than that so you know if
I sound kind of sarcastic and I got that
little funny laugh going on that's
because what's out there as far as
information on sad is ridiculous it's
hilariously
utterly you know you know silly I mean I
don't even know I can't even find words
it's really because it's that bad so you
know they're like oh okay wait a minute
you know maybe um you know when fall
late fall comes in Winter and you're
getting the these different symptoms
that's Sab it's a real thing I'm glad at
least the medical communities I'm glad
at least the World Views it as something
thank God we're there but that's not
where it stops and that's not what it's
all about it's much bigger than that and
that's what we're doing today that's in
today's show I'm so excited about that
so we're really going to explore that
get into that so we have answers I mean
who wants to wait more you know another
you know 50 years for answers on sad
come on we don't want to do that we
don't want to do we want them today and
that's the bottom line we want them now
um so yeah hey check out you know
medical medium.com check out the
Facebook page check out all the great
stuff that we're always putting out
there um every single day uh you know we
post I'm on there too I'm all answering
questions you name it so check out
Facebook uh you name it Instagram
we put out everything and information so
people can heal people's stories
people's healing stories constantly on
Instagram of how they're healing um from
you know from what's in life-changing
foods and medical medium books and so
you know check out all that and see some
inspirational stories too so if you're
somebody who you know you're not sure
where where you're going with any of
this and and you don't know what you
know you feel like you don't know what
you're doing or something or you're you
it's taking time to heal whatever it may
be you know go on to the Instagram and
take a look and and check out all the
different um stories of people changing
their lives from getting rid of all
their ecoman psoriasis and getting rid
of aches and pains and severe
fatigue um so if you need motivation
beond this show if you need motivation
and you need information you go to the
Instagram go to Facebook and the medical
medium Facebook and check things out
because that's there for you and you
know that's not there for me that
Instagram page isn't there for me you
know it's not about it's not about me
that's not what it's about um someone
was telling me the other day and they
were saying well you know what's
interesting about your Instagram and
everything else you're not plastered
everywhere and it's kind of funny
because
someone someone else said I didn't even
know you existed if you were real and
until until recently a little snip bit
of a video that popped up with you
talking I thought you were a fictional
character but it was an information site
of advanced information helping people
heal and information that they' never
seen before and the reason why I'm not
plastered in every nook and cranny of
the Instagram and plastered on every
nook and cranny of Facebook is because
this is about you guys this is about you
and and you know and getting you the
answers getting you the information so
you can heal getting you the stories
getting you the things you need getting
you the you know all the different
motivational um from people healing and
everything else and so um it's there
it's a resource for you is what I'm
trying to say and cuz that's what
matters that's what matters not my silly
face stamped on everything I need I need
basically you guys getting what you need
I wake up in the morning I say does
everybody have what they need do they
have what they need to heal and what can
I do more is there something I can do
that I'm not doing so that you guys can
get what you need and so that's what
it's for check it out you know the
Instagram and everything else in the
Pinterest and everything else we do um
so if look if this is your first time uh
on here you know my story I'm sure I
mean if this is your first time on here
you don't know my story at age four um I
Heard a Voice perfectly clear that
diagnosed my helped me diagnose my
grandmother of lung cancer I've used
this gift my entire life and uh helped
helped tens of thousands of people heal
and and and and more so that's a little
bit about me so let's go into sad that's
what we're that's what we're waiting for
that's what we're here for today so
Seasonal effective
disorder um here's the thing about this
this sad that's so important to
understand
sad is really just a red flag it's a
sign it's a sign something else is going
on that's what it is is see what we do
in the medical communities today um both
conventional and even some alternative I
I I mean I will say that and look I love
both sides I love conventional I love
alternative medicine of course and
everything in between and you name it
but here's What's Happening Here is we
we don't know what's causing
something so we give it a label and a
tag that's what we do give it a label in
a tag like sad and we say well it's
obviously happening for people in the
winter so it must be the seasonal thing
they start feeling better in the spring
and summer so it must be that's what it
must be but that's where it stops it
stops right there and then if we get a
little smarter we're like well maybe
they need Vitamin D maybe they need
Vitamin D from the Sun maybe they need
supplementation of vitamin D and it kind
of stops there and that's pretty much it
and you know I mean sure we could go a
little farther and say well maybe you
know they're lacking some other things
and so forth but it's it's way bigger
it's way bigger than that so I want to
start with the fact that sad developed
where you know a lot of people were
experiencing these strange symptoms
during the winter and they felt better
in the summer and the strange symptoms
were you know the you the sadness the
the loneliness the depression a little
bit of anxiety some nervousness right a
whole bit and that's kind of you know
that kind of caught on over the years
and became sad but there's just as many
people experiencing that in the spring
and summer too so they experience it in
the spring or summer and it's also kind
of random some people experience it in
the spring and summer some people
experience it in the winter some people
experience it in the fall some people
it's only in the spring it's really a
hot mess what I mean a hot mess is it's
it's not even labeled right it's not
tagged right there's nothing going on
with as far as the advancement of it it
it it that's why I was saying earlier
how ridiculous the whole thing is first
of all there are real problems people
are suffering with and dealing with
there are real issues sad is real in a
sense where you're not feeling good
that's as real as it gets you're not
feeling good and because there's just as
many people getting it in the summer and
then maybe they only get it one year out
of three years does that mean it's sad
and there's people that okay they get it
every every winter but then there's
different levels and
severities now here's where we go wrong
if it gets too severe it's not sad
anymore come on so if it gets too severe
it's not sad so if it's just mild it's
sad you know what I'm saying you are you
are you you know you're you're following
me with this because so if it's more
severe so the ache and pain is not just
kind of feeling like oh listless and a
little low energy and a little kind of
achy it's you know I got bad aches and
pains I got problems now all of a sudden
it's not
sad but but the little
achiness and the little you know the
little symptoms of low energy versus
severe fatigue and heavy achiness is
just basically the beginning or a milder
version of something else that's
happening but instead of like coming
coming to that conclusion or or or
coming to the to the you know to
realization and revelational I idea of
understanding that hey you're dealing
with low-grade something you're dealing
with mild
versions mild versions of something
that's bigger and in some people it gets
worse and a lot of people it gets worse
and I me there's people that have sad
every year for 10 years where they come
into the fall
they come into the winter the fall of
the winter and they're they're they're
feeling you know depressed they're
feeling achy and tired they're feeling
the low energy they're feeling
completely disconnected you know and
they have this and then it Sparks up and
they're feeling better in the spring and
summer and it goes on like that for
eight or 10 years and then one winter is
exceptionally bad all of a sudden severe
fatigue aches and pains that are crazy
um real serious severe depression um all
kinds of symptoms tingles and numbness
everything else with it and then finally
it's like now they're not what they're
not in the sad category anymore what
they were experiencing for eight years
before it got really bad or a bad year
hit was the mild versions of problems
real problems real
situations like forget this whole sad
thing what the hell I mean we're talking
like
that's what I'm trying to tell you is if
you're not feeling good in the
winter okay that means that because it's
winter because it's winter because it's
fall and yes the sun isn't there and all
these things that do support our health
and it's freezing freezing but cold and
it's just oh my God you know wind
blowing and snow piled up there and a
lack of light yes those are all things
that don't support us as much so if we
have something happening underneath it
it could worsen if someone has some ra
or a little bit of arthritic thing going
on or arthritic thing it's going to get
worse if someone has some btis
inflammation of a shoulder or something
which could be from a viral thing like
shingles or something yes it could get
worse without those you know the
beautiful sun without you know without
having snow piled up lack of Light
freezing cold temperatures you know dry
temperatures being real dry in the house
all winter long and yeah your btis could
act up is that
sad could you know could you be feeling
you know more tired because you have
adrenal fatigue and and it doesn't help
you're not getting any sun and adrenal
fatigue gets a little worse yes is that
sad that's insane
it's insane to just call it sad I'm
sorry and look if you guys somebody's
getting mad at me right now saying I got
sad that's what's he talking about look
just hang in there hang in there because
it's it's about getting you answers for
your sad it's about getting you answers
and I am not undermining or you know or
or making fun of the severity of sad or
sad itself I'm just letting you know
that when we get tricked when we get
tricked and fool into something it's
worse it's worse than than you know so
what that means is anybody with a
symptom should be taken completely
serious no matter what and it should
never be thrown into sad it should be
taken dead serious it should be taken
really serious do you know what I'm
saying like really
serious no joke that means you got Got
Something Brewing and it's in the middle
of the winter it shouldn't be just
thrown into this sad thing it should be
like wow what's going on that means that
when conditions aren't perfect in your
life so ma'am sir when we should really
look at this if conditions aren't
perfect in your life you start not
feeling good so something's obviously
happening we shouldn't just throw some
some lame label that puts it in a
category
that makes it not
serious if you know what I mean I so so
it's like okay you got some fatigue
kicking on in the fall and
winter and somebody else doesn't so that
means you just get affected by fall and
winter no your condition is getting
affected by fall and winter what's going
on inside your body that's already there
that's not happening with someone else
that's getting affected by Falling
winter not fall and winter is the
problem and you're just
sensitive it's yeah of course you could
be sensitive overall but you got there
could be something else happening so
look let's talk about the symptoms they
can range from feeling kind of sad to
severely depressed that mean suicidally
depressed is really bad and you know it
could be like a little bit of anxiety
nervousness to severe anxiousness and
severe anxiety it could be feeling a
little tired when fall and late fall
winter come along to feeling really
fatigued where your arms are heavy your
legs are heavy if a practitioner or
doctor diagnoses someone who has heavy
legs and heavy arms and is that fatigued
in the winter and they diagnosed it as
sad they should be
fired they should be fired by the
patient okay so because if it's in the
middle of the winter you got you can't
lift up your arms you can't lift you
can't move your legs too good you got
severe fatigue that's chronic fatigue
syndrome and it's not Lyme disease
that's chronic fatigue syndrome that's
Epstein bar virus that is literally an
Epstein bar coming on heavy in the
middle of the winter and you know so
it's and look you know hey could be
other things too meaning like someone
has you know more getting more problems
in the middle of the winter they could
have something else too that's Brewing
no matter what so that you know the
symptoms can range from
feeling kind of achy to severe arthritis
to feeling really arthritic or constant
you know a little bit of aches and pains
to severe aches and pains if you're
dealing with some aches and pains and
you and they come on in the winter and
your doctor kind of doesn't know what
they are and and blames that on sad it's
because they don't have an answer to
something else that's subtly there or
missing on tests or the labs and so it's
better just say you got sad sad needs to
be just kicked out just kicked out gone
someday and instead you got some
depression you probably got something
else like let's figure out how many
heavy metals you have in your brain
that's causing your depression you know
let's figure out how toxic your liver is
you know your liver struggling then if
you have depression you know cuz it's
probably got a lot of toxins if you got
severe exes and pains then it's
obviously there's a virus there's a
viral issue do you have the shingles in
the system do you have an Epstein bar do
you have cyto magler virus do you have
something else what happens is if if
you're not you know if you're you know
if you're you're stayed away from
getting sick and you just get a little
extra tired or lonely not lonely but a
little lost feeling or tired or feeling
a little bit unmotivated when winter
comes along and you know there just just
little tiny signs that maybe 10 years
from now it could be even more and so
let's nip it in the butt let's clean
things up let's get things better and
stronger in your health so that your sad
isn't worsen because you know in all the
years the decades I've been doing this
and helping people I've seen people have
you know symptoms of sad tell me they've
had symptoms of sad for you know for for
a long time okay for a good 10 years and
then it seemed to get worse and then it
was then it was called finally something
else from a you a really good
practitioner or something said you know
what you got something else going on on
and and what was really happening and
I've had people tell me too what was
really happening Anthony said for 10
years I was just getting a little tiny
symptoms of that I thought it was
sad yeah and and and so we need to take
it
seriously if you're feeling depressed
when that winter comes along and okay if
you're feeling depressed when summer
comes along you know we just have to
know what's going on are you detoxing
you know it's funny because when we hit
Spring our bodies detox themselves our
liers start to detox and if there's
enough poison and garbage and viral
byproduct and heavy metals and
pesticides and Plastics sitting inside
your liver and prescription drugs maybe
antibiotics from you know from 30 years
ago in your life and it's all sitting
inside your liver and that Springtime
comes on your liver is going to be like
giving it a kick like kick kick it's
going to start trying to you know it's
going to try to start pushing some of
that out of there pushing some of that
out of your liver so and that stuff that
stuff hits the bloodstream when it hits
the bloodstream look out and that could
be the onset of Boom um you know the
whole Seasonal effective disorder for
the spring and summer because that once
that neurotoxin and the byproduct and
pesticide byproduct and Plastics and you
know whatever it is and you know um all
of that radio you know Isotopes all that
stuff that gets trapped in livers
whatever it could be it gets in there
when that starts kicking out then you
know you can get you know onset of some
depression you get onset of some anxiety
can get onset of something and boom you
get diagnosed with Asad for
summer and you know it's ignored of
what's really
happening and in the fall you know our
body does another systematic change in
the fall you know our spleens tend to
detox in the fall and spleens get filled
up with all kinds of stuff spleens get
really heavy they're like they become
like little footballs and they get heavy
and they do a little kick out in the
fall too you know and the liver does its
little kick out sometimes in the fall
people are different not in everybody
but it can kick out in the fall and
spring what I'm saying is you know
there's a lot of different reasons there
another thing too is late fall is when
sad you know comes on with with the
majority of people it's late fall so and
probably the majority of the people it's
late fall fall and that's when the you
know foods change in people's diets and
they put a lot of you know I mean you
got the Thanksgiving thing so you're
doing all the Thanksgiving holiday food
then right after Thanksgiving you got
the whole Black Friday thing then after
that you got whatever you got Christmas
and the holidays and you're at work and
you're eating cookies and then you're
you know over your aunt's house and
over here and you're doing this and yeah
it may not seem like it's a lot but it
adds up and you might have a drink or
two or just something else or an eggnog
or whatever it is and you know you've
already probably most people I mean most
people you know who are not really
health-minded probably already not
eating that great anyway summer and fall
but they're probably exercising a little
more they're a little bit more active so
they're keeping the poisons at Bay and
then come late fall they get a little
bit more sluggish because they're not as
active they're not get you know making
time to go walk in the park and then
they're eating a little bit more more
then the liver starts getting clogged up
the bloodstream starts getting thick
like oil and grease gets in the
bloodstream and you know o less oxygen
to the brain and then you start getting
symptoms whether you're starting to get
a little bit of viral symptoms or
something else you start getting
symptoms and then it's blamed on sad
instead of everything else that's really
happening so look I could support the
the um diagnosis of nsad kind of
diagnosis and I can I can you know but I
know I could support it if it helps you
to think it's sad I support it but what
I'm trying to say is sad is a name for
we don't know what's wrong with you we
don't know why you start feeling weird
in the spring and summer we don't know
why you start yeah that's the the people
who actually get the as sad in the
spring and summer we don't know why
you're feeling weird for going into fall
and winter and we don't have have a clue
that's what the label means the label
means maybe it's the seasons because
it's winter time and you're Fe not
feeling so good and that's what it means
so let's just be let's just have it on
the table and be straight up on it
straight honest about it because if I'm
honest about it and we're straight up
about it and it's just on the table
right then you know then then you get
better you get better you know can't it
can't be you know you can't get snowed
on this stuff so when the snow starts
falling and you're getting diagnosed
with sad you can't get snowed as well on
that angle okay so we got to get we
can't get tricked it's important so what
do we do about this how do we handle it
what do we do first of all realize
that's you're a little bit more
sensitive because something else is
brewing inside so the change of season
and the lack of things that we need like
so going into lead fall we're not
exercising as much we're not taking
walks in the air we're not doing all
kinds of things you know the cold damp
air outside and then the dry heat air
inside the house you know like here's an
example which is with people who have
sinus stuff that goes on their sinuses
start getting worse when they're trapped
in the house and it's you know you got
the heat the dry heat or the forced air
in it's winter sinuses get so bad
I've seen diagnosis of of sad for people
who their sinus problems start coming on
in the winter and they say well it's got
to be sad because it's coming on in the
winter and it seems to only do that then
and meaning what's really happening is
they have other things going on in their
sinuses mean not so bad but something's
happening in there so that when
conditions aren't perfect it acts up
it's not sad there's just it's acting up
cuz something's going in there maybe
they got a little bit of of strap maybe
they got some some scar tissue in their
sinus from years ago from a sinus
infection from 30 years ago whatever it
is there's something else
happening so what I like to do with with
the whole thing if someone says hey I'm
an sad sufferer I got sad like I'd say
what I do is say look let's try some
things let's get a little zinc in you
let's get a little extra zinc to
strengthen your immune system because
your aches and
pains okay we can call it sad fine we
can call it we can call it anything we
can call it you know you know D we can
call it D we can call it you know re
whatever we want to call it you know
let's let's let's just get some more
zinc in your system let's build that
immune system up let's get it stronger
and zinc is critical for sad sufferers
critical like one of the biggest ones
and you know I like the liquid sync sulf
sulfate um I have that listed on my
website if you want want to know which
one's the right one and stuff because
you got to get one that doesn't have
preservatives you have to get a zinc
that doesn't there's some zinc out there
that are like poison when they hit your
mouth you know um I might have told you
this before but I've tried so many
different supplements myself with Spirit
meaning asking Spirit then I would you
know would get the supplements I would
ask spirit I would try them I would test
them all these different things and the
zincs that are out there they're they
have so much citric acid in them and
that literally it burns your mouth mouth
in such a way that it's unbelievable so
just be careful about like those kinds
of zincs get the one that you know I
recommend or one like it identically
like it then you're good um if you like
zinc capsules like Z zinc panate from a
really reputable company like the ones
that I list then then you do that um
that could work too but I would you know
the liquid one's always best B12 is like
one of the godsends one of the most
beautiful God sense of you know that we
have on this planet is B12
supplementation the right kind for
knocking out sad so what is the B12
doing what's it doing how can it you
know get sad better you know like I
found it to get it better well it's not
because you know someone's just dealing
with the Seasonal effective disorder and
the B12 you know is fixing their
Seasonal effective disorder it it's not
that it's because something else is
happening like a lot of s when you're
dealing with depression and the Mel Mel
colly thing the feeling lonely feeling
lost feeling you know like like hopeless
feeling that feelings of hopeless and it
gets worse in the
winter that's
neurological see that's neurological if
you look at most sad symptoms okay if
you want to pop on or something one of
the websites what you want to look up
the sad symptoms they don't say
neurological of course not because
they're trying to pin these they're not
because they don't want you thinking
it's neurological they don't want you
thinking your depression is neurological
depression is neurological no matter how
you slice the cake how you slice the pie
whatever it is it's neurological and if
it's depression that was set off by
losing a loved one it's still your
nervous system suffering from the loss
of a loved one so even emotionally
speaking so something terrible happens
in somebody's life because you know we
all we all face struggles throughout our
life and we all have to we have to wear
our armor and we have to be strong
spiritually and emotionally and we have
to you know we have to get through our
battles and we have to push through
everybody goes through things we all do
and when that happens and it hits us
hard and it really hits us hard and it
breaks our armor down you know and slams
us on the ground and we're hurting and
we're flapping on the ground you know
and um it's it's it's the nervous system
that's getting hit we get let down when
we get betrayed we get backstabbed by a
partner or a friend or a lover or
whoever or a spouse or whatever it is in
our lives we get you know backstabbed or
betrayed in some way or some kind of
commun communication goes disastrous and
breaks down that's hitting us
neurologically it's hitting us our mind
it's hitting our mind it's hitting our
brain but and then if none of that's
going on and there's none of that going
on you don't have any of that there's
nothing happening there like there's no
big losses and there's no you know
there's no betrayal and there's no
heartbreak and there's none of all this
stuff and but yet you're feeling that
depression and you're feeling that
sadness and you're feeling all these
other things it's still neurological
it's still central nervous system so if
you look at symptoms and stuff they're
not even they don't even go there if you
find something on the Internet this why
I always say at the beginning of the
show you're going to you're going to
hear about stuff here you're not going
to hear anywhere else it just doesn't
exist out there and so when you're
dealing with the with with all these
different feelings including physical
feelings like anxiety that's
neurological anxiousness is nervous
system okay so it's not just depression
it's anxiety's nervous system okay if
you're feeling um if you're feeling
aches and pains those are nerves that
are hurting aches and pains are nerves
you see and you know focus and
concentration issues that's a big one
with sad guess what focus is
neurological that's
neurotransmitters concentration that's
neurological that's neurotransmitters
all you need is a good dose of heavy
metals in the brain like we talked about
in the heavy metal detox show and you
got focus in concentration problems
that's nervous system that's not
sad but that's what I mean when you look
at all these feeling disconnected that's
central nervous system feeling you know
all those feelings and you know when you
the only one that's not central nervous
system that really is you know a symptom
too like another symptom that we really
deal with is weight gain and that's not
neurological that's liver that's your
liver getting real sluggish in the
winter could be the foods that you've
eaten anything like that could be the
fact that you got a l gr viral thing in
the liver could be um you know more
pesticides and antibiotics stored up in
your liver from years ago could be
anything and and then that's what the
weight gain you know can happen too um
but that's not neurological that one but
most every
symptom with sad is central nervous
system it's neurological so for that to
be just taken off the table thrown away
that in meaning why that information
doesn't exist maybe they didn't Discover
it yet maybe maybe I'm giving them too
much credit they just didn't Discover it
yet or something and you know fine but
hey you got sad and that's the answer so
okay so that's that's what it comes down
to so so what can we do to battle it B12
is like for the central nervous system
so that's what I was talking about
before before I ran off a little bit on
you guys before I ran off I'm sorry
about that
B12 is for the central nervous system
sad improves from every aspect of it
from the depression from the anxiety
from from the aches and pains from the
fatigue
and and hey fatigue that's neurological
too unless it's just adrenal fatigue but
most people who are experiencing more
than just adrenal fatigue are
experiencing neurological fatigue with
the adrenal fatigue so the
B12 is is for all of this including
somebody who's got weight gain issues
because the liver needs more B12 if it's
sluggish so that's a weapon secret
weapon so where are we now we're going
into the winter is that what it is so
you know this is such a that's look
whether we're going into the summer
whether we're going into the spring
whether we're going into the fall it
doesn't matter okay it doesn't matter in
the end cuz cuz sad originated at first
where it was just winter then for some
reason it broadened and became exactly
more summer but it's really anytime any
season overall and look if you're
somebody who it's definitely hardcore
winter where Winter's when it happens
and I start feeling worse then yeah but
everybody feels it different at
different months and different times
different times of the year different
times of the seasons So Different
Seasons so it's you know so it's
important to do the B12 that's a big one
spirulina I love that one because
spirina holds so many powerful nutrients
to support it's not just about vitamin D
believe me if if if I literally had two
options like someone someone it say I
didn't feel good okay and I knew what
that was Spirit told me whatever or say
I didn't say say whatever I mean you
know say spirit said both these things
say Spirit didn't want to tell me what
what what was better for me okay so
let's let's just say that because I know
it's hard to say because spirit always
tells me what's better for everybody
what's better for me too and all that
but say spirit said well you got two
options here in front of you or somebody
put two options in front of me it was
spirulina and vitamin D they said you
can only have one option you can only
choose one option for you not feeling
good and let's just label it
sad okay um you're feeling a little this
feeling a little that let's just label
it sad I would go with the spirina 100%
go with the
spirulina because the spirulina is going
to have so many more nutrients for real
reasons why you have
sad so if you're dealing with a little
fatigue you might be experiencing a
little bit of a viral load you might
have some heavy metal spirina is good
for all those if you have deficiencies
let's just pretend sad is just
deficiencies well spirulina outweighs
vitamin D any day if you're going to
take vitamin D take vitamin D3 and I
support vitamin D3 I'm just saying
spirulina overrides it and so there's
things we can do that are just amazing I
like lemon balm for sad cuz lemon balm
is is like a nerve tonic it's not only
antiv my role in case your sad is low
grade Epstein bar low- grade chronic
fatigue low grade shingles low grade
some other kind of bug low- grade stpa
cacus whatever it is lemon bomb is great
because it's an anti- viral
antibacterial it's like an
antibiotic but I would I would you know
I would use lemon bomb in a second
because lemon bomb is also relaxing to
the central nervous system and it's
strengthens the central nervous system
and like I said sad really is 95%
neurological symptoms that are mild and
some severe unless a doctor you know
unless you go to 10 15 20 30 doctors and
finally some doctor says hey you got
something else going this ain't sad you
got something you know something's
happening here and even if that's the
case regardless of whatever lemon bomb
is going to be helpful for it so lemon
bomb is another secret weapon now out of
the foods get foods that have life to
them in your diet you're coming into
winter chances are you're eating a
little differently in the summertime we
might eat a pint of
strawberries we might eat a pint of
blackberries we might have more apples
maybe in the early fall or something or
late fall but we get into winter and we
forget and don't realize these Foods
disappear and these foods help protect
us they protect our nervous system they
keep us strong they keep us healthy so
if you're someone that's afraid of fruit
to begin with and you got sad or you you
you believe you have sad or you've been
told that whatever we can call it
anything I'm totally cool totally happy
with that but if you got sads you know
happening then you can't keep fruit out
of your diet 100% you can't be on a
fruitless diet you don't want to be on a
fruitless diet I'm not saying stop
everything else you like and what you
eat and all the whether it's animal
protein or not or whatever it is I'm not
saying that you just can't keep fruit
completely out fruits holding that
sunlight even if you're in it's in Dead
Winter and it's a piece of fruit that
was ripened in South America it was
ripened in you know whatever Costa Rica
it was it was ripened in Ecuador it was
or wherever it was ripened in um you
know across the across the world
wherever it was it still was harboring
that seasonal sunlight light the power
that's in there the minerals that were
ignited by the sun and the whole process
and that is helpful because it holds all
these different nutrients and and and
chemical uh function function nut
nutrients and phytochemicals and stuff
that we don't even have our fingers on
there's thou you know if you look at
life-changing Foods you know can't
scratch even the surface of the of the
you know hundreds of thousands of
phytochemicals that aren't discovered by
science and research yet and I like I
talk about in life-changing Foods raw
honey has over 200
,000 Miracle phytochemicals to stop
disease cancers illnesses you name it
that are inside raw honey and you know
raw honey alone is great for for um for
you know a sad and so and that's another
great secret weapon but you want to
bring in a few fruits if you can things
that you remember eating in the
summertime you know um maybe a little
bit more red leaf lettuce maybe a little
bit more green leaf lettuce and you
bring these different foods in that you
don't normally eat in the winter if
you're just eating um only meat and then
a few you just like you know I don't
know canned dead vegetables it's not
going to be enough you want a little
fresh
spinach and you want you know you want
some other different things I mean some
celery if you can um maybe a few walnuts
would be really good very helpful for
you know the nervous system you do a
handful of walnuts handful of hemp seeds
um you can do different things even if
it's just adding them in here and there
you add them in I like celery juice you
guys know that are you doing your celery
juice by the way have you you missed it
today you missed it no you want to get
you want to get that celery juice in you
okay I don't want you forgetting to take
it celery juice is incredible for
sad well what am I saying sad well it
means something else is going on you
know could be the neurological stuff
could be the liver being sluggish and
stag stagnant and
toxic um you know it could be it could
be all of that and it usually is and it
really is so that's really important to
know um when we're low grade viral when
we when we have these different things
going on in with us and we're
chronically ill because we got the
low-grade viral thing so say somebody
with Hashimoto thyroiditis you guys know
how how everything I talk about that
we're Epstein bar causes Hashimoto that
means the Epstein bar virus is sitting
inside your thyroid when you have hasim
well when winter time comes symptoms of
you know Hashimoto can can amp up
Hashimoto can get the thyroid can get a
little bit worse sometimes during the
winter and um because anything you have
whatever that might be whether you're
prone to UTI whether you're whether you
have um you know gastritis intestinal
tract disorders you know IBS they tend
to worsen anyway under winter
conditions everything we have regardless
of what it is we walk around in life
tends to worsen now sometimes when it
worsens in the summer it's also because
of the bad air in the summer we have um
we have those heat waves that are filled
with extreme amount of toxins we're
talking loads of heavy metals in the sky
during these humidity heat waves that
hit that hit you know um up there in the
north and you name it in the summertime
where it's really humid the humidity is
up but the air quality is down there's
less oxygen in the air it's filled with
tremendous amounts of toxins falling out
of the sky you know radiation you name
it so we get waves of that in between
when the air gets a little better and
nicer days happen those waves of that
swell people up when when you have
chronic illness going on if you're
dealing with a little bit of chronic
fatigue and you got a little bit of
Edema and you got a little bit of flute
retention and that heat wave comes on
with that bad air you might feel it you
might feel like the effect of it and
have to be in the air conditioning and
everything else because if you go
outside you feel it and then that's
blamed on
sad see that's blamed on Seasonal
effective disorder so you go to the
doctor and you're like well in the
summertime I I can't handle the heat I
suffer more that's because something
else is happening and then you know hey
your doctor might say well you just got
Seasonal effective disorder and then you
start feeling depressed you can't go out
enough you can't you know you don't feel
that great when you're outside and
there's there it's because of these
different circumstances so when we're
sensitive with all kinds of different
issues whether it's sinuses whether it's
UTI whether it's stomach problems
whether it's aches and pains whether
it's fatigue whether it's depression
anxiety you name it they tend to worsen
when the winter comes on and for some
people when the summer comes on not for
most people but a lot of people does it
could hit and like I said even in
between at different times too so let's
look at other options to get rid of you
know to get rid of what is called sad
what is called Seasonal effective
disorder you know to help the mood and
everything else well you want to you
want to do the heavy metal detox okay
because if you're dealing with
depression and you're dealing with
anxiety and you're dealing with um the
mood the mood swings and even if
someone's giving you a diagnosis a
bipolar which isn't it's another thing
that they don't know what's wrong that's
just you know a term for being up or
down that's not a real diagnosis that's
another label and um so if you're
somebody that's been up and down you're
all over the place and it's hard for you
to focus and concentrate and you're on a
high 1 minute not a low one minute toxic
heavy metals and so you want to get on
that that heavy metal detox that I talk
about in the recent show um and you can
go to my blog you can go to my blog and
find the the tox the heavy metal detox
you can go there and find it it's in the
books but the bottom line is you getting
these different things in you so let's
cover a few more the lemon bomb was
critical that's a big one even golden
seal is good to test out for sad golden
seal is antiviral antibacterial so if
whatever condition you're dealing with
and it's worsening a little come winter
or worsening a little come summer do a
week on golden seal um people their
lives turn around do a week or two on
golden seal so you know and then always
look for the right one a whole bit like
I said you know you know um we recommend
the stuff that I believe is the safest
and the best and and the body's
friendliest and so that's one I like too
that's a great one and there's other
things you can do ibrite ibite is an
herb that is incredible it's an
antiviral antibacterial but I like
ibrite because ibrite has um it's not
just about being antiviral antibacterial
it it it allows us to clean up our blood
a little bit
um it's kind of like a blood cleanser
same thing with red clover red clover so
if you go to your health food store or
go online we have some sources too that
we list if you go and check out the
sources and you get red clover
flowers and you make tea with it every
single day all winter
long it's going to help clean the blood
while you're going through winter it's
going to help keeping your blood clean
it's a great blood
cleanser and so what that does is it's
helping your liver because a lot of
people's sad is liver problems but liver
problems that could set off neurological
symptoms so the liver could be sluggish
stagnant filled with heavy metals filled
with poisons and then it's it's
releasing into the bloodstream affecting
the central nervous system so you want
to clean up the blood so red clover is a
great one too nettle Leaf is remarkable
for sad it's anti-inflammatory it's
incredible anti-inflammatory what
happens is is our sad is blamed on you
know our symptoms of sad like I was
saying before aches and pains which is
inflammation of the nerves is blamed on
sad at the doctor's office you go on
nettle leaf and it starts to calm down
those nerves brings down the
inflammation then you're just addressing
the sad diagnosis turmeric turmeric tea
you can buy turmeric and its whole form
at all the health food stores now I like
that simmer it in you know in a mug of
hot water squeeze a little lemon in
there with the turmeric throw a little
ginger in there it's another secret
weapon to sad whether it's summer or
winter and you could have your turmeric
pieces in there and they could be you
know sitting in a hot cup of hot water
you can you know simmer it too as well
you can simmer it making like almost
like a sou soup and then there's the
healing broth the healing broth we have
the blog post on the healing broth we
talk about it all the time at Medical
medium you guys check check it out it's
in the life-changing Foods book The
Healing broth is like a miracle worker
for Saad both summer and
winter and um and that's incredible
soothes the nervous system helps calm
the liver down helps clean the blood out
helps get the intestinal tract stronger
raises the hydrochloric acid you name it
that's what it's doing meaning you name
it for sad it does and it's really
helpful so bring that one in too so
there's all these different things we
can do and I want you to keep on doing
them like I said don't forget about the
fruits and in the vegetable Department
you know there's a lot of good veggies
you can you can use for sad okay like I
said before you know celery's and Herb
that's a great one cucumbers you know
people shy away from cucumbers all
winter long it's the worst time to shy
away from them bring them back in no
matter what you know even if they're not
that great looking at the store peel the
skin off if you have to and bring
cucumbers do a cucumber juice maybe
cucumber apple juice just once a day and
watch the sad lift watch the sadness
lift watch things start lifting up and
you know and so that's something to
consider too is is just bringing in more
cucumbers have salads with cucumbers
avocado is really good for sad that's
another one helps support the nervous
system it's easy on the liver so avocado
you bring more in you know some people
that tell me about their C and they're
like you know what I'm like what do you
eat they're like I only eat oatmeal in
the morning um you know and and then for
lunch I have um I have chicken salad for
lunch I'm like well we had a salad
that's good and a chicken fine but then
it gets you know and they say well then
it go goes all
downhill towards the end of the day and
it's like cookies in the winter and I
can't help it in 3:00 in the afternoon
I'm having piece of cake like piece of
pound cake or something and then it just
starts getting worse towards the end of
of the day and you know that's when it
should be like handful of walnuts
handful of hemp seeds celery sticks
apple slices um oranges secret weapon
sad is oranges tangerines and oranges
these are like liquid Sunshine so if you
juice them you know with like little
Tangerine juice or orange juice or
whatever think about that how the
sunlight that's in that fruit that
sunlight holds a lot of different
nutrients meaning it UPS the nutrients
in the tangerine and the orange it UPS
it the sunlight and that sunlight
physical sunlight that hits the orange
and you know ripens it orange over time
and makes it that that beautiful color
that powerful medicine develops right
there between the Sun hitting it and
entering into it along with the
phytochemicals and the tangerines and
the oranges and the vitamin C and the
calcium and everything else and it
really UPS the game it can change your
Chemistry it's amazing let's talk about
melons melons contain highly active
fluids that bind to poisons that cause
sad you know the poisons I'm talking
about like the toxic heavy metals that
affect our nervous system um pesticides
that old pesticides that are in our
liver all kinds of different issues that
affect our nervous system our liver our
toxic blood that we can get all of it
you know these melons they have this
highly active fluid that's
life-changing um mangoes mango strength
the nervous system with their bioactive
Trace magnesium combined with phenolic
acids so just know that the mango has
this bioactive Trace magnesium sitting
inside of it with this with these
phenolic acids combined it strongly
supports our nervous system and and just
as I was saying before our sad Seasonal
effective disorder is central nervous
system based it most of it literally
almost every part of sad is central
nervous system based papaya incredible
for sad because by far it's one of the
most powerful gut restoratives and our
guts are tied to our nervous systems so
papayas are that powerful see the papaya
has not only this digestive enzyme thing
going on it's got 500 over 500
undiscovered enzymes in papaya they're
incredible for our guts and our guts are
so wired to the nervous system so think
about bringing in some of these Foods in
any way you can a half a papaya here and
there maybe you could find a good mango
get a tangerine in there and literally
this could be lifechanging and will be
lifechanging so do it when you can take
one day at a time even if you just bring
in one food a day so one food a day one
food every other day you know one food
hey look if all you can do is bring in
one food a week it can help it really
can't even if it's subtle even if it's
just mildly there you know a little bit
help it matters because your body will
actually use that food it'll use it for
you even if you don't feel the effect
yet but if you can get it every day then
you'll feel the effects faster of course
because your body's going to be able to
get more of it and that matters and you
know all these things make a difference
to build up you know build up your
immune system build up your neurological
system build up your liver and get you
out of this
diagnosis and also protect you so that
your sad doesn't get worse down the road
and develop into more Depression more
anxiety you know and and all these other
different symptoms along with it more ex
and pains more fatigue you name it let's
not go there let's let's head it off at
the past Lord knows enough people have
enough symptoms and they can't even get
out of bed you guys know know I know
many of you are dealing with it and
can't function and you you know it's
enough of that's going on so let's all
work on getting better and moving to the
right direction moving to the right
place with all of this so the bottom
line is realize hey you know let's not
get tricked let's not get fooled about
the labels were handed so much let's get
down to the bottom of what's going on
what's really happening you know what's
the deal
and that's the direction we need to go
that's the key so I would just
incorporate some of these different
supplements bring in some of the foods
without a doubt if you know somebody
going through this you know offer them
some of these options it could be really
helpful really life-changing and make a
big difference in their life you know I
got to tell you guys you know every
morning I wake up and I say there's a
lot of people out there okay there's a
lot of people out there that can't
function they they they struggle
they can't they feel like they're stuck
with their illness and I think about it
all the time and I want you to know you
can get better and you will get better
there's no doubt about it I'm with you
the whole way through so just just you
know hang in there with me and
everything I'm throwing at you you just
you know take it in and a little at a
time if you can only do a little you do
a little I stand behind you 100% I love
you I care about you I truly do and I
believe in you okay I'll see you next
time hang in there
bye-bye