hello welcome to secrets to gut health
webinar exciting thank you for coming
for this webinar and listening or thank
you for you know tuning in and being
involved and uh it's an honor really
truly an honor to uh just be here
talking to you and and and being all
together like this and just look it's an
honor just to know that you're there
that you're you want to learn this
information and um and want Ms my heart
and it really does it really does you
know I get I get uh get a little tery
when I think about it because listen you
know it it's you're becoming an expert
you're really becoming an expert it's
like there's something about that that
just it gives me tingles up and down
my raises my neck hair gives me chills
and tingles the good ones not the
symptoms not the symptoms and it gives
me the good feel heing to know that
you're changing the world with me that
we're doing it it it you know it it was
so hard it started out in childhood with
Spirit saying to me look we have to get
ahead somehow of the misinformation
that's out there in any way we can we
have to help people and and hearing that
when I was young it just it was too much
it was just way too much what is he
talking about what is spirit talk
talking about and it was really hard to
really kind of bite into that and then
you know as the years went on I said
okay it's time to do this it's time to
do this now we have to really do this
because there's so much misinformation
out there it's flooded like never before
and I remember even 10 years ago 10
years ago there was there first of all
there was barely any information out
there number one I mean I was giving
information just as advanced now um to
my to my clients all the time and other
doctors at that time but there wasn't
really you know it was still kind of
early 10 15 years ago still kind of
early in the making of of of what was
happening out there with the
misinformation all you know flying
around the internet it wasn't so
saturated there weren't so many
different belief
systems saturated in in the system out
there of
misinformation so there was lack of
information there was a lack of
information and this was really hard
really hard especially for hard for
younger people that were sick with
chronic illness oh my God and you may be
one of them you may have been one of
them and you may be one of them now a
younger person now dealing with symptoms
and things like that now and you know
and and it it's it's difficult well back
10 15 years ago there was just nothing
there there was nothing there and uh you
go a little bit further really nothing
there oh my God and so I was able to
deliver this information just as just as
up to dat and Advance as it is decades
ahead of what's out there even now was
able to deliver that to people back then
going all the way back but there wasn't
there wasn't that flood of
misinformation that was out there to a
degree now oh my God and and so that's
why it's so important that you're
becoming an expert look the thyroid
healing book when you actually get into
this book the
information is is
mind-blowing and you'll become that
expert in in the thyroid world in the in
the thyroid help in the thyroid health
and you'll be able to help anybody and
if you don't want to help anybody it's
okay you just you work on yourself but
what's going to happen is somebody's
going to you know you're going to bump
into somebody and they're going to be
like whether it's an aunt an uncle
whether it's an old friend what whatever
it is and they're going to be like yeah
I got this thyroid problem and you're
going to know so much so much and it's a
big deal it's a really big deal so it's
an honor to just have you here and you
know back like I said back 10 years ago
and a little further when you were when
you were younger when mean meaning when
someone was young at that time and had a
problem whether they had a condition
coming on mystery symptoms you name it
they're going to doctors and there was
just nothing on the internet and what
was out there you know I mean wasn't
that great so that was difficult and
then of course if you're if if you know
10 years ago if if you weren't a young
person and you were you know you were
whatever a little bit old or whatever
and then we sick chronically back 20 30
years ago oh my God you know it's it was
so difficult people ha have been through
so much with their journey in healing
and now today they they have challenges
that are a little bit different
challenges of so many different things
to choose from so much different
information to choose from where to go
what to do how to do it and and that's
why I you know I've always always say
that's why I say in in front of my radio
shows too now that this is the only
place and and I know that's pushing it
right the way I'm saying it I know it
but it's I promise you it's true this is
the only place where the information is
not tampered with and it's not
manipulated
by any kind of interest group but along
the way if other information was or you
know medical funding with the strings
attached and the the botched up research
the thumb on the scale research you know
the lobbyist that no one knows about in
alternative medicine I mean oh my God
there's lobbyists in alternative
medicine nobody knows this I mean nobody
talks about it it's
unreal and the internal Kickbacks the
persuaded belief systems both
conventional and alternative and the
private panels of people the private pan
panels of people that make decisions for
you that have don't even have health
problems so they don't even know what
you went through and the health field
payoffs and the trendy traps that are
online and so yeah and and of course in
other books so I say that this is the
only place that doesn't have that no
this information's pure it's untampered
with it's clean it comes from the source
I was born to hear and that Source makes
you the expert that Source makes you the
expert ERT it takes you to that next
level that level you know you just we
can't find any other place right now
when it comes down to chronic illness
when it comes down to chronic illness so
and that's most important because
chronic illness leads to so many things
it leads to all kinds of trouble and
problems and everything else chronic
illness that's where we're in trouble
here meaning in the industries and we
have to we have to do something about
about it and that's what these books are
that's what the thyroid healing book is
so thank you for being here at this
webinar we're talking about the secrets
of gut health the secrets of gut health
and I want to I want to kind of tie it
into the thyroid a little bit because
everything right now is getting blamed
on the thyroid too so the thyroid
Experts of the day are trying to push
everything into the thyroid every
symptom into into it being the thyroid I
don't know if you're experiencing that
yet I don't know if that's something
that you know you you've come across or
you've experienced yet but that's what's
happening so it's all getting pointed to
the thyroid if it's not getting pointed
to Lyme disease it gets pointed to the
thyroid now that's what's happening so
you know any kind of aches and pains
fatigue um you know brain fog confusion
uh no sex drive um all these different
things you know that you have loss of
libido whatever all that it's getting
it's getting thrown into the thigh
thyroid package now that's where all
that's going weight gain everything else
gets thrown into the the thyroid
package and maybe you're not up maybe
you haven't gotten to that point yet
maybe you haven't maybe you're just a
curious thyroid information Seeker
you've been told you might have a
thyroid problem you haven't really been
through too much you're not diagnosed
with Hashimoto or maybe you've been
diagnosed with
Hashimoto and you know you're not really
you're not really being thrown into that
whole new package that's coming out
lately that's trying to be like hey this
is ahead of the curve this this big
package of misinformation where there's
a whole bunch of experts now on thyroid
claiming that all these symptoms are
your thyroid and and how glorious is it
that we have this big
answer and so it's making the thyroid
Experts of today look like they're
they're they they know what's going on
but that's not how it works all these
symptoms are not thyroid related are not
thyroid
related and they're even
throwing um gut health issues many
different gut health issues
into into thyroid
relation now we're going to break this
apart we're going to talk about what's
going on thyroid problems thyroid
problems and I have I have over a 100
symptoms and conditions in thyroid
healing that explain to what's going on
to what degree if it's thyroid related
or not thyroid
related and there's um there's there's
undiscovered hormones within the thyroid
that are not even discovered by research
and science yet in what these hormones
do and what your the capabilities of
what your thyroid does that research
research and science hasn't even touched
upon what the thyroid can do for you and
what is doing for you even when it's
hypo even when it's partially removed or
removed you wouldn't
believe what it can
do
so basically though so the hip thing the
hip trendy new thing is you package it
all into thyroid so you know you go to
your doctor just gaining some weight and
I got some bloating let's just it's
probably your thyroid now oh let's see
oh yeah the thyroid numbers are off or
the thyroid numbers are fine but I still
suspect you have a hidden thyroid
problem so we're going to start
addressing that no matter what well per
menopause menopause oh no it's your
thyroid definitely your thyroid meaning
that's what you're going to hear that's
what you hear and men too look men too
men will will hear thyroid now they're
just you getting pushed into the thyroid
cart
too you know it's like yeah it's like
being online you're ordering something
and there's a shopping cart you're
getting pushed into the thyroid cart um
yeah memory loss brain fog difficulty
concentrating you skull packag and
thrown into the thyroid insatiable
hunger don't get thrown into the thyroid
puffy face puffy eyes is that thrown
into the thyroid edema thrown into
thyroid meaning fluid retention or any
kind of uncomfortable nature aches and
pains anything little bit of fever
whatever fever on and off or or just
lots of different things like depression
depression thrown into the thyroid
that's one that's really getting pushed
into the thyroid now by the experts by
the new expert of today
um and we're going to we're going to
break this up a little bit we're going
to get into it a little bit and I know
this is a gut health show and and and so
if you're you know tuned to hey I wanted
to hear all about gut health he's all
he's all hung hung up on thyroid but
there's a reason why we're kind of
chopping into that a little bit there's
there's a reason we're going to chop
also
into
celiac disease right I mean some of you
are probably like interested in that one
um leaky gut colitis IBS sibo bloating
gastritis so you know those are pretty
fun to get into too right so we're going
to do that candida we'll get into a
little bit of candida too right but
we're GNA get into some other cool
things too with it all and um and we got
some time we got some time to play we
got some time to play and do this so
that's what we're doing okay so um you
got your herbal tea do you have what you
need you're relaxing cuz uh these
webinars do take a little bit longer
than just the radio show that I do and
so forth so you know make sure you're
nice and tucked in or relaxed or however
and uh if you're taking notes you're
taking notes or whatever you need to
do um so let's talk about this a little
bit constipation getting thrown into the
the whole thyroid the whole thyroid
package
lately um well if your thyroids
not not uh up to par if it's not
producing what it needs to produce if
it's not producing the hormone it needs
to produce if there's anything going on
with the thyroid whatsoever um if it's
inflamed if there's
Hashimoto but you also have other
symptoms involved and that's why
everything's getting packaged into the
thyroid so it's like one of these things
where you know a doctor an expert or
somebody will be like well um there's
constipation too so that it's got to be
the thyroid so the the thyroid hormones
are lacking so the constipation is going
to be happening so that's something
that's occurring right now in the in the
new world of medicine that we we live in
today but they don't have much to do
with each other they don't have much to
do with each other at all all
constipation you know that's that's
mostly with other things happening like
inflammation occurring in the small
intestinal tract inflammation occurring
in the
colon that's more to do with
constipation um less peristaltic action
due to
inflammation um the nervous system
certain nerves going all to the colon or
the small intestinal tract that that
allow for creating that peristaltic
action maybe not be getting the right
signal through those nerves the person
may not be getting the right signals
going through those nerves going to the
colon going to the small intestinal
tract to give it that twist it
needs a liver
issue big one for constipation sluggish
liver stagnant liver that's a big one
for
constipation very big
one okay so these are more what we're
talking about why would the intestinal
tract or colon be
inflamed could be a viral issue going on
inside the liver a little bit of old
Epstein bar maybe some other kind of
virus in the liver going
on and maybe a little bit of strep a
cacus a little bit of strep chronic
that's always in the intestinal tract
small intestinal tract or large
intestinal track causing some
inflammation little bit pockets of ecoli
causing some inflammation as well um
toxins coming from a sluggish
liver and there's a lot of different
toxins that sit inside a
liver and those toxins can get into the
colon and into the intestinal tract
let's cover some of those toxins toxins
from medications such as thyroid
medication yeah the thyroid medication
is is a funny thing because it builds up
in the
liver so it just builds up it builds up
it builds up it builds up the liver has
to absorb it like a sponge Non-Stop for
years and years and years then it has to
figure out a way to get that thyroid
medication out liver gets nice and
sluggish it can't function anymore
thyroid medication has to get out
somehow it finds its way inside the
colon over
time and sits in the lining of the colon
doesn't leave so fast medications
they're not quick to leave the body
they're not one of these things that
they're just so quick to leave the body
that's not how medications work
especially thyroid medication is not a
medication actually leaves the body so
quickly toxic heavy metals lead chromium
nickel so lead chromium nickel Mercury
aluminum
copper uh arsenic the list goes on heavy
toxic heavy metals inside the
liver viruses Epstein bar hhv6 shingles
cyega
virus viral toxins that creates so many
symptoms that we talk about in thyroid
healing when I say we it's spirit I talk
about in thyroid
healing so all all the different
symptoms that we get for chronic
illnesses like chronic fatigue syndrome
all the tingles and numbs all this
different stuff there's neurotoxins
related and but like I said you know
these illnesses these symptoms get
totally thrown into the thyroid basket
now that's what the experts do cuz
experts don't
know you know the the recent information
it's out there internet or books or
whatever they just don't know where
these symptoms come from so hey they're
Heroes it comes from the thyroid now
that's the new thing so now the heroes
it's not coming from the thyroid it's
not the thyroid is just one more symptom
with everything else it's one more
symptom with everything else that's the
big secret that's the big
truth the thyroid is just one more
symptom the thyroid does have problems
it does get injured it does get involved
we're going to go into into that a
little bit today but we're going to do
that even more in the next webinar it's
going to be focused mainly on thyroid
this is about the
gut but so what happens is everything is
just thrown into the thyroid
basket so you can have the neurotoxins
inside the liver the dermato toxins
inside the liver viral casing so that's
dead bodies of viruses and bacteria and
all kinds of great stuff pesticides
herbicides fungicides rodenticides
insecticides
they all sit inside the
liver
radiation sits in liver solvents and fat
fat sit inside the
liver fats it's old rancid fats culate
and they just sit inside the
liver and they weaken the liver make the
liver sluggish and then we have
constipation we have
bloating we
have sometimes B of
gastritis we get to a point where we can
get set up for diverticulitis
diverticulosis down the
road our candida levels can rise cuz
candida is trying to save our butts
trying to save our
butts it's a whole another thing we'll
talk about a little bit I know I talked
about it before on one of the radio
shows but try to give you guys even
additional information if I can so so
there's all these things that sit inside
the liver make it sluggish make it
dysfunctional and the liver plays a role
more in thyroid symptoms than anything
else
almost that's what's unbelievable and
the liver plays a role in so much of our
gut health issues it is unbelievable how
much the liver liver plays a role in our
gut health issues when the liver
weakens breaks down it gets sluggish it
gets stagnant and it can't produce the
bile need
it it can't produce the bile the bile
strength the bile salt strength is
reduced so when that bile starts popping
out the
gallbladder and it starts popping out of
the gallbladder and it's getting down in
there and the small the the top of the
small intes track in the dadum in that
whole
area it's weak it's weaker it's weaker
bile fluid it's
weaker when it's weaker it can't break
down
fat so the fats go rans it to people on
a high fat diet there be a lot of e like
eating a lot of chicken which is high
fat doesn't matter if it's lean breast
with no skin on it's still high fat it's
just you know cuz that's the calorie
inside the chicken if they're eating too
many nuts somebody who's eating too many
nuts you got a vegan eating too many
nuts way too many nuts and nut Butters
um way too much chocolate or whatever it
is then you got you get all that fat
that the B's having a difficulty break
down someone's eating lots of grass-fed
beef got all that fat in it doesn't I'm
not talking about brisket I'm not
talking about ribs I'm talking about
just the leanest cut you could find
still lots of fat in
there if someone's just you know I don't
know someone's eating tons of coconut
oil and lots of avocados too many
avocados they're eating six eight
avocados a day people do that and and
it's a good healthy
food and look if you're in the animal
protein yeah lean grass-fed beef is the
the safest way to go but all these fats
what they do they're hard to hard to
break down see I don't I don't I don't
stick myself to a belief system Spirit
told me a long time ago if you fall into
one belief system I'm done with you
spirit said Spirit was kidding Spirit
has a sense of humor you have to have a
sense of
humor you have to have a spir a sense of
humor I've actually asked Spirit about
that along the way I said why do you
have a sense of humor spirit Spirit said
that you know that truly tapped in joy
that truly tapped in compassion that
truly tra tapped in love that truly that
true true
place there's humor there's joy and
humor with it there's lighthearted
nature in in in it and spirit said look
you can't get this Bel system and you
can't just stay with this one belief
system and you get stuck in that and
then you can't help everybody you just
help some people because part of that
belief system is good like there's no
processed
foods everybody's adopted that at this
point so then you do help somebody you
help somebody that's on a fast food diet
to get off fast food diet to eat a
certain way doesn't mean it's the right
way entirely for their conditions so you
can't fall into a belief system right
and so I can't do that I'm not allowed
to do
that and I wanted to fall into a belief
system badly just like anybody would or
any practitioner or any healer whatever
I wanted to Spirit wouldn't let me kept
me on my toes to make sure you get the
right information I wanted to believe
candida was really bad I wanted that I
mean that's what I wanted like yeah
candida no spirit said no you kill all
your candida you die you can't live
without Candida
candida allows absorption of nutrients
to get into the bloodstream to allows no
that's that's the osmosis machine that
candida is your
lifeline we're not told that candida
gets out of control it grows because
you're dumping so much because okay okay
this is a good point right here that I
got to connect is the bile salts get so
weak from the liver from the liver
breaking down with all this
garbage that the bile salts weaken can't
break down the fats fats get rancid they
go into the intestinal tract and guess
what feeds off of it
bacteria so candida has to step up its
game it has to say no no no no you can't
do that I don't want strepa cacus
feeding off all this and creating sio
yes I don't want uh stakus feeding off
of all this rancid fat that can't break
down enough and rancid protein that
can't break down
enough I don't want that being fed to
strepa coasy koi seiff staff I don't
want it being fed to Epstein bar to
shingles variety number
21 a non-r rashing one I don't
want this being fed to all that so
candid is programmed programmed by
something above our
bodies up in the atmosphere up in the
heavens up up high candida has a message
being delivered to it all the time it
has a the will to keep you alive so
it'll rise up and it'll grow and then
some somebody's going to say oh you got
your candid is out of control that's
your problem we have to kill off your
candid to no the problem is we have to
stop
feeding some of these bad bacteria and
other things that create sibo and
everything because candid is trying to
save the day it's trying to eat all that
food so it ends up growing more and more
because it's trying to eat all that bad
food that's rancid and not breaking down
so it could save your
butt so but I wanted a belief system
when I was younger I'd be like Oh
Candida spirit said yeah well I want to
tell you about this fungus like oh
fungus is bad bad no and spirit's like
don't fall into a belief so you have to
understand what this does no matter what
information lies out there so I can't
look at information I can't ever I can't
I can't read books and that I get
polluted because that information's been
polluted somewhere or originally
wherever it came from and so in order to
keep the stuff pure and clean so it
comes to you pure and clean untampered
with so that's how candida works so when
the liver gets sluggish and breaks
down and gets weaker it's still your
hero your liver is still your hero you
got to love your liver you have to love
it but it's still your hero that's not
your thyroid that's not your thyroid
causing the symptoms that's not your
thyroid causing the constipation that's
not your thyroid causing brain fog
difficulty concentrating those are
poisons and
toxins those are poisons and toxins
coming from other things like for
instance brain fog that's that's a
symptom from Epstein bar that's a
symptoms that's a symptom from
neurotoxins floating around in the
bloodstream produced by a virus and the
liver has a lot of neurotoxins in it
from a virus like Epstein bar it just so
happens you may also have a thyroid
problem too eventually
and thyroid healing explains why because
the thyroid becomes a victim another
victim another Target for something like
Epstein bar but originally the the brain
fog is from pollutants from the liver
weakening from it having something going
on in it in
it and the difficulty
concentrating it's also you know heavy
metals oxidize and they're in the liver
they oxidize and they're they can be in
the brain too and oxidize and then
viruses such as the epine bar can feed
off of the heavy metals and create more
neurotoxins and then more brain fog but
then you go to the doctor they see also
something that's low on the numbers of
the thyroid and then boom you got a
thyroid diagnosis connecting to that
symptom and that's that's not Advanced
enough I got to tell you that's still
years behind that's still Antiquity
Antiquity compared to what we're we're
delivering to you guys I'm on saying
that because I'm boasting I'm saying
that because you got to have the right
info you don't want the wrong
info I can't tell you how many people
who met me along the way said if I only
had this information 20 years
ago where were you they said to me I
said oh I was giving this information 20
years ago I was giving that information
25 years ago even more even further I
was doing it I just didn't meet you you
had no way of knowing how to get to me
at that time but it was
there and when you when you have this
information you have knowledge you only
strengthen from it and you only heal
from
it
so
constipation happens is when all these
fats they don't break down good enough
all that protein doesn't break down good
enough and the protein won't break down
good enough because your hydrochloric
acid levels go down they weaken in the
stomach
hydrochloric acid weakens in the stomach
hydrochloric acid weakens in the
stomach then gastric juices
weaken gastric juices weaken gastric
juices weaken we get in trouble then
protein doesn't break down good and that
rots in the small intestinal tract feed
sibo which is strepa cacus sibo is not
just you if if you haven't heard my CBO
show sibo isn't just okay that's the
label that's what it is practitioners
don't know sibo is
mostly strep they don't know that strep
is the dominant bacteria that creates
sibo that's the one that's the one that
camps out that's the one that does the
most that's the that's the sibo
Creator
so you got rotting protein going down
into the small intestinal tract and into
the into the colon you got rotting
protein going down in there you got
rancid putrid fat going down so your B's
weak it's not breaking down the
fats your Hydrochloric acid's weak it's
not breaking down the
proteins you get a Feeding Frenzy it's
like being on a boat and throwing a
whole bunch of chum is that what it is
Chum
it's called Chum I think you throw a
whole bunch of chum in the
water buckets of it blood guts fish guts
you know fish heads just throw it in the
water and then all of a sudden you
know 20 minutes later you just see a fin
of a
shark now that's what it's like you know
when this stuff drops into the small
intestinal tract you get this Feeding
Frenzy and this Feeding Frenzy can go on
for years before you even get a sio
diagnosis it but you could be getting
constipation in between it and and out
of it you may get constipation just
later on not even
yet
and so as the bacteria is eating the
food then you been the new thing now
because I even think practitioners are
kind of forgetting about candida they
kind of know that there's holes in that
one so now they're just everybody's
getting a sibo
diagnosis so they're getting sibo
diagnosis you got a gut problem with
sibo you got a gut problem with sibo you
no you got a gut problem with stress
it's other bugs it's strap but mostly
strap eating eating and
eating you can't eat is just trying to
protect you trying to trying to save you
but this can cause this can cause
problems all of it can cause problems
meaning you get the constipation you
could get eventually inflamation from
strep growing outgrowing the
candida and then you get the
constipation then you get diagnosed with
IBS BS of
constipation bounce of constipation on
and off bloating gas go to another
doctor and they're like you got
irritable bowel syndrome what does that
mean I don't know maybe you got celiac
disease what does that mean oh
autoimmune that's wrong too it's not
autoimmune that's wrong Celiac isn't
your body destroying itself that's a
massive mistake you know there's a
chapter well no there's a set of
chapters in thyroid
healing and
you know when you when you read this set
of chapters I think it's
like I don't know 12 or 13 14 chapters
on the great mistakes and one of the
greatest mistakes is autoimmune blaming
the body for destroying itself
Celiac is now considered the body
destroying
itself body attacking itself body
attacking the colon body attacking
organs body attack you know the
intestinal tract so that's where celiac
disease headed and that's where down
that's where it is
now
um so it's not the body attacking itself
it's not at
all Celiac first of all gluten is a
trigger the reason why gluten is a
trigger is it it feeds streps it's one
of streps favorite foods chronic strep
where did you getron strip well if you
have it in your system at your childhood
and if you've taken any antibiotics in
your childhood or throughout your life
those antibiotics just you know
strengthen the strep up along the way
that's how it works for all of
us well that could lead to sibo that can
lead to just plain old symptoms IBS it
can lead to
Celiac and then when you get something
like Epstein bar in in the system and in
the liver slowing down the liver and
doing other things and the Celiac
symptoms can get worse because the liver
gets
worse the liver if the liver's sluggish
and slow the bile doesn't break down the
fats if your Hydrochloric acid's low the
proteins don't break down your Celiac
can get worse you eat one piece of white
bread your Celiac flares up because the
strep is flaring up meaning the strep is
getting a Feeding Frenzy you have a
piece of cheese over a neighbor's house
and then 3 Days Later your Celiac is
up it's not the body attacking itself
this is another great mistake great mist
stake so that's how Celiac works it's a
little touch about it
um hydrochloric acid isn't just one
blend science and research hasn't
discovered that it's a blend of seven
and you can have three out of that seven
below but one out of that seven be high
and that's all they can do they can get
a false reading oh you got good enough
hydrochloric acid because because they
don't know what they're looking for if
science and
research hasn't doesn't know something
exists they haven't developed a test to
find it so then it's not on the
radar that's how it works same thing
with the two undiscovered hormones
that's in the thyroid healing book those
two undiscovered hormones that I brought
to the table in that book for the first
time in history I think you're going to
really appreciate because when you read
about what these do it's unbelievable
what they do but science of research
doesn't know they exist because they
haven't they don't know what they're
looking for they have developed a test
that's not how
it's not science of research stumbles
across things they don't know what
they're ever looking for with anything
going all the way back that's how this
is just how it works and I've had
scientists tell me this tell me that
they just it's all about stumbling
across
things that's how it is it's if you're
lucky to stumble across
something that's that's how research and
science
works you know
and and so they haven't stumbled across
the other two hormones of thyroid has
they're too comfortable with thinking
they've already figured it out so
they're not even going to look in hopes
to
stumble so
um they haven't stumbled across the
seven blend of the hydrochloric
acid so that's that's what I'm trying to
say I don't want to tail off on tail off
to Never Never Never Land but what
happens is that with the hydrochloric
acid if you have a few of the different
blend that's
weakened it's not going to do its thing
it's first of all it's not going to kill
bugs the way it needs to kill bugs it's
not going to break down protein the way
it needs to break down protein so
protein's rot and they feed strep which
can get you any kind of diagnosis in the
end like IBS Celiac I mean it can get
you any kind overall it can get you a
Crohn's
diagnosis it could get you any kind of
diagnosis and that's how it works
colitis is a virus in the shingles
family it's one of the viruses in the
shingles family there's over 30
varieties that we brought to the table
if you heard that somewhere else now
that's only because it came from me
originally so you know so you're not
like oh wait I heard that no no it came
from here it's important to know
that so you just so you know hey this is
how it works with kius colitis is a
shingles virus that inflames the light
in the inner Linings of the colon and
even can move up a little higher than
that to the small intestinal tract and
you can get the ruptures you can get you
know blood vessels can rupture and you
can also have it mild with there's no
there really mild mild blood vessel
rupturing but that's the shingles virus
causing
that but well you know that's thrown
into autoimmune 2 the body attacking
itself that's not the body attacking
itself creating colitis and inflammation
there's a
pathogen the shingles virus creating
inflammation Celiac is not inflammation
created by the body attacking
itself the body's looking for a pathogen
the pathogen is INF flaming the lining
of the
colon that's how it works so important
to know so important to
know I mean you know if if someone I
mean
someone had the option you either know
the truth or you
don't well actually that's not even a
good example to use there's people that
don't want to hear the truth they don't
want to know the truth there there's
there's plenty of them so I I mean you
might even know somebody I mean so
that's not even a good way of putting it
all I know is I would want to know the
right information in my life and I do no
matter what um okay so so let's go back
to some of this so leaky gut let's go
back to leaky gut too
you know what happens is the liver
breaks down it's sluggish it's slow
nothing's working right the BS aren't
breaking down the fats hydrochloric acid
the seven blend that's undiscovered
isn't breaking down the protein properly
it's going in the gut it's
rotting and it's in there and what
creates is ammonia you got ammonia gas
ammonia gas is not leaky gut leaky gut
if someone had a leaky gut they'd be in
the hospital with 105 temperature and
sep sepsis starting they would actually
be in the
hospital what happens is when someone
gets a colonoscopy and they go and and
and they get a puncture which happens
all the time and they get a puncture you
know the nurse practitioner or whoever
it is or the doctor um is is or the you
know is running up the running up the
camera you know with the wire and
running up the camera and it all of a
sudden it gets snagged on a corner and
it
punctures as they're kind of driving it
up there and it happens all the time
honestly the mild punctures are like one
out of 10 more severe ones are you know
probably uh 1 out of 15 one out of 20
something like that and when you get
that
puncture you you think you're going to
go home with that after that test and
you may but you end up with this raging
fever unbelievable pain absess growing
in the colon and you're back in the
hospital I've known people after the
colon oopy I've known people that have
had to sit in the hospital for 6 months
after that baby just totally just 6
months Ley
gut here's an example if you get
diverticulosis and you got those
pockets and when those Pockets even leak
the slightest bit because they get so
bad the pockets get so bad and and and
they rupture these little pockets and
there's lots of strap and ecoli in these
little pockets and they rupture so bad
that when when even any anything gets on
the other side of that colon you got a
fever and you're in the
hospital there's no having leaky
gut be your condition unless you're
literally suffering and you're ending up
in the hospital with that fever and that
sickness so the leaky gut hole thing is
off totally off totally off I can't even
go I mean I can't even it's so I talked
about it in book
one but ammonia gas builds up with
everything I told you about how the
liver works and how nothing's breaking
down and how everything goes rancid and
and I told you that was telling you that
that's the ammonia gas builds off of
that rancidity that rancid those
rancid pieces of food rancid fat the
liver collects as much as if it it is as
it can out of the bloodstream and the
liver becomes fatty because it's trying
to save you in different
ways but it it's all going down into the
intestinal tract and there's a Feeding
Frenzy going on on top of it and and and
and gases are produced from The Feeding
Frenzy and not only that though the
rancid nature most importantly the
rancid nature of the food because of the
weak gut releases a gas that gas is
ammonia ammonia isn't leaky gut it has
ghostlike qualities it can go through a
bone ammonia can go through a
bone literally goes through your bones
it can pass through you and out of your
skin like a ghost walking through a
castle and going right through
Stone right through Stone so ammonia
just literally it can go through
everything it's not about just going
through the lining of the colon or the
intestinal tract guys it's not about
that and into the bloodstream and make
you sick and it doesn't necessarily make
you that sick when it even enters in the
bloodstream so it's called ammonia
permeability but what it does is it can
go through bones it can go through your
teeth it it'll just go through you just
right through you and out whatever part
of the skin it's going to go out that's
what this
does and and it's not good for you and
it's not healthy for
you but that's that's really as about as
extent of Le gut as you can go and it's
not leaky gut that's not leaky gut
ammonia permeability is not really leaky
gut at all because there's nothing
leaking out of your gut because ammonia
will will leak through anything it'll go
through anything in the body there's
nothing that can stop it not an organ
nothing it just goes through it has a
pass to go through everything in every
crevice and drive through every single
cell there is to get out of your
body well that's what it
does even when the liver tries to be
that that hero like it is and try to
collect it and gather it and and and and
suck it up it just goes right through it
again
so um so as far as the leaky gut thing
no no no no but there's
neurotoxins that are a different kind of
poison that get into the bloodstream
that are in the bloodstream and they get
in the bloodstream from the liver and
they account for so many symptoms that
are being bagged into thyroid it's
unbelievable right now everything's
being bagged into thyroid chronic
fatigue syndrome oh it's your thyroid
after all so that's what they're all
trying to do now that's what the experts
are trying to do now I can't tell you
how off this is it's not on at all it's
not in your favor it's not on it's not
real what happens is that when when you
now chronic fatigue syndrome gets thrown
into the thyroid problem or it'll go get
thrown into Lyme disease one or the
other and everybody with lime disase has
thyroid problems and now they're all
confused thinking okay maybe it's a
thyroid problem in the end now too
but it's not it's just chronic fatigue
your chronic fatigue or somebody's
chronic fatigue is is another symptom
that's Epstein bar creating that your
thyroid being off for not doing that
good it's a whole another symptom it's a
whole another thing going on it's
separate
separate it's not the thyroid creating
the
fatigue even
if I mean I know people missing their
thyroids they have no fatigue
I know people missing their
thyroids that are not even on
medication that don't have
fatigue so I mean there's so many holes
in the trendy theories that they're just
trying to all bag up right
now so anyway let's see if we can talk
about some more stuff puffy face puffy
eyes that's liver and lymphatic system
it's not
it's not you know just the thyroid
that's not the
thyroid now with hyperthyroid you can
get the bulging eyes that's different
than puffy eyes puffy puffy face puffy
eyes puffy face gets thrown into
hypothyroid no it's just that somebody
with hypothyroid also has a really
really toxic sluggish liver and
lymphatic system the that's how it
works oh what's the symptoms of hypo
thyroid oh puffy eyes um puffy face um
no no no
no it just so happens somebody has a
thyroid problem too but they also the
liver and lymphatic system is creating
puffy eyes puffy face because someone
else can have a thyroid problem all the
same with no puffy eyes puffy
face I mean honestly honestly you guys
you wouldn't I mean why isn't anybody
even focusing
out there
and figuring this out yet cuz they're
not going to we have to do it and you
have to be the expert and we have to do
it spirit said to me a long ago you have
to do it I said I don't want to do it
there says no you have to do it I picked
you I I go I don't want to do it I don't
I don't care when I was younger I was
like I don't care I just want to have
fun or do something
else and spirit says no no no you have
to care you're the one why am I the one
spirit said because you're pretty tough
I God no I'm not tough spirit says yeah
you're pretty tough you're going to
survive this you're going to fight for
it and survive it and I had to and it
was no fun so but we're here we're here
so anyway
um says puffy eyes puffy face how it
works bulging eyes for
hyperthyroid that's because fluid
retention goes right behind the
eyes that right there is is viral the
same virus that creates
hyperthyroidism um edema so edema edema
fluid retention that's getting us if if
a if a doctor can't find a kidney
condition or a heart condition they
associate that immediately with a
thyroid or hypothyroid edem is a liver
condition it's an undiagnosed liver
condition which is part of the gut part
of the guts well we're on gut health
today so that's that's the you know part
of the liver condition
um so we talked about IBS a little bit
but we can go into IBS a little bit more
IBS is just just basically liver that's
not functioning good an intestinal tract
that doesn't have a healthy environment
because it's got so much petrifying food
and and uh and putrifying fat and and
rotting protein so and basically from
poor digestion hydrochloric acid issues
and then things like strepa cacus can
really get out of control and that's
what IBS is um you can get swelling
inside the the colon lots of swelling it
can get inflamed um you can have
diarrhea and you can have constipation
diarrhea constipation you could have
parts of the colon elocal valve all that
be um you could have this an inflamed
seeum you can have the ilocal valve
being inflamed uh due to bacteria and
inflammation because of bacteria that's
uh IBS you can have even you could be
viral and have a lot of viral toxins
inside the intestinal tract that cause
ibs2 as well they'll probably just say
IBS is autoimmune down the road too
because they're just going to have to
point to everything being the body
destroying itself because they don't
know what's wrong with anybody and
that's what I talk about in thyroid
healing because they don't know what's
wrong with anybody so they're just going
to point it out to being it's it's
either your genes or your body's
attacking itself excuse me going to
clear my throat here so
um so that's what happens so
everything's going to go to autoimmune
no matter what even CBO I mean sibo
whatever even
IBS you know all of that's going to go
there all of that's going to go there
now you can have gastritis without
having a lot of gas I want you to know
this this is something I haven't talked
about um anywhere too um so anybody with
gastritis you may not get diagnosed with
gastritis but you can have gastritis it
depends on how toxic the gas is so you
can have bloating and pain and not move
any gas but yet it's there you can have
no bloating and sharp pains and it be
little tiny pockets of gas very little
but the pocket of gas is so
toxic that literally it hurts the nerves
so in your intestinal track and this is
a secret here too and your intestinal
tra you've got you know all your nerves
go to your intestinal tra it's like your
second brain it's kind of the second or
third brain in the body so all your
nerves go to the intestin inal
track and um basically your intestinal
tra is like a puppet with a whole bunch
of strings attached to it somebody kind
of dangling that you know dangling a
puppet making it dance okay so the
controller on top who's doing all that
is the
brain and the brain is is giving orders
nervous system is giving orders directly
to every single every single spot in the
intestinal tract and
colon and um
so what you know so what's happening
there what's happening there is that
there's so many nerves going on in there
that have even even slightly inflamed in
the colon or intestinal tract if
slightly inflamed if a little pocket of
gas that happens to be very toxic from
either you know some virus viruses or
toxic coming you know you know basically
the liver has so much poison in it or
you got the too much bacteria sibo
creating bacteria like the strepa cacus
going on and you get this little gas
bubble and that gas bubble's just moving
around and it hits hot spots it hits hot
nerves inflamed areas and when it hits a
hot nerve oh man you got cramp you got
pain you got a sharp pain you got all
these different things but you don't
even have to be releasing a lot of
gas in order to have this type of
gastritis so that's something to to uh
Chomp into that's some information there
I want to talk about insatiable hunger
this is interesting because insatable
hunger is being being thrown into
hyperthyroid it's like a definitive
symptom right now today of like
hyperthyroid insatable hunger now I know
this isn't a hyperthyroid
webinar but this is a gut health
webinar
so insatiable hunger is in the gut
health Arena even though it gets thrown
into a mental disorder it gets thrown
into a mental disease it gets thrown
into some kind of okay I love when the a
Theory comes out where it's like well no
there's a shut off switch in the brain
and you're not producing a a a chemical
that actually is supposed to do you know
supposed to shut down your hunger I love
when that that stuff happen starts to
happen being sarcastic now we know that
um but insatiable hunger gets totally
thrown into the basket of
hyperthyroidism and the irony is is is
there's more people insation hungry that
have
hypothyroidism the other irony is
there's just as many people is
that that are insatiably hungry that
aren't dealing with a thyroid problem at
all but like I said it's it's got to go
somewhere if nobody knows what's going
on with anybody if nobody knows what's
going on anybody with anybody out there
you got to throw you got to knock the
pull balls into one of the pockets so
you know so the whole thing with
insatable Hunger gets thrown into
hyperthyroid now ins satiable hunger is
a liver glucose deficiency so it's a
glycogen storage deficiency in the liver
so anybody who's just really hungry or a
little bit more hungry than somebody
else or too hungry people would think
you know they can't get enough carbs
they can't get enough anything they just
they're always hungry that is or if they
feel like they binge all the time you
know or they have to binge or something
then they go without food then they
binge and it just there's just always
this hunger that just takes over and
they they can't put down a piece of food
or something like that I mean whatever
it is that they talk about out there
whatever that that's that what that is
that's a glycogen glycogen is glucose
that stores up in a liver in a good
liver and meaning in a liver that's
really strong and healthy it stores up
and it sits in there so it stops ins
satiable
hunger but what happens is when our
liers weaken once again due to the
process like talk the better
earlier what happens you lose your
glucose Storage storage your glucose
storage goes away your glycogen storage
starts to dissolve in the liver so then
the message is the liver sending it out
of of insatiable hunger to try to get
carbs back
in and a lot of times people don't just
know how to do that they don't know how
to just eat some potatoes and some you
know fruits and other things like that
instead they're eating eting all kinds
of things which causes problem too
because if you're eating all kinds of
stuff the liver is too weak to kind of
break it all down the bile can't break
you know break the fat down hydrochloric
acid can't break down the protein and it
just becomes a hash Posh of different
things too much fat in the blood too
much fat in the blood stops sugars from
building up in the liver if you can't
build up sugar in the liver you can't
get your glycogen storage back up to par
inside the liver if you can't get your
glycogen storage back up the par inside
the liver then you get insatiable hunger
then you keep on eating more and more
Abominations of whatever you can
find but really what the liver wants is
low fat the liver wants lowfat low fat
and low protein and what the liver
really wants is lots of fruits lots of
vegetables lots of fruits sweet potatoes
winter squash things that have
carbohydrates but it doesn't want all
the
fat this way can break the food down
better with the bile salt and the
hydrochloric acid that's been weakened
and then the sugars can actually fill
the liver and all the fat in the blood
won't get in the way because you won't
be eating so much heavy
fat and that's what takes care of
insatiable
hunger so that's another secret
um well I mean we got so much to talk
about I'm just I'm just kind of I'm in a
place where do I want to go into be be
cautious about some things we do for the
intestinal tract do I want to go into
that I think I want to go into that a
little
bit okay sodium bicarbonate that's a
trend and everything what what I find
about that when we eat that try to get
that in the intestinal tract to make us
either alkaline or drop down candid
levels or whatever somebody just thinks
of each day um you don't want to do the
sodium
bicarbonate way too hard on the
intestinal tract way too hard on the
liver it's not a good thing to do so um
I would consider backing down on that if
you know someone doing it or whatever
just just you just don't want to do it
anymore um not good for the intestinal
tract lining not good for good bacteria
doesn't help good bacteria you don't
want to injure your good bacteria so
that's the whole thing so the whole you
know the whole I mean I've seen some
terrible things happen from sodium
bicarbonate I've seen people with the
worst Crohn's or the worst colitis
actually take that stuff and literally
end up in the hospital it's not not
smart I've seen even worse happen to
people who've taken dious Earth
particles um look the one thing about
picking on a product or picking on
something is you know I get people angry
I understand that but I also have to
watch your back um I'd stay away from
diet Tous Earth particles because it's
too harsh on the intestinal Linings and
it tends to saturate the Linings and not
leave meaning it leaves eventually it
just takes too long to leave so it
Smothers it suffocates good bacteria on
the lining it also creates malabsorption
too much dious Earth particles stop
absorption does it doesn't even allow
candida to absorb for you properly it
doesn't even allow your body to absorb
properly so dious Earth particles was a
really bad Trend in a really bad fad
it's just that what happens is you know
once these things get rolling there
ain't no stopp
[Laughter]
once these things get rolling there
ain't no stopping I don't know what else
to say out there you know um so I would
avoid diet tomas's Earth particles since
we're talking about gut health and um I
didn't want to forget that if you've
already taken it fine whatever just stop
taking it okay some people feel okay
with it some people you know I find that
women they're the ones that get the
sickest from it uh men who don't have
intestinal tract problems they can tend
to do it not really feel a difference
they don't know it's all good whatever
but um but if a guy has a really bad
intestinal tract problem that it will be
bad I've seen people get sick that way
guys get sick women get way sicker from
it um way sicker from it I've seen some
terrible things happen so just hold off
diet tomus Earth particles as a remedy
as a detoxification method or
remedy which leads me to Clays Clays
clays CL l a y right clay I think that's
how you spell clay clay isn't a good
thing either so Clay is way too harsh
way too abrasive like sandpaper on
intestinal Linings you don't want to
sandpaper your intestinal Linings when
your nervous system delivers messages
down to your intestinal tract and your
intestinal
tract is now doing the peristaltic
action it's it's trying to move that
clay and then Foods going down grabbing
onto that clay and rubbing it on the
sides of the intestinal tract rubbing it
on the sides of the intestinal tract so
you're getting clay like sandpaper fine
sandp paper you know there's something
called bonami bonami or something I
don't know if if you have to say it in a
fresh in a French way I think it's you
know I don't know if it's a French word
or whatever right bone bonami whatever I
don't know bone Amy that stuff in a can
right you know that's I take that stuff
and I I like that stuff don't eat it I'm
not talking about eating it I take the
can and I put it in the sink and I scrub
out the sink it's a fine fine fine
powder it's a fine
powder you know I'll throw it in the
toilet and I'll scrub out the toilet the
toilet toilet brush with that
stuff and it doesn't feel gritty it
doesn't feel like sandpaper at all feels
really smooth for some reason when you
put it in your fingers and you rub it
together it's like super smooth it's
like soft really soft but when I powder
it up in the kitchen sink or in the
bathroom sink and I take a sponge or I
take a cloth and I it just gets rid of
every stain and you could just you could
just scrub and wipe and you could get
rid of every stain even like water
stains that have copper in the pipes and
everything else you know all that all of
a sudden you're you got a sparkling
clean sink in stainless steel sink too
in the kitchen you can get it like
spotless clean
looking and yeah why they're really soft
and smooth and silky stuff because it's
it it acts of sandpaper once you apply
pressure so when you have Clay and even
dious Earth particles and it's on the
lining of the intestinal tract and
colon what happens is food will go
against it and rub it'll put pressure if
you eat a bigger meal more pressure more
pressure I'm not saying don't eat big
meals I mean whatever you eat meals that
you feel comfortable with more
pressure and it rubs rubs along the
sides of the colon in the intestinal
tract and it doesn't clean it it doesn't
clean it it's not what it's doing not
what the clay is
doing somebody's probably out there
saying yeah what about animals though
they eat clay and they stay healthy they
do that they're known to eat some clay
your intestinal track isn't built like a
deer's intestinal track I can tell you
that it's not built like a deer's int a
deer can Munch up the most impossible
things and the most toxic things in
swallow sticks and Twigs with toxic
alkaloids I mean I'm talking about real
toxic alkaloids make you sick I mean put
you in a hospital you ate all those
Twigs if you even if you even uh Juiced
those twigs and Juice those alkaloids
out of you know different Twigs from all
kinds of different levels of of of I
mean all different species of bushes
shrubs and and trees man you even drank
a an ounce of that juice you'd be in the
hospital the tannins in there which just
to just annihilate you meaning it
wouldn't kill you You' be so
sick
um even Maple Ser I mean even Maple
Water Maple Water that they boil away to
make maple syrup Maple
Water has so much Tan in it that if you
drink too much Maple Water you'll just
be like drooling you'll drool I I
remember I was actually I even did that
one time I I love Maple Water you can
only have a little bit of it this stuff
is medicinal Maple Water is different
than you know like maple syrup when they
boil it down to the sugars Maple Water
has a lot of tannning in it a lot of
tannin it's hidden in there they drink
it it's like wow that was the freshest
cleanest water I've ever consumed it was
like a miracle and it is when you drink
a little bit of Maple Water it's like a
miracle but let me have more Spirit like
try not to overdo it don't overdo it I'm
like no I'm I'm I'm with a friend we're
in the woods it's his maple it's his
Maple set up he's got it all set up he's
got the containers up against the
trees and you know we're Upstate and
he's you know he's doing it we're up
state in Maine and he's doing it and
we're so this is great and I'm like I'm
guzzling the stuff I'm like this is
incredible this reminds me of coconut
water when I'm drinking fresh coconut
water out of the coconut and and you
know and I'm drinking them and you I'm
drinking it and all of a sudden I'm like
oh crap
I didn't say crap I said the bad
word at when it happened I think I said
a couple of bad words I think I said I
said the other bad word too oh
bleep and you know and it was like I
feel those tannins uhoh overdid it and
spirit was like told you but when are
you going to learn you don't listen to
me sometimes I said yeah I know I'm
stubborn and you know and so it was the
tannins and that was just and that was
Maple Water and I was drooling I had the
drools for like three days until this
day when I think of maple water drinking
Maple Water my stomach turns and I feel
nauseous tannin can actually give you a
memory that connects to the nerves that
were affected by the
tannin so I like Maple Water I just
can't drink it and if someone does drink
it just drink a little and then have
another you know week later drink a
little or a couple days later drink a
little I believe in Maple Water so I'm
not anti- Maple Water I believe in it I
want I want people to try it just don't
drink a ton of that stuff don't drink a
case of that stuff or like I did a
gallon of that stuff at once too much
tannin at once I have a memory to it why
am I talking about the
tannins I'm talking about the tannins
because a
deer or any other animals a deer has a
different intestinal tract than us okay
it can eat things you couldn't believe
it can eat it can eat clay yeah it can
eat clay it can eat dirt it can eat clay
no problem it can eat clay it can eat
different varieties of Clays and
different at different
places on the
planet but it can do that for a reason
the intestinal tra is built entirely
different than ours in many ways and we
can't handle that CL and like I said the
bonami and the sink we can't we can't
handle that
clay so just giving you that as another
another another tidbit here that's what
I wanted to not forget I feel like that
after we explored so much with the gut
and everything else in the gut health
that I was going to forget that um any
any herble tea going on anybody got
something can I drink something now it's
we're already past an hour we still got
a ways to go and I'm going to have a sip
just bear with
me
so I could just keep my throat
moist so the liver's role is to create
ble to break down fats to thin them out
in the bloodstream so our heart doesn't
weaken so our heart isn't bombarded by
high
fat
but what we do is we end up getting in
trouble and we get our liver broken down
and it gets stagnant gets sluggish and
it gets problematic and we can't even
protect our heart diabetes diabetes is
going to get thrown into the thyroid
trap as well you know I guarantee you
that's going to head into the thyroid
trap diabetes it's going to be one of
these things
where where um it's going to be like
well you know what diabetics people with
type two diabetes develop develop a
thyroid problem so obviously it's the
thyroid that's it's all part of the
thyroid no it's it's not the diabetes
type two diabetes type two is a liver
condition that's a liver condition
that's a liver becoming
dysfunctional and losing its storage
losing its glucose losing its glyc and
storage not being able to break down
fats and then the fats building up
building up in the heart building up in
other places building up in the
bloodstream so it it's really kind of a
separate
issue what is
connected what is connected in general
with the thyroid and everything else the
thyroid is a is a symptom become
symptomatic mean part one of the things
that gets affected by not by anything
but something else what happens is when
we get all these different symptoms that
are liver related a lot of them we get
all these different symptoms that are
being thrown into the thyroid bag
tingles and numbness confusion brain fog
aches and pains all these different
things that are keep that keep on
getting thrown into the thyroid trap um
you know symptoms hot flashes uh thrown
into the thyroid trap um you know the
the list goes on I'm I'm forgetting
about a lot of symptoms I'm sure you
probably are thinking how come he's not
saying this symptom well it's probably
that symptom too um and uh so when it
gets thrown in there there is an
affiliation affiliation is most these
symptoms are created by a viral
condition by the Epstein bar an
underlying cause it just so happens the
Epstein bar if you've read book one the
Epstein bar gets into the thyroid
causing a thyroid problem too which is
one of these things but it's not the
reduction of the thyroid horm hormones
or the thyroid becoming problematic or
nodules on the thyroid that are causing
all these other symptoms that are
causing these problems and that's the
that's what we have to get across it's
important the thyroid you can get a
temperature fluctuation if a thyroid is
problematic that's a symptom from the
thyroid that is one of the symptoms from
the thyroid the thyroid has very few
symptoms when you have this is an
example I have people that don't have
thyroids or have th their thyroids have
been killed
off and they still kept all of their
other symptoms all of their other
symptoms there's people that just have
had hyper hypothyroid sorry
hypothyroidism Hashimoto they've gotten
their numbers better their Hashimoto
even backed down you know and and their
numbers got better they had hypothyroid
and their numbers got better and their
thyroid got better but yet all their
symptoms stayed all their symptoms
whatever they were tingles numbness
vertigo aches and pains your brain fog
confusion you name it I mean the list
goes on oh the weight gain if yeah
weight gain all of it but for some
reason if thyroid was back to normal the
doctors
felt because it wasn't the thyroid that
created those symptoms to begin
with so why am I even going here now in
this webinar because when it comes down
to the gut when it comes down to our gut
health and secrets of the gut health and
everything it's not the thyroid causing
the gut health problems and that's where
it's going next that's where we're
heading now into trendy misinformation
thyroid world as the books keep on
getting stamped out with
misinformation you know listen I
wouldn't have any right to say that at
all if if I wasn't giving the given the
gift that I was given and and that gift
is for you it wasn't for me I you know
and I know that I was told that and and
I was like Hey a gift this is gift for
me to have it's p this gift isn't for
you it's not for you okay this you're
you're you're going to help you're going
to help but it's not for you all right
and it's for you guys so that's why it's
important to know so you're going to
find that if you had a sibo diagnosis
you're eventually going to get thrown
into the thyroid thing with it you know
along the way I mean seriously and you'd
think well why would that be small in
small intestinal track you know you know
bacterial overgrowth
why would that get thrown into um into
thyroid it just it's it's going to it's
going to you know that's going to be
kind of thrown in Lecky gut's going to
get thrown into thyroid everything
everything gut related is going to get
thrown bloating cramps in the gut you
know anything going on in the gut is
going to get thrown into the thyroid and
that's that's where it's going so I
wanted to do a gut health show because
of this very reason um even Celiac is
going to get thrown in there
over
time so what can we do what can we do I
mean I can keep on going about the
Mysteries and the secrets and the truth
about our gut health and everything
which I hope you guys find
interesting but what can we do for it
and stuff you know the celery juice
thing many of you know maybe some of you
were new to this whole thing celery
juice is undiscovered mineral salt
subgroups that they can't find they just
sodium is not all sodium and research
science hasn't put you know hasn't put
50 million 100 million $200 million into
into analyzing celery or celery juice um
it hasn't done that it'll just keep on
putting those hundreds of millions into
jeans because jeans are great because
they're so interesting as heck everybody
believes in them and it's incredible to
use as a blame game for everybody it's
your fault your jeans are bad that's why
you got thyroid problems it's your jeans
it's always jeans jeans jeans jeans just
never fall for that it's one of the
great mistakes that wrote and thyroid he
you can read about that one and then I
think you're going to really like that
when you read that one you'll be like
okay now it makes sense more than I
could just tell you right now in our
time frame but but they're not going to
put $100 million into celery it's not
going to happen or a billion dollars
into celery and celery has all these
different subgroups of salts entirely
different undiscovered entirely
different those are the subgroups that
actually rebuild the seven blend to
rebuild your hydrochloric acid so yeah
do I sound like a broken record do your
celery juice I probably do but also I
find that people forget to do it anyway
so it's good I keep on telling tell
saying it you know
so okay so um do 4 ounces of celery
juice get the big stalks throw it
through a juicer go to a juice place
just get straight celery if you can't
stand it put a little apple in it if you
can't stand straight celery put a
cucumber in it I I'll deal with that I
could live with that but the more juice
the better your hydrochloric acid builds
up and you find a lot of your symptoms
can go away because once your
hydrochloric acid is build up your liver
gets a little stronger your liver which
is behind so many different gut health
symptoms and other symptoms once your
hydrochloric acid gets built up
stronger then protein doesn't rot and
that means whether you're a vegetarian
and you're eating soy protein I don't
really like soy protein let but I
understand if that's all you got is some
tofu I totally get it but or you're a
vean that's eating tons and tons of nuts
to try to get protein and nut Butters or
you're an you know a a whatever an
animal protein lover that you know loves
the high protein animal diet and no carb
diet and that's what you love or
something and you're doing lots of meat
and chicken and pork or whatever lamb or
whatever you're doing and eggs you know
the point is is you want that stuff to
break down better so it doesn't rot and
purify as it goes through the gut don't
do eggs eggs feed every bug in the
body and uh they just do I I I can't say
it enough eggs create so many gut health
problems I want to talk about this part
about gut health too by the way um with
regarding to to how gut the gut health
works with so many people with different
symptoms many people feel like they
can't digest anything and you you might
be one of them right you might be one of
them and um and you'll feel like you
can't digest but there's some things you
feel you can eat that you digest fine
it's not that you're digesting it fine
it's just that you don't feel it touch
nerves the nerves in the intestinal
tract sometimes get so IR irritable and
irritated especially if you have a lot
of neurotoxins if Epstein bar is inside
the liver or in the body or even inside
the thyroid which by the way um I
brought to the table for the first time
in history sepin bar sits inside is is
is the thyroid problem you're going to
read about it more in thyroid healing
than I even did in book one medical
medium um of course and and what happens
is if you got the Epstein bar in the
liver and it's feeding off of pollutants
solvents garbage poisons
toxins it's then releasing those poisons
and toxins into into your body okay into
your bloodstream into your blood stream
they get into the intestinal tract they
get into the bladder they cause nerve
sensitivities which can give you a sense
of citis too in your in your
bladder um they can these toxins build
up they get in the intestinal Linings
and they hit all the little nerves and
they make them sensitive you eat
something like you chew a celery stick
you feel like you won't digest it you
chew a cucumber you feel like you're not
going to digest anything you eat
something like some lettuce you're going
to feel like it hurts it doesn't digest
anything cuz what it's doing is it's
touching the Linings as it's going
through the intestinal tract and it's
hitting every single hot nerve along the
way including fruits that have berries
and berries that have seeds and so forth
it just it hits line hits the
lining and you may feel though that when
you eat an egg you feel like you
digested it perfectly and I understand
that if it feels good then I get it but
the reason why eggs don't touch the
Linings of the intestinal tract and the
colon they don't touch the Linings they
actually sit in the middle as like a
glue that just goes through it doesn't
trigger off nerves cuz it's not touching
anything that's why so many people are
like I can eat an egg but if I eat an
egg on some lettuce it's the lettuce I
can't digest the lettuce you're you can
digest the lettuce it's just that it
hurts if you have those one of the if
you're one of those people with a really
really really hyp sensitive gut issue
hyper sensitive intestinal track issue
it's going to
hurt they have to think you have to you
have to know that that that's why it's
doing it now avocado I noticed though I
can get avocado in people sometimes some
banana if it's ripe in the right way not
fully rip not too ripe overripe and not
under rpe and you know things like
winter squash can be a lot smoother for
people that are in that condition
they're really sensitive sometimes
potatoes can and avocados can there's
you know there's different foods
steaming vegetables till they're
literally they fall through a fork the
fork falls through it can also you know
kind of help but I get it and if you eat
too many things raw and crunchy and all
that it's going to touch it all but it
doesn't mean you're not digesting it
doesn't mean you're not digesting it but
when you drink the celery juice and the
cucumber juice you could do cucumber
juice too you it's like soothing it
starts to heal those Linings and heal
heal those nerves by getting rid of
those Epstein bar poisons out of the
liver and out of the intestinal lining
which eventually will make you less
sensitive on the
nerves so that's important what not to
eat don't eat dairy don't eat milk
cheese butter kefir yogurt if you can if
you have sibo if you have a gut problem
if you have Celiac if you have anything
going on with intestinal problems and
you might be like oh I already know that
I'm on this do diet this big diet it's a
low it's a low carb high protein diet
they already got that
down but did they have it down 35 years
ago when I was telling people no they
didn't trust me they
didn't and not only that it might have
that part down but you don't want to be
on high high protein which is high fat
ends up being high fat you don't want to
be on that with any kind of intestinal
tract problems even if some of your
symptoms AR rested you can still get the
putrification the sluggish liver and the
liver can get more sluggish over time
set you up for more type 2 diabetes like
pre-diabetes and blood sugar problems
down the road when you're older you want
to get more fruits and vegetables and
which is the next thing I want to talk
about is getting more fruits and
vegetables
in you want you can't be afraid of fruit
when it comes down to gut health so one
thing where I always get stoned where
people meaning they try to Stone me to
death over and and throw Rotten Tomatoes
at me and throw you know and throw
sticks and they get the pitchforks and
the shovels and the Torches and they
just you know and they chant and they
get angry because there's so much fruit
fear that developed and I've said this
before I'll have to say it again it only
started from one guy one guy that's
popular in natural alternative medicine
that didn't like
fruit he but he what he did like though
is to sell it he liked to sell it
packaged in little capsules so he can
make a ton of money off of everybody so
they wanted to dominate that market so
he didn't want people eating fruit but
he wanted them to buy their little you
know fruit capsules are little
antioxidant special little fruit
capsules to make some
cashola so so you know but spread the
word into basically a few different
modalities of medicine spread the world
in word in you know Oriental medicine
which I love spread the world word in um
um you know Eastern medicine different
varieties of Eastern medicine spread the
the word in acupuncture it's you know
you know that that variety of all
because Oriental medicine isn't just
acupuncture there's different there's
different like sectors of of Oriental
medicine it's got spread into that whole
area then it got spread into also
alternative Western
medicine um and it just it just got in
there like a virus stay away from fruit
causes problem causes harms causes harm
causes this causes cancer it's bad it's
sugar it's bad but what fruit does is it
clears out strepa cacus out of the
intestinal tract it can't feed strep it
clears out bad funguses not candida
candida lowers because of fruit yeah it
lowers because it's it's there's no need
for candida to raise and eat garbage
because there is no garbage fruit is a
natural healing
food so don't be afraid of fruit eat
more berries if berries are the only
thing you can eat eat more
berries one of the greatest healing
foods of all time for the intestinal
tract is the banana I'm going to be
straightforward another one of the
greatest foods all time of healing the
intestinal tract is is
papaya is
papaya two amazing Foods I've seen
people with the worst conditions in
testinal tract conditions eating papaya
and banana blending it together and
recovering from the most catastrophic
Crohn's catastrophic colitis other
health conditions that were um that were
intestinal tract and recovered meanwhile
they couldn't recover from just doing
eggs or proteins are just proteins and
no
carbs I've seen this over and over again
over the
years sure sure if you're really healthy
and you're just gaining a little weight
and you want to go on a high protein
diet low carb diet you want to exercise
two hours every day and you want to do
that and lose some weight and feel
better there's nothing wrong with that I
support it fine but remember your liver
still will need what it's going to need
so you don't get problems down the road
if you're somebody dealing with a health
condition that's gut related now you
want to incorporate a little bit more
fruit fruit but you can't put fruit on
top of a steak you can't put fruit on
top of a pile of nuts you can't put
fruit on top of a whole bunch of
tofu you you just got to you got to know
you know you got to know how to how to
do it you got to know how to do it so
you bring it in and if you are still
eating animal protein you have the
animal protein at the end of the day
maybe your last meal of the day so this
way you can do a little bit of a
smoothie in the morning maybe a smoothie
in the
afternoon um that's
important so you know you can totally do
anything like that gut health smoothies
I like the heavy metal detox smoothie
but any kind of smoothie banana
papaya you don't have to do green
smoothies if you don't want to if you
have a sensitive gut issue totally
sensitive gut gut issue completely like
you're just hyper sensitive and you
don't want to put a whole bunch of
greens inside of a
blender or some kind of fancy blendering
machine um I understand um just do
something gentle do maybe a little bit
of barleygrass juice powder do that in
papaya uh and banana a blender of papaya
and banana and just try to sip a little
of it get a little bit of this in you
um so that's that's you know that's okay
you know there's different things to
bring different ways to bring in a
little bit more fruit into the diet with
the gut health
issues but realize too that what you eat
may not affect your gut until days later
you may eat something and not realize
it's a causing a problem three days
later there's a delayed effect and then
whatever you ate that moment you thought
was the problem like for instance you
can eat a piece of fruit but if you
actually have something in you that's
moving through you and it finally gets
to that sensitive spot down there by the
ilocal valve and it gets to that second
sensitive spot down there and then it
hits that inflamed spot right when
you're eating an apple and the Apple
never even got down past the dadum yet
it never even got down out of your
stomach yet but yet the timing was right
where peristaltic action because you
were just eating per peristaltic action
just squeezed finally some food that you
had two days ago right down to your yo
sequel you're going to blame the
Apple that's another confusion that
happens all the time all the time so
then but you'll still eat that bad food
that you ate 3 days ago because you
don't think it caused a problem because
it it didn't get to that part in your
intestinal tract to cause that
problem yet that's another thing to be
concerned
about probiotics that's a big thing
everybody worries about and everything I
would try to grow something one time a
year any time a year whatever you can do
grow anything grow it in a pot inside
grow Sprouts because you get those
elevated biotics that nobody knows about
it's still a secret I put it in book one
I talked about it before in radio shows
and nobody still knows about it out
there it breaks my heart elevated
biotics is not a microorganism that's in
dirt okay those are weak they need to
hide in dirt elevated biotics sit on the
leaf they sit on the leaf like in the
garden they sit on the Tomato in the
garden they sit on things in the garden
they sit on an apple on the Apple Tree
they sit go to the Farm's market and
just get you know some organic apples
and I guarantee you they'll have the
elevated probiotics I mean not probiotic
the elevated biotic right on top of it
and you get that elevated biotic and
that produces B12 inside your intestinal
tract that's the elevated biotic that
saves your life you even have some of it
in you in your in your
elium you even have some in your alium
that you might have gotten from a
raspberry you picked walking on a trail
20 years ago way better than probiotics
can ever
be
so that's something you want to do in
your life you want to try to get out
pick a few berries go to an organic farm
that lets you go out there and you're
picking your pint of strawberries right
there and you eat one strawberry or
whatever it is do it next year if you
missed it this year maybe blueberry
season's out right now and you can go to
a a farm somewhere but you know it's
it's whatever you you can do like that
grow something in your garden grow
Sprouts inside the house grow some
different Sprouts fenig Greek sprouts
red clover Sprouts um you know grow you
know a little bit broccoli Sprouts kale
sprouts kale routs are amazing um pees
they'll have the the
bacteria these microorganisms that are
unstoppable they bypass the stomach
hydrochloric acid even no matter what
kind of hydrochloric acid you got built
all seven blend up the par it can't kill
these microorganisms and they go down
deep into the gut and they get our
health back in our gut kale Farmers
Market kale will have so much of this
this this microorganism on the leaf if
you eat one piece of this kale you can
help restore your gut to get it back to
where you need to start start stomping
on um stacus stomping on eoli stomping
on viruses inside the gut I mean
honestly that is one of the most
powerful secrets of all time that Spirit
blessed me
with so I can tell you and it's that
elevated biotic that's a
lifesaver and it saturates the intested
inal Linings and it sits in the Elum
where where it loves to stay cuz that's
where it loves to go and camp out mostly
but it goes all through the intestinal
tract sits in the helium and it creates
B12 the kind of B12 that stops
methylation problems methylation
problems are caused by Epstein bar
they're caused by Epstein bar creating
tons of toxins setting off the
methylation G mutation test how do I
know Spirit told me how do I have proof
because I can get people to reverse that
Gene by getting rid of their Epstein bar
and getting their toxins down so when
they get the test the doctor's like oh
wait a minute you you don't have a gene
mutation what happened what happened
what you never did to begin with you
never did to begin with so methylation
has a lot to do with these elevated
biotics on those kinds of foods so
that's another secret to getting
yourself better I've seen people do it
over and over again all since I was a
child all the way to
now back years and years and years ago
you walk into a pharmacy
and you say you got a probiotic they
wouldn't even know what one
was
and even even funnier than that tell
them about elevated biotics on top of a
Leafa kale that look like you're
insane you know the thing is is uh I
mean you go all the way back look for go
into a pharmacy back 253 30 years ago 25
years ago 20 years ago 15 years ago and
ask for golden
seal and they'll think you're like an
alien with like two
heads now they're the experts
everybody's an expert now
unbelievable but I want you a real
expert okay I want you real I want you
to take the expertise you do have and
some of the jewels and gems you did find
in some of the misinformation that's out
there because there's still some goodies
in it all you just got to pick and
choose you got to pick it like fruit on
a
tree you got to pick it like you know
you just got to pick through it hold on
to those pieces that you did learn from
some great people out there but take
these truths take this information tuck
it tuck it under your
arm okay and be be that real expert I'm
excited that you guys are here I covered
excuse me dry throat I
covered a lot
but I know there's other things to cover
and we're going to have to keep on doing
this stuff and doing this stuff okay so
listen some other tips okay probiotics
you can take a regular probiotic any
kind of probiotic you want you can take
the ones you know they're soil born
microorganisms you take other probiotics
um I'm okay with that I'm okay with that
of course they're not totally unhelpful
okay so there's a couple of them that I
do have on my website that I like I
think there's a couple there they're not
totally unhelpful they they they're they
can Aid in some ways and digestive
enzymes it's it's give or take some
people like them some people don't some
people say they give belly AEG some
people say they've helped them it's all
about trying it out and seeing what you
like I'm not against you know digestive
enzymes um it takes digestion believe it
or not to to actually you know break
down and digest an enzyme capsule but
they have helped some people and some
people they haven't so it's give or take
um so I'm totally for that too is as
some options um celery juice I fine is
the greatest secret weapon Spirits ever
created I mean or ever given me I've
ever seen aloe vera is another one so
fresh aloe vera you cut the leaf open
don't use the green part don't blend the
green part you cut the leaf open you
scoop out the gel you put it in your
blender add some water blend it make
yourself fresh alloy juice it's
incredible for your intestinal tract
lining and your and your gut your
health okay so that's another great
great one that I've I've talked about on
and off think about herbal teas very
important nettle Leaf teas an
anti-inflammatory for the intestinal
tract because it squatches down some of
the bacteria it's also has alkaloids
that are anti-inflammatory so nettle
leaf tea lemon bomb tea kills off strep
ausy coli C diff staff and even fste bar
virus lemon balb te for the intestinal
tract that's fine one more thing I think
I want to leave you with be cautious on
all the cleansings all on the intestinal
tract cleansings that are out there CLE
cleansers and cleansing programs and
everything else be cautious even if one
did you pretty good don't keep on doing
it over and over again just try to eat
more leafy greens try to get more leafy
greens and more fruits in your diet over
time it'll do more than than a 30-day
cleanse because the 30-day cleanses put
your adrenals under arrest they put they
put dur rest or they put them under
stress I mean they put the adrenals
under stress they put the LI this liver
does not like to be cleansed and purged
and pushed like that so it puts the
liver on under massive stress it puts
the kidneys under massive stress it puts
all those different programs I don't
care how fancy they are how many herbs
are involved how much maple syrup and
cayenne Pepper's involved how much
whatever's involved How much olive oil
is involved be careful with all those
flushes liver flushes the gallbladder
flushes the cleanses all the different
variety of cleanses I won't name them
all and be careful okay the body doesn't
like to be pushed that hard bring in
more leafy greens more fruits and
vegetables vegetables get the celery
juice in every day and get rid of the
foods that you normally eat that you
know you shouldn't be eating that we
talk about here spirit and I and at
Medical medium get rid of those Foods
because you can't keep on doing cleanses
every single year you're going to break
down adrenals you're not going to you're
not going to farewell from them in the
end you've got to find a rhythm keep the
bad foods out and do the longer term
thing for your gut health that's the
most important message I can give you
guys I love you and and I stand behind
you and uh spirit and I got your back
that's right spirit and I got your
back know that I care and uh I'm honored
truly honored you're here I can't even
tell you seriously I can't even tell you
you know when I got this gift when I was
four years old and I told you earlier
during this webinar that the gift was
given to me for you it was given to me
for you it's for you guys that's what
it's for and um just take advantage take
advantage take anything you can get from
it anything you can get from it okay I
love you take
care