may
concern the four plotters podcast
episodes at Medical Me podcast at Apple
podcast are back they were gone but they
are back which is a very exciting Moment
In Time those episodes garnered over a
million listens over a million
listens and they were suddenly taken
down a few few months ago not by us by
any means and now they're back if you
want to find out what happened go to my
telegram link is in the profile link is
in the description go to my telegram
account so you can find out what
happened some of you guys might have
noticed they were taken down and removed
and now they were back months later and
you can learn all about what happened
why and how to whom it made a concern on
any
level but they have like I said garnered
over a million listens and they are
jam-packed with information the plotter
shows the four plotter shows they are
back that's right there is some justice
all right so we're talking about
shingles oh we got another announcement
to make medical mean podcast at Apple
podcast the episode The
episode now I gotta watch out on Tik Tok
because it's a brand new episode medical
mem podcast at Apple podcast you guys a
brand new episode launched today
seriously this episode though you know
what I'm talking
about that right I can't say it on here
CU I will probably lose Tik Tok just
like just like I did remember Tik Tok
deleted my account a year and a half ago
or or so whatever and I had over almost
close to a million people on Tik Tok uh
in a whole bit and boom gone and then we
got the Tik Tok account back we had to
start out from scratch and then when I
talked about something the other day or
whatever it was weeks ago um they got
rid of the live option now that's back
so it's incredible but I got to watch
what I say so what I'm trying to tell
you is check out the medical Me podcast
brand new episode today today it's
launched and it's
about
[Music]
okay that's what it's about you listen
to it twice already crispy
perspective amazing all right you guys
but today listen today today okay those
are some of the announcements but today
we're talking about shingles shingles
shingles this is going to be good we're
going to cover some detailed information
it's critical for people who are
chronically my mysteriously suffering
from chronic illness if that made any
sense people are struggling out there
suffering with symptoms and may not
realize or don't realize or highly doubt
they realize that the shingles can be
behind why they are suffering why they
are struggling the shingles and I'm
talking about the shingles on a rooftop
talking about the shingles on somebody's
body or in their body without having a
rash and that's interesting because
we're going to cover that topic too
because medical research and science
without a study is just starting to talk
about shingles viruses with no rashes
present internal shingles that's
interesting because who right here
published almost a decade ago I was the
first to talk about that that shingles
variey is without rash is because of
spirit of
compassion exactly how would I ever know
that how would I ever find that out it
never existed anywhere published here
first medical research and science
almost a decade later are starting to
talk about it they don't have a study
where did they get the information I
wonder because millions of copies of the
medical medium book One have gone around
the globe and countless doctors are
using them and so forth all around the
globe right scientists and everything I
wonder where they got that non rashing
shingles thing that they don't have a
study for incredible so this is good so
let's cover some of this information I'm
excited to see you guys glad to be here
what's in front of me right now pray
tell pray tell what's in front of me I
got some eggs over here probably on IG
you can't see that Tik Tok can you guys
see some things too I got some eggs over
here watch out I will drop these give
them a spin whoa got to be really
careful there whoa got some eggs over
here in this section what's this
Sushi how many people are getting sushi
so I'm going to go out and get some
sushi hi I'm on my YouTube channel and
I've been doing all kinds of fashion and
everything else it's Fashion Week at
Coachella and I just went and got some
sushi everybody you said look look and
check it out it's right here and I Love
Sushi I have it every day Sushi we're
going to talk about why that might not
be a great idea when you're dealing with
shingles
also this plate won't come off I have it
taped on there I got some eggs right
here and some bacon and I got some
gluten toast toast that's gluten toast
how do you like that some gluten toast
right there and what is stick of butter
I got a stick of butter right there
interesting okay got some peino Romano
got some uh what else do we have some
other types of cheeses prevalon right
got some brie cheese right here you guys
the says I just finished listening to
the alcohol podcast did I just say
something thanks aw
amazing um Seno Studio says I love the
alcohol podcast
incredible it's really good isn't it did
you hear hear that guy in the middle of
the did you hear the guy in the middle
of the podcast what was wrong with that
guy did you hear that all right I got
some Bri over here I got a
cheeseburger a
cheeseburger double
cheeseburger and over here which you
can't see on IG which is also difficult
to lift up for the moment but it's a pan
with two eggs in it right
there there we go very interesting all
right it's mm school right so we're
talking about shingles you see I got a
bunch of different foods out there and I
also have some other props and so forth
like a bug prop right there which is the
shingles virus let's go into it a little
bit this is really interesting okay the
chicken poox myth whoa that they're
going to they're going to talk about
this later too so not only did they take
medical medium info on the non- rashing
shingles but I guarantee you mark my
words right now I don't care if it's a
100 years from now I don't care if it's
50 years 20 years from now I'm telling
you right now they're going to take this
right here this is next because they're
busted they're busted check this out
ready the chickenpox myth contrary to
the current beliefs of medical research
and science one way that you can't get
shingles is through
chickenpox your doctor May tell you that
if you've had chickenpox sooner or later
you'll get shingles you guys know this
do you guys know this like do you know
this information Med conventional
medical research and science or
alternative it's all the same now
they're both together they're in bed
together by the way sorry to say it but
they're they're in bed together okay
anyway contrary to the current beliefs
of medical research and science one way
that you can't get shingles is through
chickenpox did you hear what I just said
your doctor May tell you that if you've
had chickenpox sooner or later you'll
get
shingles they'll say sooner or later
you'll get shingles if you had
chickenpox you'll get shingles okay now
they're going to take this too I know
it's coming I know because a birdie in
my
ear named s so birdie and my ear is
telling me they're going to go with this
one next and it's coming it's kind of
exciting by the way biggest mistake they
made they say shingles is contagious
we're going to go into that part yet
with I can't wait this is not the case
the only thing chickenpox has in common
with shingles is that they're both
viruses in the herpes family that can
cause a rash what that means you guys
chickenpox isn't the shingles they're
not the same thing they've been feeding
that one that's a huge mistake by the
industry they've been feeding that huge
mistake to people for decades and
decades what a lame mistake me km says I
never had chickenpox and I have shingles
indeed you're right and and yeah that's
how it works because they're two
different bugs a major mistake in the
medical world two different bugs and
just like they made a mistake because
they didn't know about the non rashing
shingles until they took it from the
medical medium book just that mistake
alone here's the second mistake they're
going to have
to they're going to have to chalk up
they're going to have to cough up and
that second mistake is
coming chickenpox is an entirely
different species of herpes
virus from shingles entirely
different
chickenpox shingles or shingles
chickenpox shingles
chickenpox
exactly they essentially have nothing to
do with each other nothing to do with
each other yeah so they're going to take
that too coming up pretty soon
eventually you're going to see something
come up and it's going to be like we've
just discovered that chickenpox is not
the shingles they're two different
viruses but there there what it is is
they're going to be busted I have
delivered that information for decades
published it in here many years ago and
talked about it for years okay why are
we being told shingles is chickenpox
related when it's not why are we being
told that
this is a prime example of
misinformation that was accepted at one
point because it sounded like it made
sense it was a theory that sounded like
it made sense just like the autoimmune
theory that sounded like it made sense
where your body is attacking itself but
your body isn't attacking itself because
that's a theory that they never proved
they never witnessed an auto antibody
under a microscope attacking a gland or
a cell or an organ you guys
they never witnessed the immune system
attacking a gland or an organ it was
never witnessed it still isn't today
millions of people are walking into
their doctor's offices getting
autoimmune diagnosis and with not a
shred of proof that their body is turned
on them or their body has even gone
after a gland or an organ or tissue it
is made up made up BS by the
industry and everybody's just sucker it
into it and that's the world we live in
and if you know how the world works and
how corrupt the world is overall with
different different things realize it's
corrupt in everything and that's part of
it right there all in its own you guys
somebody just asked what book it is it's
a medical medium New Edition medical
medium book one New Edition it's an
incredible book talks about epscene bar
talks about the shingles talks about the
conditions and symptoms it creates Ms
fibromyalgia thyroid problems
hypothyroid all of it is in here this
thing's packed it's jam-packed with
protocols and in information that's
mindblowing okay this is prime example
of misinformation that was accepted at
one point because it sounded like it
made sense then was perpetuated to the
point where it's now ingrained we have
it ingrained in everybody's
Consciousness it's like very deep in
their skull in their brain that shingles
means chickenpox they're the same thing
once you had chickenpox you're going to
have shingles which is nonsense that's
not how it works not to mention that
medical research and science don't have
a lot of accountability when it comes to
viruses no they don't we know that
already just from
2020 they lack information and know very
little in this area the plague of sea
has shown this to be true we know what
I'm talking about the plague of sea okay
still till this day I'm not going to
mention that
word it's the best I can all right let's
go into it a little bit shingle
transmission and triggers as with as
with any virus in the herpes family
there are numerous ways to catch
shingles to catch it to transfer it you
can get it passed down from your
parents you can get it through a
transfusion of infected
blood you can get it through an exchange
of bodily fluids you can get the
shingles through and exchange of bodily
fluids very easily from a public
bathroom
from a handle on a carriage in the
grocery store you can get shingles
easily just see you now and even from
the blood from a chef's finger from the
knife chopping up your food in the
restaurants the biggest mistake they
made they say
shingles is
contagious if it's contagious then you
can straight up catch Jingles you don't
need
chickenpox huh
what wait a minute what did I just say
that's the most screwed up thing I've
ever heard come out of my
mouth I mean jeez looks like I'm getting
something going on there on tick so
yeah
so I can just tell you right now when
you think about this think about this
think about how crazy this is right
so if shingles is
contagious right
and then you can catch shingles from
someone else who has
shingles where's the chickenpox
part where does that go what happened
there with
chickenpox someone please tell
me I'm confused I'm scratching my head
on that
one think about this one is this not M
blowing right they say that you can only
get shingles from chickenpox so you have
to have chickenpox first and then it
soals goes dormant in the body and then
you get shingles later on in your 50s
and 60s when you're 50 years old when
you're 60 years old that's when you end
up getting chickenpox right that's what
we're told so this is kind of funny
because I'm thinking about this for a
minute because how does that work so if
someone has shingles and then you go
near them and they have shingles you
catch the shingles from them but you
don't catch
chickenpox how in
the
world does that work Bust It bust it
again once again bust it they didn't
think that went through when they told
everybody shingles is chickenpox all
these decades all these doctors were
told in medical school that chickenpox
is shingles never saw a shred of
evidence or proof I know I've talked to
doctors that have gone through medical
school no one's ever seen a petri dish
or or something under the glass the
looking glass of a scope that determines
what the difference is there or anything
about it so here you are you're told
that shingles is chickenpox you have to
catch chickenpox first or have
chickenpox and then it goes dormant and
then your shingles comes out like 50
years later how's it possible that you
can catch then shingles directly from
somebody who has shingles you should
then really technically catch chickenpox
everybody should be getting chickenpox
from somebody who has shingles and it
must start start off that way before it
becomes shingles 50 years from that huge
mistake bust it once again let's go into
this a little bit signs you could be
suffering from the onset of a shingles
infection include flu like fever and
chills feeling headaches or migraines
aches and pains burning pain itching
tingling and rash puls or blisters if
it's an actual rashing shingle if it's a
non- rashing shingle you're not going to
see it on your body you're not going to
see the
rash medical communities believe that
those last two symptoms red rash and PS
always accompany shingles in fact this
is merely the classic presentation of
one type only of the Zer virus so this
leads us into the next thing here okay
if medical research and science are now
saying because they took from medical
medium book one here they took the
information that there's more than one
varieties of shingle there they took the
information of that there's this non
rashing variety of shingle that sits
inside somebody and they call it
internal shingles
right they're really saying there's more
than one variety and that's the whole
point in this book I talk about how
there's more than one variety there's
over 30 varieties and even more and it's
climbing because of mutations because of
people Contracting them and spreading
them so the classic herpes Zer virus is
you get it across one side like on the
side here of the rib or somewhere in the
back right here or you get a strip of it
along your back or on your side or maybe
down here lower by your butt right and
you get the strip have anybody have you
guys ever had that right the classic
herpy Zer variety that's one right there
okay and that's one type if a patient
displays PS and blisters that look
different then the barcode style rash
and the blisters and pbls are in unusual
areas doctors often won't consider it
shingles at all but now they do now they
do 10 years ago when this book was was
okay put into
motion medical research and Science and
medical doctors only believed in the
classic variety of shingles where it was
just this one strip on you and it had to
be
textbook
now they're calling shingles in all
kinds of different shapes and sizes just
like identified in this book medical
media medium including internal shingles
which is non rashing pretty
amazing is this book available yet H he
says yes go to amazon.com us or wherever
you are and get it it's the new edition
it's medical medium New Edition you'll
see the little gold emblem right there
right that the publisher put there which
is millions of copies sold in the
medical medium book series so check it
out it's this one right here the new
edition
okay all right let's go into it a little
bit deeper we talked about transmission
it's easy to
catch if the medical
world in the medical world shingles
seems like an open and shut case you got
a patient with the textbook rash skin
pain on one side That's all
folks close the case close the door on
the case but it's changing now so so
let's go into some other different stuff
we're talking about classic shingles and
we're going to cut into some of these
other ones there are seven strains of
shingles that cause rashes you guys you
might be able to identify some of the
stuff happening in your life through
this right here while the resulting PS
are painful if they're in an easy to
spot location that the doctor Associates
with the standard variety of shingles
then they look like the classic
perversion doctors are accustomed to
seeing in medical school in a sense that
they can be a blessing it's that one
classic variety of herpes
Zer because the rash makes it more like
that your doctor will see and realize
what you have and that's helpful and
they won't call it idiopathic so they
won't say you just have this strange
rash we don't know what it
is okay however most shingles rashes may
be unidentifiable to the doctor because
of their location and pattern let's cut
into some of these all right we talked
about the classic shingles let's move on
upper body sh shingles let's hit that
one the rash appears from the chest
up that's that's a shingles variety
where the rash appears from chest up
okay on the upper chest shoulders or
neck but not on the arms this rash is
the closest in appearance to the most
common shingles variety so that's an
entirely different strain so when
anybody has shingles from chest up neck
top of shoulders chest up that's a
different variety of shingles
these are important to know if you've
been somebody that's your plagued with
trigeminal neuralgia and you got aches
and pains and you got all kinds of
different fatigue and other issues
constantly and nerve pain and you're
you're you're squeezing your teeth down
and crunching them up and breaking them
in the middle of the night you got to
wear a mouth guard all the time like all
this is good information that's one
variety here's another variety of
shingles both arm
shingles you can get them on both arms
okay rash appears EX exclusively on both
arms and on both
hands also the rash has an altered
pattern somewhat spotty with large and
small P sometimes spaced apart on arms
and hands that's a variety all on its
own that's not the chickenpox bug that's
not the chickenpox virus it's not that's
its own separate okay identity its own
separate virus by the way there's a
reason why I have all this food here
because I'm going to talk about how sh
Les loves these Foods we're going to go
into that a little bit here's one right
here one arm
shingles the rash appears on one arm
only it can be either arm but not both
arms it's one arm only so you get the
shingles rash on one arm and one arm
only okay this breakout also has an
altered pattern somewhat spotty with
large and small Pall spaced apart let's
hit another one head shingle
brutal people
commit life ending because of it I have
to not say that word or I'll probably
lose Tik Tock but people commit the end
of life if you know what I mean from
head shingles that's how bad head
shingles is for so many people where
they get the shingles on their head or
they get it somewhere in their mouth or
they just get it in their sinuses and
their head
face the yeah people don't want to live
when they have that happens all the time
out there it's really
sad the rash appears on the top and the
sides of the head including the face
also you can have this variety inside
the mouth on the tongue throat or
anywhere else in the
mouth
shingles can be really bad it can kill
someone it can it's life-threatening
there's different variety ities there's
like I'm reading here your classic
shingles other varieties of shingles but
somebody can have more than one variety
of shingles they can have two or three
varieties of shingles but can be
lifethreatening
that's how bad shingles can hurt and be
someone may have to be literally on
morphine prescribed by their doctor
because are the neurologist or so forth
because shingles can get so bad could be
on the face head it could be in the
mouth it could be on the tongue it could
be in the throat in the
throat which is
brutal it can be right in the tongue it
could be all in the mouth and it can be
on the hypoglossal nerves the cranial
nerves going through here it can be on
like the Ooa Factory nerve you got the
hypog glassa nerve you the facial nerve
you got it can be anywhere in these
nerves which is just really
brutal the resulting PS are tinier than
those of the above strains so it's
different than your regular herpes Zer
that's on the side of you
right and they sometimes have little
horns on top you can get a variety of
shingles in the mouth on the face on the
tongue that have
horns like
horns and they're just brutal so many
people have lived like this still doe
today they get it out there and they and
medical communities often misdiagnose
this type as a fungus that needs to be
treated with antifungal or steroid
cream
mistake major mistake which leads to
terrifying
stuff so when someone literally is
suffering and they have shingles in
their mouth and their throat and they're
in Untold Agony that no one can ever
understand because their nerves are so
lit up in their cranial area their
facial nerves are so lit up their their
hypoglossal nerve is literally so lit up
they got the shingles eating away at the
nerves and just ripping into their mouth
and then the medical communities believe
it's a fungus that needs to be treat it
with an antifungal or steroid cream dear
Lord dear
God I can't even
inset yep aaine over there on YouTube
says what about shingles in the back and
sciatic nerves indeed of course we're
going to talk about
that okay let's head into the next one
both leg
shingles rash appears on both legs one
leg two
leg rash appears on both legs but
nowhere else it has a different
appearance than standard shingles with
pbls that look almost like
constellations up in the sky right
there's the little dipper there's the
Big
Dipper I mean I've talked to people
throughout the the years throughout the
decades and doctors where it's like
there's constellations on them where
it's like the Little Dippers on their
leg the big dippers on their leg
Yeah
constellations th says over there on
YouTube my mother also had it on the
left side of her body and on her back
and she also had it lingering nerve pain
for about a year and a half it was quite
horrible for her can you imagine in your
mouth in your throat or on the head on
the ear with your throat and mouth how
bad that could be people get it all the
time out there it's devastating tragic
actually
tragic so the both leg shinkles shows up
like all these different pretty
constellations as if you're looking at
the stars up there
right okay go a little bit
vaginal area
shingles this is a very bad bad bad
variety of
shingles and it's its own strain and
it's brutal and it's caused a lot of
problems with women they suffered
greatly with
this and I've heard stories out there
and I've seen things and I've talked to
doctors and top Specialists throughout
the years and people have ended their
lives because of this variety of
shingles affecting only women this
strain causes a rash that appears
outside but near the V vagina between
the rectum and vagina or on Lower
buttocks or inside the crotch area The
Strain is especially notable because
doctors often misdiagnose it as sexually
transmitted herpes okay so there's a
shingles
variety that gets a misdiagnosis all the
time of sexually transmitted Herpes
Simplex 2 think about that right how
many women have this Jingles virus but
it's misconstrued and misdiagnosed as
herpes simplex 2o think about that
right that's that's devastating for a
lot of women but there are more women
getting diagnosed with this variety of
shingles which is not on the docket the
medical research and science dock it yet
remember this is all advanced
information and research and science
just took recently they just took the
non- rashing shingles part out of this
book but they're they're going to
they're going to get other pieces and
they're going to take other pieces out
of this book as well as we go as they go
along they don't care they're
Shameless so this strain is notable
because doctors often misdiagnose it as
a sexually transmitted herpes creating
unnecessary emotional pain for hundreds
of thousands of women globally it's a
shingles
variety that's between the vagina and
the rectum or other areas in the crotch
and so forth that is an ongoing
infection of shingles that just comes in
goes and gets diagnosed as herpes
simplex 2 by the
system the primary way to tell these
illnesses apart is that the strain of
the shingles virus we're talking about
causes substan IAL pain while genital
herpes herpes simplex virus 2 HSV 2 is
typically less painful this variety of
shingles virus is so
painful but doctors they're just like
well I know we think it's Simplex 2 but
it's so painful it's far more painful
than Simplex 2 this shingles virus I'm
talking about vaginal area shingles
virus is far more painful than Simplex 2
also this shingles virus creates puls
that are relatively spread out in the
genital area and lower buttocks while
hsv2 pules tend to Cluster within a
small
area so hsv2 Herpes Simplex 2 clusters
in a small
area and right and there you go and the
uh this variety of vaginal shingles
tends to spread out more
okay and that's a brutal variety of
shingles let's go into shingles
neurotoxin talk a little bit for a
couple of minutes shingles neurotoxin
talk all right one of the misconceptions
about shingles is that the virus is
lurking directly within the skin
rash that's never the case the virus
lies much deeper underneath the skin and
even inside the bloodstream and liver at
the very same time positioning itself
for the most effective inflammatory
possibility on your nervous system so
what this means
is that medical research resarch and
science thinks it's really at the right
by the P it's the P right they think
it's there but really it's positioned
deeper and even in the liver in other
place it's still contagious but it's
deeper in organs and in the
bloodstream however the virus releases a
unique mix of neurotoxin so the virus
releases a neurotoxin it eats food it
likes right it eats cheese
like nice right it eats cheese it loves
butter this is what it eats the shingles
viruses all eat
butter
butter they do so when someone's dealing
with chronic shingles and chronic
shingles and they're suffering in all
kinds of different ways don't even
realize it they don't even need a rash
the non- rashing variety and they're
suffering they're eating butter and
their viruses are staying alive cuz the
viruses are eating the butter they're
having a field day they love gluten
nobody knew
that hey W gluten has been around a long
time you're not the man that discovered
gluten no I'm not but s so is the one
that discovered that viruses such as
shingles and epine bar feed off of
gluten and nobody knew that nobody knew
that gluten fed anything in the medical
industry or the Alternative Health
industry nobody knew that gluten fed
things like bugs that's mm info I'm only
reminding people you'll see it out there
now cuz it's constantly poached and
never cited
okay another food right here right
cheese gluten right there okay this is
interesting so the sushi so the
sushi why should that do anything or why
should that be a problem such a healthy
food it's like real food so many
different influencers eat it all the
time I mean if you just look around and
you see influencers out there there
they're all like sushi out that's what
they do right it's every night but what
happens is viruses like epine bar and
shingles feed off the mercury in the
tuna they feed off the mercury in the
tuna that creates a really good
neurotoxin for viruses eventually
Landing somebody with a sickness at some
point because the viruses will get
stronger and stronger and stronger as
they're feeding off of more and more
Sushi which is the
tuna the
Mercury
okay the virus releases a unique mix of
neurotoxin and dermatoxin combined
here's the difference between an Epstein
bar I'll just use this for an Epstein
bar right now okay the difference with
an epine bar is it releases a neurotoxin
when it eats its favorite foods okay
like cheese it'll release a
neurotoxin but not necessarily A
dermatoxin so much it can can release a
dermatoxin but not all varieties of
epine bar release a dermatoxin just some
okay the difference
with
shingles is it will release a unique
blend of neuro and Derma that's the
difference right there with the
shingles and in these seven strains I'm
talking about the viral poison travels
outward to the periphal nerves and
lights you on fire and then you're on
fire suffering from
shingles all right let's hit shingles
without rashes for a little bit too okay
it's got so much to cover and a lot of
information good to see you guys coming
on here
great lots of fun stuff to talk about
and I'm also going to share the book
because everybody keeps on asking this
is medical medium book one New Edition
when you read this book you'll be mind
blown this this book speaks to the soul
of the person who's
suffering it speaks to the person who's
been the the underdog it speaks to the
person who has been misunderstood it
speaks to the person who has been living
with symptoms that maybe aren't visible
and they're suffering inside they're
tormented inside but their symptoms
aren't really exhibiting on the outside
so that people see and they're like you
look good you look great how are you
doing and you're like no I don't feel
good I got tightness of the chest I
don't feel good I'm tired all the time I
got brain fog I got like OCD and all
kinds of different problems now and I'm
not doing good and that's what this
speaks to because the information in
here is real information and answers to
why you're sick and then giving you
validation and answers to how to heal
does it get any better than that it's an
Incredible Book make sure you check it
out we're into shingles right now a
little bit and you guys just before we
move on to the non- rashing shingles
which I'm excited to talk talk about I
just want to say if you just got on here
okay check out medical medum podcast at
Apple podcast I put out a new episode
it's about drinking it's about drinking
I got to be careful my word choices here
it's about
drinking don't miss it and check out my
telegram please because the four platter
shows are back they were removed months
ago not by me I mentioned this earlier
and now they are back and you'll hear
why and how when you listen to the
telegram on on what happened okay let's
go into shingles without
rashes the eight non rashing strains
produce a neurotoxin and they hurt they
hurt so what people need to understand
is these non rashers really hurt bad
let's hit one right here neuralgic
shingles also known as diabetic
neuropathy does anybody have diabetic
neuropathy or does anybody have
neuropathy because I said this for years
that there were more people with
neuropathy than there were with diabetic
neuropathy just for the record right
there another thing that I think the
industry is now taken from this book I
think I saw it like a year ago out there
and there's diabetic neuropathy but
that's only some people with diabetic
neuropathy they're diabetics with
neuropathy all diabetic neuropathy is
you guys is a
diabetic with
neuropathy and then there's all these
other people that aren't diabetics and
they got
neuropathy there's more people with
neuropathy than there is with people di
that diabetics with neuropathy okay all
right just want to make sure that's
clear all right neuralgic shingles which
primary attacks the lower extremities
creating nerve pain like numbness
burning in in the legs burning in the
feet it's often called diabetic
neuropathy and misidentified as a
complication of diabetes this is a huge
medical myth that needs to be debunked
unless there's an obvious injury or
imped to the nerves the sensations a
patient is feeling is not
neuropathy it's something else it's the
shingles it's inflamed nerves because of
non rashing shingles I wanted to cover
that a little a bit if you know anybody
dealing with
neuropathy okay take this book to your
doctor and say is it the
shingles let's see p fiction says I get
neuropathy but I'm not
diabetic I I believe that because people
that's what happens there's so many more
people that are not diabetic that have
neuropathy there's so many more it's way
more than anybody can imagine actually
all right so I talking about about that
um okay this variety of shingles occurs
more often in patients without diabetes
than in patients with
diabetes so Sophie norstrom says what is
neuropathy it's a mysterious condition
medical research and science doesn't
quite understand entirely they just know
it as pain they just know it as nerve
pain they believe happening in the
legs primarily in the legs that's what
they've said all these years okay
let's go a little bit deeper in let's go
into this this variety of of um shingles
this is a non rashing we're a non
rashing varieties you guys here's one
maddening itch shingles so maddening
itch shingles okay like crazy just just
itchy you can't reach the itch you can't
reach it you can scratch all you want
but you can't you can't get in there you
can't reach it all
right this virus creat creates a
continually moving itch that can't be
scratched that's because the virus is
irritating nerves too far beneath the
skin to be reached with fingers that's
your
nerves it's like I'm itchy all the time
but I can't really touch it it you
almost touch it it almost feels good but
it's not enough you're not finding the
spots because the itch is deeper that's
what variety that is if the virus is
empowered by a weak immune system and or
by triggers stick of butter some gluten
some Mercury from some sushi some eggs
how about some eggs as well
right
and and other things that can easily
feed your shingles virus perfumes colog
air fresheners scented candles all the
fragrances all the stuff the detergents
the fabric softeners the uh whatever
just it keeps on going going going the
air fresheners in the cars right boob
boo boob
yeah it could all feed it and get that
one worse okay let's go to a a vaginal
shingles non rashing vaginal shingles
okay this virus affects only women it
goes deep into the inner vaginal walls
and inflames the nerves there okay it
also travels inside the bladder and
rectum to wreak additional Havoc
creating a burning so irritating it's
akin to torture that's vaginal shingles
a non- rashing
mysterious vaginal
shingles if a doctor doesn't dismiss it
as being all in your
head I can't tell you how many times I
heard that throughout the decades
doctors dismissing this variety of
vaginal shingles as being all in the
woman's
head because she or he can't find the
cause she or he will typically
misdiagnose it once again as a hormonal
imbalance and prescribe hormones to
treat it this is not an effective
treatment and can sometimes make the
situation work worse many women have
truly suffered from this variety of
vaginal
shingles okay and the medical industry
ignores it fancy that all right kitis
shingles boom non rashing
colitis you guys know anybody with
colitis anybody diagnosed the colitis at
all do you know somebody that might be
suffering with colitis if you guys are
having trouble on IG just go to YouTube
go to rumble um I'm on Tik Tok right now
if you guys are having trouble with IG
because I could see there's a lot of
trouble on IG
today okay medical communities don't
know that this virus is responsible for
almost all cases of colitis you can
watch me stream live live right now I'm
live right now at medicalmedium.com just
go to medical medium.com and watch this
okay Colitis symptoms include intestinal
pain blood in the stool weakness and
weight loss
colitis colitis has always been a
mystery illness and will continue to be
so until medical research reveals that
it's a variety of shingles colitis will
be a mysterious illness for years to
come unless medical research and science
says
uncle
and
literally chalks it
up and admits it's a variety of shingles
the only way they're going to do that is
if they poach and steal something else
from this book which will be
this medical research and science
believe colitis is an autoimmune
condition where the immune system is
attacking the lining of the
[Music]
colon oh my God
tired and and freaking
bored tired and freaking bored
man excuse
me I'm
just I'm going to take a nap I'm so ti
so so tired of the
medical research and science
believes colitis is in autoimmune
condition where the immune system is
attacking the lining of the colon with
no no evidence and no data and no
studies showing
it they believe it's just your body
attacking the inside lining of the colon
causing inflammation this belief means
that doctors typically try to treat
Colitis with immunosuppressive drugs
even worse antibiotics which make the
virus
stronger so that personal colitis
suffers
more steroids can put put the colitis in
remission but no one's addressing the
true nature of it which is the shingles
virus all
right okay guys arm and leg burning
shingles burning arms burning legs does
it ring a bell to anybody you know
burning
arms burning legs just just seeing it
sounds familiar boots McGee thank
you thank you this virus creates a hot
burning pain in your arms and legs hot
burning pain in your arms and legs can
do a dance hot burning pain in your arms
and legs we can do like a total CH
leading dance to that unlike the rash
based strains that attack arm or legs
with this strain the nerve inflammation
and Burning Sensations all take place
far below the skin so you can't pinpoint
or find relief your arms burn your legs
burn you can have just legs
sometimes arms but really sometimes it's
both and you can really suffer with that
and they'll never know 50 years from now
they might finally kind of come up with
maybe that was shingles all
along here's one right here okay mouth
shingles
TMJ trinal
neuralgia Bells py Bells py
okay the only way ever the medical
industry ever Associated Belle's paly in
any way to viral if it was ever going to
be shingles would it would have to be a
rashing
version a rashing version
okay now the medical industry has taken
the bell's paly information from medical
medium book one and now they're using
it okay this virus affects the gums or
the area of the jaw different area of
the jaw gum burning
gums right it's also responsible for
Bell's paly viral inflammation of
critical facial nerves fasal nerves
trigeminal neuralgia and TMJ disorders a
result of trigeminal nerve inflammation
and pain people don't realize I had so
many arguments with people in the health
movement throughout the years whether
they're like aw TMJ is the mandible
joint it's not it's it's it's not it's
when someone's joint is worn out and
it's not shingles I'd be like really
because their joint is inflamed that's
how it wore out their jaw was
inflamed hence it was in
pain
before the jaw fell apart on the person
they suffered in pain they were inflamed
in the jaw and then 20 years of it their
joint just started to fall apart yeah
you had to have the shingles there first
the shingles had to be there first and
then the TMJ the mandible joint stuff
had to happen
later it's really frustrating it's
frequent frequently mistaken for a
dental issue leading to unnecessary root
canals let's do one more ranal let's do
one more ranal we'll do another ranal oh
oh crap 10 root canals later we didn't
know something else is going on in there
but science of research hasn't figured
it out Juliet lellan says I think I have
non- rashing shingles causing TMJ right
jaw pain and pain in my right side of
the face and ear on and off for a few
years I can't seem to get rid of it and
currently it's worst it's worst post
dentist okay um all right you guys so I
was doing that with the Bells py and and
so
forth Okay frozen
shoulder who there got the frozen
shoulder frozen
shoulder frozen shoulder is brutal for
so many people I've seen people where
they're so Frozen so Frozen They're
disabled they're disabled like they're
they're literally in a
sling and they they get the massage they
get the they get work done on it they're
at the doctor every minute frozen
shoulder and it's brutal like it just
seized up viral frozen shoulder shingles
virus causes causes the frozen shoulder
it's another thing science research
actually took from the medical medium
book The
Original right there it's where the
information comes
from this virus aggravates the nerves in
the shoulder causing it to freeze up for
anywhere a month or a year you guys I've
seen people with frozen shoulder for a
year they've had it for a year or more
because the shingles virus was freezing
their shoulder this condition is often
misdiagnosed as infectious
btis oh it's just a case of btis what
the hell is btis that's not an answer
you can put any name you want on it Wing
itis veritis whatever you can call it
whatever you want you know and so the
thing is is what people don't realize
that's not an answer but shingles the
virus created the
btis see how it works medical me
information did this for people that's
why it was so mindblowing that's why
it's been a movement all around the
world I never had to do marketing I
never had to you know hire PR and
massive marketing firms like everybody's
doing right now in the health realm
including people in the medical Med
community that used to be in the medical
M community and their influencers and
they've taken all their followers and
ran and they're just they're hiring all
these marketing companies helping the
market everything never did that medical
medium information no we never did that
it was just about boom answers people
found it and told someone else that's
how it was done real answers people
found it and told somebody some somebody
else and what happens is that to know
this right btis isn't an answer but what
the medical medium information did was
it said no there is something CA causing
your
btis there's something causing your
frozen shoulder it's a shingles virus
but more than that protocol for the
shingles virus so you can heal faster or
heal when people can't heal right all
right here's one right here I don't like
this shingles I don't like the shingles
topic I don't like talking about the
shingles I find it very frustrating in
many ways one is because people have
been tortured to death by shinkles out
there in their health and throughout
their struggling and suffering shingles
has really done a lot of damage to
people and it breaks my heart so it's
it's a tough one for me it hits the
emotional Core Body on fire shingles I
do not like this variety I've seen
people out there they've gone through
this this one really really stinks okay
this virus makes every part of your body
feel like it's on fire like third degree
burns on fire Sim ously and relentlessly
it operates by finding a central
location by the ganglia deep in the
nervous system and releasing its
neurotoxin this is a variety of shingles
that gets into that different areas like
the cranial area and so forth cranial
nerves which spreads throughout the
whole body and inflames nerves
everywhere needless to say it creates a
great deal of anxiety and fear and these
challenging
emotions can prompt the adrenal glands
to produce an abundant amount of intense
adrenal
hormones there's shingles varieties like
this one that creates this problem where
the the adrenals are flooding like crazy
because the virus inflammation is
causing so much trouble in the nervous
system and the nerves are inflamed INF
flared up and the adrenals are just
exploding with adrenaline and that's
part of why this thing turns into a fear
monster there are shingles varieties
that are this
bad this in this is an ESP special
terrible shingles condition but
thankfully relatively rare keep in mind
that the body always has the ability to
heal even from this uncommon
variety it has the it has the ability to
heal when given the right tools and so
forth all right here's so I want to read
a little something here guys don't mind
healing shingles being stuck with any
kind of shingles is painful and
stressful whether you have a variety
that creates a rash or doesn't it can
can be maddening okay fortunately there
are simple yet powerful medical medium
protocols for this
condition Protocols are here for this
condition the goal is to knock the virus
back it's to knock the virus back okay
that's the goal into a dormant State
knocking the shingles virus back into a
dormant State kill off as much of it as
possible or kill it off all
together all
together okay
yes render it virtually harmless okay
all right you guys and there's this
thing is so packed there's even like
Healing Foods in here talking about what
to eat with the shingles there's a
shingles protocol right here with herbs
and the whole bit take it to your doctor
ask your doctor what's right for you
take the book to your doctor okay
there's a shingles protocol right there
and here's all the shingles and the
information listed in here it's in
medical
medium right
there okay all
important important
information you guys just just for the
record I am working on
a working on some type of situation
where I could do the first book signing
I've ever done I've never done a book
signing
like I've never had been in a situation
ever where I was sitting there I never
did a book signing for my publisher I
never did a book
signing like you know a real one so um
kind of a bucket list thing too all
right because people have been asking
asking me that forever they're like how
come you're like one of the only authors
or the only author that anybody really
can find that never did Even though
there's been all these books all these
years there's never been a book signing
but I'm trying to make it happen where
it's in person you bring your books you
know a lot of you guys got like three
four books some of you guys have one
some of you guys have like you know all
of them and you bring your books just
drop them right on the table in front of
me I'll sign them okay and um yeah and
say hi in the whole bit I'm working on a
location I'm working on a um you know
where I'm going to do this I'm probably
going to just do this in one place
so I'm not going to I'm not going to
travel around the world I can't right
now um I've been thwarted in so many
ways um from this last terrible year and
everything of all the false garbage and
everything else that has happened where
I'm so behind on everything but get on
my medical medium
newsletter if you can get on my medical
medium newsletter go to medical
medium.com or check out the newsletter
it's in the profile and and so forth in
the bio so you know so I can let you
know where I'm going to be and give you
enough leeway enough enough time okay
and I'm trying to work out something
where it's in a place Janette it might
be in La it might be an LA yeah so just
giving you the four warning you guys so
it's it's most likely going to be an LA
yep check out telegram
t.me slmed medium my telegram account
t.me slmed medium okay go on there I
just released some information today
about my four podcast episodes the
plotter episodes that are back now I
want you to know what happened cuz so
many people are like where did they go
what happened and then rumors were
spread around of why they were gone you
want to go and check out my telegram so
you can see that okay and get that
information and I release a new um
medical meem podcast episode one about
drinking fun fun fun new podcast episode
It's called alcohol the ghost of sugar
alcohol the ghost of sugar but yeah it's
going to be in La saw somebody else also
to say la so um I'm pretty sure that's
where it's going to be I hope that's not
uh I hope that's an okay thing for you
guys but I'm going to be there in person
I'm finding a place to do it where maybe
it could even work out where it's really
cool like something really cool along
with it all so I'm pumped about that and
I'll be in if you want to come up say hi
and I'll sign the
books anyway that's my dream that's my
dream okay trying to make it happen I'm
going to let you guys know when I know
more information soon a whole bit but
check out on medical medium book one New
Edition by far um the most incredible
book in the health scene ever because
the street cred and what it's done for
people and healed so many people
throughout the years and still is every
day okay all right you
guys um oh check out with check out heel
with Amber too check out her Instagram
page so heel h l with
wi Amber a m b r at heal with Amber um
she's putting out a lot of incredible
stuff and information um she's putting
out incredible truth and evidence and so
forth and um she's setting the record
straight um for anybody who's been hurt
by what's happened and any so many
people have been hurt we know because
people have contacted us we have
hundreds and hundreds actually who have
their healing was thed they've been
injured by it um we're building a whole
thing with it and it it's unbelievable
in the sense where they're going to be
heard it's really scary what happened um
in the last couple years with all the
false stories um and everything
perpetuated by people that obviously
tell false stories and we're going to um
yeah we're going to talk about that more
as we go along anyway so check out heal
with Amber you know follow her page and
so forth so you can get the you know
clear precise information about stuff
anyway guys you don't have an Instagram
you're on Facebook though well that's
cool you're on Facebook AR you guys um
I'll see you next time lots of love many
blessings have compassion for yourself
be easy on yourself okay if you're
dealing with these shingles viruses know
that your body can heal know that your
body can heal so many have done it
before you remember that and that's the
track record you want you want to know
other people
healed other people did it you can too
love you guys