What public authorities are learning is
that something's being sprayed out of
jets up in the sky above the states,
above towns and cities. And it's under
the guise of geoengineering.
Geoengineering is supposed to be
barerium, reflective metal. When dropped
out of the sky, it's supposed to reflect
sunlight, cool down the planet, stop
global warming. That's the goal anyway.
But that's not truth. That's not what's
really happening. It's way more
sinister. Geoengineering, the release of
dangerous chemicals out of planes every
single day are for other reasons. For
destructive reasons, for despicable evil
reasons, has nothing to do with saving
the planet. What they're doing and what
they're doing up in the sky and the
chemicals that they're dropping on
everybody is a crime. It's a crime on
humanity, an evil, evil one. And it
happens like clockwork every single
hour, every single day. Nobody knows
what it is that they're dropping on
people. We're not supposed to know
anything. And if anybody questions it,
it's a conspiracy theory. You got a
tinfoil hat or you're just a paranoid
crazy prepper. Let's just put it this
way. There are a lot of things flying in
the air that are spraying stuff on
everybody. Really simplifying it,
is falling out of the sky and evil
people are doing it.