I had sibo and gastritis after my mom
passed away 10 years ago after seeing
every doctor every nutritionist every GI
doctor and even getting fired from a few
doctors because they didn't know how to
help me they were all directing me into
the wrong path and steering me away from
fruits and vegetables and it wasn't
until my kidney started shutting down I
finally picked up the book and did
everything exactly how he said after
about a year everything just started
turning around got my life back and I
was able to eat Whole Foods and fruits
and vegetables curing my sibo and my
anxiety and my insomnia and my gastritis
and it's just you know been such a
struggle for 9 10 years up until that
point I am just so thankful for Anthony
Williams because I wouldn't be standing
here living the life with my two
children and my family if it wasn't for
Anthony Williams
[Music]