hello this is Anthony William medical
Medium you're listening to the medical
medium radio show where each week we
bring the most advanced healing
information that's even decades ahead of
what's out there now so we all have a
chance to heal and move forward who has
10 years to wait for answers for people
who really have been sick who haven't
been doing good have had a hard time who
have struggled it's everything 6 months
being sick is everything one month being
sick is everything all of these are
everything and you have to you know you
have to it's amazing what you you see
out there and how people think and
what's going on and they I've run into
people and they're like who cares what
do you mean looking for answers for 10
years who's looking for answers for 10
years and I'm like what are you kidding
me there's 250 million Americans in the
US I mean just literally here in the
states 250 million people even over that
now that have mystery symptoms
conditions illnesses chronic illness I
mean it's legit and the thing is and I'm
not even talking globally today we're
talking about detoxing we're talking
about detoxing okay the you know is
there right way to detox what's the
signs of detox what are the signs what
are the symptoms of detoxing are you
detoxing did you do a cleanse did you do
you know the whole bit so cleansing and
detoxing that's really the nature of
this show and that's what we're going to
be covering and I think you're going to
be quite surprised because there's there
is a lot to cover there is a lot to talk
about so I think you're going to be I
think you're going to be surprised
because so hang on for this show this is
going to be great let's get into it
let's start talking about it so there's
so many different cleanses and cleanses
cleans cleanse programs and you can get
by you can buy into so many different
things out there and um you guys
probably know I don't sell anything I
don't sell any cleansing programs this
is not a infomercial where you listen to
the podcast in the first 10 minutes is
selling all these products and you know
what I mean and I don't know if you guys
have picked up on that yet have you and
you're sitting there selling all these
products and all these programs
everybody is trying to get rich fast
right now that's it's crazy what's going
on and I'm not saying is anything wrong
with that people can do what they want I
mean I get it people try to survive but
the thing is is that we're we're talking
about people that are sick and we're
talking about people that you know
chronically ill and we're talking about
people that are not well so you know
it's it's resources are minimal for so
many people you know when we write the
medical medium book spirit and I and we
put the information in there and
spirit's information in there you know
you can get the book in in the library
you don't even have to buy it and you
can learn how to heal and use your
resources on a minimal level so that
when you do get things and have to get a
certain supplement or something to help
you it's going to help you it's not just
hey look you wake up one morning it's
like oh I I you know I trained in this
this weird school and now I'm going to
be like putting out a program and
selling all the stuff and next thing
know it's MLM or whatever it is it's not
like that and the point the reason why
I'm even talking about this is cuz with
cleanses now you'll see a lot of cleanse
programs cleanse things like you know
and you can buy into all these different
things and the thing is is are you
buying into the right thing some of them
have all these powdered herbs in there
just all this powdered stuff and
powdered shakes and powdered herbs and
powdered stuff and you know and people
they don't know if they're getting
symptoms of detox if they're not getting
symptoms of detox and all the leaders to
all these different programs all no no
you're detoxing you're detoxing oh no no
that's detox detox without even having
an idea that someone's a getting maybe a
reigniting a reignition of some kind of
illness or some kind of viral s the
thing is is this before someone even
detoxes it would be good to know what
the hell's going on and what's really
wrong with the person so that's the
whole thing too the one thing I don't
like I have to be honest is there's a
lot of a lot of different experts out
there offering cleansings and cleansing
cleansing cleansing programs or whatever
it is and detox programs and they're
offering these things okay and but they
don't even know why people are sick they
just think it's all gut health they just
think it's all gut they think oh it's
just all gut problems you're just toxic
and it's all gut problems and you have
to detox they have no idea that the
liver may have three or four viruses in
it like two Epstein bars one shingles
one hhv6 a cytoma virus and then and and
other stuff like that they have no clue
they have no clue that that um
autoimmune disease isn't the body
attacking itself they have no clue that
it's it's actually viruses inflaming
tissue they have no idea about the
medical medium information which is the
truth and why hundreds of thousands and
thousands and actually now in the course
it's Millions going on all these years
that have actually healed and are
getting better and they have no idea
that so they're just like you know buy
into the cleansing programs buy all
these supplements with alcohol in them
by all these powders you can get all I
mean there's so many different things
out there and I'm going into this right
now because it's it's madness out there
and for you to understand if you're
detoxing not detoxing what's the signs
what's the symptoms everything else you
have to know how it works out there
because that's a part of it cuz if
you're Downing all these powders and
taking all these alcohol supplements and
you're just doing juice only and you're
doing all that yeah you might be
cleansing a little bit you also might be
making yourself sick with with
irritating the crap out of the Linings
of the intestinal Linings with all these
man-made powders that think it's good
for you and just you know and you're
spending $2,000 for the program and
everything else I mean seriously it's
just something to think
about so so what you're going to get
here is you're going to get you're going
to get the truth and you're going to get
it straight right here about cleansing
and detoxing signs and symptoms and
everything else and how to kind of kind
of take care of yourself keep yourself
safe so you could do it so you can do
some cleansing now the thing is is that
every single program that takes away all
the different foods every every single
um program that takes away all the bad
foods processed foods I mean not all the
bad foods but take away at least the
processed foods and they take away the
processed foods you're automatically
cleansing
so if somebody if somebody believes in
this high protein diet and this you know
and it's a clean high protein diet it's
got some green juice in it it's got um
now they're bringing celery juice in
these things but they're not
contributing to the source where it came
from by the way which is medical medium
of course you guys know that with the
celery juice and because it went around
like wildfire and everybody's being
pushed into the band wag and everybody's
jumping on the TR and no one's saying
mean not not every just there there are
some experts out there now they're like
I their egos are so big they're not
going to contribute it to where The
Source came from it's unbelievable it
happens I mean you never thought it
would come to that to this day and I
thought everybody at least had like you
know a little bit more little bit more
something to them it's it's unbelievable
and so the deal is is this is if you go
on to this healthy paleo diet you go
into a healthy animal protein diet you
go on to something like that and you're
taking away processed foods because
you're used to eating donuts and cookies
you're going to be detoxing you're going
to be detoxing you are it's it's all the
different levels of detoxing and if if
you go on a plant-based diet and it's
just it's a say you go on a vegan
plant-based diet and it's all cooked
it's all cooked and even though it's
high fat all these diets are high fat
out there by the way you go on a the
vegan um plant-based diet and it's high
fat it's vegan it's all it's all cooked
food plus you know oils and sesame oil
and lots of tahini and nuts and seeds
and everything else you got all this
stuff going on in there and soy and soy
oil and whatever it is that could be in
it and you got that going on and it's
it's not process there's no processed
food in there the gluten gone the um
it's vegan there's no eggs and dairy
yeah you're going to be
detoxing but there's different levels of
detoxing there's different stages
there's different places somebody could
be for cleansing and detoxing and that's
kind of how it goes and and you know
it's it's it's
a there's a lot to cover is what we're
about to jump into there's a lot to
cover it it's uh it's diverse it's
complicated but we're going to going to
simplify it in the best terms and the
best way possible and where to start and
how to go so if you're someone and
you're on kind of a toxic diet you're
eating whatever you're eating bread
you're eating cookies you're eating
different things you're eating some
processed food not all processed food
but a little bit of processed food you
may think that you eat pretty healthy a
lot of people do that they'll be like I
eat pretty healthy I don't eat that bad
I only have a little bit of this a
little bit of that once in a while I
have a bit and then when you really ask
them you crack into it's like two weeks
ago they ate some M&M's you know two
weeks ago a week ago they had soda you
know what I mean and you you crack into
it it's like a candy bar you know what I
mean it's like you crack into it and
they they're already eaten some
different things and or they might be
like I did have a bagel and cream cheese
so I had a bagel and cream cheese and
they'll be like well I love the New York
style Bagels I had one you know last
week and when you really look into it
they're not eating that good and a lot
of people do this and it's all about
survival it's all about doing the thing
but then then they try to do well I had
a chicken salad so I had chicken on top
of a salad um I had that yesterday that
was healthy they say um for breakfast I
had some oatmeal or I didn't eat at all
I just had my coffee and then I had a
chicken salad for lunch for dinner I had
some salmon and you know but then then
another you know which is not at least
it's not that processed that wasn't that
processed although coffee is processed
even though that's not that processed
it's like so they might actually be like
you know eating a little bit better
feeling a little bit better just by
doing that exercising whatever it is but
it's all the different layers then if
you go a little bit further like take
away all of those things meaning take
away the bagel and cream cheese you have
take away you know the candy bar that
they had last week take away um some
kind of doughnut they ate take away
these different things take away some
kind of fried food they had at with a
friend going take away a slice of pizza
they had one weekend then detoxing
starts to happen if it's a month of wait
a minute I'm not going to have that
slice of pizza wait a minute I know I
listen I know you serious detoxers are
probably laughing right now saying okay
when is he going to get into the serious
stuff because we've already been doing
we've already been cleansing and
detoxing I've done a 30-day 30-day juice
fast he's got to start going into he's
what's he talking about I'm we're going
to get there we're going to get there
it's important for you to know all of it
so what happens if that person stops
that slice of pizza twice a month stops
that Bagel twice a
month detoxing happens that's how it
works and there's different levels of
detoxing and that's automatically a
person detoxing it's going to
automatically happen say everybody's
eating clean okay say everybody's eating
clean clean paleo diet no processed food
clean vegan diet no processed food clean
raw vegan diet no processed food of
course clean you know high protein diets
with different fancy names on it no
processed foods everybody's eating clean
right everybody's eating clean and think
about that but they're all eating high
fat so they're all eating clean and
they're all
detoxing better than they would if they
were eating High you know processed
foods I mean processed foods so they're
all detoxing a little bit they're all
detoxing but if they're all on high fat
they're not going to detox that much
they're not going to detox that much you
see where I'm getting I'm getting where
can you be on a diet where you're
detoxing all the time so you don't have
to do radical crazy detoxes and mess up
your body and make you sick and we're
going to go into that and then as you're
making yourself sick in your radical
detox you're being told by the experts
or the people who sold you the detox or
anything else that you're just detoxing
when really they didn't call the shots
right and your body's going into like a
cyto storm basically it's going into
it's going into a storm and you're and
and meanwhile you know what I mean you
could be definitely detoxing in that
30-day radical cleanse but you could
also be not doing yourself a favor and
when you come out on the other side you
could could be feeling better and some
people don't feel better when they come
out of the other side so just hang in
there we're getting we're going to get
there in this show so say you're on all
these clean diets but they're high fat
no processed high fat meaning it's if
it's the Paleo it's chicken and meat and
then you got that twice a day and then
on top of that you got nut Butters in
your smoothies in the morning and you
got something in your coffee some kind
of fat in your coffee or fat in whatever
your water which is ridiculous so you
got all that and then you got the you
know you got the vegans and they're
doing all just avocado they're doing nut
dressings with lots of nuts they're
doing nut and Seed crusts because you
know for little desserts and you put
fruit on top they're putting you know
it's all about nuts seeds some people
are all about oils in the vegan movement
some people are all about lots of
avocado and flax lots of flax going in
lots of flax seed all that flax seed oil
and all that so say you're doing that
okay the thing is is yeah you were
eating cleaner than if you were doing
the processed foods and all the gluten
and everything else you're eating
cleaner so you are detoxing to a certain
degree and people get some benefits
they're like whoa I switched to vegan
and I came out of a processed food diet
or a junky diet switched to vegan it's
really been helping me but you're still
on this high fat diet and you're not
going to cleanse that much past that
point you're going not going to detox
that much that past that point right
same thing with the belet paleo diet or
any kind of high fat high protein diet
you're getting out of the processed food
and you're going to be doing a little
bit better you're going to be exercising
you might lose a couple of pounds you
might gain it back later but you might
lose a couple of pounds you're
exercising and you're detoxing a little
you're feeling a little better you got
the junk out of your system you're not
going to get a you're not going to eat
pizza and but you're but you're detoxing
only to a point to a point there's so
many layers and steps and when people go
from from 100 to Ground Zero whatever it
is you call it and they miss out on all
the
steps they detox yes but they also can
make themselves sick sick with their
detoxing program and it becomes just a
whole Calamity a whole bunch of Calamity
and then after their cleanses they don't
even know how to eat right afterwards or
where they're going and they're back
into confusion
land and I'm going to talk about signs
and symptoms and all that when you're
doing that but and and and say for
detoxes that are intense we're going to
cover that it's early in the show we're
we're going to get there
so then the next level is lowering those
fats so you're on these clean diets
clean paleo clean high protein clean
vegan clean raw raw vegan clean
vegetarian whatever now you're lowering
the
fats and it's just like the like the
vegetarian the vegetarian that's saying
well I don't eat processed foods I don't
eat gluten I'm a vegetarian but I do eat
some fish I do eat some eggs well you
got you know high fat in the fish you
got high fat in the eggs got high fat in
the cheese and you start bringing that
down and and vegetarians still eat
avocado and they still eat lots of nuts
so you got high fats and all those and
you bring all that down same thing and
so the deal is when you bring the fats
down that's when the cleansing really
happens that's when the cleansing really
happens on a safe level on a safe
level no one knows what happens inside
their body you can be the greatest
expert be like okay here's all the
powders here's all the neutral pow
powders you me ingesting every day you
just mix this concoction up reminds me
of the old carpet baggers used to sell
or you know used to sell like a potion
in a bottle and then everybody would
come up and they be like here's your
potion right here this is it it'll make
you youthful it'll make you younger here
it is and you know people are lining up
and they're buying this bottle this
bottle of with this tonic that's just
probably like 90% alcohol 10% some like
one herb or something or who knows
what's in there dirt and it just it just
it just it reminds me of that you know
it's like no this was tested people have
tried it I you know a uh a pharmacy
actually helped me make this that's a
carpet bagers phes used to actually used
to they used to um make these tonics and
send guys out to sell them phes used to
and it used to be like one herb with
just filled with
alcohol and you know the thing is is
like yeah we're not that far off from
that believe it or not we're pound I
mean like production lines right now
cleansing powder cleansing this protein
powders all this and what you just fill
up your smoothies and whatever it is
you're cleansing you're detoxing who the
hell knows what come on I mean come on
like whatever I mean I'm saying you know
you got to know that that when you
really think about the irony or or when
you think about how ridiculous it is of
like okay you know what's happening in
the body you know what the liver's doing
you know what the kidneys are doing you
know what the intestinal tract's doing
and I love a lot of these guys they're
just like oh yeah know the intestinal
track's doing this oh how do you know
how do you really know it's amazing so
so when it comes down to Cleansing you
have to look at the liver and you have
to look at it with respect you have to
not push it you have to not M you have
to not push it over you can't you can't
you know what happens is it's like the
first time your child goes to a diving
board in a poll and and and and wants to
dive off and is standing there scared
and it's like somebody coming behind her
or him and just pushing her in in the
water and it's it's just you can't push
your liver to doing something you have
to give it a chance you have to work
with it gently and carefully cuz it will
push
back it will push back and you know and
that that can happen just like if you
push your son or your daughter off off
the diving board too early in life when
they're too young what they might push
back and they might not want to do it
again they might not want hot get on
that diving board ever again you just
don't even know so what happens is that
the liver doesn't like to be pushed hard
you got these people on on all these you
know regular you know standard American
diets of course and then you push them
into these radical cleanses you sell
them and then they waffle and they don't
even know how to eat afterwards they
just waffle in between they're still
binging on Pizza still binging on their
old their old patterns it's it's about
gradually getting someone to cleanse and
heal not pushing the liver overboard
because you don't know what's in
somebody's liver let me tell you
something with Liver Rescue I I talk
about it all in there whole section on
what's a big section on what's in
people's livers and it is vast it is
absolutely vast you want to dump all
that stuff out at once the liver will
suck it all back in it'll suck it all
back in you won't even get rid of it you
dump it all out of the the bloodstream
at once and the liver will bring it all
back in to save your kidneys lives to
save your kidneys Health to save your
kidneys so you so you you want to you
want to do this carefully you want to do
it good and easy and one way of doing it
is lowering your fats one way of doing
it to start with is getting on a clean
diet if it's animal protein you love and
that's the way you do it get on the
cleanest animal protein diet you can
make sure there's a lot of fruits and
vegetables in there that's right if
you're if you love The vegan movement
you love the vegan diet and you know
plant-based whether it's raw or just
whatever any kind of eating
um you you you go for that 100% you go
for that and you make sure of course
there's always going to be lots of
fruits and vegetables in there so that's
going to be in there but you you bring
the you go into these clean diets and
then you lower the fats you start
bringing them down before you do
cleanses you got to say how much F overt
fat did I have today well I had chicken
which is really high in fat I don't care
if it's the chicken breast I just so you
know I'm going to tell you right now one
of the one of the the Great Tricks I'm
going to give you the tricks of all the
movements I'm on not I'm not on one side
or the other I actually work for you
guys you got to remember that there's
belief systems in ideology are ingrained
in food so when you're animal protein
lovers there's there's a whole society
not saying you are cuz you're just
you're somebody that's eating but
there's a whole society out there that
wants to pumble and and and beat down
and literally Troll and break down the
vegans and the vegan movement and and
the vegans in the plant-based world and
the raw raw vegans and all all the vegan
world and they're also in a they're in a
tricky situation they they they have a
tough environment too so it's
everybody's like everybody's battling
each other and everybody's but the
vegans are The Underdogs these always
they've always been The Underdogs I'm
going to tell you right now because
there's this many vegans there's this
many vegans you see my hand I'm holding
my hand up you know like this many be
vegans like a grain of rice compared to
this many animal protein eaters so you
know there's and I'm going to go into
this for a little bit too it's where the
vegans get picked on a vegan is not
allowed to get sick there's even though
there's this many vegans when a vegan is
not allowed to get sick all the animal
protein people are allowed to get sick
they're all allowed to die in hospitals
because they're just there's millions
and millions and millions and millions
of them there's nothing wrong with it
it's just they're all all allowed to get
sick you're allowed to get sick eating
animal protein you're allowed to you
don't get you don't get you don't get
crushed by any any any propaganda or
anybody but if you're vegan and you just
get one cough you just cough
once you cough once and and and the
animal protein you know people not not
the PE you not like people you know that
are in I'm talking about the experts and
other people in the field that are all
part of the propaganda they'll just be
like they'll want to C oh my God that
vegan sick exactly there you go you're
you're sick because you're on Plants
you're sick because you're on Plants so
there's the you know the vegans have
been the
underdog it hasn't been easy for them
but the deal is the deal is on both
sides of the aisle okay you lower the
fats and then you start to cleanse and
you prepare your body how many overt
fats did I have I was back to chicken
chicken high in fat I don't care who
what where I don't care what scale you
can hop on the internet how much fat is
in 4 ounces of chicken breast and it'll
lie to you because those are government
standards of how much fat is in a piece
of chicken every Farm is different every
chicken is different one chicken could
have three times more fat than another
chicken how can a standard be written in
how can they have a standard that's
utterly
insane every tree is different some
trees I I've had nut trees in my life my
great-grandfather had nut trees I
remember one walnut tree being so high
in fat it was insane it was like eating
a buttered it was like eating a buttered
croissant and then his other walnut tree
a different variety and it was and um
you know a different variety it had
hardly any fat it was like it was like
it was like fat free almost and then
there was this other peacan tree he had
which was grown it was grown on a
different part of the farm little farm
there on his property and you I remember
my great-grandfather and that peacan
tree it was like it was really rich and
then at my aunt's house her peacan tree
same kind of pean grown on different
soil at her house it had it was like low
fat barely any fat probably cut in half
to a quarter how is it possible to just
say oh how much Fat's in nuts here put
it on dial it in the computer how much
Fat's in this chicken every single Farm
is a the chicken has a different racial
fat and some of them are so high in fat
it's insane I don't care if it's if it's
pasture Ray free range it could be be
really high in fat the same thing with
any kind of animal product so what
happens is that you got to bring your
animal products down a little bit and
you start to cleanse you don't have to
stop them all together if you love
animal protein and then if you're vegan
you got to bring your nuts and seeds
down you see listen I'm working for you
guys I'm not working for the belief
systems I'm working for you guys I'm
hoping anybody new who comes on the show
learns that for the first time that I'm
the only person out there that's working
for you working for you I'm not selling
you a cleanse I'm not selling you
something I'm not selling you whatever
get my book in the library I don't care
all million people listening right now
just go to the library it doesn't matter
to me just have the book so you can heal
and what happens is is that you know
when we lower these fats we start to
cleanse we start to heal we lower these
fats we start to cleanse we start to
heal and what happens is you cleanse you
detox you prepare your yourself your
body gets into a rhythm it finds a
rhythm so that you don't get sick when
you do something more radical and you'll
know if it's a detox or not do you see
where I'm going this is so important
this is where I'm heading then you can
see right there what's going on I'm
trying to teach you how to read your own
body and give you information in order
for you to do it so you can be in a good
place and that's what I'm trying to do
so you can be in a good place so you
could read your own body so when you
lower your fats and you're a plant-based
uh you know girl or guy and you're
plant-based and you start bringing down
nuts and seeds and the oils you start
bringing down the avocado and you get
more lower fat more lower fat when
you're animal protein you have your
chicken once a day you have you know a
little piece of uh grassed beef once a
day then once every other day same thing
with the plant plant-based have avocado
every other day bring in more fruits and
vegetables cuz guess what cleanses us
guess what cleanses us it's not chicken
and meat chicken and meat don't cleanse
us and I have nothing against chicken
us guess what walnuts don't cleanse us
guess what um olives don't cleanse us
and guess
what okay uh almonds
cashews macademia nuts don't cleanse us
olive oil doesn't cleanse us it doesn't
it doesn't allow Det toxin
cleansing it doesn't cheese doesn't
cleanse us grass-fed beef butter will
definitely not cleanse you that'll shut
down a cleanse in 10 seconds
flat that'll shut down sorry about
laughing there grass-fed beef butter I
mean grass-fed butter will literally
shut down a cleanse in 10 seconds you
want to shut down your cleanse you want
you want to stop cleansing eat butter
every day eat butter you put put butter
in your coffee if you want to never
cleanse ever
you can't know butter is not going to
let you cleanse I'm just saying okay so
the deal is is when you bring down these
fats you're cleansing on a deeper level
and you're getting your body ready ready
so when you buy into something and
hopefully you don't buy into something
that's not good like be cautious with
all the powders meaning buy into cleanse
like cleansing powder programs and and
all these powders you put in smoothies
or put in water and just be really
really cautious with all of that garbage
you'll find natural flavors in that
stuff and the ones you don't find
natural flavors there probably glutamic
acid naturally in there I mean there's
all kinds of things are thrown in there
it you just got to be careful and the
Linings of the gut and intestinal tract
small intestinal track the stomach
lining everything gets so irritated and
earable from all that all those powders
and garbage and even alcohol supplements
all going in there and in the name of
cleansing you and meanwhile it could
activates something it could activate
something it could activate a viral
issue by dropping down your immune
system and you could be sick throughout
your cleanse and detox and your
cleansing teacher will be like oh you're
just detoxing oh you're detoxing oh
you're that sick oh you're just detoxing
you can't move you're just laying around
in bed you're you're
detoxing you know and you know oh you
got a rash that popped out oh that
that's detoxing that's not cuz you just
ignited your shingles virus that's
detoxing I mean CU they don't know what
the hell's going on they don't I'm just
be honest I'm be I'm going to be
straight out I don't know what's going
on I know this seen it done this seen it
heard it all of it whatever been there
done that you name it seen it all seen
it all out there in the world that's
what I mean and so the thing is is that
all these years at Spirit and I it's
been about making sure you safely do
things so that when you do get a sign
that you can navigate you can actually
navigate and know where you're going you
know there's a ship captain that used to
be a client of mine years
ago and and he you know what he said to
me he said you know the thing about you
is you've been able to help me with my
health for one reason when no one else
could I said why what you you give me
the tools like what's on my ship so I
could see where I'm going so I can
navigate and know where I'm going you
give me the maps you give me the tools
you give me the compass you give me
everything so I can so I can you know so
I can float my boat and send and move
that ship so I could you know so I could
do what I need to do so I could work you
know and the thing is is that made a lot
of sense to me and he and he said to me
he said because I've been through all
these other things and I've tried these
different things and programs and
different concepts and they give you all
this stuff they tell you this but it's
but it's not really what's happening and
you lose all
navigation and the thing I want you guys
to be able to navigate I want you be
able to kind of be able to find your way
through and so when you lower the fats
it's the first first it's a first big
step after the second big step is no no
junk food you know no pizzas no cakes
cookies donuts no Bagels no gluten no
cheese no eggs and then you you drop you
know I don't care if you you know
whatever diet you're on high protein get
rid of the eggs and cheese vegetarian
get rid of the eggs and cheese vegans
already got the EGS and chees she's gone
and then then you're in a you're in a
better place and then you're doing the
low fat you're bringing the low fats
down and you're getting ready so if you
want to do a cleanse like the medical
medium 28-day
cleanse man you're actually already
there and you will be detoxing you will
be cleansing gently without making
yourself sick pushing your liver too far
the problem is when you do radical
cleansing and you jump into it your
liver
expels all this poison but it has to
bring it back up meaning like the liver
will take it back in it's not like the
liver the liver will literally bring it
back in to protect you and then it'll
learn it shouldn't let anything out
anymore so you'll be on like your 10th
day of a radical cleanse and your liver
is going to shut down it's going to be
like I already excreted poison was
pushed into it forced into excreting
poison now I have to absorb all that
poison back then I'm now going to shut
I'm going to shut up I'm going to shut
it down I'm going to I'm going to that's
it and your liver is just going to like
back off and you're on your 10th 11th
12th day and your liver's like I'm not
letting out a single poison because it's
just going to hurt the person cuz a
liver has that ability I talk about it
in Liver Rescue of how it
works and so if you if you haven't got a
copy of Liver Rescue yet go to the
library whatever go to the go to Amazon
get a copy of Liver Rescue whatever you
got to do but you you should have it and
here's here's the deal you could do some
radical cleansing but you got to get
yourself prepared and get yourself ready
and you have to get yourself to a place
where you're you're respecting your body
respecting your liver and you're not
dumping too much junk in there while
you're doing it juices are a great
cleansing tool all the crazy
powders that cleansing programs sell I
would
ignore because you'll never know if you
made yourself sick or if you're
cleansing or detoxing
you'll never know you'll never ever ever
ever know I'm telling you right now
especially in the powers have like 10
things in them 20 things in them 30
things in them you think you're going to
know what's making you sick versus
what's detoxing you and so forth or
irritating or scratching your lining or
whatever it is or overburdening
something you just you don't know so all
the
powders they all have to go when you're
actually doing doing something more
radical a cleanse like you're doing a
juice cleanse or something else they
have to go it's important to know and so
you know and another thing too if you're
going to do any kind of radical
cleansing don't run around doing errands
all day don't have life going about like
crazy and you're running around and
you're doing all these things and you
don't don't I wouldn't do that I would
try to like plan on some downtime some
chill time and if you can't do that I
understand but I would try to have some
downtime some chill
time and and and expect to keep it
lowkey even if it's a 10-day cleanse
5-day cleanse 5day juice cleanse
whatever 7 7-Day juice cleanser whatever
it is you got to back down your schedule
itinerary you have to just kind of like
okay let's just calm down let's not run
around like a mad person let's not try
to do all these things because that's
not good because your
detox will be different cuz your body
will know you're actually exhausting
itself so it will hold back its poisons
you'll actually hinder your detox if
you're doing too much while you're
detoxing while you're
detoxing so here's the deal like the
medical medium 20day 28 28 day cleanse
is one way you can cleanse safely and
you can do it longer term and sustain
yourself so you can
actually uh ignite healing okay that's
one way of doing it you know I have I
have a
90day 90-day thyroid okay thyroid detox
and thyroid cleans and heal and
everything else and thyroid healing but
Liver Rescue has a 9-day cleanse for the
liver and it's and it's going to involve
some food and it's going to involve some
juices and the thing is is that that's
the healthier ways of doing it it's
about working for your body you working
for your body treating your body with
kindness so let's talk about symptoms
and signs and everything
else okay so you went from processed
foods to eating clean you went to
processed foods and junk foods and pizza
and everything else and cheese and
butter and fried foods you went from
that to a clean paleo clean protein
clean vegan diet whatever it is you went
from that to there you might get a funny
taste in your
mouth you might get a very mild headache
at first you might start feeling
Sensations like that you might start
sleeping better you might start sleeping
worse these are all little signs then
they subside then when you start lower
your fats whether it's high protein um
you know high protein diet or the vegan
diet you start lowering your fats so
you're eating clean but you start
lowering your fats and bringing in more
leafy greens and a little bit more green
juice so you know that's what you're
doing now that's what people do now
that's not what people do but you lower
your fats that's what you need to do
that's what I mean you lower your fats
bring in more fruits more greens um more
juices and that's what you're doing and
you're going to get bad taste in your
mouth you're going to get a little
cranky you're going to get a little
irritable but you're also going to feel
a lot better you're going to have days
where you're feeling kind of like you've
taste some metal in your mouth you taste
funny you know it's different things
your eyes might be
tearing more you might you might have
sleep disturbances it could be up and
down left and right you might be
sleeping better you might be sleeping a
little worse for a night you might be
getting a little couple a little bit of
spasms in the body when you're sleeping
that your you know may be a leg cramp
here and there because toxins are being
released but you're going to be feeling
better and stronger and better if you're
eating enough too I mean if you're not
eating anything that's a whole another
story but these are all some symptoms so
you're going to just you know like that
you might actually when you lower your
fats your avocados nuts and seeds oils
you lower your chicken your meat down a
little notot you lower your fish fish
whatever it is and you lower all of that
all of a sudden you're going to
bathroom's going to be different you
might get a couple days of some loose
stools you might get a couple of days
where you get you might get one day of
diarrhea you might get one where it's
just it's runny stools just you might
get one day like that you might get a
little bloating for a moment little
bloating and cramping but you might be
experiencing all these things before you
even went into any of this but these are
some signs of of detox right here and
you can be experiencing it with problems
you have with your liver and your
intestinal tract before going into
cleanses and then you can experience the
same thing while you're
detoxing and so these are these are all
things but yet you're getting increased
energy you're feeling better you're
doing it right you're lowering your fats
and then you can take your fats out all
together you're 100% fat free 100% fat
free which
means if you're paleo if you're high
protein you're off animal protein for a
little while so now you're in like a
real cleanse you're in a real cleanse
now cuz you can't cleanse you can't
really cleanse deeper if you're on
chicken and meat I'm saying there's
nothing wrong with eating chicken or
meat but you're really you're not going
to be able to cleanse like really
cleanse on a deeper level and if you're
vegan you're not going to be able to
really cleanse at all on nuts and seeds
cuz the nuts and seeds are the chicken
and the meat you see how it works the
nut seeds are the chicken the meat the
fish that's how it is for the pale a
guy and so once you take out those fats
you're now cleansing on a deeper level
now you're fat free for a while you can
be fat free for a week you fat free for
2 weeks and guess what the 28 day
cleanse medical medium book one that's
fat free for 28 days and that's a
cleanse in fact it is a deep cleanse
that doesn't make you sick you can get
some symptoms little cleansing and
detoxing
symptoms and if you don't follow that
28-day cleanse you can just be fat free
and just bring bring in lots of fruits
and vegetables bring in lots of fruits
and
vegetables okay and juices but stay fat
free can even bring in some steamed
potatoes if you want and some steamed
winter squash and some steamed
vegetables and if you're raw vegan then
lots of fruits and leafy greens and some
juices and and what you do is you're now
no fat no overt fat and now you're
cleansing now you're cleansing if you
can handle that for a week if you can
handle that for 2 weeks if you can
handle that for 3 weeks or 4 weeks then
you can handle something more radical
you can actually handle an actual
cleanse in a deeper level there's
nothing worse than going from you know
point A to point Z literally by not you
know that's like shocking the body and
the reason why I'm going into this part
of the of this radio show is when you
shock the body you know what happens
your immune system drops and
crashes your immune system
crashes that's what happens and a lot of
people who have to cleanse and do things
and everything they're already sick they
already got Epstein bar they already got
aches and pains they already got tingles
and numbness they already got problems
bloating cramping in their gut Crohn's
colitis they already got IBS they
already got glut gluten problems
methylation issues and everything else
under under the sun they already have
all these things headaches migraines
balance issues weaknesses they already
have all
that and so when you're already having
all that and it's already viral and
everything else Under the Sun and you
from point A to point Z really quick and
you go radical you shock your body you
drop your immune system more and you can
get a reignition of the shingles
reignition of neck pain jaw pain
reignition of back pain reignition of
knee pain reignition of everything brain
fog you name it and be like wait a
minute and someone could be telling you
you're detoxing you're detoxing this is
what it is cuz someone didn't even know
what the heck is even wrong with you
didn't even know you're viral and you're
sick and you got things that you need to
heal you've been sick for years they
just think you're' just been toxic
there's a lot of detox Specialists are
like Oh no you're just toxic they don't
even know the person has a viral issue
they have no
idea and
so and they might be spouting out
viruses now because of what we did at
Medical medium of of teaching the world
right now about how viruses work and why
everybody's sick but but the thing is
you just don't even know and then you're
kind of like in cahoots you're you're
you're you're reignited your immune
system is is is locked down and shut
down you reignited a a viral issue now
you're trying to recoup from your your
healer is saying no you're detoxing
detoxing detoxing that happens all the
time but when you do it the right way
your immune system stays strong your
body won't be
shocked that's why like the 28 day
cleanse in medical medium book one or
90-day thy thyroid rehab or or the um or
The Liver Rescue The Liver Rescue 369
you guys will see the deal is is
that is the bottom line is
you got to treat your body with respects
it'll treat you back with respect
because you got to remember we're the
ones not entirely our fault but it's
part of our fault about dirtying up our
bodies it's partly our fault it's not
all of our fault the rest is the fact
that the world is that toxic and we come
into this world as a baby already with
toxins in our liver in our body it's has
nothing to do with us and then there's
this one little part that has something
to do with us but it's really not
entirely our fault just a fraction of it
is because you know we we kind we tend
to know better now in this day and age
not to eat that buttered croissant but
we do it anyway but it's really I get it
we're under stress we're under pressure
we're just we're in survival mode we
just eat what we need to eat and I get
it you know it's probably not you know
exactly but the thing is that we still
there's some responsibility that we have
is what I mean and we can't push we
can't push the liver in the other parts
of the body we got to be really careful
so when you do the fat free you're
already preparing yourself if you can do
fat free for 3 Days whether you're
somebody who's high protein Paley or
you're somebody who's vegan if you can
do fat free for 3 to 4 days what a great
place that puts you in incredible you'll
be detoxing and cleansing you might get
and if you're really toxic here's
another thing everybody's body is filled
with something different some people's
bodies are filled with tons of
pharmaceuticals some people's bodies are
filled with DDT DDT I swear to God I kid
you not DDT from literally their
forefathers I it's unbelievable some
people are filled with Mercury some
people are filled with all kinds of
different Metals it's unbelievable some
people have lots of virus a lot of
people everybody's got a viral issue
somewhere in there it was one or another
and we got all these different things
going on inside of us and some people
much more some people much less so
somebody doing fat free for seven days
it's a big deal for them cleanse and at
least keep their immune system strong
and cleanse and and thank God they don't
go radical someone else somebody else
you know who's really really yeah who's
who's not as toxic or more toxic
whatever it's going to have a different
thing they when they're doing the 7-Day
or 5day or 3-day low fat but it's a
great way to get you in a place to
protect you it's a great way it's a
great it's a great scale to kind of come
down on a cliff to come down carefully
on so you're protected you protect you
that's the whole point with cleanses so
you can do more radical if you can do
fat free whatever aisle you're on in
food belief system and bring in more
fruits and vegetables and do smoothies
and everything else you're going to be
in a lot better place you're cleansing
already and you're not going to kill
your immune system for a while you're
not going to drop it you're not going to
kick the crap out of your immune system
so that whatever's lurking doesn't come
raging out and that's the difference
between that's what happens is all these
detoxes out there and you get sick
people doing them and they go through
hell and back partly because they're
filled with all these irritating powders
in their gut but lining and it's just
making them absolutely miserable the
other part is it totally annihilates
their immune system so that their
viruses whatever made them sick for the
last 20 years is coming out full force
then when you start recovering from all
that it's like a relief cuz you've just
been through Hing back you may not even
be better than you were before you
started but you feel like you're
recovering thank God so then you're like
oh yeah I went through the biggest detox
of my life and you're just back to
square one from when you started I've
seen that happen guess what thousands of
times over the years and you don't want
it to happen that way you want to know
if you're really sick if you really got
sick in your detox you want to know it's
a real detox
happening so that means you do the low
fat for a while or you do the 28 day
cleanse and if you want to go to
something more radical and you want to
do juices only all day
long and you can you do juices on a
juice fast we're doing juice and water
every day juice or lemon water and then
juices cucumber juices celery juices
other green juices and you want to do
that if you get really sick that is your
body cleansing Full Throttle full
force if you don't you're Pro you're not
going to probably also get unless you're
really toxic is what I'm saying cuz the
ma majority of people that aren't that
toxic like well you know it depends
there's I mean people are really sick
and toxic there's no question so be like
half and half you get 50% people that
are only like certain toxic level and if
they're cleansing like that doing the
juices and everything like that and you
nav you know they're just going to be
like oh my God yeah I know I feel it I
feel tired that's what they'll get I
feel
tired and then you get these other
people that are so toxic they'll just
like I feel sick I just oh my God I
can't function I got to lay down I got
to just rest all that poison coming
out but at least you prepared yourself
and got you in in in the right way for
detoxing and cleansing unless what
people don't realize you got a fever
10034 someone's saying you're detoxing
or am I detoxing cuz I had a smoothie
and a celery juice the fever is because
you got the flu people catch it all the
time and I mean they they catch a flu
they catch what what happens or a sty
you can catch really easily or you
picked up you picked up food poisoning
because you went and ate somewhere at
some restaurant and you blame the detox
un like you're you're vomiting your
diarrhea that's not that's not possible
for a smoothie that's not possible for
gentle detoxing and everything else so
let's just cover some key points avoid
cleansing programs that sell you
thousands of dollars stuff and sell you
lots of powders and powders and powders
and whatever and even including alcohol
supplements avoid that avoid
it you want to do a cleanse you want to
do a safe cleanse cleanse your liver and
everything else and experience what
detox symptoms really are safely are
without killing your immune system and
knocking things down and everything like
that go fat free go over it fat free
just just to be leafy greens and fruit
on top of your leafy greens and and do
the you know heavy metal detox smoothie
and and just or do a smoothie you like
or whatever it is you don't even have to
do my stuff I don't sell anything I'm
just talking about my directions you
don't even have to do my directions you
don't even have to do my 28 day cleanse
from medical medium book one you don't
even have to do you don't even have to
do my heavy metal detox smoothie if you
don't want to you don't have to do my
celery juice if you don't want to okay I
don't sell celery juice but it's since
I'm you know I'm the spirit and I
brought celery juice to everybody that's
what I mean so it's like you can do you
can do the you don't have to do
those if you want do your own green
juice do your own smoothie do your own
salats do your own steam veggies with no
overt fats get yourself cleansing every
day and experience what the symptoms are
that are really detoxing cuz that kind
of cleanse is not going to make you
viral like a virus come out or make some
bacteria go wild when when the detox
expert thinks that that back that that
you know that you're just experiencing
detox
no you
know so anyway as far as other radical
cleansing if you're doing water fasting
whatever you jump yourself into just
don't try not to run around keep busy
try not to do this just kind of like
stay at home read you know watch watch
you know videos on your computer just
you know do things like that keep it
chill if you do any water
fasting um if you do anything like that
you do any cleansing like on that level
but going from high processed or or high
clean high fat diet right to radical
cleansing you're not going to be able to
navigate what you're really doing with
your detox especially if there are
products someone's telling you you have
to ingest during the course of that and
if they're not telling you to do that
and you're just going from point you
know point A to point Z like that and
you're experiencing detox yeah you're
going to be detoxing without a doubt but
you're not going to really be able to
navigate through it you should come down
come down carefully like I said come
down carefully and safely you know get
out of the bad foods to begin with
processed foods get out of dairy
products get out of eggs get out of
cheese get out of all that get out of
you know gluten of course and bread and
bad grains the bad ones get out of all
that come down the
ladder and then when you're sitting here
whether you're in your high protein land
or in your high high you know when your
vegan land come down on the overt fats
bring them down lower the chicken lower
the meat lower the nuts lower the oils
and avocado lower that down for both you
guys on both sides you know that that
people that love this people that love
that bring it down and then you want to
cleanse go over it fat free for the
Paleo and high protein people that means
Animal product free for a while doesn't
mean you can't go back to that it means
animal protein free for the for the
vegans and a plant-based and the raw PL
raw vegans it means no avocados for a
while sorry no cashew no cashew cream no
cashew stuff no no almonds all day long
no you know no walnuts no handfuls of
nuts no anything just bring you bring
get rid of all that bringing in fruits
and vegetables and you bring in more
juices I prefer celery juice because
you're at least going to be taking care
of your liver and and your brain and
everything else and I prefer the heavy
metal detox smoothie this way you're
capturing all heavy metals in case
something starts to detox so that's what
I prefer I'm saying if you want to do it
the right way and include you know
bringing out those overt fats and you're
bringing that down bringing it down and
then you want to do something more
radical that you want to buy into
somebody else's plan or you want to buy
into something like that or you want to
go search on the internet and you find
this other detox thing and you want to
do something like that at least you're
actually going to be safer because
medical medium got you safer in a safer
place in a better place prepared for it
so you might be able to navigate better
but but stay away from them you know to
too much of the crazy stuff and some of
you might might you know do love juice
fast fasting periodically well you
should be doing it this way before you
go into your juice fasting whatever that
is that you that you're buying into or
you found or someone else is teaching
you how to do make sure you do this
stuff before you do
that so all of this is
important so what happens is when people
get pushed into cleanses and stuff they
get confused because couple things could
happen their immune system dropped they
reignited total sickness that they've
already had for 10 20 years and they're
being told they're just detoxing
okay that happens a lot seeing it over
and over and over again and what I mean
that's somebody curled up in agony pain
feeling sick rashes all this other stuff
and then you get people you know that
that you know they they don't have that
going on and they're just doing all
these Powers all this stuff all these
protein pows all the real cleansing
powders whatever and their just guts are
sick I've seen people like their guts
are sick because all that powder is like
literally scratching the Linings and
inflaming the Linings and it's not good
for them at all and you see those people
and they're on the toilet and they're
just like on the toilet and they're like
I think I saw a worm they're on the
toilet I think I saw something I think I
saw this and that and you know there's a
whole bunch of people that do that and
and the detox Specialists are like oh
you're detoxing you're on all these
you're on all these things you're just
you know what I mean it's it's it's it's
madness out there be
careful you can do it a different way
you can do it a way that the body you
could res respect your body so your body
can respect you so that if you do
something like I'm going to do a juice
I'm going to do a juice cleanse a
smoothie cleanse just smoothies clean
smoothies where it's just like it's just
fruits and some greens clean smoothies
and you're doing that for a week you're
doing fruit and and greens and your body
won't go into shock raw vegans are
probably happy hearing that right now
raw vegans that are listening to me
right now they're probably like totally
they're totally happy about that yeah
because right there you you won't shock
your body especially if you've already
come down with the overt fats for
anybody for a Paleo high protein person
you need to be you just knock out the
fats which is the animal proteins for a
little while if you want to do a cleanse
and do just just do
smoothies just do smoothies not with all
garbage in them don't do that wrong do
smoothies where it's just fruit and
greens do that for a week if you want to
do a a you know a fat-free cleanse
there's there's different ways you could
do it where you won't shock your immune
system you won't ignite a sickness and
you can navigate the real detox and know
what the symptoms really are the the bad
taste in your mouth the lethargy the not
feeling so good the tiredness the
fatigue everything even the brain fog
whatever comes you know it's real and
not fake and it's real I love you guys I
hope you got something out of the show
honestly I can do 10 shows on this I
know that anyway I love you take one day
at a time I believe in everybody and man
I'm just proud proud proud proud proud
and bless you bless your heart God bless
you guys I'll see you next
show