live right now this is an amazing day
we have alyssa de gotti live right here
a dear friend of mine incredible human
being
and she's overcome so much chronic
illness and sickness her she's a hero
to many of the people in the medical
medium community and
she writes music that's so validating
and powerful and we have her right here
she's going to sing angel of mercy and
then she's going to talk about her story
which is
mind-blowing and then
if she's up to it she's going to do
another song and i think she is
after that so i am honored
honored to have you here right now live
alyssa and um and
it's incredible thank you for coming on
thank you for being here thank you for
actually
you know wanting to share your powerful
music
and music that just is so
moving it's to the heart and soul like
no other and
i'm just honored you're here i just
wanted to say that
everybody's coming on now so much thank
you i'm so honored to be here
thank you for having me it's truly like
the greatest honor
incredible incredible and um
if you feel like feel like starting i
i'm i i'm here we're all here
everybody's coming on this is incredible
angela mercy
this is angel of mercy amazing
honest
[Music]
i've been feeling
hopeless
his story can't
[Music]
i don't wanna do this on my own
then i'm scared of being alone
hey ain't tell my mercy
[Music]
this world is heavy
so much to carry me
will you take it from me
[Music]
hey
this world is heavy
so much to carry you
will you take it from me
[Music]
can you hear me can you hear me
can you hear me
[Music]
can you hear me can you hear me
hey
[Music]
mercy
can you hear me
[Applause]
will you take it from me
[Music]
i'm sorry
incredible and absolutely
incredible oh my god thank you
okay so i dropped something in the piano
if you heard something um
the song just i mean moves me to tears
like every time and there's it's just
because you know i think about your
story
and what you went through and the
struggle
and i mean from not being validated from
being
six as a child i mean
literally as a child that's how it
started for you and
and then to become then
really really like stricken
with the inability to even swallow or
eat i mean your condition was so
hard to live with i can't even imagine
you were out of place
you were at a place of just absolute
despair
and and hopelessness because i mean you
couldn't eat you couldn't swallow
you couldn't you could barely talk no
one knew what was
wrong yeah and i mean
and you survived it you survived it but
you not only survived it you
you came from i mean you came from that
and you rose above it
and like like if you can
if you feel like sharing your story that
would be amazing
um i'm sure i would love it too oh
awesome
awesome i would love to
where do i start you know i mean you see
i mean i know that like people don't
realize what it's like to be sick
when they're young young too and
a lot of people they they get sick later
in their 20s
but you also experience that too when
you're 23
and yeah and you were you also
experienced that but you
experienced being sick when you were
young too with the utis at like nine
years old
right and and everything at like six
months old
six months old i start i can't i came in
like kicking with a high strep load
um yeah i was sick as a as a baby
um and i had chronic stress i just had
like
you know pneumonia bronchitis um
strep throat until i had my tonsils out
and so i was really sick as a kid
and then i started my cycle at nine so
pretty young
and then with that came all these other
symptoms and that's when
um pretty severe acne started and
weight gain and um constipation all
these other
things that i think as society we just
think are
normal because they're common so i
didn't really realize that none of that
was
like i didn't really identify as being
sickly but
i i did struggle i struggled a lot and
i think the first big um
the big hit that i took was when i was
in high school and i had a near-death
experience with
blood clots in my lungs yeah that was
the big one
that was a big one that just kind of
like
rocked my world because you i sort of
felt invincible
in a way you know um at that age and
that just
i didn't know what to do with that
because i
didn't have answers for why that
happened to me it was just sort of like
this
random hey one day you wake up with
blood clots and almost die
and we have no answers for you so i
didn't really know how to process
any of that and um it was about two
years
after that experience that i started
having panic attacks and i started
having
anxiety and everything just kind of just
kept building
and then um when i was 23
i just it was like a flip switched and i
couldn't swallow
one day and um
yeah it just like went downhill from
there and i i went
through i mean i saw every doctor every
specialist
had every test done i had my esophagus
stretched um i didn't even need to
it wasn't even um
a physical thing i i mean it was but it
felt like it was more
up here than an issue here i'm sure i
felt
because it was it was neurological it
wasn't exactly
mechanical it was the nervous system
and something that just doctors don't
have answers for
and you went to exactly you did
everything you did
you seen every doctor every specialist
i drank the barium i had all the
everything
and it wasn't even food getting lodged
it was truly like
truly neurological and and i was told
it's all in your head it's just anxiety
and i remember
it's so sad i remember begging to have
a diagnosis of a neurological disease
because then i would have an answer and
hopefully
would be able to have a cure or
something but to hear it's just all in
your head it's just anxiety
terrified me because i thought how am i
ever gonna get through this
it just kept getting worse and worse and
i felt so alone
i felt so alone because nobody not only
to know doctor
or therapist or specialist i mean like
top psychiatrists nobody had ever seen
this
not even this phobia which it turned
into because i tried to just
fight through it at first and cope with
it and then i ended up
choking so bad which i felt like was
from my own doing because i almost had
like this hyper awareness of
not being able to swallow and um and
then i just started to starve to death i
just couldn't i couldn't even
drink like drinking water was even
harder
and i just started to like
kind of just waste away and then my
nervous system i feel like i had a
complete nervous breakdown
um that's the best way to describe it i
kind of felt like i had
no skin and all my nerves were exposed
and just constantly like
like my brain short circuiting and i
could not function
and nobody understood and i felt so
alone
that was probably the hardest part um
yeah so you know you're
you're a hero in my eyes okay because
you know like there was something inside
of you and i i know that the medical
medium
community can relate because they're all
fighters
and and that's what's incredible about
this community right you know the
incredible i mean right and um
and it takes something inside of us and
you have that that's just that
because i mean there are people out
there that if
they ever had that condition and
struggle i mean they didn't doesn't mean
they would have made it either
you you are that much of a fighter and
thank you and it's it's
it's so powerful and the thing is and
that's with you not being validated
there was never any validation
going back through your whole life of
being sick it was never like you got
this validation like yes alyssa you're
really sick
and we're going to figure this out or
yes you're really experiencing this
i mean you were told that it was all in
your head yep
you're told that overall well
before the blood clots right the blood
clots in your lungs and before your
blood clots
they they were like you're it was like
when you had pain
you had pain for weeks yep and
no there's nothing wrong with you and i
was told i was being a hypochondriac
from multiple people
and yeah that was that was hard because
i
i was so young but my body was sending
me signals and maybe my intuition
i don't know i feel like i was getting
i i just had this new awareness in my
body that i didn't have before and so i
started to
feel like i i it's almost like i just
had this intuition that i was
gonna die or something because i felt
like i was
and um everybody just dismissed it and
then
i never complained of pain because i was
you know i had been through it already
at that point by 17 and i just had a
high pain tolerance i really just didn't
complain and so i i woke up and i
thought i was having a heart attack
it was the most excruciating pain i
could not get relief from
in my back and my chest and um i took
like eight advil
and i went on my way my mom booked me a
doctor's appointment i went to my
pediatrician
and i was told it was just viral and let
it run its course i i did just to be
safe
i went to the hospital i got all the
tests everything came back
clear so i went a week misdiagnosed and
then
fortunately they they found out why i
had that pain so that was such a miracle
in itself but
i had no answers i had like
i ended up for months getting you know
crazy amount of blood draws and just
like
no answers i'm just told it was
autoimmune it was like a year straight
up blood draws
which which like keeps weekly multiple
times a week yeah
and so you were just like you're just
fighting for your life
yeah like at that point i felt like a 95
year old woman
like just just to sit up straight and
just to walk to the bathroom and brush
my teeth and
and this is my senior year of high
school so it was it was rough and i had
to give myself
shots in the stomach every day and
it was it was crazy
and then you know and then when you and
then you're you're pursuing your musical
career
and yeah yep you were out in l.a
yeah and um and then boom
it's like the pt the ptsd just
hit so hard yeah and now you were in
crippling anxiety and the one thing
about the medical medium community is
they they know about crippling anxiety
and yeah
so many have had all of it the tightness
of the chest and
and you you can't even think you can't
you know
you can't even exist it feels like
you're just you're suffering every
single second and you got hit with such
a like a like a
mega amount of it like insurmountable
that like really like got you just it
was like you were crippled
and you you lost everything you like
everything you just lost everything and
that's what people don't understand is
with what that's like
i mean you lost your musical career in
that moment
you lost relationships you lost
friends there was just it was it just
they all came crashing down
and here you are standing
here you are standing you're stronger
than ever
and you know and you can look back at
that and just be like oh my god but
but when when you go through that kind
of thing
it's it it changes everything
about a person and that's why i like you
my hero because you got through
that you're my hero and it's
it's like and all all they can offer at
that time
was just what benzodiazepines was like
here's a benzo
i had a pill case
[Laughter]
you have the big pill case with all the
men
here's my monday here's my tuesday
here's my wednesday
mm-hmm that's just brutal
it was it was awful and
i think it was just like not knowing how
to
trust myself after that because i was
navigating it
all alone and i think that was the
hardest part
and i am so deeply eternally grateful
for this
community this medical medium community
because
i feel like i have my family and i feel
so seen and so just like there's this
beautiful belonging
and and understanding between all of us
because
i know so many other people out there
have
experiences too and so
it's an honor it's an honor to be here
and um
yeah really grateful and then like
and so what happened like there's like
you were praying you were
you were at a place of of loss
with it all and how did you even find
the medical medium
information was it the first book is
that how it happened
so yeah i was basically mattress island
i it was i was at my lowest absolute
lowest
and um was just you know
just like couldn't get couldn't get
worse and i was scrolling on facebook
and i saw
there was something about you i just had
this moment of truth and
just this miraculous like knowing that
this was my answer this was um
this is my ticket so i immediately
ordered
your first book and found your
radio show on anxiety and
my entire life changed in a second and
um it's been four years now
that i i thanks to you i have
healed remarkably um i never ever
thought i would
even be here today let alone thriving in
this way and feeling better than i knew
was possible
to even like achieve a level of
feeling in my body and home in my body
which is something that i
always longed for and i i just never i
never
imagined that i would i would be here
and that i would be singing
and um and doing any of this so
it's remarkable and i i i love your
first book it's my favorite
and um i i went right to the angel
chapter
and i learned about the angels and how
they can support us and
and i put that in my back pocket and
then um
it was it was christmas that year i was
alone and i had
nowhere left to turn i i was i newly
found
medical medium information and um
i just kept you know i just was like had
nowhere to turn except for
god and medical medium and music
and i sat down at this piano and i just
started to pray and out came this song
and i never thought a soul would hear it
well it's a it's a famous song
in the medical medium community so many
know the song
and where can before you sing like
another song
like where can we find your stuff like
where can everybody in the medical
medium community who doesn't know about
you
and anybody else who sees this where can
you find your stuff like is it your
your instagram page is it your you know
where else you know like it's you can
tell everybody
yeah for sure so um you can find me on
all platforms all socials instagram
facebook youtube
clubhouse tiktok and there whichever
platform you use if you're on facebook
there's a link in my bio or on instagram
and that link will take you
to all of the other links and it will
take you to itunes if you use itunes or
spotify or
pandora or apple music so hopefully that
makes it easy
to find or you could just google me
incredible i see people commenting and
some
some people are saying that your story
is very similar to
you know parts to what they have gone
through and so
um and it there's you know there's a
in the world of like chronic illness and
sickness you know there's
there's no real community i've noticed
when it comes down to when you're really
sick
and and so it's
it's an incredible thing for you to come
out of that
and find your way here with medical meme
information
and i always think there's something and
i know so because spirit of compassion
always tells me that there's something
so special in the people
who have risen out of those ashes
and have found their way with the
information and
in this community and it's more
spiritually powerful
than than i've seen in other places
because
another place is just like well there's
no real answers
it's the smoke and mirrors you know that
well you see
it all and and then
to come out of that and to look at it
from a distance
is just incredible and you've really you
really you've
really just possessed that empowerment
you know that that thank you empowerment
that's just
incredible and it's really you i mean
the information was there but it's you
because you you've gone through it you
went through it you were
just you know suffering you had a
hundred symptoms
isn't that mind-blowing yeah that's like
i made a list what were some of the
symptoms that you had
ah i mean you have like all the
neurological symptoms right you have the
oh everything you know migraines yeah
everything neurological with
the nerves and the horrific debilitating
brain fog and depersonalization
like so out of my body that i just
didn't even feel like i was like living
in this dimension
um where you can't function um
panic attacks severe panic anxiety
depression i had
i i had felt like parkinson's i would
twitch
and my day jobs cutting hair and i
couldn't even cut hair it was like i
would twitch and convulse and
shake and have these tremors um acne
for like my whole life um which i
thought i was doomed with forever
um a horrible acid reflux since i was
little
um allergies sinus
strep food allergies chronic
constipation
um i feel like every just about
everything you've listed in your books
i've had
and i'm i'm a miracle truly like
and i yes i've done the hard work to
overcome but i would not be here
without you and god and soc
and this community so i'm just
it's the greatest honor it's the
greatest honor having me here okay
it's the greatest honor for me i'm
totally blown away
and and it means the world to me that
you're here
and that you made it through that that
you're alive
and you're here to tell your story and
um and like i said you are a hero to so
many people in the medical medium
community
they know your music they know your
story and
um and it's an in you're an inspiration
beyond
and you know and so um
i don't i there's there's no words when
i think about it too you know
that's how i feel i'm like i'm
just so like yeah there's no words i'm
so inspired by
everybody in this community and i'm just
like
honored to be a part of such a such an
incredible
family um of warriors a
healing warriors and just beautiful
incredible
heroic people so um it's just
i'm so deeply honored i wish i had words
thank you thank you for letting me share
my story and
and my voice i i think it's so
interesting that so much of my trauma
and pain and suffering was like
my lungs and my throat my voice isn't
that interesting
it's yeah it is it is and it's it's it's
like okay now my chronic illness has
taken away something
that's the most important thing in my
life it's the thing that keeps me strong
and stable
it's and i've seen that with chronic
illness where
you got somebody who's a runner you know
they do track or their olympic athlete
they want
either they're working to be that way
and then their chronic illness takes
them away from the very thing that
they want to do which is running or say
someone loves to exercise every single
day but it takes them away from that or
but with you it's like this is this is
everything to you this is
your singing the music that's your
creativity
it's your it it feels like a big part of
your existence i mean this is yeah
this is the you work for god and you
create beautiful music
music that is healing for people and
supports them so for that to be taken
away from you
which means it's taken away from
everybody else too because then they
can't hear the music they can't
they can't heal from it so it really
it's it's devastating to both you and
your life personal life
and it's sad because people can't heal
with your music if you're not
able to actually do it and sing it
and but now we have you we have you in
our life you're in our life you're
you're here you're making the most
incredible music do you want it do you
want
are you up for another song or i would
love to
and i think it's fitting because this
next song i'm gonna do
is it speaks to to the soul's gold and
and it's my rising from the fire rising
out of the ashes and
and overcoming um whatever whatever
you're going through whatever
chronic illness or um pain or suffering
it's just about rising and um and flying
higher than ever before so this is
called watch me fly i love this one and
i hope you all love it
[Music]
feels like my world's crushing now
but i know that this has to
[Music]
from the fire
this is
[Music]
this is all new to me
but i see beauty and the breaking
[Music]
now i know where i stand
if i fall i know that i'm gonna live
in the moment
[Music]
leave it all behind even when i'm
nervous
[Music]
i'm gonna fly
i'm ready to fly i'm ready to fly
i'm ready
[Music]
even when i'm nervous
this is
[Music]
incredible that
that's incredible thank you
i don't even know what to say i don't it
amazing amazing first of all the song
is so incredible and then and then
you're singing it here on top of it
it's just like i don't even know like
pinch me thank you
pinch me am i is this a dream is this a
dream am i just dreaming right now and
i'm about to wake up
that's me
thank you so much well if anybody just
got on here i'm with alyssa degatti
um uh i'm so proud of her
for just what what she's accomplished in
her life she's she's suffered through
chronic illness like
no one can imagine and she's risen out
of it
she's telling her story she's she's
blessing us
right now blessing us with her energy
her time her music her songs her
talent her you know you know her
creativity
and her gift and just to spend the
greatest day
um everybody on here are you guys gonna
come to instagram
with us because we're gonna do this on
instagram
and we're gonna we're gonna be talking
about everything
and yeah we're gonna be you're going to
sing again i think
i'm going to sing again oh my gosh i
hope everyone comes oh
my god oh my gosh i am like blown away i
can do this
all day this is the greatest thing so
we're getting so excited
everybody guys um come with us to
instagram
and um we're gonna do it there and we're
gonna talk and
we're who knows what we're gonna talk
about with this it's just so incredible
this is so incredible
yeah so all right so anyway
you know where to find alyssa with her
platforms you know
where she is listen to her songs when
you get a chance everybody should go to
um where her songs are and definitely
listen to them because i'm going to be
doing that i'll be listening to them all
night
all right okay we're hentai thank you
anthony
all right