my skin what's wrong with my skin my
Skin's got stretch marks my skin has
cellulitis my skin has all kinds of
different dots on it my skin has all
kinds of different little scars my skin
this my skin that I want my skin to look
good I want my skin to Glow I want my
skin to be beautiful I'm talking about
the Skin Potion that's what I'm talking
about today and I am pumped up and I am
excited and I'm going to cover what
happens to our skin in general you can't
fix the skin from the outside we can try
all we want we can try our hardest we
can do everything we can slather all
kinds of stuff on our bodies we can be
slathering all kinds of essential oils
we can get ourselves soaking wet with
oil and everything and hop in bed at
night we can do a seaweed wrap with oil
all over us hop in bed at night wake up
in the morning and do it again the next
day we can put whatever we want on the
surface of our skin it's not going to be
enough it's not going to fix the
elasticity problem that people get this
is important your skin is the whole
organ that's the big old organ right
that's your organ if you hurt a part of
your stomach a little part of it the
entire stomach gets affected if you hurt
a little part of your liver the entire
liver gets affected if you hurt a little
part of your skin the entire organ gets
affected by it it compromises the entire
organ your skin and so it's critical to
be doing the right stuff it's critical
to build up that collagen From the
Inside Out heal up the skin from the
inside out not from the outside in I
know so many of us is always like
outside in outside in outside in really
it's inside out that's the key it's all
about immune power it's all about immune
system our immune system patrols that
area and right under the Derma right
under the skin our immune system needs
antioxidants in that area antioxidants
are one of the critical
Builders right there silica one of the
critical Builders stopping oxidative
stress because oxidative stress lands in
the Deep depths of the skin it winds up
trying to find itself escaping through
your skin when you're under stress and
you're going through all this stuff
emotionally mentally our immune system
drops all that adrenaline's coarsing
through our veins leaking up through the
skin that's why we have a bad skin
looking day when we've been through hell
and back with stress when you're under
stress all those free radicals are
pouring through your system along with
that adrenaline emotional challenges
what's happening is the bottom of your
your Derma right underneath there is
starting to soak it all up it's soaking
up the adrenaline and as it soaks up the
adrenaline it tries to rid it as quick
as it can so the bottom of your Derma
right here right where your skin even
starts and even before it starts right
before that deep layer even
starts that area right there acts as a
sponge it sponges up all the adrenaline
from flight uh fight ORF flight right
here all the adrenaline from any kind of
emotional stress
whatsoever it sponges it up what are we
doing to protect the skin because that's
how our skin ages really quick and
really fast and what are people going to
do they're going to micro needle they're
going to exfoliate the crap out of their
skin and then they're going to use all
kinds of different ointments and
different creams that have all kinds of
fragrances in them that hurt our skin
once again it's from the inside out and
it's about getting to the deep
underneath layer into that sponge into
that Derma right here way further deep
underneath the follicles that's where it
counts that's how you heal the surface
that's how you heal the middle we can't
control every situation we can't control
the stress runder the oxidative stress
we can't control someone else and what
they do we can't control the weather we
can't control a hurricane we can't
control the evil that happens on this
planet and there's a lot of evil
happening on this planet we know that
can't control any of that but so many
people are worried about their skin I
hear it until the cows come home so what
I love about the Skin Potion what I'm
showing you is immune system and then
building blocks for skin I'm going to
get some water get a little bit of water
here this is warm water so to make the
Skin Potion you need some warm water
first things first we're going to put a
scoop in here of the micro then we're
going to put two capsules of the MSM the
bamboo silica right here I'm opening
capsules then I'm looking for a little
knife here because I'm going to put
orange you can choose lemon but I'm
going to put orange and there's a reason
why orange is going in here it's not for
flavor and it's not for Taste although
it does taste good because it's a juicy
orange we're going to squeeze half an
orange in here the reason is because
what's in this orange are two things one
is calcium there's a little bit of
silica and orange too and there's
vitamin C three things what we have in
this orange are three things but I need
those three things because I am
introducing those three things in its
living form fresh out of an orange to
the pure form here so what we're doing
is we're introducing the actual
synergetic blend of these together now
here's the cool thing the orange in
there not only makes it taste good but
what it's doing is that vitamin C inside
the orange right there is connecting to
the two kinds of pure vitamin C in here
in the immune power we're mixing them at
the same time we're connecting the
calcium the vitamin C and silica to the
MSM we're connecting the silica that's
naturally in an orange there's a little
bit in an orange we're connecting that
to the organic bamboo silica we're
connecting that to the two other
varieties of vitamin C powerful vitamin
C and we're putting it all together and
we're making our Skin Potion all right
so let's get some warm water in
here and you have the Skin Potion right
there by the way you guys know I work
with vimergy just you know the link in
the description Link in the profile puts
in one cart the discount and the
products so it puts the micro C it puts
the lemon balm it Point puts the MSM the
5% off the free lemon balm in one
product right there and then we add that
to the Living Water of the orange
bartender give me
another