I hear it all the time my skin my skin
what's wrong with my skin my Skin's got
stretch marks my skin has cellulitis
cellulite cellulitis people say it
differently my skin has all kinds of
different dots on it my skin has all
kinds of different little
scars my skin this my skin that I want
my skin to look good I want my skin to
Glow
I want my skin to be
beautiful I'm talking about the Skin
Potion that's what I'm talking about
today and I am pumped up and I am
excited you might want to watch this
this is going to be very important and
I'm going to cover what happens to our
skin in general you know have you ever
done that micro needling where you get
that roller and everybody's doing it uh
uh
uh not good good you know the micro
roller the micro
needling not a good thing you don't want
to miss this little episode here because
we're going to talk about a Skin Potion
I'm going to make it in front of us
right here which you see is micro immune
power right here in my hand so I just
want to show you it's one thing right
there what you also see is the vimergy
mm right there okay and this is going to
be very interesting cuz I'm going to
show you guys what I'm going to make and
why it's important because right there
you're talking about the collagen
Builder the micro immune power with the
organic bamboo
silica you can't fix the skin from the
outside by the way you guys know I work
with
vimergy you can't fix the skin from the
outside we can try all all we want we
can try our hardest we can do everything
we can slather all kinds of stuff on our
bodies we can be slathering all kinds of
essential oils we can get ourselves
soaking wet with oil and everything and
hop in bed at night we can do a seaweed
wrap with oil all over us hop in bed at
night wake up in the morning and do it
again the next day we can put whatever
we want on the surface of our skin it's
not going to be enough it's not going to
fix the elasticity problem that people
get this is important the reason why I'm
even doing this right now is because oh
my God if I hear it one more time my
skin my skin medical medium my skin what
do I do hey medical medium I just found
your book and I have skin problems
what's the best route to go like it's a
skin skin skin and what about stretch
marks why do we get stretch marks and
why do they stay there people gain
weight they lose the weight and the
stretch marks are there how how do we
best help those stretch marks heal and
do their thing all this matters you have
to build the skin from the inside out
it's critical mm info for
years Delia says yeah my sister really
messed her skin on her face up by doing
micro needling she has a lot of
discoloration from it too so I want to
talk about that with the if you've done
the micro needling and hey you might not
be off the hook right there I want to
talk about this isn't about tattoos
being bad or good but I want to talk
about instead of what I've always talked
about right about ink I want to talk
about the surface of the skin I want to
talk about that with the inks if you're
some of dealing with tattoos and you've
done all this kind of ink and you've
done whatever maybe you just got a
little bit of ink behind your ear maybe
you have it on the back of your neck
maybe you shaved your head one day and
you have it on your head maybe you got
it on your leg maybe you got it on your
lower back wherever the ink
is the skin gets affected so I want to
kind of give you guys a oneone on what
happens when we have Micro injuries on
our skin and how that plays a role on
all of our skin did you hear that so
when you're micro needling your face
right which don't do and you can do
whatever you want I'm just saying I tell
my family and friends don't do with the
micro needling but what happens is your
skin is the whole organ that's the big
old organ right that's your
organ and if you let's take an example
here if you hurt a part of your
stomach a little part of it the entire
stomach gets
affected if you hurt a little part of
your liver the entire liver gets
your
skin the entire organ gets affected by
it it compromises the entire organ your
skin and so it's critical to be doing
the right stuff it's critical to build
up that collagen From the Inside Out
heal up the skin from the
inside
out not from the outside in I know so
many of us is always like outside in
outside in outside
in really it's inside out that's the key
so I want to talk about we're going to
make we're going to make a Skin Potion
right here I'm excited about that this
is the vimergy micros immune power with
the organic bamboo
silica this is the vimergy MSM with the
bamboo silica we're going to be joining
these two we're going to be putting
these two together and vimergy is going
to give any anyone who's actually
getting this a free lemon balm and 5%
off of the MSM on top of it so the free
lemon bomb which is nerves and nervous
system which believe it or not when
you're dealing with nerves and your
calming nerves it's helpful for what
it's helpful for your skin I'll talk
about that in a little bit too so this
is really exciting Wendy says my skin is
now better than ever following medical
mean and protocols look
medical meum protocols have always been
incredible for the skin but a lot of
people they have skin injuries and don't
realize this they just have all these
kind of micro injuries on their SK
mosquito bites create micro injuries on
the skin course acne creates micro
injuries on the skin micro needling
creates mic micro injuries on the
skin small tattoos all around the body
or large tattoos create all kinds of
injuries to the Skin So and the skin
gets
affected on the
hole on the
hole well don't worry I just only did it
here or don't worry I've only micro
needled here but the skin gets affected
everywhere because it is the organ it
feels it everywhere it knows it
everywhere
and so that's
important so I want to just cover all
that plus a bunch of others you guys
just got here right we're talking about
the skin we're talking about a Skin
Potion the micro C and we're talking
about the MSM combined so I'm going to
show you the potion combined right we're
talking about the organic bamboo silica
we're talking about the MSM no caking
agents no
impurities I mean that alone is insane
no one realizes all the powders they get
all the different supplement powders out
there everything from protein Powers
every kind of powder it's
loaded with impurities load
it load it with impurities and anti-king
agents load it with that and they're
allowed to do it and vimer will not do
that will not do that how are you going
to help your skin when all these
impurities are thrown into all of the
supplements out there and the powders or
anything how are we going to
actually help the skin when all this
garbage is put into all these
supplements out there someone please
tell me cuz I'm scratching my head on
that it has to be good stuff and the
skin has to be healing has to be
strengthening and enhancing on the
inside out
important to know you cannot eat a
sheep's eyeball to fix your eyeball you
cannot eat a Bine heart to fix your
heart you cannot eat a kidney to fix
your kidney you cannot eat a pancreas to
fix your pancreas you cannot eat a
stomach to fix your stomach I'm sorry
it's not going to happen you can't eat
liver to fix your liver I am sorry to
say I don't mean to be the bearer of bad
news but you cannot fix your liver by
eating liver it's
Insanity absolute lunacy that's
lunacy so if you think you're eating
liver out there or you get some kind of
liver supplement or whatever it is or a
heart supplement and you're eating it
thinking it's going to help you in
somehow or some
way it's
lunacy I hate to break the news to you
this isn't about judg guy one or
anything it doesn't work you can't eat
someone's brain and fix your brain even
if it's a human brain even if you're
actually eating a human
brain like they make it legal in this
sick world and you're actually able to
eat a human brain it's not going to fix
your brain it doesn't work like this
we've been sold this for a very long
time and in the supplement World they
still sell it they still push it there's
something about it oh I'm going to get
this liver I'm going to eat this liver
right here that's that's dried and
dehydrated I'm going to put this in my
smoothie I'm going to eat this liver and
put this in something because it's going
to fix me right that liver I'm going to
eat is going to fix me oh this must be
good for me it's not it's not good for
you in fact it's worse for your skin
it's worse for your
skin you can't eat muscle
tissue to give give you muscle tissue it
doesn't work and you can't eat an
intestinal tract to fix your intestinal
tract you just can't it won't work and
it doesn't work these are critical piece
pieces of information landmarks that's
what they are they are landmarks to
understand and you can't eat
skin you can't eat skin to fix your
skin it's not going to happen you don't
think that's the serious thing out there
it's serious because it's in the mindset
of the supplement World about eating
liver and fixing your liver about eating
something and fixing it that's what
we're taught out there and it's Insanity
it's actually
Insanity for some reason people in
health whoever actually supports it
which there's tons of people out there
they've lost their minds because you
cannot eat skin to fix your skin you
can't eat collagen to fix your
collagen millions and millions and
millions of bottles and jars and
packages of collagen have been sold to
the suckers for years that's right
millions billions of dollars have been
made off of
collagen and everybody or almost anybody
and
everybody has purchased that thinking
they're going to actually build their
collagen how how many years have you
seen it how many people do you know were
putting collagen inside their smoothies
and collagen inside mixes tell me have
you done it how many people do you know
how many ads have you seen how much
information is out there about collagen
and taking collagen to help your
collagen you've seen
that it doesn't work you can't take
collagen and fix your collagen you can't
take a beef liver and fix your liver you
can't eat somebody's pancreas to fix
your pancreas you can't do it and you
can't eat somebody's nose to fix your
nose and you can't eat their damn ear to
fix your ear it doesn't happen it
doesn't work and the reason why I'm
saying this is because collagens don't
work out
there and so if you're looking at skin
cuz I'm I'm driven mad about skin stuff
I hear it all the time like my skin my
skin what about this on here what about
I put this on here what about I put that
on there and what if I do this how about
if I take all this
collagen if you're somebody that's
worried about skin you have to build and
repair from the inside out and it has to
be stuff that's potent and Powerful the
building blocks have to be there that's
really important the building blocks
have to be
there now I'm not a skin model and I'm
not
a person that's like my skin my skin let
me do selfies let me go you know and do
selfies and post selfies of my beautiful
skin but for my age my skin is doing
pretty good pretty darn good and people
ask me every day why do your skin look
so good why is your Skin So Soft what
are you putting on your skin ew what are
you doing for your
skin no face lifts no cosmetic surgeries
no
Botox no photo in enhancements no
photoshopping on
aw no photo enhancements
photoshopping no Botox no filler no face
lifts none of that I don't do any of
that critical to know but what I can
tell you is there's things you can avoid
and things you can do to help keep your
skin good and strong and today I'm
talking about a Skin Potion I'm going to
make I'm also sh you the micro immune
power and collagen
supporter right there with the organic
bamboo silica you mix that with the
[Music]
MSM and
boom you know and look I don't do a lot
of things that destroy skin I don't do
the vinegar that destroy skin I don't do
the caffeine that destroys skin I don't
do stuff like that that but even
regardless of all those things there are
things we can do to actually pick up the
speed on Damage Done throughout the year
so the reason why I was bringing up
micro micro
needling because it got really popular
and I was like oh my God what are people
doing that's that should be called micro
scarring not micro needling that should
have been called micro scaring
ing all
right I want to talk about the skin a
little bit more what you see in front of
me by the way I just want to let you
guys know this cuz this is sick this is
sick okay this is really amazing all
right so you got the micro immune
power they give you a lemon bomb nerves
calming nerves nervous system the lemon
balm if you get it with the MSM and put
it together together get the 5% off on
the MSM that's sick it's a sick
deal and it feels good because of what
it is it's so darn clean and so amazing
there's a direct link and it puts the
products in the cart for you with the
discount link is in the profile and in
the description I want to make that
clear let me make the potion really
quick we're going to cover though a
little bit about
ink not the normal Ink Show though we're
talking about the actual skin that gets
scarred when we get ink because of the
needle going
in you want the
butterfly you want Casper the
ghost what do you want do you want a
viking right the whole thing you want a
viking with skulls around it do you want
a rainbow what do you like as a tattoo
do you want some scrip on there do you
want something cool written what kills
you does what kills you makes you
stronger what what is it that you want
on there I'm not judging anybody I'm
just saying that as an organ as a whole
the whole organ senses anything that
happens to it you know if something if
you get pinched here you get a mosquito
bite here your entire
organ is in the no it's actually in the
know of it you do some micro needling or
you try some other exfoliation it's
another thing
too for years I've watched people get
exfoliated to
death the
exfoliations you got to be cautious on
how deep those go how rough those
are and you got to be careful or you got
to be doing stuff from the inside out to
help repair and take care
of all
right I got a little skin tissue model
right
here when it comes down to skin repair
it has to start from deep down into the
Derma it has to be down deep in the
Derma here we got to go low you want to
work on skin and keep skin good good you
don't want stretch marks taking over
when you gain weight and then you lose
the weight and you lost all the L right
elasticity of the skin and you got the
skin is is way too
played and it's not bouncing back and
everybody's trying to get the tummy
tucks and they're trying to get all the
different surgeries and Tucks their skin
won't work with them or maybe you just
gained a little bit of weight and then
you got the stretch marks from a little
bit of
weight the way we have to address all of
this is always remember no matter what
that when we're addressing skin it has
to be from the bottom up it has to be
from the ground up so from the ground up
it can't be
surface it can't even be follicle
level it has to be right at the base
which is what I call the foundation of
of your skin deep within the Derma and
right under the Derma right under the
skin it's like when you peel that skin
off of a
chicken when you peel that chicken skin
chicken you want to go between that
bottom layer of that skin to the flesh
basically we're talking about
building that
deep that
deep cuz I know that a lot of people
don't realize how it works with the skin
they think it's either surface or just
below the surface it's
not if you want skin stuff to happen
it's got to be Boom at the root at the
root and not at the root of a follicle
we got to go even deeper than that we
have to go under the follicle it has to
be down there and it has to be so deep
where literally it's just under the
first layer of Derma it's actually just
under so it's between that first layer
of Derma and basically everything else
in your body it's between
there and that's key and I want people
to know
this it's not out the it's not on the
outside it's not down under underneath
the outside it's down so
low it's
basically at the bottom and then even
under that where
there's fluid to your actual physical
body Ashley says okay so how do we get
to the
root so important to know right it's all
about
immune power it's all about immune
system our immune system patrols that
area our immune system needs
antioxidants in that area antioxidants
are one of the critical
Builders right there silica one of the
critical
Builders stopping oxidative stress
because oxidative stress lands in the
Deep depths of the skin oxidative
stress fight ORF flight every time I see
anybody in fight or flight or know
somebody's in fight ORF flight or I'm in
fight or flight I'm thinking skin I'm
like my Skin's going to pay the
price my Skin's going to age
overnight my Skin's going to take the
hit anytime I see anybody talking about
fight ORF flight or anything happen
happening fight ORF
flight first thing I think about is skin
I'm like skin whoa whoa that was really
stressful skin whoo because what happens
is and when you're in firefight and all
that epinephrine is just coursing
through the body it's so corrosive it's
like battery acid when we're under
stress oxidative stress
oxidizing it winds up trying to find
itself escaping through your skin when
you're under stress and you're going
through all this stuff emotionally
mentally you might stink
more you might stink
more you're under stress you start
stinking in the armpits you start
sweating it starts to wreak you're under
you have a really stressful day you're
stinking so Manny says is that why we
look terrible after something stressful
exactly the skin takes a hit
when we're up against oxidative stress
that's why it's critical to battle
oxidative sh
stress using sh for a second which is my
next thing I want to talk about by the
way that's why but it's critical to know
that when you're up against that stress
and you're up against all that different
emotional turmoil or something's
happening or it's losses or something's
going on in your life you don't feel
like you're getting enough wins in your
life you got people breathing down your
neck You' got psychic attacks coming
whatever it is that you're dealing with
it's that kind of stress that's
producing that kind of epinephrine that
is coursing through the veins and the
bloodstream and it winds up trying to
escape through the skin desperately and
rise out of
it which leads to the next part I'm
trying to talk about which then we get
in trouble if we're if we're challenged
like that our immune system is
challenged we end up getting in a a
place where bugs that reside inside of
us start to rise up a little bit
remember you're looking at here immune
so you're looking at the micro and
you're seeing immune immune system we're
up against all this oxidative
stress our immune system drops all that
adrenaline's coursing through our veins
leaking up through the skin that's why
we have a bad skin looking day when
we've been through hell and back with
stress and then bugs want to
play well my acne is really coming out
bad I don't know my acne is really bad
these days pimples they're coming out
all this kind of
stuff and that's where oxidative strep
comes
in that's where oxidative strep comes
in so what I love about the Skin Potion
I'm
showing which I'm going to show you guys
I'm going to make it in front of you in
a minute it's simple it's easy it's fun
actually tastes good everything's great
what I'm showing you is immune system
and then building blocks for
skin immune system building blocks for
the
skin we're up against a little too much
stress we're in fight or flight we got
the adrenals pumping the adrenaline's
corrosive it's going through the veins
it's surfacing through the skin it's
leaking out of our pores and it stinks
and it's corrosive and it smells and
it's leaking out of our our armpits it's
everywhere and it smell it's on our
feet it's why people's feet can smell
really bad from fight or flight all that
stress and all that adrenaline soaking
and purging through her body and can
make your feet really smell Christy says
I've had the the flu these past 3 days
my skin looks
horrible and that's why I was saying we
get stressed out our immune system drops
pathogens can raise up like the
strep adrenaline courses through our
body we need immune system support and
we need skin support and that's what the
micro C
is there's Rhyme or Reason here this
isn't like a supplement and I'm trying
to so a supplement that's insane there's
Rhyme or Reason to why things are
powerful and
helpful we're stressed
out our body starts to break down
oxidative stress starts to
occur our cells start to take the hit
free radicals start to rise up and
saturate cells adrenaline starts to move
all through the bloodstream
and puts stress on our
Landmark which is
this the bottom of our
Derma so we're going through
life if you had a hard life and haven't
had a chance to protect yourself protect
your skin and if you've had a hard life
the skin will show it the skin will show
it if you haven't had a chance to
protect yourself and all of this as it's
happening will actually go and hit the
bottom of the
Derma the
sponge so I want to show you something
really
quick so the bottom of the
Derma acts as a
sponge that's what it acts as take a
look at this sponge right here in my my
hand if you can okay I'll show you guys
on Tik Tok show you guys on IG see this
sponge right
here sponge is actually absorbing our
skin goes up and down it
absorbs like a sponge you don't hear
this out there you won't hear this out
there of course mm
info but what it does is it acts as a
sponge see the bottom of the Derma right
there and you see the sponge I'm holding
right
here when you're under stress all those
free radicals are pouring through your
system along with that adrenaline
emotional
challenges what's happening is the
bottom of your Derma right underneath
there is starting to soak it all up it's
soaking up the
adrenaline and as it soaks up the
adrenaline it tries to rid it as quick
as it
can we got a little camera action going
here let's see what we can
do we're having fun
today this is this is an advanced skin
course right here just so you know
you're not going to learn this stuff
anywhere else you're not going to see it
anywhere else it's an advanced skin
course on how it works with your skin
plus stress plus adrenaline so the
bottom of your Derma right here right
where your skin even starts and even
before it starts right before that deep
layer even
starts that area right there acts as a
sponge that's what it does that's why
you can get dehydrated if you get
dehydrated your skin feels dehydrated
did you ever see that where you're
really dehydrated you ever run into
somebody and you can pinch their skin
and nothing bounces back you pinch their
skin nothing bounces back like you pinch
it and it's like stuck or halfway stuck
did you ever see that you guys where you
pinch their
skin because the Derma at the base is a
sponge basically it's sitting there and
it it's
absorbing and then it's
releasing it sponges up all the
adrenaline from flight uh fight ORF
flight right here all the adrenaline
from any kind of emotional stress
whatsoever it sponges it up
and then it tries to push it through the
surface of the skin if it
can and here's the thing you might be
some of you exercise a lot you're like
well I sweat it all out I exercise I
sweat it all out that's
great that's great all that adrenaline
you're yeah coursing through with all
that sweat that's right right through
your skin tissue then what are you doing
to protect your skin and collagen
because guess what that is damaging to
the skin I'm not saying exercise is
damaging I'm saying in general as all
that oxidative stress and adrenaline and
free radicals go rushing through that
sponge inside the Derma inside the skin
and it forces its way through the skin
what are we doing to protect the skin
because that's how our skin ages really
quick and really
fast and what are people going to do
they're going to micro needle they're
going to exfoliate the crap out of their
skin skin their
exfoliations left and right they're
going to try scrubs they're going to be
scrubbing their skin left and right
because that's what they're going to do
and I understand why and then they're
going to use all kinds of different
ointments and different creams that have
all kinds of fragrances in them that
hurt our
skin once again it's from the inside out
and it's about getting to the deep under
underneath layer into that sponge into
that Derma right here okay I'll move
this here so you guys can see a closeup
down here it's about that layer right
there you see it underneath the
folicles way further deep underneath the
follicles that's where it
counts that's how you heal the surface
that's how you heal the middle it has to
be addressed right here at the base and
we can't control every situation we
can't control the stress runder the
oxidative stress we can't control
someone else and what they do we can't
control the weather we can't control a
hurricane we can't control the evil that
happens on this planet and there's a lot
of evil happening on this planet we know
that can't control any of that
but so many people are worried about
their skin I hear it until the cows come
home every single day out there and so I
wanted to talk about it a little bit
because I see the confusion out there
about skin it's vast it's great the
confusion and I want to talk about why
our skin falls apart from stress and if
we're not doing anything for the stress
and here's why I like this take a look
this is the whole point here I'll get a
closeup on this as well here's why I
like this the micro immune power you put
this with the MSM and I'm going to do it
right now and make a potion you put this
together you're talking about that
organic bamboo silica you're talking
about the two types of vitamin C that
doesn't Scorch your stomach
lining it's buffered it's not like that
ascorbic acid out there that tears
people's guts up right it makes people
get the runs and the diarrhea and it
makes them not feel good and you can't
take enough of it and I'm not talking
about that other junk too that ascorbic
acid that's in the fat
lipids uh good luck getting that vitamin
C to
cells that's awful and there's no
anti-caking agents in here this stuff is
pure and that right there is incredible
and what do you do you're battling
stress with all of it you're supporting
the immune system you got building
blocks for the collagen right there
you're not getting fooled or tricked or
duped and sold collagen which as I said
before doesn't fix collagen or create
collagen and then you got the silica
which is critical for the skin and the
Derma and then combined with the
oxidative free radical breaker which is
the vitamin C and the two kinds of
vitamin C that's buffered and you
combine that with the lemon balm for the
nervous
system that's what I'm talking about you
get a free lemon bomb with the micro C
and 5% off on the MSM unbelievable let's
let's uh let's make some stuff and then
maybe we'll talk about tattoos a little
bit more and some other things but let's
go there's a direct link about this
discount okay you actually this goes in
the cart when you order it get 5% off
right there of the MSM check out the
link in the profile Link in the
description all right let's let's get
working on this I got my skin right here
let's get the stomach out of here
little bit maybe we'll move the liver as
well I'm going to eat liver like a
[__] all
right now look I get it people like to
taste the liver it's it's it's a food
for survival back years ago back if you
go 100 years ago and you ran out of meat
but you had a de hydrated liver you
better believe it you're going to be
eating that liver for
survival for survival you'll eat
dirt you'll eat anything but it's a bad
idea it's filled with toxins the liver
is filled with so many toxins you know
when I see people like dehydrated liver
and smoothies and stuff like that out
there in the health field in the health
realm I I don't want to laugh I don't
think it's funny because I realize what
it's going to do to people's skin
because liver is so filled with it's the
toxic waste dump of the animal I don't
care if it's the grass-fed of all Grassi
fed beef there is B Vine grass-fed I
don't care the liver still has filled
with poison and toxin inside that cow
and this isn't an anti- cow talk I'm
just saying it's filled the toxins and
poisons just like our livers fill the
toxins and poisons right and that liver
you eat that and that goes to the skin
all those time toxins and
poisons all right let's do this now this
is kind of fun I think this is actually
really fun all
right let's go I'm going to get some
water get a little bit of water here
this is warm water so to make the Skin
Potion you need some warm water not hot
water important to understand do not get
that tea kettle boiling where it is
really really hot and you're dumping in
that really really hot water don't do
that please in order to make the Skin
Potion okay you want water that's warm I
feel this it doesn't hurt to leave your
hands on on it you stick your finger in
there you don't get
burned that's the kind of water I like
all right first of all I'm going to put
some powders in
there and I'm going to move little this
out of the
way
okay I think I'm going to make some room
here okay first things first we're going
to put a
scoop in
here of the micro
C immune
power okay then we're going to put two
capsules
of the MSM the bamboo
silica right
here two capsules
inside our little
cup I'm opening capsules if you guys
want to know I just opened up these
capsules
okay then I'm looking
for a little knife here because I'm
going to put
orange you can choose lemon but I'm
going to put orange and there's a reason
why orange is going in here it's not for
flavor and it's not for Taste although
it does taste good because it's a juicy
orange we're going to squeeze half an
orange in here the reason is because
what's in this orange are two things one
is calcium there's a little bit of
silica and orange too and there's
vitamin C
three
things what we have in this orange are
three things but I need those three
things because I am introducing those
three things in its living form fresh
out of an orange to the pure
form
here so what we're doing is we're
introducing the actual C
energetic blend of these
together now here's the cool
thing the orange in there not only makes
it taste good but what it's doing is
that vitamin C inside the orange right
there is connecting to the two kinds of
pure vitamin C in here in the immune
power we're mixing
them at the same time we're
connecting the
calcium the vitamin
C and silica to the
MSM we're connecting the silica that's
naturally in an orange there's a little
bit in an orange we're connecting that
to the organic bamboo silica we're
connecting that to the two other
varieties of vitamin C powerful vitamin
C and we're putting it all together and
we're making our skin
potion so we got our orange squeezed in
there if you go all the way back to the
beginning here you'll see why I
recommend vitamin C
silica yep for your
skin and if you go way before this video
right here that we're creating we're
live right now but way before this is
why I've been talking about it for
decades all right so let's get some warm
water in
here and we're going to mix
it and you have the Skin Potion right
there get a little spoon
out now what I recommend is don't drink
it right right away give it a couple of
minutes give it a good spin a good mix
and give it a couple of minutes and I
like to sip on it and take it with the
lemon
balm is what I like to
do a little lemon bomb to relax the
nerves and calm you can take the lemon
bomb
before because what I'm doing with the
lemon
bomb is
reducing stress inside the
body so that's what I'm doing reducing
stress and then I'm using this right
here the Skin
Potion to battle the free radicals to
battle the oxidative stress to battle
the corrosive
adrenaline and to feed the bottom of the
Derma it's about feeding the bottom of
the Derma that
sponge if you don't have orange you can
use lemon or
lime but orange is my
favorite now What's Happening Here is
I'm giving it a minute and I'm about to
start sipping it and I want to talk
about what happens when you're sipping
this Skin
Potion I'm going to do a sip right now I
think it's been a couple of minutes just
about you feel this when you just sip
it you feel it you give it just
20 seconds and you instantly start
feeling it you feel it actually get to
places fast there's nothing
inhibiting this from getting to where it
needs to go there's nothing in the way
of it there isn't a whole bunch of fatty
lipids in there this isn't one of those
supplementation things where you got
ascorbic acid mixed with all this fat
which doesn't get to where you need to
go it cancels out itself actually it
cancels itself out this is just
literally straight mainlining it right
here make sure it's stirred
enough because the
bottom might get stuck there as you pour
the liquid in so just like anything any
kind of powder you place
into make sure it stirred
enough now you're welcome to put a
little bit more orange than what I did I
just put like kind of a quarter of I
didn't squeeze the whole thing in but
you're allowed to put more in there
and that's
fine I'm going to give it a
second it's strong you feel
it it's
intense it goes in quick it goes into
the bloodstream fast for people that are
asking there's a direct link that puts
the products in one cart check it out
out the link is in the profile link is
in the description it puts both all
three products
in one
cart we're going to take some lemon bomb
in a minute too let me see if I can find
a little bit of a shot
glass or I'll find it in a little
bit okay
now couple things to
know it just feels good it feels good
very strong very
potent when you let it co through your
bloodstream just
imagine how it's finding its
way to
here it's finding its way to
here the
bottom of your skin the bottom of your
Derma imagine it's finding its way
there that's where it's heading
to help clean that up now what happens
is when you gain weight and you lose
weight do you ever notice that some
people they lose weight their skin the
stretch marks just somehow just
disappear and some people they lose
weight a stretch marks are still there
even two people relatively at the same
weight roughly might not be give or take
a pound or two different but give or
take either way they lost weight they
weighed similar they had enough weight
on their body that was equal um Miller
says can we drink it every day or how
often could it be used every day you can
use
it you can drink it every single day how
much
water a one cup to two cups is fine if
you really have to do a half a cup for
some reason you can but one to two cups
of
water if you need to do less for some
reason you can
but you feel it every time you take a
sip of
this you feel it going through the
bloodstream because it gets there quick
because it's not being
inhibited so I want to cover stretch
mark talk a little bit let's go into
that I think stretch marks are a big
deal for a lot of people a lot of people
are upset by stretch marks they feel
that they feel upset they feel like
betrayed they work so hard to lose their
weight they work really hard and then
they have the stretch marks and they're
like wow I did all this work I got rid
of some excess unwanted pounds and now
I'm dealing with stretch
marks reason for those stretch
marks obviously is because you're
expanding right when you gain weight we
expand we swell we expand so then we get
more more more tissue growth more skin
because we're actually stretching the
skin our body overcompensates more skin
is
produced but even with that if someone
gains a few pounds or 10 lb 15 or 20 lb
and they lose the weight some people
their stretch marks are a lot worse than
some other people the reason for
that is the very base the Landmark I'm
talking about that we want to protect
and we want to support that very
landmark and
base is
deficient it's
deficient and it's saturated and soaked
up with toxins and free radicals that
have been there for
years and it's sufficient of things that
it
needs so that
sponge got overs saturated with too much
poisons fight ORF flight too many toxins
right here at the base right here at the
bottom too much
adrenalin and it got
damaged and when that base that bottom
of that Derma gets
damaged we don't it doesn't bounce back
easy the staticity is
gone collagen
weakens we lose Vitality in the bottom
of our Derma
that's where it starts to really
disappear and if you're dealing with
somebody with a stagnant sluggish liver
which is a big part of it all because
that's saturated with toxins and poisons
right Dr fine you're saying it right
there it's stagnant sluggish liver
possibly you're talking about this
too it doesn't
help in fact that's a big deal on its
own some people might have a really
toxic liver because they're so toxic
that the Derma got filled up with a lot
more
toxins and saturate it with a lot more
adrenaline and then when they lost the
weight the elti the elasticity is
actually
gone they don't have that play that room
to play anymore it doesn't Revitalize
easy it doesn't bounce back quick at all
and then we have the stretch
mark left over so what we're doing here
we're talking about building the
building blocks we're talking about down
there in that area we're talking about
restoring collagen because you can't eat
collagen to actually rebuild collagen it
doesn't work we have to rebuild the base
have to rebuild the landmark and the
foundation because in there is the
secret to fixing lots of scarring that's
occurred at least slowing down
scarring CU scarring can continue on its
own kind of like keloids do a lot of
people they have scarring on the skin
but the scarring can
continue long
past the time where you got the scar so
if you're micro
needling which is you know which people
have done you get tiny little scars over
time they can build we want to avoid
that same way when people get tattoos
the skin is
scarred a lot of people
lose they lose the
look of their tattoo they lose the shine
of it not just because the toxic heavy
metals are are diminishing and leaving
and going into their bloodstream and
organs not because that this isn't a
toxic heavy metal talk but because of
also the skin has been scarred from the
tattoo work and over time some people
their their tattoos will fade even
faster because the skin is actually
building little scars micro scars that
we can't see so that's why why it's
important to actually help our skin when
if we have tattoos to help our skin if
we've done something with our skin to
help it if we want that elasticity back
to help it if we want it to look better
if we've been under a lot of stress we
want that skin looking good and bouncing
back if we've gained weight we want
stretch marks to be eased
down all of that matters Deonte says I
don't understand when put in the lemon
with a lemon
bomb
okay so the lemon
bomb add a little bit of water to
this can be
before in the middle or
after you can do the lemon bomb before
right now I'm in the middle of of doing
this and I want to show you the lemon
bomb I I showed you guys up against
other lemon bombs right how incredible
this lemon balm is remember I did that
where I brought other lemon balbs in I
showed you the difference and what's in
those lemon balbs and
everything so that's the lemon balm
right there so you can take that lemon
balb before you actually do your skin
potion in the middle of the Skin Potion
which I'm in the middle of
it you can sip the Skin Potion for a
couple coup of
hours you can literally nurse it if you
want to and give yourself
infusions of the Skin Potion you don't
have to just send it all down one
shot you can do less water if you'd like
you can just do a half a cup of water if
you really like but you you can nurse
it that's what you should do too I mean
that's one option unless you're in a
rush or something like that give
yourself like small infusion
and you can do your lemon bomb in the
middle
bartender give me
another I better watch out Mrs Ferguson
might come down downstairs from upstairs
Mrs Ferguson might come down and Mr
Fergenson might be stuck on the toilet
and right now I don't want to disturb
both of
them re watch this live after it's
posted please because it's it's loaded
with information powerful information
now you can also take your lemon
balm after you've done your Skin Potion
so you're welcome to do that as well
just like
[Music]
that Mr William what will it be I would
like one more lemon bomb shot bartender
coming right up Mr William here it
is bartender give me another you guys
I'm very happy about all this because I
know it's going to help people and when
it helps people it matters because I see
people they're tortured with skin
products they're tortured with skin
information out there they're tortured
by what they're worried about with their
skin
I think everybody everybody is beautiful
I think you know it's not that I think
that people though they have a hard time
they want their skin looking a certain
way and I understand I understand the
pain so many people go through with skin
issues their face their
skin on their hands their arms all these
different places but I just want people
to have an opportunity that's you know
you know extremely valuable and in their
hands choices and options that matter
and help so when it comes down to skin
this the Skin Potion I was talking about
check this video out for the beginning
you can like the video or give me a
thumbs up if you really feel like it
anything like that is cool or subscribe
if you haven't subscribed but you guys
know that already someone just ask odd
parrot said on Instagram what's in the
Skin Potion it's the micro immune power
I'll show you right on IG right there
it's
that and it's the
MSM right there it's a combination along
with the
orange because what I'm doing is
introducing vitamin C from the orange to
the two kinds of vitamin C incredible
vitamin C in
here and
that's but there's one more thing I did
forget to tell you because there's so
many different things is the glucose
from the orange the reason why I like
the orange the best as the activator
here in this potion is because of the
glucose it helps it Mainline into your
bloodstream quick because there's no fat
inhibiting there's no fat in the way and
the micro C and the
MSM get into the glucose of the orange
and travels really quickly into the
bloodstream and that's what I
love just you know the link in the
description Link in the profile puts in
one cart the discount and the products
so it puts the micro C it puts the lemon
balb it puts the MSM the 5% off the free
lemon bomb in one product right there
and then we add that to the Living Water
of the
orange and the living glucose from the
orange because that's what you're
dealing with the living glucose from
from the
orange all right you guys we talked
about oxidative stress we talked about
the Derma the layer deep down the
foundation we talked about collagen how
it doesn't work we're talking about
building collagen and building the
immune
system and we can't ever get enough
vitamin C with the world we live in the
right kind of vitamin c does wonders
anyway you guys lots of love and I appre
appreciate you hanging out and if you
get a chance take a look at this stuff
I'm proud of all you guys many blessings