hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show or each week I talk about the most
advanced healing information and secrets
about health much of which is not found
anywhere else and is decades ahead of
what's out there now that's a
mouthful as I've always said who has 10
or 20 30 years to wait for answers to
their illnesses we know that now we know
that life is precious and there's no
time to spare so let's get the healing
going today what we talking about today
skin hair and nails we're talking about
those three things you know did you ever
go into the health food store and you
say see a formula and it's like you know
hair skin nails or skin hair nails or
Nails Hair Skin right and you see that
there or on the Internet there's all
these ads for these formulas of hair
skin nails uh it's an easy sell it's an
easy sell everybody's like you know I'd
like to have my nails looking a little
better and ah there's something going on
there's some white spots on there and
I'd like to have my skin looking a
little better we all want the Fountain
of Youth we all want that skin that's
you know perfect and hair we all want
the hair we want shiny lustrous
beautiful hair and so it's an easy sell
for the for the old Hair Skin you know
nail supplements that are out there and
you see them on television too um
they've been offered for years
everywhere just everywhere you know
there's always somebody that comes out
with a new one and when you really look
at it and what's in it it's like okay a
little bit of this a little bit of that
a
microscopic little bit of this and that
in each tablet along with a whole bunch
usually a whole bunch of bad stuff that
shouldn't be in that tablet that medical
medium doesn't want you on um but you
know it's an easy draw it's an easy draw
because we're always we so today's show
is about is about the skin hair and
nails we're going to go into it of
what's really going on that makes these
three things get you know funky you know
not so great uh in their appearance and
everything else is it just aging is it
aging or is it something else that's
what today is about check out my thyroid
book please check it out because and I'm
saying please because I need you to be
the best expert there is like one of the
things that spirit and I have a desire
to do is to get people better so that's
one of the things and that's on the top
of the list it's always been since I was
a child is to get people better with
answers and everything else they need so
that's always been there but the other
thing is making you the expert making
you the expert because that's how it's
going to happen even if you start out uh
with little pieces of information that
aren't
misinformation real truth and you start
out with those little pieces of truth
and you can help out your family your
loved one your friend you can help out
your neighbor whatever happens if it's
not this year maybe it'll happen three
years from now where you bump into
somebody and be like hey try this hey do
this hey what about this and it matters
it's lifechanging and it matters so it's
the other part of the equation and the
thyroid book isn't just about the
thyroid it's everything first of all
it's everything about the thyroid
everything about the thyroid to know
plus I mean and it's all the
Undiscovered things about the thyroid
and what's going on with all the
illnesses we deal with that are blamed
on the thyroid it's packed really really
packed and you know you know I'm not
just blowing smoke you guys know that by
now you've read the first book medical
medium which is that's a whole another
thing people call that the Bible a lot
of people I mean you know they call it
their Bible I mean and you know that's
packed and then life-changing Foods I
didn't let you down with that it wasn't
just a a cute little picture book you
know that that uh had a you know just a
little bit of this and that and maybe a
couple sentences here and there you guys
know that thing is packed with
information and and I I hear it I didn't
let people down I didn't let people down
with that one but this one here this one
here this you will be an expert in
chronic illness not just of course in
the thyroid Health but chronic illness
and that matters to me matters to me
greatly so check it out if you can lock
one down and uh you know it's it's
really important that everybody learns
and and learns in a fun easy way and and
just you know it doesn't have to be
complicated it does in truth and real
answers and real information doesn't
have to be complicated but you know
what's funny is they're making it
complicated out there they're making it
complicated because they don't know
what's wrong with people you know they
don't know the industries don't know
what's wrong with why so many millions
and millions and millions of people in
the US alone are sick with chronic
illness with no answers with no answers
and the answers they get whether it's
labels or whatever is still a mystery
it's still a mystery every every bit
about it and you guys know that by now
come on and you know that by listening
to the show right and and because of all
that we need to change that we need to
change that we really do and so they
make it complicated they blame you they
blame you it's you your body attacking
itself it's your genes you got bad
faulty jees it's your problem there your
DNA is all screwed up and they blame it
on you and that's how it's done that's
how it's done from the top that's the
trickery from the top the problem is
good-hearted good-hearted loving
compassionate professionals have to
follow the misinformation that's from
the top because they have nowhere else
to go they don't have a voice that's
telling them what the truth is in their
ear so they have no choice but they'll
learn the stuff that's complicated and
then just then it just gets Trinkle on
down the line and it has to change it
has to change anyway we're back we're
back on we're back on skin hair and
nails okay so let's let's uh let's start
diving into this so what happens with
the skin why are we so concerned with
the skin we're concerned because we can
have all kinds of stuff wrinkles it's
one thing people are worried about they
don't like wrinkles no one likes
wrinkles right so that's one thing the
other thing is you know any kind of skin
blemishes scars s on the skin the whole
bit so when someone gets a scar they get
a little cut they get a burn a burn SCAR
or something like that they bump into
their stove something happens um they
get cut with their their cuddly knife
they're they their vegetable fruit or
you know um food knife at their cutting
board and they cut their finger or they
cut something and there's a scar and no
one likes scars and Anything could
happen you know you can you can just you
know scratch the leg somehow and
um and and and whatever it is we worry
about the skin for so many reasons and
facial we don't like acne hey that's why
I did you know did the acne show the
acne show right and we don't like we
don't like the uh we don't like the acne
in the today's world and we don't like
scarring from acne and we don't like any
of that so we're always trying to
improve skin bags under our eyes all
that whole thing and there's a million
lotions and tonics lotions tonics skin
tonic skin lotions I know I said that
twice already and we're always looking
for the miracle topical thing I'm just
going to have to deliver this to you I'm
going to have to deliver this bad news
to you I'm going to have to there's no
topical miracle cure there's no topical
miracle cure for skin problems there
are there but but listen there are
topical
anti-viral anti- cancer you know solves
you know we can make and put together
and and so forth to try to you know put
put on the skin and on skin issues that
people are really concerned about
there's stuff like that all right
there's creams to soften skin a little
bit and moisturize skin but it's not
going to fix skin problems in a way that
we want want that's why people go to
plastic surgery and people go to Botox
cuz theyve tried hundreds of creams
before they end up going to Botox then
we got a whole young crowd now doing
Botox so Botox is so in at this point we
have all the you know 18 19 20 year olds
doing Botox now 22 year olds 23 year
olds in fact it's so in it's it's just
it's just part of the culture of today
and it's about getting the skin is tight
as possible getting the skin as Flawless
as possible but all this all of it all
of it all of it isn't the answers truly
as far as where skin problems go wrong
to begin with why we wrinkle why the
skin loosens up why it ages why all
these different things go on why we get
all these weird blemishes we get liver
spots and everything else liver spots
exactly that's a clue that's a clue
that's a clue liver spots that's a clue
the clue is it's deeper it's deeper when
it comes down to skin it's deeper so we
need to always know that we need to
always understand that so we can get our
skin to last longer without having to
manipulate the skin in other ways to be
you know to feel good or look good or be
accepted in today's society which we're
going into you know back in the
70s back in the 70s and the 60s you know
your skin was your skin there was really
no plastic surgery not really successful
plastic surgery I'll tell you that right
right now there there's no question
about it and Botox wasn't around and
your skin was your skin that's just the
way it was it was the 60s it was the 70s
and you know and you had to you had to
you had to live with it now we have
these options that make us feel like
let's not try anything else let's not go
deep let's not go deep down into the
body to try to heal something or fix
something let's just hurry up and get
the botox I'm not saying I'm not saying
if you got talkx it was the wrong thing
to do or bad or whatever look you got to
do how you feel you got to do you right
you got to do you I was talking to
somebody recently and they're like look
I want to do me you know and I was like
you know what and that's where I heard
that I was like hey that's pretty cool
do me so yeah so you have to do you
exactly right that's the hip thing and
um and I respect that and I honor that
and if it's what makes you feel good
it's what gets you up in the morning
it's what gets you in a better place in
your life I support it 100% okay I'm not
a big fan of Botox but I support what
makes you feel better and if that's what
you have to do I support it I want you
to know that I respect it I support it
I'm behind you you know what happens is
that there also this thing if someone
doesn't feel good they don't feel good
mentally they don't feel good
emotionally about how they feel about
themselves how they look and all that
then and and then I have to honor that
because that doesn't work for them
either if someone's miserable all day
long and they're miserable
and every morning they're miserable cuz
they feel like you know that they have
to they that that Botox will change
their life and change that I'm on board
someone's that
miserable um you know and they're so
depressed and they're just like you know
what I need I need to do this because I
can't I can't face people at work I
can't there's something inside of
someone that's really bringing them down
and then I understand why someone would
do that so hey I support if someone
needs to do them do themselves they need
to be themselves in some way but but but
but let's address I like doing things
naturally deep down inside let's address
what creates skin problems deep down
inside let's address what creates
problems deep down inside so you know
and listen if you're someone who hasn't
gotten Botox or anything I'm not trying
to tell you to go running off and and
get that you know that don't run off and
get that I want you to addess what's
deep inside that's the way I handle
things and want to handle things but as
I said before if that's what you've done
I stand behind you too and you should
still you should still go deep down
inside and do some healing down there so
even if you had say plastic surgery even
if you had cosmetic surgery even if you
had Botox I want you 100% still doing
things to take care of what's inside
because that's going to help you for
everything and every
reason okay so that that's what matters
so skin problems the liver the liver the
liver it plays such a role in aging and
skin problems and wrinkles and and
everything else the liver the liver gets
toxic our livers get toxic they come
here toxic from our parents yeah they
come here um toxic from forefathers they
come here with DDT in them from a 100
years ago they come with heavy metals
from a thousand years ago they come with
plastics they come with petrol oil from
our parents pumping their own gas okay
they come with that the livers and we
come into town with these livers you
know what I mean and these livers Harbor
a lot of toxins a lot of poisons and we
can get fatty liver we can get all kinds
of liver problems I know this isn't a
liver show and um which we did in the
past and we do another one in the future
too but but that's one of the places
it's like the that's the area that's
origin the origin one of the Origins so
it's not about how to carry your skin on
the outside so much sure there's there's
some really good natural moisturizers
moisturizers with essential oils there's
all kinds of different options out there
to get the skin to look flashy to look
cleaner to look a certain way to feel
moist whatever it's all good but you
still want to address what's deep down
inside and that that's so critical so
when it comes down to skin it's about
getting your liver better a big part of
it and we're going to talk about what
makes skin hair nails not so great and
the liver for the skin is one of those
things so when it comes down to that
that's where we are so what happens down
in there your liver is is receiving a
tremendous amount of blood it's pumping
in it's pouring in it's a river of blood
gushing into that and into that liver a
river of blood it's got oxygen it's got
a lot of things things going on there
nutrients you name it and the liver but
it's got a ton of poisons in there too
just pumping into the liver liver has to
filter out clean it process it get it
ready get it ready to send back up to
the heart get it ready to send back all
to the other places getting ready to
send back to you so that blood is
cleaner and gets to your epidermis your
epidermis your skin you cut your skin
right there that epidermis there right
there you cut that little top layer that
little little hunk of epidermis tissue
right there you cut that it bleeds you
scratch that it bleeds how is that
possible cuz blood seeps all the way up
through the uh subcutaneous fat level
level that's underneath there and it
seeps right through and it and it just
finds its way in the epidermis the blood
the oxygen everything travels through
tiny microvessels and it gets there and
it
nourishes nourishes the skin all those
little blood vessels the liver nourishes
the skin yeah your heart pumps the blood
of course pumping blood through your
body your blood's being pumped you got a
pump you got a pump like a water pump in
a car yeah sure you have that you got
the pump and um like a sub pump in a
basement like a water pump in a car like
uh like whatever you know what I mean
and so the deal is though that's the
liver that has to be the responsible one
to make sure that blood's prepped ready
go clean good whatnot if that liver is
sending up sending up
material in that blood it's not so great
you're going to age fast you're going to
get the liver spots yeah you're going to
get all kinds of stuff it's going to
start worsening in the skin you're going
to get wrinkles you're going to get flab
your skin you're going to get all kinds
of different stuff with the skin so it's
not about toning the skin although
that's the topical stuff tone the skin
you go to the Spas you get all these
treatments you get seaweed wraps
everything else Under the Sun I get it
cucumbers in the eyes I understand that
cucumber slices hey that's right
cucumber slice spces totally exactly
those cucumbers hey yay for cucumbers
okay Harrah
Harrah right exactly those darn
cucumbers they're Miracles right you got
to do the cucumber juice hey which
brings me back do the cucumber juice do
the cucumber juice 16 o straight
cucumbers don't just stick cucumbers in
a blender and blend it up with some
water you can do that but I don't really
like the way that tastes so much all
right so um hey I think I'm in a better
mood today myself I don't know I think
I'm in a good mood today I'm not so
heavy heavy like I usually am when I'm
so worried all the time about people and
the misinformation out there right you
guys you know I get all passionate and
razed up but here's the deal here's the
deal you get the cucumber juice 16
ounces of cucumber juice 20 ounces of
cucumber juice whatever you you get it
you drink it once a day it does help the
liver it does help the liver somebody
had it right when they sliced those
cucumber slices and stuck them in
people's eye
sockets somebody had it right all right
and and so that's what you need to do um
to help the liver right there you know
listen you can help the liver with all
kinds of things stay away from the fried
greasy Foods stay away from high fat
foods if you're a Paleo dude if you're a
Paleo chick you just just cut the fat
levels down that means make sure that
Meats the leanest you could find and
only have it once a day because you need
room for all those fruits and vegetables
that's going to cleanse your liver
because a piece of lean meat whether I
like it or not or whatever whether
Spirit likes it or not or you like it or
not a piece of lean meat does not heal
the liver that's not how it works that
that doesn't help your liver but I
support it 100% if someone I support all
diets you want you know paleo diet love
you want vegan diet love whatever I
support it all but the point is I'm
talking about what's going to help the
liver so if you if you think you got
some liver stuff going on you want your
skin really nice you cut your animal
protein down in half I'm not telling you
you have to quit it that's not my job
I'm not the food police I'm not the food
police okay I'm just giving you some
pieces of truth and you can take it you
can throw it away but I would take it
I'd cut the animal protein in half have
it once a day your favorite one okay
make sure it's the clean and lean stuff
so it's not so load it with fats stay
off the butter stay off the cheese stay
off the eggs and and keep your fats low
so if you like your salmon you like your
you know you like your hbit you like
your hache you like your salmon um you
know that's that can work too if you
like your lean you know lean chicken
breast if you like your lean turkey
breast that could work too free range
farm raised in a good Farm the whole bit
you know antibiotic free that's great
you know grass-fed beef the lean stuff
not the brisket that's filled with fat
all that fat in the brisket not the pork
stay away from the stay away from the
pork okay stay away from that because
that's not going to help your skin it's
going to age your skin it's going to age
it okay yeah sure your skin might have
got better because you cleaned up your
diet yeah but it got better maybe
because you stopped you know donuts and
you stopped bagels and you stopped you
canoli and you stopped danishes and you
stopped a lot of that and and maybe you
stopped fr food and maybe you stopped
really greasy fried bad oils and sure it
got better but it could get even better
it could get even better if you keep the
animal proteins down a notch the reason
why is your skin needs something so
critical you guys I'm going to tell you
right now what it is it's not just clean
blood it's not just the river of clean
blood coming from that
liver your skin needs the beta carotenes
and there's no beta carotene in a high
fat diet there's no beta carotene in a
really high animal protein diet and
people eat vegan diets with no beta
carotene in there either I'm not picking
on the meat eaters I'll pick on the
vegans why not I'll pick on the
vegetarians I'll pick on everybody then
okay and what I'm saying is you can have
a vegetarian diet and have virtually no
Betty kattin in that diet that's right
that's right okay and and what happens
is that skin needs it
desperately where do those beta keratin
go come from they come from leafy greens
leafy greens so you have your chicken
salad and some leafy greens spinage
chicken salad right that's what you
really like if you're vegan you have the
spinach and you throw in some fruit in
there throw in anything in your salad if
you're vegan hey you know you probably
already know but you don't want less
beta carotene where else does the beta
carotene come from comes from the
powerful color and those mangoes
mangoes but if you're mango afraid or
papaya afraid papayas are incredible the
beta keratin the keratins keratinoid in
papaya are incredible for the skin
lifechanging for the skin that papaya
because those keratins get right up up
through that subcutaneous fat they get
driven in the river of blood your liver
knows you need those keratins for your
skin but but if you don't provide with
the liver with what it knows then it's
sending up blood that's deficient of
what it
needs that's right that's right so you
need that River blood loaded with those
keratins you could even get slightly
orange skin which is a beautiful thing a
beautiful thing that occurs when you've
been eating a lot of papaya a lot of
mangoes a lot of sweet potatoes a lot of
Mam Mam is like a um you know a fruit
that's that not a lot of people can find
that's more of a tougher One beta
keratin lot of raspberries okay but
especially things like the mangoes the
papayas um and it melons with color in
them melons with color have a lot of
beta Kines and then in the vegetable
Department leafy green spinach spinach
is like one of the ultimate beta
carotene
providers it re it really is and that is
incredible for the liver liver can use
spinach to cleanse cleanse out poisons
cleanse out toxins right you guys
cleanse out all those Metals cleanse out
everything but the liver can also take
all that carotene and what it does is it
tags that carotene it tags it and it
changes it and manipulates it a little
bit it makes it capable of surviving the
travel up to the
skin it makes it possible to travel to
the skin it works with it the liver is
the the machine that changes and Alters
compounds chemical compounds it's the
chemical compound master and so it
Alters those keratin and it sends it
back up to the Derma didn't I tell you I
was going to give you information never
heard before didn't I tell you didn't I
tell you I told you that in a couple
shows ago maybe comes from Spirit that's
what I'm talking about and it's not
misinformation this stuff is powerful it
is powerful and it is real so that's
what the liver does what it does is it
tags those catenoids it Chang ches them
it Alters them it allows a form of
methylation no one has their hands on
yet in science or research a form of
methylation different than other
methylations that we talk about and it
it packages it and it sends it on its
way fueled what I mean by fueled is the
blood is fueled in a different way to
take the keratine up in there if the
liver knows keratins are going to go to
the skin it's going to make sure oxygen
supply is more so in that package that's
being delivered up through the blood up
to the skin and that's how it's done so
if your salad just has some iceberg
lettuce and it has a little kind of you
know an orange tomato that's not so
great got some chicken or tuna in there
that's your lunch with a little mayo I
don't know what people do they make the
may they you know whatever the yeah the
mayonnaise the whole bit or you got an
egg in your salad and you got you know
couple of tomatoes maybe you a couple
little tiny pieces of cucumber
and a couple of eggs in your salad and
and and yeah some tuna and some other
things or some sliced cold cuts in your
salad the antipasta salads or whatever
it's not enough it's not enough got to
get piece of papaya out have that for
breakfast you got to do your heavy metal
detox cleanse clean clean out that liver
of all the pesticides of all the heavy
metals get them out right you got to do
more and if it's overwhelming if it
feels too much take take it slow take it
slow you know slow ride just take it
easy and then take it slow that's the
bottom line and that's okay that there's
nothing wrong with that either so kot
kotes mean everything when it comes to
skin how the skin looks what it does it
means everything and then there's
something else too there's silica hidden
in vegetables and stems of vegetables
that matter for the skin that tighten
the skin silic that's just geared for
the skin not silica geared for the bones
there's two different kinds science
doesn't know that yet science doesn't
actually know science and research I'm
going to give you another science fact
that will come out years down the road
and silica for the bones is different
than silica for the skin they're two
different kinds two different kinds
science hasn't T hasn't separated them
yet and the kind that just goes for the
skin up to the skin is one variety of
silica that the liver works on making
sure you know you're provided and that's
through
asparagus those beautiful
asparagus okay that's one place it comes
from
artichokes artichokes which is
incredible for the liver lots of silicon
artichokes if you look up artichokes and
you find there's no silicon in there
it's because they just didn't they just
didn't add that part in did you know
artichokes have a thousand chemical
compounds vitamins mineral subgroups
amino acids everything undiscovered
science research just isn't getting it
done in the lab same way other things
don't work in this world where nothing
gets done in all that systematic stuff
that you know that whole realm you know
what I'm talking about how nothing
really gets done how it takes you know
takes 30 years to get something
straightened out at the motor vehicle
okay so you don't need you don't need a
lesson on how the world works
on that level so the bottom line is is
artichokes you got the asparagus it's
really good stems little stems of the
kale have silica in them for the skin
that's another thing horse tail the herb
nettle Leaf the herb you can take horse
tail horsetail is known to help help to
help skin hair and nails that's because
of the type of silica but but it's still
it's still not the same silica that goes
to Bones technically it's still there's
two kinds that are are in horsetail
there's two kinds of silica in Nettle
Leaf there's two kinds of silica in
these other things and they get
separated by the liver and delivered
that's brand new information I'm just
putting out there for you guys so you
guys have things to heal and you know
these are just different things for the
skin we're talking about now the big
skin I hope we can get to Hair and Nails
I swear the big skin thing all the time
is protein protein protein protein
protein protein you need protein you
need protein oh my God dear God if I
hear protein one more time out there
okay because it's literally just all
people kind of know in the health realm
professional realm is is protein they've
been brainwashed to thinking protein
stands for everything it doesn't it
doesn't I can go I could do a show just
on protein and yeah people will throw
Rotten Tomatoes at me and rotten
potatoes at me and stones and rocks and
they'll have torches and pitchforks and
try to burn my house down absolutely
because that's how ingrained protein is
into the system right now you can't eat
that's like literally that's
controversial that's controversal it's
not politically correct to talk about
protein right now so I have I have to be
careful isn't that silly so the deal is
is that yes proteins are important
they're important when they come from a
kale Leaf they're important when they
come from a spinach leaf spinach they're
important from they they come from a
lentil a lentil they're important when
they come from a black bean they're
important when they come from a walnut
because those are important proteins but
those proteins that come from there
still aren't really what hair skin and
nails are are derived from or made made
out of because there's thousands and
hundreds of different of of of compounds
and chemical functions and different
minerals and vitamins and subgroups that
I'm talking about that are
responsible for Hair Skin and nails and
the liver is like the master behind that
one of the Masters especially the master
so very important to understand so you
need to know it's not about more protein
more protein the more protein you do the
more tired the liver gets though you got
to be careful the more tired the liver
gets the more protein you do so you got
to keep you like like I'm saying if you
are vegan you got to be careful you
don't do just an all vegan protein diet
you got to be careful it's not just all
protein shakes if you're a vegan you got
to be careful about that there's plenty
of protein in spirulina there's plenty
of protein in barley grass juice powder
there's plenty of protein in fruits and
vegetables there's plenty of proteins
and even sweet potatoes you got to be
careful though that as a vegan or a raw
food vegan or whatever that you're not
just trying to reach protein needs 24/7
you got to be cautious on that and if
you're a Paleo person you got to watch
out you don't over inh aate with the
animal protein you got to cut it back a
bit because it will tire out your liver
no matter how good shape you think or
you're in or how good you feel you still
will shorten the life of your liver and
affect the Hair Skin and Nails
eventually somehow some way some some
possibility if you say well how come one
person's hair skin and Nails goes bad
and the other one doesn't because I told
you you come in here with liver stuff
that you inherit some people inherit a
hell of a lot more with the liver than
other people some people have so much
stress in their life early on that their
adrenals cause problems with their liver
and adrenaline kills Hair Skin and nails
you go through a loss of a loved one
your hair a year later can be shot shot
I've watched it I've seen it for decades
you go through a trying time you get
betrayal betrayal happens which is some
of the worst things that could ever
happen is when someone betrays you oh
dear lord it's probably one of the worst
and when you're betrayed you know your
hair falls apart it could fall out of
your head it can it can just it can just
come out not just that be come out like
straw turn into to straw and if it
doesn't turn in straw that week it can
turn in straw a year later this is
because of adrenaline this is because of
you know the pain we get from fear and
insecurity and being up because we've
been Something's Happened or trustman
broken or you know a loss in Life or
financial burden or stress or whatever
it
is it cranks up the adrenaline
adrenaline's corrosive it hinders the
lier it hinders everything it's okay
it's just a natural part of life I mean
but it hinders things and it knocks the
skin back it stretches the skin and if
you're worried about you you go to a
practitioner and they're all just
talking protein and only protein it's
like just that's not the answer either
of course they give you a bunch of
supplements though different supplements
and that could improve your health but
it wasn't the protein that did you need
to know you know it's other things
supplements and everything else so just
keep that feather in your cap too for
the person that says well I went to my
doctor my doctor said I had severe
protein deficient efficiency he changed
my diet for higher protein I started
getting better but he probably gave you
10 vitamins too that you never took
before in your life and that started
clearing up some deficiencies from all
that you've been through and that's why
you're improving or took away bad foods
and you're not eating cakes and cookies
anymore realize it's not protein that is
the the answer for all and you look you
hair hair care products proteins are in
there that's ridiculous you look at all
these other things proteins are in there
that's not how it works our hair stays
good because our adrenal stay good one
way to keep hair strong is is
ashwagandha and it's an herb that you're
familiar with probably some of you are
ashwagandha I you know I I I have it on
the directory at Medical medium.com I
don't sell it I don't sell supplements
just telling you that one more time I
know I talk like a broken record it's
for the new people that came on board
and and think I'm trying to be a
Salesman I I want you to get my book but
that's not to sell it I just want you to
get it for health and wellness and and
well-being I want it to change your life
I want it to save your lives but the
deal is you can go and get the
ashwaganda bring that into you can talk
to your practitioner but that's an
amazing very powerful very fruitful very
fruitful herb to make hair turn around
that's a great one it supports the
adrenals it does help the hair I've seen
people do ashwaganda for two months and
hair change so that's something to just
always know that information's out there
but I've been telling people about that
long before the internet and that so
that's information's out there I don't
know where it originally sourced from it
could have come from me easily but the
deal is and it could have come from me
20 years ago the deal is you bring in
the Ashana nettle Leaf nettle Leaf is
another very fruitful powerful way for
women to get hair back nettle Leaf do
the nettle Leaf teas nettle Leaf teas
okay drinking a nettle leaf tea great
way to get hair back lemon balm tea
great way to get hair back lemon balm
tin ures I also have the in the
directory nettle tinctures I have in the
directory nettle capsules the right in
the right kinds they get hair back
here's the deal you look at a skin hair
um formula skin hair nails formula it
might have horse tail in it but I can't
even tell you how ridiculously small
amount of horse tail that could be in
there a speck because it's it's made of
fillers and plus all these other things
maybe herbs maybe amino acids it's all
packed in this tablet but if you took
out the horse tail it would be Joker's
host you horse tail Joker's horsetail
like no joke so if you took out the
nettle Leaf in something it would be
Joker's nettle leaf and probably a
crappy kind when you take nettle Leaf
you know like three capsules a day when
you take dropper FS of nettle Leaf daily
you get the hair back and by the way
that also reflects back into the liver
and helps the liver too cuz liver has a
lot to do with hair if your liver is
maxed out if you're getting a maxed out
liver whether the doctor sees it or not
hair can start becoming problem
problematic falling out all kinds of
different issues dermatitis on the scalp
eczema can occur psoriasis I talked
about aiment psoriasis in the other show
and that could play a role in some some
scalp issue skin you know skin issues on
the head hair loss with that as well
alopecia alope IA isn't an autoimmune
disease where the body's attacking the
hair follicles and the hair falls out
that's misinformation once again the
blame is on us for um you know for it
being our fault because medical science
and research doesn't know it causes
alopecia don't I sell sound snarky and
and sarcastic now today so I have to I
can't help it I can't help it I'm not
perfect I can't help it but you know
what it is is that the alope ship you
know people who have that they're told
their bodies destroying the air follicle
so it's the body's fault no it's an
adrenal issue there's a hormone missing
out of the adrenal it's one of the
because people think medical research
and medical science thinks that
adrenaline is just made out of two
things like cortisol and epinephrine and
and no it's not it's a complicated
divide it's a
complicated um group group of hormones
really complicated science hasn't
stripped them apart and one of those
hormones coming out of the adrenals
that's undocumented undiscovered by
Medical Science and medical research is
missing missing for the woman that has
alopecia it's missing and that's why so
the aagana can be a great support to
help get that back so a trace of that
can come back to the adrenal and get
hair to grow back I've had people with
alipa lost all their hair nothing could
get it back and then it's come back with
doing all the right things getting the
liver better getting the adrenals better
see the deeper deeper issues deep down
inside so um we're going to have to
listen to this show again because I'm
going so fast with with the
information taking a deep breath deep
breath for you too take a deep breath in
we'll do a meditation now take a deep
breath in and take a deep breath out
relax exhale so um we talked about
adrenaline stress and damage causing
hair problems hair falling out can
happen months after a breakup a breakup
um uh husband and wife break up
girlfriend boyfriend break up and and it
can happen just like that uh lose a
soulmate something happens and months
later and then it can stay falling out
for quite some time because there's
nothing being replenished properly I
like spirina helps bring back hair I
like barley grass juice powder helps
bring back hair I talk to nettle Leaf
the lemon bomb ashwaganda helps bring
back hair these are some of the powerful
things that does help milk thistle can
help bring back hair a little bit milk
thistle for the liver zinc can help
bring back hair and help skin let's go
to um um oh yes silica products I would
do the other silica products so not just
horsetail or not just the silica that I
was talking about that comes from the
artichoke you can do the other type of
silica for bones it does also help with
other things so I do want silica
products in general I like them I put I
have a couple of silica products on the
directory as well so some of the things
to think about Foods Foods figs figs are
wonderful wonderful for hair figs figs
are wonderful for anything um as far as
with women with all kinds of issues with
women reproductive systems hair skin
nails figs are a big deal get the dried
figs if you can't get the the the um
other figs
I know what some of you are thinking
you're like well I can't eat sugar I
can't eat a fig I can't eat sugar well
that's just I'm sorry but that the
belief system you have to you have to
break a little bit I had to break all my
belief systems I had to break them all
you know Spirit taught me to break
through my belief systems and spirit
said I had no choice I said no no I have
a choice I I'm my own person I could
have a belief system and spirit said no
you can't if you're going to help people
you can't have a belief system cuz it's
going to be something different for for
someone else and it's going to be a
problem that they need to do and someone
who's told they can't have sugar from
fruit that's a belief system instilled
and if you have that same belief system
you can't help that person spirit said
when I was younger said no you you can't
do this then you're you're not cut for
this job I remember when I said to
Spirit good I don't want the job when I
was a kid I was I don't want the job
spirit said too bad yeah you have the
job we can't change that you have the
job so you have to survive this I said
all right I busted through my belief
systems when I was younger and
so um figs and uh cherries cherries are
also really good for the liver very good
for the liver wild blueberries are
really good for the liver too in fact
the most powerful food for the liver but
cherries are good for the liver too so
look for Cherries Berries of all kinds
are good for the liver berries of all
kinds are good for hair skin
nails um and uh and then like I told
told you about for skin the papayas the
mangoes remember that
bananas bananas bananas are great for
the liver great for the intestinal tract
flushing out poisons at the liver
ascending down to the intestinal tract
so those are great for hair skin nails
now potassium is a critical element for
the skin potassium is it comes from figs
it comes from avocados it comes from
bananas that's a good one too all right
now Omega-3s are really good for the
skin as well so they're really good
Omega-3s hemp seeds walnuts if you're
sensitive to walnuts cuz some people are
sensitive to nuts and that's true they
are I mean to people everybody's
different exactly so why I had to break
all my belief systems because someone
might not farewell with a walnut they
get sensitive they get they get the
funny kind of feeling from the tannins
of the walnut in their mouth and they
don't like that but the deal is walnuts
are really helpful for skin hair and
nails they're helpful for the liver um
you know hemp seeds like I was talking
before sprouted
lentils that's a different kind of
protein when you sprout the lentil the
protein divides into a carbohydrate
turns into a
glycogen that carbohydrate is incredible
for the skin hair and nails sprouted
lentils learn how to sprout lentils we
can help you you know go on my Facebook
group hop on the you know the uh the
Facebook group and just and ask about
how to sprout lentils
um so all these things matter so let's
go to nails for a little bit white spots
in the nails divots in the nails messed
up Nails in all kinds of ways um ridges
in the nails you guys what else you tell
me what else what else happens with the
nails pockets in the nails someone said
that little bubbles in the nails did
someone say that one um the half moon
goes away did someone say that one did
you say that one okay so yeah so these
you know the in the Nails you have all
these different problems one of the one
of the biggest reasons for that um is
zinc deficiencies real real zinc
deficiencies longstanding pumpkin seeds
pumpkin seeds Aren't Enough at first
though you but you need to do the
pumpkin seeds by the way the Omega-3s
from pumpkin seeds are really good for
Hair Skin and Nails Mega 3s Mega 6 is
for um um also in um sesame seeds are
good too but let's go back to this the
nails you get the bumps in the nails the
bridges you get the white spots you get
the you know the divots you get the
pockets you get the whole bit and that's
zinc deficiency partly zinc deficiency
the other part is a liver issue a liver
issue that's the other part of all the
nail problems that's adrenaline it's a
lot of adrenaline you've been exposed to
in your life from certain circumstances
whether it's been falling in love so you
know falling in love the first part of
Falling in Love Is is explosively
wonderful but takes a toll usually a lot
of people who fall in love the first
time they fall in love that very first
time where it's like that magical moment
you feel inside of you that's hormones
that are produced by your adrenals
that's the mix it's one of the 56
different blends that I've brought to
the table if you're new to the show and
you've never read book one you got to
learn about the 56 different blends of
adrenaline that don't exist in research
and science I don't care what books out
there I don't care what experts out
there and the top health expert they
don't know about it um yeah I'm boasting
for Spirit not boasting for myself I'm
boasting for spirit so so that explosive
falling in love thing it's like a it's
like a time bomb though in a sense
meaning like it's the most wonderful
beautiful special thing and at the same
time it wears and tears on the body and
that's why we've naturally the love
turns into a
compassionate deeper love that that's
more so than the surface explosion love
when you first meet somebody it then
goes into a companionship love a forever
love a a love of you know that soulmate
love it turns into a deeper love where
the adrenaline's aren't the adrenals
aren't surging to that degree anymore
but falling in love at the very first
time that's when a lot of people come
down with mono that's when a lot of
people come down with mono they fall in
love for the first time and they they're
up all night in love and they're they're
spending time with that person that
they're in love with and they're
thinking about the person 24 day 24
hours a day and they're not sleeping for
those first few weeks and and all the
adrenaline is pumping and surging
through their body and hormones is
surging through their body and they come
down with mono or the worst strep threat
they've ever had that happens for 70% of
the people that fall in love and but at
the same time that causes a deficiency
falling in love causes a physical
deficiency even though it helps heal the
soul too you know it's healing for the
soul it's a it causes a deficiency so
that's why you got to make sure the
fruits and vegetables and everything we
talk about are in there the herbs
everything are in there no matter what's
going on and then it's not just falling
in love it's falling out of love meaning
something happening in a relationship
that takes the toll the worst that's
much worse that's when the stress comes
on that's when the hardship comes on
that's when the Heartbreak comes on and
that really breaks down the immune
system the divorces and everything else
we just life goes through and people go
through we all go through whatever
happens in life and and that takes a
toll and guess what suffers from it the
nails they get paper thin brittle and
beaten down the liver gets beaten down
so we got to restore we have to restore
and it's not Protein that's the answer
your nails are falling apart it's
minerals it's vitamins it's not protein
it's minerals and its vitamins and
that's the key always remember that so
those nails are falling apart you want
to make sure you got the zinc the
selenium I would get the selenium
supplement I would get the manganese
supplement okay so manganese ionic
manganese check out you know check it
all out in my directory like I said so
you get the right one you don't get one
with citric acid one with poison in it
one that's just broken down all the
wrong way but you the manganese okay the
malinam hey I said that right today
malinam that's tongue twister look at
look at the word and say that one that's
such tongue twister it's not even funny
miminum selenium
manganese okay um and and zinc zinc's
the big one make sure you bring these in
do a little bit of this for a month and
what's going to happen is your nails are
going to get better bring in the silica
too bring in the silica silica is not
straight protein it's not that's not
what it is bring in the silica see and
the nails start getting better eat more
fruits and vegetables cleanse the liver
get the liver stronger stronger and your
nails will start getting better
spirulina has protein in it but it's the
keres and the spirulina that get the
skin better very
important very important the ashwagandha
gets the adrenal stronger that's why
hair grows back with ashwagandha that's
another thing that really helps the more
you cleanse your liver though and clean
it up and don't hamper it down with too
many animal fats or if you're vegetarian
or vegan too much plant protein that's
powdered or you know or in you know gobs
of empty plant protein that's thrown in
packages because vegans feel that
they're in fear that they better keep up
with protein that could wear down the
liver right so you see what I'm saying
so I'm giving you everything I got and
I'm not picking on one particular diet
I'm in it for you I'm in it for you okay
and you're doing your part if you try
one little thing and that makes me have
to do my part over here cuz cuz I got to
do it if I don't do my part then what
the heck got to do my part you guys um
okay all right so the Omega-3s I talked
about earlier look for an omega-3 fish
oil isn't the omega-3 of choice that you
want for Hair Skin and Nails you want
the plant-based even if you're paleo if
you're paleo even if you're eating
salmon it's the oils that they put
together in krill and fish oil they are
so highly concentrated that there's a
level of methyl mercury in them even the
Mercury free ones that claim they're
Mercury free they're not Mercury free I
promise you they're not Mercury free you
want the plant-based omega-3 oils check
out my information in fish oil and my
books and all that okay you know learn
from
that and um so that's another great
thing too so all these vitamins these
minerals that I'm talking about these
nutrients and these herbs help
peppermint is a powerful liver res
restorative peppermint peppermint tees
do lots of herbal pepper mes oregano oil
which kills bacteria and viruses does
really good though for the liver because
it lowers the viral and bacterial load
in the liver that that bogs down the
liver olive leaf lowers the bacterial
and and and um viral level in the liver
so those are good too and then like I
said the Melissa the lemon bomb that's
amazing for a whole bunch of different
reasons as well um so we're coming we're
coming to the end of this so the liver
is responsible for so much and it's not
a liver show but it's responsible for so
much with hair skin and Nails the
adrenals are responsible for with hair
skin and nails when we get sick and our
immune systems break down and epine bars
and all kinds of other viruses and and
bacteria also proliferate and they grow
and they they start to consume us in a
way they release a lot of toxins and a
lot of neurotoxins the body has to use
all its reserves and vitamins and
minerals
to to to to clean that up and and fight
for us so all these things do matter but
remember the foods if you can't do
supplements for some reason and you're
somebody who's sensitive the foods
matter with hair skin and Nails bring in
more lettuces red leaf lettuce
butterleaf lettuce for the Omega-3s
butterleaf lettuce has all the Omega-3s
in it bring that in every single day
you'll watch your life change bring in
your celery juice for your liver do the
Cucumber juices hydration is the other
fact for the skin people go through life
so chronically dehydrated that their
skin literally is deficient of water
from long-term chronic dehydration so
start doing the lemon water for your
skin too so I'm trying to give you every
piece I can in the allowed amount of
time we have today you know when Spirit
gave me the
gift spirit said this gift isn't for me
so it wasn't for me I was like ooh a
gift I can hear a voice perfectly clear
and I I've seen Spirit twice in my whole
life standing in front of me perfectly
clear and you know I told you you know
that I've seen spirit and and the spirit
that speaks to me and I was given this
gift hey it's a gift for me spirit said
this gift isn't for you this gift is for
everyone else that's what it's for it's
I'm I'm not gifted for me you know it it
it's I'm gifted for you you you get the
gift you get it this gift is yours I'm
handing it to you wherever I can can and
I'm going to keep handing it to you
wherever I can as well because I want
you to heal and I want you to get better
and I want you to get the information
you need you know take one day at a time
three steps up two steps back you're
going to heal don't feel you can't heal
no matter what you stay strong keep that
conviction you keep that that faith it
all matters you need a little extra
support with those things download my
free healing path if you've heard it
before listen to it one more time
because all of it counts I stand behind
you guys I love you guys dearly I'm with
you 100% in your healing processes in
your healing process um check out the
thyroid book you won't be disappoint
appointed lock one down when you can and
you're you're going to love it you're
going to love it um a lot of
professionals are going to have to
adjust they're going to have to adjust
to it because you're going to be like oh
my God I didn't know the thyroid did
that and I didn't know what was really
behind thyroid illness and thyroid
disease For the First Time The
information's getting out there so it's
going to be an adjustment period for
everybody but it's going to be well
worth it bless you bless your heart
bless your soul
bye-bye