[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 20 30 years to
wait for answers but Today's Show is a
little different Today's Show is a
little different and of course you know
we have chronic illness that's involved
in this and there's a part of how that
works but Today's Show is about your
Soul's gold so that's what it's all
about today your Soul's gold so I want
to go right into it this is really an
important show and um and if I say fast
in your seat belt it's because on an
emotional level of just getting in touch
with what's really happening it it it is
a seat belt Fastener so I I kind of
would do that would relax and get some
herbal tea or something and chill out a
little bit and just uh find a
comfortable space somewhere in the house
or at the office or wherever you are in
a car and but just know just know that
this show is about all of us who have
gone through anything anything anything
challenging any kind of struggle any
kind of difficulty any kind of adversity
in life any kind of
Challenge and confrontation just in
general with anything around us it
struggles and hardships losses all of
this this show really is about all of
that and about who we become when we're
when we're pushed to this degree of
whatever it may be and especially in
chronic illness especially in chronic
illness look when we're sick and we
don't feel good and we we don't feel
well and that could range from anything
from getting an answer from a doctor
after going to 10 doctors whether the
answer is right or wrong or we have a
label or don't have a label or we have
mystery symptoms that aren't getting
diagnosed and they don't make sense to
anyone and they get in a way in our life
and makes us feel like we're diminishing
in our life we're aging before our time
even if it's a simple th problem even if
it's a um um um condition like crippling
anxiety and we feel like something's
going on and we're aging and and we're
not getting answers or we're not being
able to perform our best we're not we're
not able to do our best and we feel like
everybody else around us maybe they're
they're able to do what they need to do
you know I always say like the reindeer
can all play and and there's he can't
play in the reindeer games when you're
challenged with some kind of chronic
illness or some kind of struggle in that
way so and there's there's millions of
people yes they have these struggles and
they have these physical struggles and
these different symptoms like maybe a
severe depression or a mild depression
maybe a
fatigue a fatigue that's unex you know
unexplainable that we don't get answers
for it of course we talk about all the
answers for those things in in these
shows on the medical medium radio shows
but what happens is though we tend to
feel more insecure when we get an
illness or a symptom or a condition we
feel more insecure we lose confidence we
lose
confidence and and it's really it's
really it's a challenging thing all on
its own to lose confidence confidence
that you once had or confidence that you
know you grew up with building and
getting instilled inside of you
and then all of a sudden something that
doesn't make sense at all and I've seen
this happen to younger people younger
people they they've they they're doing
they're you know they're living life
they're going through school they're
going through middle school high school
something happens where they're starting
to get sick nobody has any answers or
maybe they just get funneled into the
Lyme disease trap where now it's just
all Lyme disease even though that's
really not what's going on and so you
know it's it's this whole thing that
occurs and then and then it's like hey
wait a minute what about my future and a
lot of young people they get they get
scared and it their confidence just
starts to wne and waxes and wanes and
just starts to diminish and then
insecurities can build up and then PTSD
post-traumatic stress disorder
post-traumatic stress syndrome you know
it's just it just it starts to it starts
to then compile and then anything from
obsessive compulsive disorder can
develop like OCD because when you get
sick and and and the ground you're
standing on doesn't feel so sturdy and
strong we tend to you know we tend to
lose balance and he can even have a
symptom of balance loss where you got
the vertigo and everything else but even
with any symptom any condition your
footing just isn't feeling like it's as
strong as it is the confidence isn't
there a lot of the young people suffer
from migraines and then there's older
people that are still young of course
and then there's people that just when
you get in the groove you're getting
your career right you know everything's
falling pieces are falling in to place
in your life and you're you're feeling
better than ever and more confident than
ever and all of a sudden you know you're
in your late 30s and all of a sudden
something happens and we're getting an
illness out of nowhere and we're going
to doctor to doctor and it's just it's
just hit us in all these different ways
all at the wrong times whether we're
about to have a child or whether we
already have two children or three
children or one child and we're trying
to make ends meet and we're trying to be
you know we're trying to handle
everything and be responsible about
everything and now we're dealing with a
condition or a chronic
illness and you feel like you can't take
I've seen this I've seen this with so
many people I've seen this with people
in their late 20s and their late 30s
they can't even take care of their
children the way they would want to they
struggle to do so take care of their
families they have problems with their
spouses their partners because when
someone's sick it's not easily
understood especially if you've been the
rock all those years and all of a sudden
you're sick I mean there's so many
different
experiences or different you know
situations there's so many examples of
what I know you guys go through and so
many others do and I know it and you're
not alone you're not alone I do know
that you're not alone because
there's lots and lots of people going
through this and here's here's the thing
here's the thing so at different ages it
can hit and when it hits younger when
you're just starting life it feels like
you're just getting you're getting going
maybe you're coming out of college and
then all of a sudden you don't feel good
you got all these different symptoms you
have crippling anxiety you got
fatigue it's really difficult it's
really difficult it can hit you at your
core right in the heart hit you at the
core right in the soul right in the soul
and same thing if you're in your 40s
could be early 40s mid 40s late
40s where you've worked so hard in your
life trying to build what you've been
building and then all of a sudden now
you're spending all this time and all
this time just about your sickness or
just about your illness or just about
your symptoms and that happens at all
ages young people too they're spending
all this time thinking about their
symptoms and thinking about their
conditions and what they're eating and
it could be maddening and it could be
maddening and so it it it these
are struggles these are
struggles and these are serious
struggles and they challenge us and they
challenge us and they touch our
soul and they shape our
soul they shape our
soul and it could happen at any age
could be in your 50s and in your 50s
you're you're a grandmother or you're a
grandfather now and you're looking
forward you've worked your whole life
you're working forward to spending time
with your grandchildren you're looking
forward you're in your 60s you're
looking forward to spend time with your
grandchildren and and do different
things maybe start going places and
doing stuff that you never thought you
would that you waited your whole life to
do and you start getting sick and that
happens
too it hits at any age it hits at any
age it really does but I notice when it
hits at the younger ages when it hits at
the younger
ages something
happens to the soul to truly shape and
something happens to your being and your
growth and your spiritual growth like no
other and it can like I it can happen
like that you could spiritually grow
still being hit with anything when
you're in your 50s absolutely I've seen
people and it hits them then because
what happens is when when you get
challenged with something on this level
with the chronic illness or symptoms and
conditions or a diagnosed chronic
illness or whatever it is and you get
challenged with
it something occurs the weight and the
pressure of the challenge the weight and
the pressure does something spiritually
it causes spiritual growth like no other
spiritual growth can
create no other spiritual growth can
create and this even happens with losses
so it's not even just chronic illness
and and a lot of people with chronic
illness you guys and I'm sure you know a
lot of people with chronic illness still
have to deal with
losses and struggles on that
level and and breaks breakups with
relationships I've seen that happen all
on its own with
soulmates with you know I've seen young
married couples break up because someone
got ill so early on where it just didn't
suit the needs of one of the members in
the in the group there it's usually
usually for the most part women get they
they get the symptoms and they they get
sick men do too men do too young men do
too but mostly more women do and then
usually the guys are like whoa I'm only
24 I thought were engaged to be married
I this is definitely getting weird what
do you mean Hashimoto thyroiditis what
do you mean Lyme disease what what do
you mean possible rheumatoid arthritis
what do you mean lupus that's scary what
about my children that happens with a
lot of young people and they all get
scared and they all get scared and many
relationships they do stay together
through that process and they work
through and a lot of them disband
because of the confusion and the fear
and the and the just all part of it and
then you have losses on top of an
illness so maybe that's some maybe some
of you have experienced that there's so
many different levels that happen you
can have the losses you can have that
part in the struggles and you can have
the hardships and you can still have the
sickness and still have the illness and
that can be the hardships all on their
own is an illness and a symptom and a
condition and a chronic illness of any
kind that alone can be a struggle and
and a hardship all on its
own and when we're living like this when
we're living like this we our lives have
to change in Altar and Order in order to
sustain ourselves we have to fight like
nobody ever fought before we have to
wake up every day you know I always say
the athletes out there the athletes and
I've known some athletes that worked
every single day all they would work out
all day long they would push themselves
to the Limit whether they were they were
Runners whether they did other things
whether they were anybody snowboarders
whatever it was that they the Olympic
athletes push themselves like no other
and that doesn't compare that doesn't
compare to when you're chronically ill
and you wake up in the morning and I
have all the respect in the world for
athletes you better believe it but it
doesn't compare to when you wake up in
the morning and you have to push through
an illness because your all your mindset
all your mental capacity all your focus
is on what doctors am I seeing now where
am I going what is my practitioner say
what do I do what is it working is it
not working what do I eat how do I start
my day do I take this supplement do I
take this drug how do I live my life
what do I tell my family today how I'm
feeling who whatever how's my friends
are they even listening to me anymore
all this stuff and then some and then
whatever else is compiling onto all of
it because I'm chronically all of that
all of that is harder harder training
harder training than any Olympic Athlete
does all the sweat all the sweat that an
Olympic Athlete does and I know Olympic
I'm friends with Olympic athletes they
they're they're not upset when they hear
this because I'll tell you why in a
minute I'll tell you why I'll tell you
why and so all that sweat all that all
that grind that those athletes do and
they work out day in and day out and day
in and day out and they're building
muscle and they're pushing through and
they're doing what they got to
do all of that
doesn't even
touch what chronic illness sufferers do
as far as
athletically what they do mentally
emotionally what they do even physically
to push through an illness even just
simple unexplainable chronic fatigue we
know what causes all the different
chronic fatigues all of them all the
different labels of chronic
fatigue we know but but the point is is
even just pushing through that fatigue
pushing through all of that that is
harder that takes something else that
takes some kind of spiritual growth it
takes Soul power like none other
anywhere possible it takes Soul power
more so than if you're a cliff climber
if you climb Cliffs and You Freestyle
them and you climb them because that
because what happens is that kind of
what I'm talking about
here what I'm talking about here is a
whole different thing is a whole
different level and I know it and I know
it for
sure I know what I'm talking
about in Olympic athletes when they when
they they work and they work hard and
they work hard and they work hard what
happens is I've known Olympic athletes
that got chronically ill out of nowhere
and I'm not just talking about a food
poisoning epidemic mean I mean I mean a
episode not an epidemic a food poisoning
episode or um or just a really bad flu
and pneumonia or something like I'm not
talking about that I'm talking about a
chronic illness where they got weak in
the limbs where they were getting MRIs
Non-Stop and CAT scans Non-Stop and
doctors didn't even know what was going
on and they saw neurologist and there
were no answers and all of a sudden now
it wasn't about them working out anymore
it was about them trying to find answers
to an illness or they were getting
crippling anxiety on top of weak Limbs
and and and and and an illness coming on
have know Olympic athletes have gone
through this and they' had no answers
and I've had to help them and recover
them and they even said I've known a few
of them that have gone through illnesses
they said you know they were traveling
overseas it just happened out of nowhere
they just thought they were exhausted
and tired and never went away the
doctors had no
answers and they lost their Olympic
career they lost their chances there in
that moment at that time where they lost
that one chance for a gold medal but
they fought their way back but we had to
get their chronic illness better just
like we're getting everybody else's
chronic illness just like we're working
on it just like the information in the
books it's out there just like the shows
we're going to get you guys better
overall over time we're going to do it
one day at a time but what happens is
what I heard from them was the chronic
illness was something it was a whole
different spiritual bill it was a
building of spiritual power they've
never had before and soul it was a it
was a challenge on the
soul like no other that they've ever had
to
endure they suddenly had respect for
people who couldn't work out at
all respect for people that couldn't
work out at all that couldn't get off
their bed couldn't get off their couch
because of an illness because of
swelling in their body because of
inflammation because of of chronic
fatigue because of all kinds of
different neurological symptoms because
of everything because of anything they
couldn't get off the couch they couldn't
function and they all of a sudden had
respect it wasn't about get your butt
off the couch and start working out you
can do it what do you mean you're sick
your doctor gave you a medication you
should be fine you went to the doctor
they gave you some diagnosis they gave
you medication you should be back up and
exercising you should be doing your
weights and weightlifting they didn't
have that attitude anymore it was gone
that attitude was just
gone one one athlete said to me he was
ashamed because he knew somebody with
chronic
illness and he thought just go to the
damn doctor and that's what a lot of
normal healthy people or it doesn't mean
they're totally healthy inside no
because everybody could have a ticking
time bomb in them at any time if they're
not taking care of themselves sure you
can get sick but and you're taking care
of yourself you can beat sickness and
override it and move forward it never
gets sick again but the point is the
bottom line is when you know what's
wrong and you know what to do yes you
can when you know what to do for it you
know what's wrong you can you can heal
but this athlete felt terrible was
ashamed because knew a chronic person
with chronic illness and was like get
off that couch get get in the gym now
start pushing those weights what are you
doing what do you mean you don't feel
good go to the doctor the doctor knows
the doctor has all the information you
go to the doctor and the athlete also
said said to me he remembers when he
hurt his Achilles heel for a little bit
it healed up it was just a small injury
he was off the foot for a while and he
just kept on doing weights and other
kinds of exercises he
said he said to the person I've had
something wrong with me I had an
Achilles heel problem I persevered
through it I I pumped weights I did what
I did it healed the doctor healed it he
casted it up everything was back I had a
little PT physical therapy and I was
perfectly fine and he told his chronic
illness so what's your excuse go to the
doctor this chronic illness person says
I got this fatigue and once I start
doing anything every single thing hurts
in my body to such a degree that I can't
even do anything anymore and it makes me
worse and then three days I'm three four
five days in bed because of it and he
said that he just thought it was all an
excuse he felt terrible when he got
sick terrible he felt terrible about
being sick he had to learn what building
that soul and spiritual power really was
he told me he knew about people you know
who felt fell fine and didn't have any
real illnesses or symptoms and
conditions and they would go and travel
up some mountains they would climb a
mountain it' be a spiritual experience
and they would sit on the mountain top
and look out at the heavens look out at
the sky and they would just you know
they would just
literally they would be like putting
their hands together they'd be praying
they would be looking for spiritual
growth he said he knew people like that
that have done that and he said
that spiritual
growth wasn't anything compared to what
he had to suffer and go through when he
had chronic illness and he had to fight
to get better it was nothing like he's
ever experienced before he said it was a
lot harder a lot harder than just going
to the gym and sweating and sweating and
building muscle and staying diligent and
staying and staying competitive and
complying and complying and stating
staying competitive he said there was
nothing that was a joke it was a
joke compared to when he got sick and he
he couldn't even turn his head he'd get
a spasm and didn't even know why and the
doctors were throwing their hands up in
the air saying oh maybe you got lime
let's send the labs out maybe you got
this maybe you got multiple sclerosis
maybe you got something else and here's
a drug try this and try that he was
slowly or quickly I'm sorry quickly
learning how flawed the medical system
was in chronic illness he said Anthony
you've been telling me that for years
we've been friends and I always
respected what you did as the medical
medium he said I always respected what
you did but I never understood who you
worked on I never really understood who
you really worked
on because I know you've worked on a lot
of people and I know you worked on all
kinds of people and then all around the
world and all walks of life but and who
You'
helped but what happened was he realized
how flawed the system was he realized
how flawed science and research was he
realized how hard you have to fight and
the mountain you have to climb surpasses
the mountains that people have climbed
and sat on doing their prayers and
meditations which is a beautiful thing
nothing wrong with that if you guys have
an opportunity to do that that's
exciting but that spiritual growth he
said didn't even touch the spiritual
growth he had to face he had to face
himself he had to face fear he had to
face his confidence that he built up his
whole life he had to face everything
insecurities that he didn't even know
existed filtered it and came in and they
taunted him like demons and they they
literally ripped him the
shreds as he realized Not only was the
system flawed Not only was it was like
sand falling through his hands as he was
chronically sick and exploring every
Avenue possible and then coming to me
and begging for me for help help and I
gave him that
help and he
recovered and he said I swear to God I
will never ever ever ever ever look at
another person who's chronically sick or
has a simple symptom or has one symptom
in the way I looked at them before I
will never ever ever I have the most
compassion the deepest respect he said
to anyone who has ever struggled because
I've had to live through it myself and I
said it's too bad though it's too bad I
said it's too bad and he says what do
you mean it's too bad that you got to
experience it to see it I just wish
people that were feeling good or good
enough to function in their lives would
not have to
experience what people are going through
on that level to respect it he just said
I know I know what you're saying it's a
see it to believe it World you've said
that to me before it's a see it to
believe it it's it's only real If you
experience it I know you've told me that
all this time and I know I'm cliche to
what you've said and it's true I've
experienced it i' I've had to see it to
believe it but I'm telling you now
Anthony I will never look at another
person who's who's dealing with
something the way in the light I've seen
before because when I'm in the gym now
and I'm trying to prepare for the next
round of Olympics for that next Olympic
day and that NE next Olympic gold and
silver and bronze and I'm trying to
prepare to get that I still know it's
chump change compared to what other
people are going through you taught me
that I lived it I learned it myself and
it's chump change is what it
is that's that's that's that's
true I said to him it's true it is chump
change it is and I said look I got
respect for what you do working out as
and and to that degree training and that
having that kind of having that kind of
religious religious compl Appliance to
training like you do I know that that's
a gift all on its own and it is a gift
and I'm not disrespecting that at all on
any level on anywhere I'm not
disrespecting that at
all but it's true it's chump
change to what chronically sick people
have to endure to heal and rise out of
the Ashes to rise out of the ashes
that's rising out of the ashes like no
other it's an entirely different
challenge than working up a
sweat than working up sweat daily and
training and whatever sport or whatever
venue you're in whatever that may be
that doesn't touch what people have to
do when they're chronically
ill and you know what happens when
you've been through symptoms and
conditions and you've been through strug
struggles and hard times and you've been
challenged and you've been pushed to the
Limit and pushed to the max you know
what happens it's a weight it's pressure
and it's a weight and that pressure and
weight does something it's heavy it's so
heavy we need we need to make it light
and Airy and we can with
truth that pressure and that heaviness
that we bear that monkey on our back
that gorilla on our back that we bear
that giant
knapsack of rocks and stones that we
walk around with when we're struggling
with the symptom and condition when
we're fighting for our lives when we're
fighting for sanity when we're fighting
the demons when we're fighting
everything and we're we're dealing with
also loved ones that don't understand or
maybe understand but don't we deal with
all the things we deal with friends we
find out who our friends are really are
and who they're not and whatnot and we
just forge ahead and we have to forgive
everybody and we have to have
forgiveness and we have to train
ourselves to have forgiveness and we
have to tap into that heart and soul for
that forgiveness you know I often hear
out there about
forgiveness let me tell you something
people with symptoms and conditions and
illness and chronic illness and diseases
that have suffered and fought their way
they have to find forgiveness for the O
people around them like no
other I've talked to people and I talked
to all kinds of people over the years
people that are feeling okay or feeling
fine or whatever and living their lives
and like oh forgiveness yeah yeah I got
to tap into forgiveness got to I know I
got to talked to my my I talked to my
counselor and my counselor said it's all
about forgiving it let me tell you
something I'm going to tell you
something right now when you're dealing
with chronic illness and you guys know
and you're pushing through it's almost
like that forgiveness that you have to
have for the people around you it's a
whole another ballpark it's a whole
another challenge it's a whole another
game it pushes you to a level in a whole
another way like no other in anything
before because you have to forgive
everyone around you you just have to
maybe you're not going to forget that
cliche I can forgive I I'm never going
to forget maybe you can't forget but you
got to forgive for sure for real and you
know you have and you know you've done
you guys know how it works and then you
got to forgive yourself but you got to
forgive yourself with a level of
compassion you have to forgive yourself
with a level of comp
compassion the same level of compassion
you just have to say they know not what
they do the people around you they don't
understand my ESS they don't understand
my chronic condition they don't
understand my symptoms they don't
understand the crippling anxiety really
they're trying to understand they don't
understand I have to have compassion for
that I have to have compassion for them
for not understanding I have to forgive
them I have to forgive myself I have to
have compassion for myself I have to pet
myself on the back with everything I
have I have to have compassion for
myself to push through this and get
through this
and fight through it and rise out of the
ashes and fight through my illness and
get through this chronic situation and
get these symptoms behind us so I can
behind me so I can move forward forward
with life in other ways that I haven't
been able to do it because I've been
stifled and held back and haven't been
able to push
through and I need to do that and I need
to get that done but I I'm working on it
with everything I have but my chronic
illness holds me back holds me back but
let me tell you something it's holding
you back but it's creating something
like never before inside of you it is
building something like never before
inside of you it
is something changes within you it's not
just the Forgiveness of two others that
don't understand or whether they
understand or
not God bless them it's not just that
it's not just the Forgiveness to
yourself and having that compassion to
yourself which is critical you have to
have compassion for yourself it's not
even that something builds in the soul
something happens in the soul that could
not happen in lifetimes that could not
happen
otherwise that doesn't happen otherwise
it won't happen for someone who just
lived their life Fancy free with really
no challenges all the way to the end and
just passed away later later later on
their soul won't be like
yours no it won't and everybody's soul
is different I know that that's not what
what I'm saying everybody's soul is
different I'm saying something bigger
than that I'm saying something bigger
than all our souls are different I'm
saying when you're pushed to the Max and
you're pushed at a level like this and
you've been through struggles and you
had the symptoms and conditions and
you've gone through the losses and the
struggles all all over emotional and
physical all of it what happens is your
soul your soul
changes like no
other it becomes gold like no other
true gold it's your Soul's gold I'm
talking about it's your Soul's riches
it's your Soul's value it changes in
every way
possible it it goes above and rises
above all the gold medals anyone can win
it rises above all the solid gold medals
it rises above Treasure of all Treasures
it's more than just diamonds and
emeralds and rubies it's more than just
all the platinum and gold and silver
it's more than all of that because it
has a spiritual meaning within it and
inside of it that's built inside your
soul like none other can ever touch in
any spiritual
Endeavor in any spiritual
Endeavor you know I've known I I I've
known a woman before and and I still do
I just haven't we haven't spoken a long
time we speak every I think it's like
every four or five years she contacts me
and she says hey how you doing I miss
you you busy saving the world i' be like
H I don't know about saving the world
I'm just trying to get the information
trying to help everybody and you we talk
a little bit and everything like that we
met a long time ago because she had this
this experience a religious experience a
spiritual experience
she was in a car she was in a
car and that car
crashed and that car was
mangled it was
mangled and when she was in that car
when she was in that car she had a
premonition that it was going to crash
there was no signs of that there were
nothing in the way there was nothing
going on there was nothing happening she
had a premonition it hit her the car is
going to crash
the car is going to
crash and she was she was like what do I
do is this real she she felt like it was
just like something just told her and
she couldn't tell if she heard it she
thought it she felt it she said it was
all the above she felt it she heard it
she felt the whole
bit
and well the car
crashed and there was a few cars
involved and the outcome was was
horrific she was trapped in the car they
had to cut her out of the
car when they did they were positive
there was going to be really nothing
left of her when they cut her out of the
car she stood
up she took a
walk and it was like she never even was
touched she was never even
touched it was no one could believe it
Emergency Services didn't it was
unexpected
explainable and what happened was that
voice she heard a voice she heard was
what she believes was an
angel that's what she believes she's
positive it was an angel because it
could be nothing else in her mind and
everything
else but she walked away with spiritual
growth and she walked
away with something
something it changed her life she was a
different person she said she was always
short kind of nasty and mean she felt
before that
experience she felt that she was not her
best self she felt she was even kind of
always had a jealousy about other people
and kind of purposely would do things
that she felt that she knew was
bad but we're all human we make mistakes
we do that and I I said to that I said
look whatever people you're good you're
a good person we people do things they
just do things she said yeah but it was
I wasn't a good person Anthony I wasn't
a good person when I came when I climbed
out when they pulled me out of that car
and I would walked around like nothing
happened and there wasn't even a scratch
on
me and and one of the one of the
responders said there's no question she
has both broken legs in there the way
they were Twisted in there and the metal
was compiled I said just the the legs
couldn't even be bent that way they said
it's not even possible so they were
expecting there was nothing wrong with
her she got out she was like she was
like a rubber band in
there and protected as if her body
turned into jelly and then just reformed
and shape shifted out of it she said
that she said that one of her family
members one of her cousins got ill with
a chronic illness and this was after the
fact after this experience after this
religious experience after the spiritual
experience after the soul
Experience One one of her family
members I think was her first cousin
fell ill with a chronic illness and she
decided to devote her time with her
family member because she was a changed
person after her experience in every way
and she walked the walk with this family
member and took her to all the doctor
appointments and took her to 50 doctors
and took her to 80 doctors and took her
everywhere and then heard every symptom
over and over again and stayed over the
house and had her stay over her house
and watched over her prepared her food
taking her to functional doctors
alternative doctors Witch Doctors Al
every every doctor possible from here to
Brazil to every part of the world and
continent she spent the money she earned
in her job on this person brought her
everywhere on the planet for help and
watch this cousin of hers who she adored
and just loved dearly suffer and
struggle with everything in every way
possible and she saw that her cousin
that her this beloved
cousin had
Soul like none other that her experience
could not even touch it couldn't even
touch the experience that she had in
that car wreck pulling out of there and
changing her lives life did not even
touch what was happening in her cousin
in her body what was happening in her
soul on every level to the to the degree
she witnessed it she watched it she saw
the symptoms she heard it she even felt
like she felt it she went to every
doctor appointment she saw every loss
urve from it she saw every bit of
confusion she saw where science and
research completely fell short of of
even helping her she saw it all and she
said that right there that right there
and living through that and what she
lived through and what her cousin lived
through said was like a thousand car
accidents with a Thousand Angels in the
car and walking away way completely
changed as a changed person a thousand
times over still she felt didn't compare
or touch what the Soul's goal that built
up in this person her cousin's Soul was
built up with the gold and the treasure
and the dimes and Ruby she was in awe
she was in awe to this person to this
relative of hers she looked to her with
the highest regard the highest respect
and the highest Integrity possible she
looked to her as a hero she looked to
her as if she was Martin Luther King and
and Gandhi she looked to her as if she
was a savior she looked to her because
she saw she saw like no other would she
went through and the soul of her changed
and she watched it from when the cousin
fell ill all the way going year after
year and she stayed with her cousin
strong and she took care of her and she
helped her along the way and she said
Anthony I swear to God I swear to God
the the the my cousin's soul is unlike
any Soul there is and I said I
understand I understand she goes I knew
you would because you're like the only
one to understand this kind of thing and
I knew you wouldn't and she called me to
tell me this and we talked all about it
and she said I knew you would understand
and I said I said look I said Gloria you
have to understand I said it is the
souls gold you're talking
about it's it's a compilation a
compilation
of the jewels of struggle and the gems
of
loss and the Diamonds of hardship and
the platinum and the
gold of that of of the struggle in
nature of the hardship of it all and the
loss and everything you fight for and
all day and every day you fight for and
let me tell you what that Soul's goal
does and here's the part I want to tell
everybody right now this is what this
Soul goal does
to begin with the illness and the
struggles we get and the chronic illness
and the symptoms and the diseases that
we're challenged with are to try to stop
us from becoming something it's trying
to stop us from doing the good in the
world it hits special people if you have
an illness if you have a symptom and you
have a condition it's because you're
special in a certain way already there's
something inside of you that's probably
supposed to change the world and will
and what happens is and what I say by
probably because you can change the
world in different
ways and so because someone is going to
say I couldn't change the world there's
no way I doubt that no no no no no
because you you would change the world
in a different way there's so many areas
of the world you can change and there's
all these people everybody that has the
symptoms and conditions are supposed to
be they're supposed to without those
symptoms and conditions they're supposed
to be World Changers so something gets
in the way of that something comes the
chronic illness the disease the symptoms
come and they challenge that and they
try to stop that from happening but what
happens is it backfires and it always
does it backfires and it always does I'm
telling you I know this it backfire
backfires and what happens instead is
not only do you fight through your
illness and struggles and build that
Soul's gold not only do you do all that
but you change the world with it and
after it it comes I've watched it I've
seen it all these decades people
changing the world because they got sick
even on the smallest ways but you need
to know the smallest ways are some of
the biggest ways there is some of the
greatest ways there is that changes the
world and I'm watching it out there and
I see it out there and I'm telling you
right now it's real and it's
happening so our Soul's gold does
something for us those wounds do
something for us that pressure does
something for us everything about it
does something for us like never before
it pushes us to the limit of not only
supposedly to change the world that we
were supposed to do something but it
even pushes us further so we actually do
so something does happen so something
does alter in the world so we do things
around the world around us it could even
be I don't mean in the world in a ho and
maybe that too of course for many but
it's all in the above it's all of it and
Gloria saw her cousin do that not only
become the soul she did which was
unimaginable to her which superseded
which climbed above all other aspects of
what she felt was spiritual growth even
in her
most unbelievable experience that
occurred in her car crash and I said
yeah but that car Crasher was a big deal
she said it was nothing compared to
this nothing compared to what I've
watched my beloved cousin go through do
and
become when I speak speak to her and she
speaks Anthony when I speak to her and
she speaks there's a sound in her voice
that I hear a power that I
hear a power like no other that I hear
that comes deep within the
soul and it's it's
big and it's
profound and I said yeah that's the
treasure that's the treasure you're
hearing coming through that's the Soul's
treasure the Soul's treasure you're
hearing come through and it rides over
every every Medallion it rides over
every medal that hangs on anybody's neck
it rides over any
achievement any academic achievement it
rides over it it rides over it there's
there's you know I've run across a lot
of young people I told you that close to
17 roughly give or takes 17 out of a 100
college students come home not cuz they
want to they come home not because they
hate school they come home not because
they they've lost interest they come
home because they're sick with fatigue
they're debilitatingly in pain they get
all these random diagnosis no one knows
anything they come home they bedridden
and they have to start from scratch and
they don't finish their college
degree they don't go back to the
university 17 out of 100
100 every year and
every across the board he just times
that by the Thousand so it's 100 what
170 out of a thousand then times that by
10,000 times that by 100,000 and what
happens is what I've heard from so many
of them that I've had to help and
recover and get their lives back so they
can go back to school someday so they
can go and live their lives what they
would say is my friend just got my
friends just graduated they just
graduated
but well some of my friends graduated
with honor some of my friends graduated
they graduated and they got their
degrees and they they got all of that
and they were able to attend graduation
and they said and and and they felt
terrible they felt like they were a loss
of life they felt like they were losers
they felt like whatever and I said I and
I said no no no no no no what you have
that's building right here is more
valuable than a degree a degree to hang
on wall it's more valuable than and look
I'm not trying to undermine those
degrees and achievements they're they're
wonderful and they're and we need those
in life and all those things this not
what I'm doing I'm just saying for the
ones that need to hear this because it's
the truth is that what they're what
they're achieving climbing out of their
illness there's much greater me you
can't you can't hang that on the wall on
a
plaque in fact it wouldn't do it justice
it wouldn't you couldn't hang it on a
wall you couldn't put solid gold the
diamonds in a plaque and you just it
wouldn't even touch what's what's
inside the the St the the students that
have seen that have had to become
students of their soul students of their
heart and soul and of their chronic
illness and Experts of their chronic
illness to rise above it rise out of the
ashes and heal and move forward and get
better and get better and then yeah sure
go back to school again go back to
school again and you know what many of
them that have helped have gone back to
school recovered and gone back to school
and they've gotten their degree and they
said that degree didn't really have a
lot of meaning compared to what they've
gone through sure they they they
respected it they honored it it it
whatever and it it did what it did and
it had its purpose it had its purpose
absolutely but they they would tell me
more than one say but what I've learned
my whole life's changed and where I'm
going at this my whole life's changed my
soul's changed I'm changed as a person
on every
level and you know and I and I told told
those stories to to my friend Gloria and
she said
well it's definitely similar it's
similar my cousin's gone through because
you couldn't hang it on the wall you
couldn't put it in a plaque you couldn't
embroid embroider it with diamonds and
and emeralds it just wouldn't do it
justice and when illness and and
struggles and hardships try to hold us
back when they try to hold us back to
stop us from changing the world it
backfires and it totally blows up and it
explodes and it goes backfires and we
end up changing the world more than we
would have ever done
anyway we end up rising out of the ashes
and healing we end up getting better and
stronger but what happens is we have
something no one else has we have the
Soul's gold like no one else has and we
have this power nobody else has and as
we heal all through it and move forward
anybody we talk to the words that come
out of your mouth are different than
they would have ever been anytime else
else and they're profound and they
change the lives of others whether they
can tell in that moment or they can tell
later on and they if they don't tell in
that moment that's fine they and it ends
up changing their lives later
on something happens that no one can
touch no one no one's got their finger
on that no one's got on you no one's got
on you something happens when you go
through what you've gone through and
your Soul's gold builds and strengthens
and becomes like no other your spirit
your heart and your soul like no other
before and it's you can't touch that no
one can touch that out there you need to
know that no Fancy free person who
hasn't had any real symptoms or
conditions you know some sniffles or
something or whatever they go to the
doctor they take an antibiotic or
whatever it is no one can touch what
you've gone
through and no
one no one has the soul that you have
sure they have a wonderful individual
soul sure we all well that we all do
here but this is different this is
different you need to know what you have
and you Harbor you need to know what's
in your hands you need to know and I
think you do because I think you've had
to do the forgiveness I think you've had
to find the forgiveness I think you've
had to have compassion for yourself and
Pat yourselves on the back you have to
have
compassion you better believe it
you know what you've been
through you have to be easy on yourself
you have to have a light heart through
it because you have to understand what
kind of treasure you're talking about
what kind of treasure you're dealing
with what kind of treasure that's within
you what kind of treasure within inside
your soul what kind of treasure you're
about what kind of treasure is in your
hands you have to be easy on yourself
you have to have a light heart you have
to with all you got you got to keep a
light heart through your healing process
no matter what challenges you on a daily
basis no no matter what you got to push
through no matter what doctor you have
to go now and see no matter where you
have to figure something out no matter
what have you been through you have to
you have to keep the faith you have to
keep a light heart and you have to Pat
yourself on your back and you have to
compassion you have to have compassion
for yourself with everything you have
and when your doctor doesn't understand
or doesn't believe in what you're saying
you have to have you have to have some
forgiveness there absolutely because
when you're building that Soul's gold
you're just going to have to have the
Forgiveness there that's what helps
build it and you got got to forgive
yourself and you got to give forgive
yourself because what happens to
everybody who falls ill what happens to
everybody who's sick longer than a week
longer than two weeks longer than a
month longer than six weeks longer than
two months what happens to everybody
who's sick for longer than what their
their what the world thinks they're
supposed to have or do what happens is
they hate on themselves they hate on
themselves they think back of all their
mistakes and they think back of
everything they did wrong and they
blamed themselves and they convinced
themselves they created their illness
and they look back at everything they
did and they look back at their
shortcomings and their weaknesses and
they look back at the things they've
said to people and they look back
whatever you do do not go back there and
look at all
that because you're a good person you're
a good person and you're Rising above it
all and then some because what people
don't do when they're not challenged
like this is they don't care even to
look back at all that stuff they don't
even really want to look back at all
that stuff they just keep on going ahead
whatever bad habit they've ever had
whatever systematic Behavior they've had
they just keep on forging ahead and you
know and and even polluting people and
even causing trouble and and daggers
coming out of their mouth at other
people or whatever it is whatever it is
that's going on out there there what
happens when you're sick and you're
chronically ill you end up looking back
and you start judging yourself and you
start putting yourself on the hot seat
you can't do that you can't do that you
have to understand who you are you have
to have compassion for yourself you have
to forgive yourself that's that's for
sure you have to have all of that but
you have to have more than just that you
need to know you need to know who you
are and that Soul's gold and what's
really happening and what's being forged
what's being forged in your soul and who
you are and how you're Rising above this
and you need to be easy on yourself and
have that light heart with everything
you
got and move
forward your Soul's gold is like nothing
else and nobody else everybody's Soul
Souls gold is a little different it's a
little different in different
ways that's a little different and a
little bit more powerful in other ways
and another person's Soul's gold is a
little bit more powerful in other way
ways and well that's what's happening
there but your Soul's gold is unique to
what you've been through and what you've
gone through in life and you struggled
through and the value of that can't be
matched by any golden fortnox it can't
be matched by any treasure there is it
can never be matched by anything so you
need to know what you Harbor and you
have and don't let the demons do the
talking
so many with chronic
illness suffer from just just the the
OCD
involved from from the struggle itself
don't let that get to you you keep a lie
heart through all of it no matter what
you're hearing when you're sick no
matter what you're hearing when you're
depressed no matter what you're hearing
when you have anxiety no matter what
you're hearing both inside your head and
out outside around from any people or
anything like that don't let it get to
you don't let it get to your core
whatever you do and if it does get to
you then you know what it's another gold
coin it's another gold coin more
valuable than any gold coin there is
it's another religious gold coin it's
another spiritual gold coin it's another
profound gold coin that builds up in the
treasure box but don't let anything get
to you your treasure is also your
treasure is so so profoundly vast as it
is you forge ah head you keep a life
heart you heal and you respect your
Soul's gold and you honor your Soul's
gold you know that everything in the
past that you've been through and
everything you've gone through tomorrow
and during the day and through all your
struggles in life all the way from the
beginning and everything you you blamed
yourself on cre thinking you created it
all or anything you've known just know
that your treasure out outweighs all of
it it is part of it it's so vast and
Powerful it can't be touched or matched
by anybody no matter what
bless you I love you guys and just know
that I truly care we're going to do this
together we're all going to rise out of
the ashes together I love you and uh God
bless you I'll see you next show take
care