melons are one of my favorite foods
one of my favorite fruits when melon
season comes around I like to have
spirulina with my melon I want to show
you how cool this is
check this out I'm gonna crack this open
here we go and then I'm going to scoop
the seeds out
just like this
I'm gonna try to do it so you guys can
see
I like melons when they're juicy
when they're ripe not too hard and
crunchy I will eat a melon if it's like
somewhat crunchy
but it's not my favorite I like to have
them when they're sweet and juicy and
ripe but you can also you gotta look out
because you might accidentally eat an
overripe melon which isn't fun you can
taste it where it's kind of fermented
and stuff this one's perfect I'm pretty
sure I'm gonna put the spoon in and
that's the way I like it maybe a little
bit more riper than that so here's what
I like to do I like to take spirulina
and this is emergy spirulina
right here I've endorsed this company I
work with these guys and there's so many
reasons why
they're the only ones out there that I
can find that don't put anti-caking and
anti-binders
in here so there's no agents hidden in
here that's not disclosed because
companies are allowed to stick these
anti-caking agents inside their
spirulina or inside all their different
green powders protein powders and all
that and then they won't put it on the
label you'll never know you're eating
that well these guys don't do it they
won't that alone is such a big deal for
me because it's scary to know there's
things inside your supplements that you
don't know about you can't identify you
have no idea what it is but it's in
there right these guys don't do that so
here's what I like to do with Spirulina
for years I've been putting spirulina in
my melons
so what I'll do is I'll just take a
little bit like this and spirulina
is incredible for you
so essential fatty acids are in
spirulina
just putting some in there there you go
so I want to show you what this looks
like so
I'm gonna put some more
beta-carotene
essential fatty acids
there you go so many nutrients
phytochemical compounds
so I like to eat it this way I'll take
it to my office whatever I'll I'll
actually take it to go
it can get messy so you got to look out
because spirulina can be messy but it's
such a powerful
incredible
source of so many different nutrients
look at the color all on its own I mean
you know when you see that and the
purity of the Bemidji spirulina
is unmatched
it's not from China it's not sourced
from China and you'll see that out there
spirulina that stores from China this is
from the U.S
it's the purest form I've ever seen
you can taste it
you can see it
and if it ever clumps
that's fine because you know there's no
agents in there stopping it from
clumping
and that's not a good thing
but so if it ever does Clump that's a
natural progression of something that's
so pure it doesn't have something
interfering with it that's not being
disclosed on the bottle so anyway you
guys that's spirulina inside the melon
that's how I eat it I love doing it this
way try it sometime