steamed artichokes i got them steaming
right now in this pot
okay with two dipping sauces
and it's a recipe you guys haven't seen
it's in the medical medium new edition
which has a 28-day cleanse this book is
unreal it's got the lyme disease chapter
it's got you know the depression chapter
this
is such a book chronic fatigue syndrome
all that epstein-barr anyway making a
great recipe
um got some extra artichokes right here
that i didn't cook yet
but i got artichokes in this pot
steaming away right now
the two dipping sauces one's gonna be a
mustard
dipping sauce another is gonna be
zucchini dipping sauce
good to see you guys it's going to look
like this i hope something like that
so glad you guys are coming on fantastic
and let's get started on this recipe
first thing is i can show you how i prep
the artichokes so when you guys
steam yours sometime that you can see
how i do it so it's something i'm going
to do with these artichokes
i'm excited when is the book coming out
it's like any day now or any it's like
in a week or so or two weeks i don't
know i think it's maybe two weeks
less than two weeks it's coming out you
might want to get
a copy of it the new edition medical
medium
um it's a revised expanded book and it's
packed with information a 28-day cleanse
it's got the angel chapter in there it's
got the meditations chapter in there
um michelle you're addicted to steamed
artichokes right
that is a good addiction now that
is a healthy addiction okay
yeah anyway instead of the addictions
i'm always talking about all the time
just don't get addicted to ayahuasca
that's a bad
addiction i'm gonna tell you right now
that's an addiction that will
potentially kill you
i don't care what anybody says i don't
care what anybody who stinks they're
spiritual says
that ayahuasca is dangerous stuff and
can brain damage you
even if it doesn't brain damage you when
you're doing it when you're in that
ayahuasca ceremony
it can it can future brain damage you
down
the road and it can and it will
so that you're like 20 years down the
road you're like what
what what's my name that's how bad that
stuff is okay
so give me a forewarning there
okay so uh
i'm on you know i'm look you guys
i'm on the artichokes right now they're
steaming up these are almost done i've
been steaming them for a while
before we even start it so i want you to
know that just in case you guys are like
how did he steam those so quick
do artichokes only take five minutes of
steam now they take like 40 minutes
30 minutes depending on the size these
were pretty big ones if you take a look
at this one
so
pretty good sizes so let's just talk
about what i have right here
i got some thyme on this plate right
here
fresh thyme fresh dill in here got some
green onions this recipe calls for
chives i didn't have chives
um and i got some green onions though
got some parsley got some zucchinis
you're gonna need those too
zucchinis right and you're gonna need
some lemons
too as well i'm gonna read some comments
um
whoa rebecca says lost 40 pounds
following you
following the medical medium stuff
incredible incredible
someone said ljax said
what the heck is ayahuasca something you
don't want anything to do with
um yeah aren't those big aren't these
aren't these big
incredible so let's get going you guys i
want to i want to show you guys
everything here
um so
to start with these things are finishing
up so we'll just give them a couple more
minutes i'm going to turn down the heat
get this to chill out turn it down
and then i'm going to get them out and
we're going to plate them up we're going
to make some dipping sauces
but let me show you what i did
see these got the long stems and i
noticed that sometimes in the grocery
store
you'll see them with short stems so when
they
when they prepped them for the grocery
store they cut the stem off now
the the longer the stem
so if you after you steam it if you eat
it all the way down to the lower stem
it's really bitter
so down here about right here
this inch inch and a half you guys is a
really better section
now i like to what i like to do
sometimes is even though it's bitter
okay even though it's better i do like
to
looking for my uh knife i do like to
peel this back a little bit like this
sometimes
and because i don't like to waste it i
still like to eat the stem
first of all artichokes are really
expensive
these are organic ones okay but you'll
see what i'll do i'll show you what i
just did right now
just so you know so i just peeled back
that stem here because that's the rough
part is
this the skin on the stem that's edible
all this right
just cut a little piece of this off but
it gets a little bitter down here at the
end
but still i just love it i mean i love
the artichoke heart
this attaches to the heart of the
artichoke so it's attached
which is you know and so you you know
but it's tastier up
higher up about here in the stem i mean
right about here sorry about that
so just want to show you so i'm just
prepping this artichoke
these are almost done if you just got on
here so i'm making steamed artichokes
with two dipping sauces mustard dipping
sauce zucchini dipping sauce
mustard maple dipping sauce i have the
maple syrup right here
it's in this little tray and the
zucchini herb
dipping sauce which i got some zucchinis
right here
so what i like to do is cut the top a
little bit back so i'd like to cut the
top off a little bit
so all these pieces so i'll take the
knife okay
you guys see this and i like to cut the
top off
so just like this okay
let me just get rid of these
so now i have that
so now you can steam them whole the
recipe
calls for steaming them whole right so
in this pot right here they're just
about done
i turned down the heat there
there's a couple of whole ones just like
that but i cut one in
half too and i'll show you that
but that one's prepped now let me cut it
in half too
all right so because i want to show you
the inside because you can cut them in
half if you really want to
and i'll do that that's next let me do
that here so i'm going to
send this knife through now these are
tough to cut sometimes
all right that's the inside okay
you got a couple of options you can take
a spoon and get this
furry stuff out which is like the seed
pulp inside this
that's the furry a little fur that's
going on in the center you can actually
scoop that out
and you can take it out after it's
cooked as well
so move these over
so i want to answer some questions too
as we're making these
i'm going to lift up the lid these are
done first time growing artichokes
amazing that's so great
so take the lid off
these are going to be really hot
lucy lou hey how are you doing
good to see you're here the comments go
up and i can't catch him in time
um chelsea i have really bad
separate dermatitis i need advice please
it's all about the liver chelsea when it
comes down to dermatitis so it's all
about the liver and you're in luck
because this is an incredible
healing liver food it just is this is an
incredible
thyroid healing food an incredible liver
healing food
when you're healing the liver you're
healing the skin
that's where you're heading so when
you're healing your liver
you're healing your skin that's the key
so
dermatitis stagnant sluggish
liver filled with lots of toxins and
this meal has no fat in it so this is a
no
fat meal there's no oils in this meal
and i'm saying this for a reason because
i'm talking about your liver and
dermatitis you want to get dermatitis
better
you got to get off the fats or lower the
fats or reduce them
so you don't see oils in this meal and
you're not gonna see nut butters you're
not gonna see
avocado you're not gonna see pork fat in
this meal
you're not gonna see chicken fat in this
meal you're not gonna see
corn oil vegetable oil you know you're
not gonna see anything canola oil you're
not going to see
grease you're just not going to see any
of that in this meal
and that right there is the key to
getting the liver
better is i want to show you guys always
show you guys these
low fat to no fat actually no fat meals
and because what happens is every time
you're eating fat
your liver has to spill out a lifetime
of bile reserves
to break down the fat to try to thin it
out to save your life
to save your life and i'll talk about
what that fat does
it builds up into your arteries it
becomes the plaque
in your arteries science research
doesn't know that
they just don't know that which is
interesting right
so the whole point about these meals is
about reducing that fat or eliminating
the fat at least a little bit
in your life like a moment in your life
like whether it's a cleanse
whether it's a 20-day cleanse i mean you
guys should check the book out
it's on amazon you know get it so you
got this information but like the 28 day
cleanse you'll see
there won't be any fats in there so
that's important i mean unless you want
to stick a little bit of avocado in
something or something but i recommend
trying to have a moment in your life to
have the fats out of there so
you can get rid of the dermatitis get
rid of your skin problems
help get rid of your acne help get rid
of your eczema psoriasis vitiligo
because your liver is killing itself
every time you dump
fat in there like a whole bunch of oil
and grease and too much animal protein
and i'm not against animal protein i'm
not against plant
plant fat either and plant protein
people but
the whole point is is that when you're
dumping in all that fat your liver is
killing itself
to actually thin out the blood that's
what
biles for bile is released to try to
always save your butt
and to break down that fat so it thins
it out to get it either out of your
system someday somehow some way right
and that's one thing and then the other
thing is adrenals
every time you're eating fat your
adrenals are pumping
because you're you need adrenaline to
thin out your blood
so oxygen can go to your brain so your
brain sends them it's the minute you eat
all this fat
and many eat all this avocado and
avocados a healthy fat i get it but if
you're eating it every day and then
you're having chicken for dinner and you
had avocado toast for
for breakfast you had something for
lunch oil
on your food for lunch oil on your salad
for lunch chicken salad or whatever
you're doing tuna fish
you get all this fat in there and then
your adrenals are running all day to try
to thin out the blood
to disperse the fat in your bloodstream
your brain
tells your adrenals i need adrenaline
fast you have to thin out the blood or
you're going to kill me the brain
and you're going to kill me the heart so
that's how it works so i'm trying to
give you guys a chance to heal and when
your liver gets stagnant and sluggish
guess what you've got that dermatitis
coming on you've got stuff coming on
you get that rosacea coming on all of it
and look i talk about the stuff
you know cleanse the heel you can take a
look at that liver rescues another great
book
information on this so cleanse the heel
and then of course liver rescue right
here
but yeah guys so
and then what happens your liver gets
stagnant your liver gets sluggish and
you end up getting
the sun spots so now it's sunspot time
right
you know that's another thing too and
then if you're jacked up on caffeine all
day you really get those sunspots
like really get them you know because
the liver is going into
overdrive trying to absorb all that
adrenaline all the time and that's
another thing too
we're eating all these fats your liver
is killing itself to break down the fats
your adrenals are killing themselves to
release adrenaline to break down the fat
to thin out your blood
and then your liver has to do this
massive cleanup it has to suck in all
the fat that it
that it can't disperse and and it has to
suck in all this fat so you get the
fatty liver
and then you get the dermatitis you get
all kinds of problems you get the gout
you get i mean everything goes wrong and
and your liver is killing itself to
absorb
all that adrenaline it's killing itself
to absorb all that fat and then we just
get in trouble right there
gail says liver rescue yeah
so i mean seriously i mean
it's important to know it really is
so um let's keep on working on this
i'm excited you guys lots to talk about
thanks for everybody coming on being
here if you guys just came on here we're
about to get started
we're kind of moving through just just
covering a couple questions
um so that's important and let's talk
about what we're making steamed
artichokes which is a real healing food
and i want you guys to have the healing
foods right
everything you put in your body i just
saw geographical tongue that's liver
ella that's the liver right there so
just know i mean it's time to get the
liver healthier that's what geographical
that's what the geographical tongue is
that is
a liver that's heating up way too much
because it's
overloaded with toxins and poisons and
eventually what comes after geographical
tongue
comes after it is weight gain sometimes
during it sometimes before it but after
it can come out
you know so got to get that liver better
it's important gail you're reading
liverescue now so awesome awesome
um rebecca does the body need fat
the body gets fat from every single food
there is so
the body does need traces
of fat but that's traces and guess what
it's in all your food there's fat and
artichokes
there's fat and potatoes there's fat and
bananas
there's fat and butter leaf lettuce
there's fat in fruit
mangoes there's fat in every vegetable
broccoli has fat in it
broccoli green beans have fat in it um
so you know that's every single food you
eat an apple has fat in it
an apple has fat in it so we already got
the fats in those foods
so technically you're not fat free on
any of these meals because there's
traces of omega-3s
in these foods there's traces of
omega-3s
six and nines in these foods right here
so we get that there
and it's okay to do avocado it's okay to
do some nut butters it's okay to do
um hemp seeds and and sesame seeds and
have some of that but that's not what we
do
that's not what we do here's what we do
it's
we fat ourselves to death that's all we
do that's what we've been taught
you just fat yourself to death that's
what we're taught it's fats all day long
all day long tuna salad for lunch eggs
for
fat everywhere cheese milk cheese butter
oils
okay sure you're doing healthy fat
you're doing some avocado
for one minute you're doing avocado yeah
you got a healthy fat but your body's
already like whoa healthy or not just
slow that stuff down
because you do an avocado toasted you're
throwing peanut butter in your smoothie
then you're doing chocolate cacao
straight fat
then it's like it doesn't stop so okay
are fats good for me
are they good for my body well some but
there's no such thing as any moderation
and there's no such thing as anything
being balanced all it is is fat all day
long
no moderation no balance no nothing
everybody's choking
that fat down they're just sending it
down send it down
sucking it down and it's nonstop
so unless someone decides intermittent
fast and the only reason why they
intermittent fast
is because it's by hit and miss it's
because someone accidentally one day
discovered
that if they don't eat all this food in
the morning
they start to feel a little better but
what they don't know
is they're not eating fats in the
morning anymore they're
actually holding back the fats they
don't even know it
intermittent so-called intermittent
fasting experts don't even know why
anybody starts to even feel better
when they intermittent fast and it
doesn't even mean it's the right thing
to do
because you're really supposed to have
fuel no matter what during your morning
and day
so you don't burn out your adrenals but
in intermittent fasting experts or
whoever they are
they don't even know that they're just
all like
they're just all like oh you're burning
fat you're burning fat you're burning up
carbs
you're not eating in the morning your
digestion is getting a little stronger i
mean that's pretty much as far as it
goes with them they don't know anything
else
and but what's happening is when you
when you're holding off
all that fat in the morning your liver
starts to bounce back
nobody knows that but your liver starts
to bounce back
and that's what happens so are we
getting any fats yeah we're getting fat
so getting them in the artichokes that i
got right here i'm about to plate up
we get them we get them in every food we
eat
and yeah if you want to have some sesame
tahini yeah if you want to have a little
peanut butter a little almond butter
yeah if you want to have some hemp seeds
a little avocado or something
but we don't do that we don't have a
little bit of sesame tahini we don't
have a little bit of
peanut butter we have tablespoons of it
all week long on top of the fact we have
chicken for dinner
whether you're vegan plant-based if
you're vegan you're still going to do
all these oils
on top of drowning things with olive oil
eggs
eggs are filled with fat that's what
they are i mean that's the whole point
it's
it's like we don't do anything but fat
no one's like i'll just eat that piece
of fruit and some greens i'm good for
now
are you kidding no one's doing that
nobody's doing that
it doesn't exist so it's and if it does
it's from
from medical medium information teaching
people for 35 years if it does exist
so it's because they never did it before
i got into the health scene 35 years ago
it was fat fat fat fat and it's still
fat fat fat today
and the dairy products straight fat
kefir
milk goat's milk sheep's milk sheep's
cheese goat's cheese
oh i'm on goat's cheese i'm not eating
any fat what
that's a head scratcher to me right
there are you kidding
and so it's all about just fatting
ourselves to death
boom just that's we're killing ourselves
let's just kill ourselves
because pretty much that's what it is
but it's a slow death
that's what it is we fat ourselves to a
slow death and then eventually
and here's the thing here's the sad
thing that plaque in our arteries
you know what it's made out of it's not
made out of cholesterol that's that's
how that's how
science of research is so off the mark
they're off the mark on all chronic
illness they're off the market 90
99 of all chronic illness are off the
mark
and i'm not talking about the robots
they create
that science creates to to get an
aneurysm out of somebody's brain when i
talk to a
neurosurgeon that's amazing but that's
what i'm talking about i'm talking about
chronic illness i'm talking about
everybody else
everybody the whole world who's sick
with symptoms science research doesn't
know why anybody's sick
so and plaque in the arteries that's
from fat
and toxins combined congealed
that's from fat in your system running
through the pipes
you gotta you gotta see your system as
pipes right and what's running through
those pipes is fat let me just have this
avocado right here that's some fat let
me have some more nut butter in here
let me have chicken and put some olive
oil on that chicken
let me have some salmon and make sure i
cook it in olive oil
make sure i keep on doing all that and
what happens is and it would have
a look let's do more coconut oil let's
do more more coconut butter
let's do ghee let's do whatever we can
find and
what we're doing is we're running fat
through our pipeline
non-stop running pipe fat through our
pipeline
and it and because of that that fat is
also
toxin soluble so the more
fat that you got running through you the
more fat that's in our bodies
the more toxins absorb into those fat
cells fat cells absorb
pesticides herbicides fungicides
petrochemicals
colognes perfumes scented candles
because the list goes on pharmaceuticals
boom cold medicine antibiotics
benzodiazepines
anti-inflammatories just all day long
toxic heavy metals
and all that all that fat absorbs it all
right absorbs it all and then
the fat congeals and guess what
our defense mechanism is holy crap
what do we do and and it just starts to
line
it lines the sides of the river which is
your pipeline
your arteries your veins start to line
it and line it and line it so what
you're going to be told
you're going to be told to kill yourself
slowly by every health professional out
there
all the podcast doctors all the health
gurus all the trainers are just going to
teach you to kill yourself slowly
by saying fat's good for you you need
fat as if you're not even eating fat
you're pouring it on everybody is
they're also going to tell you
caffeine's good for you too so not only
you dumping all this fat in
your food everywhere you they're dumping
all the caffeine in
they just they the the recommendations
you get from all the gurus and health
guys and everything else
it's all to slowly kill yourselves
that's what it is
it's all counter sensibility
it's counselor it's counter sensible
it's counter common sense it's stupidity
at its
highest you guys and
and it's like it's it's unbelievable
it's unbelievable
and it's counter intuition it's
unintuition they
unintuit you everybody is unintuiting
you
you just get all your intuition robbed
and stolen
and theft it you guys have no intuition
left
sounds like an insult but it's just a
fact what happens is
because every time i talk to people the
most intuitive people in the world they
tell me the most intuitive people in the
world do all their spiritual practices
they're sitting down they're doing all
their prayers
they're doing all their meditations and
then i hear they're like burning scented
candles
and they're pouring fat on their food
your intuition
your heart and your brain and your your
body's your body doesn't want all that
fat going in there to kill you
and your body doesn't want all that
caffeine going in there to kill you and
all those chemicals so
whose intuition are we talking about i
want to know like someone please tell me
whose intuition's working
because every day all day long all i see
is
doctors and practitioners and healers
and everybody else and their intuition
is
in the garbage it's in the garbage bin
because they're not using it i guess
everybody's born with it and then it's
stolen from us by the caffeine industry
and by the chemical industry and by
every other industry and it's stolen
by the health industry big pharma
soldiers did they steal
our intuition it's it's unbelievable
it's actually it's actually unbelievable
when you think about it
um jody says for me eaters what's the
healthiest meat to eat
lamb beef chicken seafood kangaroo
believe it or not fish is still
the healthiest okay so it'd be like
trout
be like salmon sardines right there so
if you're into animal proteins
you're better off having trout salmon
sardines
haddock that's another one right there
so haddock sardines
salmon you know get a hold of some
mackerel that could be a possibility
um i'll give you the most unhealthiest
okay and healthiest of all if you're an
animal protein person
pork keep it out never have it stay away
from it
it'll kill you fast it'll age you faster
too it's so high in fat
that will cling into your arteries and
it's all fun and dandy when you're 22
years old when you're 25 years old 28
years old you know it's it's
it i get it you know we're all
indestructible when we're 25 we're
indestructible
you know what i mean and but man when
you're 60 and you're like wait a minute
what i got to get a double triple heart
surgery what do i need to do i got to
get two valves done i have to get a
stint put in a shunt put in
wait a minute what do i got to do and
and then you're laying on the table and
they got to run them
they got to run a scope they got to run
a scope through your leg
up through your arteries and veins and
they gotta think and then they gotta
find out where your arteries are
collapsing
because of all that pork fat and then
they gotta shove a stint in there
it just is no fun but when you're 20 and
you're exercising and you're on this
this keto diet and you think you've
learned everything about health
i noticed is everybody's a health expert
now like every 25 year old's a health
expert it's just unbelievable because
they went keto
and lamb might be cautious about it's
really high in fat
if you're going to do animal proteins
you really like animal proteins and you
keep it to grass-fed beef but you don't
overdo it that's one option
grass of beef just don't don't overdo it
if you're into animal protein
i would do turkey over chicken even
though turkey's
high in fat too i would do turkey over
chicken
i've listened i've i've been asked this
a million times by doctors by all kinds
of people by
the most powerful people in the world
that want my help and it's like what
animal proteins i do anthony i'm not
going to go plant-based so what animal
proteins am i going to do well let me
help you
i want to help you eat animal protein i
want to help you if you're plant-based
too
and so it'd be like you'd be like okay
well when i go through things
with people i'll give you the give you
the rundown you could do a little bit of
grass-fed beef if you like beef fine
i would stay away from chicken yeah you
can have it if you want but i would stay
away from chicken
it's way too high in fat um the turkey's
better than the chicken even though
turkey's high in fat's still better
than the chicken for you so that's
something to think about
fish like i said the salmon the trout
the haddock the sardines small fish
like sardines really good option really
good option if you're into animal
protein
and it's got lower metals in it don't
get fooled by the fish thing
hey he's talking about fish why is he
doing that when he's about getting toxic
heavy metals out
first of all we're getting metals
everywhere everywhere anyhow you're
in grass-fed beef it's in there it's in
every animal protein
it's on every vegetable it's in every
vegetable organic or not
toxic heavy metals are in every single
organic vegetable every single
organic food you've ever eaten toxic
heavy metals are in
so when it comes down to fish it go with
the smaller fish they do have less and
go with wild caught but yeah
i would stay away from tilapia stay the
heck away from it
so anyway there's some you know there's
some information for you guys
so i got a plate here i'm gonna get
these these
these artichokes these are really well
these are really steamed
really good i'm gonna get a utensil
and get getting utensil out here
you guys have great patience
and i'm so proud of all of you for all
that you're doing
look i want you guys to build back your
your your intuition i want it strong
i want it strong because it can become
really strong
it can so i got an artichoke on here
um anthony i need
and anthony i need to know how to heal
my lyme disease
and the co-infections please deborah i'm
going to give you some important
information let's work on that now
okay let's do that
um i'm just grabbing a hand towel sorry
about that you guys
so lyme disease look i recommend this
book
right here for the lyme disease
information okay
and get it free of the library once the
book comes out because eventually it's
going to end up in the library
and i love that because i've actually i
i what i do is i set aside funding and i
get i try to get
help with getting books in libraries so
people can read the books for free
something i've done for years um and if
you don't have the 16
20 or whatever it's going to be the
other thing is
cleanse the heal has a lyme disease
section in cleanse to heal
with supplements and protocols just like
the new addition does with supplements
and protocols for lyme disease you can
take it to your doctor find out what's
you know
your doctor can see what's right for you
or not if you want talk to your doctor
about
what to do and all that if you want but
the protocols are here okay that's one
thing to know
and then it's about supplements the best
supplements and that's what matters too
so using a b12
that's not good won't get someone better
down the road
versus a b12 that is good so that's the
other thing
it's like like the vimergy products is
what i recommend doctors so i tell
doctors all the time
i go if you're giving your patients
another type of b12 then
the the effective rate of actually them
healing is going to be a lot less
that's why the vimorgy products i always
promote i promote other products too
that are actually really good
vimergi is the one i use that's why it's
always on my counter it's the one i use
so
um vimerges v is in victor i m
victorimergy.com vimrgy.com i'm not
sponsored
but the point is is that when it comes
down to lyme disease it's like
when you have neurological lyme it's you
got to have the right b12
and you ask your doctor if this is this
is fine fine to do or whatever
but this is what i would do if i had
lyme disease neurological lyme
that's the b12 i'd be using it's in and
that's
just the starting point of like okay
then i would learn about what foods not
to do
vitamin c is critical if i had lyme
disease i would be on microsee
the vimercy microc that's what i would
do personally me i'd be taking six
capsules
twice a day that's what i would do if i
had lyme disease that's the microc right
there
and this goes with this goes with
conditions and symptoms of all kinds too
i mean
this is all critical stuff um
so and and then there's a bunch of other
stuff too this is getting metals out
anybody with lyme disease has toxic
heavy metals off the charts
off the charts even if the blood test
doesn't show the toxic heavy metals
if you got neurological lyme disease you
got metals inside the brain nervous
system
liver all that's important to know so
that's where the vimrgy spirulina and
the heavy metal detox smoothie comes in
so these are just some things um so i'll
give you a couple tips about lyme
disease
lyme disease is viral not bacterial
science research actually now
are taking medical medium information
they dump the whole bacterial thing so
you know how you say you see the
co-infection thing you see
all right and there's a lyme disease
in the original book here but this is
the new edition with the lime protocol
all that stuff that's in this i showed
that to you earlier
um so you guys can show that to you
again see if that helps
but the co-infection thing just give you
a quick rundown about that
that is old school now so that's old
school
because science research jumped ahead of
all the lyme doctors
so you got these old lyme doctors now
going by old school
and the blood labs going by old school
right they think it's still bacteria
that's what they think it's not bacteria
it's it's viral it's viruses so
but but when you say cofactors that
means you got the old lyme doctors
that means you got the old you got the
old school
process that process already
hurt and hindered tens of thousands
hundreds of thousands of women in the
last 40 years
so more than 40 years because it's not
viral it's not bacterial it's viral
sorry about that
but so what happens is science research
they know now
it's not bacterial so that cofactor
thing
that thing is actually just old school
it's almost like someone didn't get the
memo at the blood lab
but the blood lime labs they don't want
to lose all their money and they don't
want to lose everything they did
so they're trying to save their skin so
they keep on doing the same old thing
even though science research
already the boss the boss of all of them
science research now
has basically declared cleared it's not
bacterial
so here you've got like it's like a
ghost ship you got the
the lime labs still looking for
co-factors you've got
lyme doctors still looking for
co-factors when that's not the problem
that's how sad it is it's so sad mm-info
has always talked about it being viral
and now science research
pulled it out of bacterial years after
publication of the book and now they're
looking for different things so it's
important to know when you're healing
okay so i'm gonna make the dipping sauce
i have the
artichoke right here i'm just gonna put
it over
got the artichokes there's a cooked
artichoke
cooked half i have that's a half of a
cooked artichoke right there
so the heart is right right in this area
you've got to scoop out that little
fiber that little fiber the
seed fiber right there i could show you
that too
let me put these here so um
let's make the uh first of all i gotta
get a bowl
and gonna whisk up a sauce
so this is the mustard maple dipping
sauce
so i'm gonna have two tablespoons of
maple syrup
i'm going to drop some of this in here
like that
some maple syrup is good two and a half
tablespoons of lemon
juice now if you're worried about lemon
you shouldn't be okay there's no signs
of research that says lemon has done
anything wrong to anybody but for some
reason everybody believes it hurts them
hurts their teeth really what happens is
it's all the caffeine that's sucking
life out of everybody's teeth
sucking the calcium out of everybody's
teeth it's on that apple cider vinegar
it's all the vinegars i've been talking
about right
that's what's actually robbing from
people's teeth it's lauren henry
love cooked artichokes hey lauren good
to see you
lauren's a expert on mm info
um good to see you here
yeah i mean the real artichokes are so
good
what i'm doing is i'm making the mustard
maple dipping sauce right now
i'm adding some lemon and
i need a little bit more lemon than that
i want to get two
two and a half tablespoons of lemon
juice so i'm going to cut one more lemon
lunell good to see you here
so you know when it comes down to
healing
the supplements matter the foods matter
like what foods to do what foods not to
do
anybody and everybody has a chance to
heal it's how you play it
right like it's about applying the
information
if you're somebody that doesn't want to
apply all the information or they only
want to apply one thing
and then you get sidetracked and all
this other information out there
like throwing in collagen and
doing you know doing something that
maybe won't be the best for you
downing the charcoal pills doing cruella
whatever it is that's out there
you're not going to go to the finish
line doing too much fat when you're
trying to heal
you're not going to get down the finish
line you're not going to get down there
so
if you want to heal it's about really
applying as much as you can
of what works that's a big deal to
healing
so i'm gonna need some mustard so let me
do a little bit of that so
about a half teaspoon of mustard powder
let's get that going
making the mustard maple dipping sauce
a little mustard powder in there like
that
all right we got that so um
what else do we need we need the cayenne
a little bit of cayenne now you don't
want it too hot
i tend to spike everything and it gets a
little too hot
it's kind of like an accident i just end
up throwing too much in there but
i i think i did good right there so
mustard powder cayenne
a little bit of thyme fresh thyme half
teaspoon tea
teaspoon got the fresh thyme in here
dropping that in there okay
and let's see if there's anything else
in here and then
um some finely chopped parsley
let's do a little bit of that i'm just
gonna move this bowl over a touch
let me get some parsley going
so you don't have to have a lot of
parsley for this one about a teaspoon
finely chopped parsley
there we go get that chopped up
anyone can heal lyme disease anyone
anyone countless people already have
with the medical medium information
[Music]
lyme disease is viral that's why a lot
of doctors now are testing for
epstein-barr
with their lyme patients because of
medical medium information because
really in truth epstein-barr is the
cause one of the causes
one of the main causes
put a little bit of that parsley in here
i'm gonna whisk this up that's one
dipping sauce
what you're gonna notice about these
recipes you guys
is you're gonna notice i'm not salting
you guys out with a ton of salt
no salt really
[Music]
because that'll get you in trouble too
i mean all we do is salt ourselves out
salt fat
vinegar lots of fat salt vinegar that's
what we do
that's what everybody does
and then we hit the msg natural
flavoring that's all everybody does too
lots of natural flavoring so it's like
salt vinegar
fats natural flavoring nutritional yeast
yeast you know you know the game is with
nutritional yeast
they put the word nutritional before it
yeah that's how they got you no it's
yeast
and east is filled with a lot of bad
stuff msg
you know what i never liked about the
whole like edible yeast stuff it's like
okay what about yeast infections you
know
it's what about yeast infections it's
like okay
why do i want yeast
i mean i'm confused about that one a
little bit
let me just throw yeast on my food like
that's real smart let me just throw
yeast in my food
and then let's put the word nutritional
in front of yeast like
fancy that one okay
that's one dipping sauce right there
okay so i'm just one dipping sauce gonna
make another dipping sauce
i need some room over here i'm just
gonna put that over there for now
um so when you think about it
so worst thing you can have is yeast in
general
and as far as nutritional yeast just
don't put that word in front of it
yeah you can find a nutrient in
everything that's bad for you you can
find a nutrient in every single thing
that's bad for you
out there there's nutrients in snake
venom
do you want some snake venom right
there's there's nutrients
in snake venom should we start calling
it nutritional
snake venom that's what we should do
like their
black the black widow spider the venom
of a black widow spider
is nutrition and there's nutrition in
there there's minerals in there
trace minerals so nutritional
venom spider venom i mean what
nutritional yeast
lauren said yeah if everyone is so
worried about candida why are they
eating nutritional yeast lauren
it's so true oh my god it's so true
right and they're down in this stuff
down in it
they're not like let me put a half a
teaspoon of nutritional yeast here
they're like let me pour that stuff on
my food let me get it nice and tasty
i mean exactly
totally so let's see we're gonna make
i'm gonna make this zucchini herb
dipping sauce so i need some zucchinis
here one a half cup
of chopped zucchini let's do that
jess smith laugh out loud i love the mm
he's factual and hilarious i'm honored
i'm honored i am
so i'm gonna do about one and a half
cups of zucchinis
i'm gonna use these two zucchinis that
should cut it
lunell is laughing
you guys i'm really honored you're here
in my kitchen you know
i'm really honored you're here pump says
everybody hit the
like button for aw that would be awesome
man
i don't like asking you guys anything
you know
i don't like doing that
you know i feel bad if i ask you guys
stuff like that like hit my likes or
whatever or
you know i just want you guys to heal i
want you guys better
it's just that's what i really want
so i'm gonna add some lemon juice so i
got the zucchini in here
i'm gonna take a few out do about one
and a half cups that should cut it
and um you guys i'm live right now on
youtube
live on facebook at the same time by the
way in case you want to know
i know on youtube you can see it on the
tv if you set it up that way
singrit said haha my tcm doctor
did give me snake venom in an herbal
formula
interesting and also a bad idea
really bad idea
that's a neurotoxin stuff scares me man
chinero says is collagen healthy for the
body
no because you can't eat
if you got an eye problem do you think
eating a sheep's eyeball or a human
eyeball is gonna fix your eye problem
no if you got a kidney problem kidney
disease do you think you should start
eating kidneys
you think it'll fix your kidney um you
got a brain disease do you think
desiccated brain
in supplements is going to fix your
brain i mean if none of that's going to
work if you got collagen problems
because your collagen is disintegrating
because of caffeine damage
because caffeine is what kills her
collagen it's like
you're losing your collagen and your
skin's falling apart you know your
skin's wrinkling and sagging and
everything because your collagen is
going away
you're aging before your time that's
because of caffeine it's from chocolate
caffeine and from toxins and other
things too it's not just caffeine
but caffeine is a big one and you know
you lose your collagen you can't just
eat collagen to
fix the collagen the body doesn't work
like that the collagen will go in and
you'll poop it out that's it
go in and you'll poop it out it's just
it doesn't find its way all of a sudden
to where your collagen is supposed to be
produced and then you
produce collagen i mean this this this
this shit's psycho out there
it's actually psycho the stuff that
they're doing like or the trends that
are out there
they just think you guys are all like
suckers or something you know
and i get it that's how the system's set
up it's like the butter and the coffee
thing how stupid is that you may as well
have your eggs toast
toast and bacon with it i mean how dumb
is that
like it's like it's psycho out there it
really is
and it's it's all there to just mess
everybody up
and make money while they're doing it
it's crazy
let's put some tablespoon of lemon in
[Music]
here
get it going
cmos anything good about it yeah it's
fine
it's not going to get the metals out
like dolls and the heavy metal detox
smoothie or spirulina
but it it's fine you can do that
see moss i'm not against it at all so
i'm going to do one tablespoon of lemon
juice i didn't get much out of that
lemon for some of that lemon
didn't have a lot of juice in it you
know how that happens
here we go here's a lemon that has a lot
of juice in it there we go
so
are facial laser treatments harmful or
beneficial
micro needling harmful
microneedling not good
not good not good just letting you know
not good at all body's trying to
overcompensate for itself when you micro
needle just like everything else and
eventually you'll have more problems
later on your skin than than than
where you started from you get like
micro needling leads to micro scar
tissue
that's what it leads to micro scar
tissue is what it leads to
and so i'm not a big fan of that right
there
just so you know
um so that's one thing
laser treatments of what happens is
we get we get the sun spots from the
toxins and the caffeine
caffeine especially creates the sun
spots so i mean
that's one thing right there so the next
thing you're doing lasers for that
let's talk about skin cancer for a
little bit too so um
i've got one dipping sauce i got one in
the making right here so i'm gonna put
some raw honey in here
two teaspoons of raw honey
let's do that it's about two teaspoons
just doubled it up
this is gonna be really good this
dipping sauce is incredible
i'm gonna put a half a clove of garlic
small garlic clove in here really
you guys i just it's about protecting
you you know it's it's
like you know tough love tough love
you know
[Music]
i know i'm pretty harsh about stuff
truth is tough
truth truth truth is tough but it's
about it's about making sure
you guys are protected in any way i can
looking out for you guys
and you know that's a big deal
trying not to let you guys get suckered
into stuff like rishi coffee
mushroom coffee just trying to get you
guys like
in a safe zone so you don't get tricked
by all the different trends collagen
other things too butter in your coffee
whatever else garbage is out there a
dumb idea
and i just want you guys protected you
know it's important um
like apple cider vinegar the teeth
dissolver just
ruins teeth like nothing does just that
and caffeine just destroys teeth it's
it's like i mean if you guys like going
to the dentist in the future and you
like getting your teeth rolled and you
like getting
implants and bridges and root canals and
you like getting jaw disease
and you know lose your bones and your
jaw and everything else it's like
then caffeine caffeine caffeine lots of
chocolate because chocolate will make it
so you
you lose your jaw i mean you'll loop
down the road you lose your teeth your
teeth all wiggle out
it's like and that's what happens it's
caffeine doing that
it's caffeine and chocolate doing that
but yet everybody will tell you
chocolate's such a great thing to do
it's medicine it's plant medicine and
what a crock that is
it's like what do i do do i just be
quiet about this stuff and just try to
do my thing and be like
oh here's my book uh here you can get
better you guys or do i tell you like
everything straight do i just lay it out
on the table like i always have
for 35 years with everybody i've ever
talked to i can't change me you know i
got to make sure i look out for you guys
and that's that's what i'm about
um you put a little water in here
a couple tablespoons all right
and i'm gonna put a little green onion
in here chives but i'm gonna do green
onion
not gonna do a lot
so do some chives in there i'm doing
green onion i have them right here on
the board you see that
and i'm going to do a little bit of
parsley
it's about a quarter cup of some loose
herbs
quarter cup of loose herbs a little bit
of parsley some dill
right i got some dill here that's my
dill
i got some thyme here do a little bit of
that too okay
so and then i'm gonna blend it up let's
see what we get
but like if i don't give you guys just
the straight up on stuff i mean then
you're gonna just get like
tricked into stuff you know and that's
not good
it's not good especially when you're
sick or you don't feel good
i'm making the dipping sauce right here
this happens to be a really incredible
one
this is the recipe out of the new
edition
it's taking a little bit to spin
okay
so when it comes down to skin cancer
science research wants you afraid of the
sun now huh
he wants you afraid of the sun
i'm not telling you to go out and get a
sunburn
all right there we go
that's the dipping sauce i'm excited
so there's two dipping sauces with these
artichokes so science of research will
say hey
you know the sun is where your skin
cancer is caused the sun is the problem
the sun is a bad thing that's that's
what's going on
um it's all about the sun causing your
skin cancer like i said it's it's
but you know why did the sun just all of
a sudden go bad or something like that
like
because skin cancer is is more people
that don't go in the sun get skin cancer
than people that go in the sun
so why is the sun all of a sudden like a
problem
and the other thing is is what billions
of years go by and the sun went bad all
of a sudden
so i'm scratching my head on that one in
the last 20 years the sun went bad
so now the sun's the problem you know
in the last 20 30 50 years the sun went
bad so billions of years go by
and now all of a sudden the sun is bad
like just like our jeans so just like
our jeans went bad
so our genes went bad millions of years
our genes went bad okay um
billions of years the sun went bad now
so everything's just going bad but
but it's not the petrochemicals and the
pesticides and your air fresheners
it's not the toxic heavy metals in your
pharmaceuticals
that everybody's playing with uh from
big pharma it's toxic heavy metals and
every pharmaceutical it's not that it's
not the caffeine everybody's drugged on
it's not the drug dealer selling all the
caffeine right now like the mushroom
coffees and every other caffeine and
chocolate and everything else
to get teaching influencers to just sell
all their chocolate now and everything
else put their name on some chocolate
and just get more kids high and more
people high and more people high
it's not any of that no it's not the
radiation going through the airport
i mean jesus christ you go through the
airport and you get radiated to death
it's not that no it's not the msg and
all the natural flavors and all your
powders and all your supplements and
liquid supplements and all your foods
and packaged foods it's not the natural
flavors
that which is straight msg it's not the
ddt you're breathing in it's not the
asbestos you're breathing in driving
down the highway with your window down
and all the asbestos is coming in from
the sides of the highway
from asbestos breaks for 100 years it's
not the fire retardant on your
your bed sheets and your your bedding
and your your mattresses
no it's not the fire retardant on your
clothing it's not the fungicides under
clothing either
it's not that no the sun went bad that's
why you got skin cancer the sun went bad
i mean it's ridiculous it's like science
research fell asleep or something or
they're just
they're just so negligent so negligent
it's
it's almost it's almost too much at this
point it's almost
so ridiculous and too stupid that you
can't even like
you can't even i mean i don't even know
what to say anymore it's
oh man anyway okay so
we got a dipping sauce i need a bowl and
here it is
[Music]
so this dipping sauce is really good
it's a zucchini dipping sauce it's got
the lemon
and so i'm just getting it in here
so i got this sauce it's really good so
i got these artichokes here i got more
in here
right you guys see that just want to
bring it over
so so we're told it's not the suntan
lotions right what about the toxic
suntan lotions tell me those can't cause
cancer
i'm not saying burn yourself and sit in
the sun and get and get them
but what about the suntan lotions the
sunscreen right
toxic stuff you go to the beach and that
stuff is so
lethal like it's it's reeking off of
people like you go to the beach
and you don't sell you don't walk on the
beach and be like oh
clean ocean air let me breathe this in
you know you do when you go to the beach
oh my god i'm choking on cologne perfume
and
conventional laundry detergent and
sunscreen filled toxic heavy metals and
chemicals from companies
let me just breathe in all that suntan
lotion that's what happens when you go
to the beach
and you know skin cancer yeah the sun
hand lotions
talking about skin cancer so it's the
chemicals in the suntan lotion
the chemicals that are in there and um
and then you know our own toxins you
don't need to be in the sun
that's a whole point you could be
sitting at home and your liver is all
stagnant and sluggish with all the
toxins i talked about including the
radiation the ddt the pesticides and
chemicals and the gasoline
you're pumping in your gas tank we can't
run from all this stuff
but that's what i mean it's like that's
where the skin cancer comes from
and then you need the viruses too
because some
some some skin cancers are not viral
straight from toxins
and chemicals but then some skin cancers
they're viral
so you need to feed the viruses all
these toxins to create a skin cancer has
nothing to do with the sun
sun has not nothing to do with it same
thing with sunspots
the sun has nothing to do with sunspots
it's like i love that one
what does science research do do they
just wake up one morning and say we're
just going to the crap out of
everybody we're gonna sit in the lab and
not do anything we're gonna sit in the
lab kick our feet up and not do nothing
and then we're just gonna tell him it's
the sun we're just gonna make it up
there's no study that shows it we're
just gonna make it up
and i'll tell you why it's like that
because they don't want you knowing why
you're sick and they don't want you know
why you get skin cancer and they don't
want you to know why you got problems
and they don't want you to know what's
going on
they don't want you to know about that
about what's in the medications
they don't want to know wants you to
know anything they want you blind they
want you just
they want you just not knowing nothing
melissa says have you ever been asked to
host your own television show
a thousand times you have the best
information a
thousand times i always felt that if i
go and do one of the television shows
been asked by every major network
practically in the world to take on the
medical medium and do the medical medium
series the medical medium show
i've been asked all every network you
name the network
they've asked me okay and they've asked
me for 15
years 15 plus years i've been asked
long before social media i mean
15 plus years before social media right
and
um and i've turned it down because i
feel like
once it gets you in that rat race once
they get you in that
then you're screwed because you're gonna
be so wrapped up in that
that like that rat race they put you in
you're not going to be able to help
people like really help people you're
you're not going to be able to
be personable you're not you're not
going to be able to break bread with
your people because that's what i like
doing with you guys is breaking bread
with you guys
and those days ago they'll just be gone
next thing you know you got to get a
publicist see i don't have i don't do
that
i've been told a million times you need
pr you need publicist because you're
you're well known in the world you're
blah blah celebrity or whatever the heck
i'm told that all the time but the
minute you do that and then they're
going to force the publicist on your
force and then the publicist is gonna
say
don't you go near those dirty people
don't you go near those dirty little
people
don't you go near all those fans they're
they're just fans that's what they are
cause that's your publicist will do be
like
those are just fans you just stay away
from them don't talk to them
don't be transparent you're just you're
in your big tv show now and that's what
they'll do and i'm like i'm not going
that's not
my people are my people and meaning like
you know what i mean it's like you guys
are family so it's like
no i don't want to go and do that and
that's why i've turned it down because i
remember
many years ago been asked to do the
major networks make ask do tv shows and
there's a disconnect that happens once
you start going there
and that disconnect takes you away from
you know
the people who matter in the world and
getting them better you
you you know unless it's done right and
i haven't found that
that way to do it but that's how because
what i've done is focused on the books
so i was worried that the
tv careers and those big careers and
netflix careers and all the big
you know which are hey they're great for
somebody else maybe but i was always
worried that
though that career sector would take
away from
me sitting in my office at my desk
and making sure you can save your life
with these books i was afraid that
once i start doing all that tv heavy tv
stuff there's no getting these books out
to you guys anymore to save your lives
this book has saved millions of lives
around
the world right here the original book
this is the new edition
and and it's and i'm not going to get a
chance to tell you about the best
supplements you think if i do a tv show
i can tell you
what the best vitamin c is the vimergy
the microc and the
the curcumin there's no way like it
won't be a chance to do that
so anyway it was all about focusing on
writing the books
and that's why and you know and i was i
in and i've been asked to write them
from people who are in need and
you know and i didn't want that
disconnect the disconnect that happens
when you
go to tv land and now your fans are just
you know it's
it's i don't like that you know it's
it's not it's not about that because
i've seen that out there i've seen that
so anyway i want to share the dipping
sauce and everything else
so um these are the artichokes that's
the dipping sauce
so i just want to show you something
here okay um and here's another dipping
sauce right here
so that's one that's the maple mustard
maple dressing okay
that's the zucchini dressing right here
zucchini herb dipping sauce
that's the mustard maple dressing i
don't know if you guys can see this
it's not easy to see there we go it's
kind of hard to see
link is in the description by the way
okay so the book
recipe is in the new edition right here
it's 45 recipes in this book i added
and 28 day cleanse everything's been
expanded this thing is just
an incredible book so check it out wait
for it to come out in the library if you
want and
and you know after it comes out but it's
coming out in a couple weeks
you can get it at amazon.com
trisha marie said yeah the mustard maple
there you go anyway guys
the goal is to use this in the dipping
sauce you take the leaves off
these are so tender right now you see
this
take the leaves off put it in the
mustard maple dressing like that
it's really amazing
incredible
once again i might have put too much
cayenne in there
you guys that's amazing
i'm heading over to ig and tick tock
right now
so let's do it
come on over come on over to tick tock
the the view on tick tock's insane
so that it's such a great view when
you're on tick tock watching it
i'm going to be on ig at the same time
as tick tock let you guys know
all right if you want to see me live on
tick tock
then my profile my pick it's going to
light up
hit it click on it and watch me live
i just thought somebody said i'm coming
great awesome i'll see you there
jennifer you're going there too
cool cool can't wait i'll see you guys
had a great time with you guys
and i love you much i'll see you soon