out of the new book the new edition and
i'm hoping it's going to look like this
so let's hope so and it's a strawberry
banana salad
out of the new edition right here
medical medium
right here new addition revise and
expand it it's on amazon if you guys
wanted to take a look at it
um so i'm going to make the strawberry
banana salad
so this is a special recipe it really is
because it's
really healing because when you put a
healing food like strawberries healing
food like bananas
with greens leafy greens
that's the key it's the leafy greens
i've been saying that for years and
years and years
and that's what's always been missing
out of all the diet belief systems out
there it's always been the leafy greens
it's been missing in all the plant-based
diets
and it's been missing in all the vegan
diets vegetarian diets
sure somebody will have lettuce here and
there but the leafy greens have always
been missing
and medical medium information has put
the leafy greens
into diet belief systems out there now
so now you'll see plant-based people
all of a sudden start mentioning leafy
greens you'll see other people start
mentioning leafy greens
for the first time in health history and
it's that important so it's been a lot
of years of teaching teaching teaching
so decades of making sure people learn
about leafy greens and you guys are
going to learn because i'm going to talk
about the power of these leafy greens
the mineral salts in the spinach there's
gonna be some basil here too
and butter leaf lettuce i got a red
butter leaf lettuce
is what i have so that's gonna be
the red butter leaf lettuce for today um
the recipe
shows a green butter leaf lettuce but
you can use the red butter leaf it's
beautiful
you can use the green butter leaf here's
spinach right here
spinach is really a healing food i mean
it really is it's packed with trace
minerals
it's packed with phytochemical compounds
these things are anti-aging
really healing so i'll talk a little bit
more in depth about what these foods do
when it comes down to chronic illness
like fibromyalgia chronic fatigue
syndrome
hashimoto's thyroiditis all kinds of
different skin conditions eczema
psoriasis these foods
matter so when people are afraid of
plant foods
because they say they got like
anti-nutrients in them or something like
that
their foods with anti-nutrients and
stuff it's really ridiculous these are
the foods
that help us get better and help us heal
so
anyway you guys so i'm making the
strawberry banana salad if you just got
on
here that's what i'm gonna try to make
it look like right there
it's from the medical medium new edition
revised an expanded link is in the
description
check this book out it's packed i'll
talk about the book a little bit too
as we go go on and i want to answer
questions some health questions are fine
i'm going to talk about caffeine a
little bit
going to talk about chocolate a little
bit today i'm going to talk about
fragrances
and we're going to go into that too so
lots to talk about
great you guys are coming on exciting
day
right happy valentine's and
so much to do um so i'm going to start
making a recipe and we're going to cover
some cool stuff too you pre-ordered the
book yay
amazing incredible so i'm gonna read
comments gonna answer
answer questions like i said um
how to heal reynalds you know i'm gonna
cover that in a little bit too on that
whole condition
i think we should talk about that a
little bit later so we'll do that
um yeah let's make the recipe let's get
started we're going to answer questions
cool so first thing is the leafy greens
let's
let's get that going and this is so easy
too
such an easy recipe and that's one of
the key things it's like make it as easy
as possible making
make it as healing as possible all that
matters start with the leafy greens
right here so some spinach so i'm going
to put some nice spinach leaves now you
can chop
your greens up i'm going to chop them up
a little bit
kind of give them a little gentle chop
is what i'm going to do just you know
a couple of them but you can leave a lot
of them whole
and that's you know you can do you can
do either or so i'm going to put some
spinach in
probably cut a few pieces up too so i
got this beautiful spinach right here
getting it in the bowl i'm going to take
a few leaves
just give them a little chop too
you don't want them shredded you want to
keep them
still you know a decent size this is a
baby spinach just letting you guys know
now different times of the year there's
going to be different kinds of spinach
there's going to be
really big pieces big leaves
roughly leaves of spinach that's out
there i'm just cutting a few pieces of
baby spinach getting it in here
i'm going to put some butter leaf
lettuce in here too i'm going to put
that in here
now you can do i mean look if you don't
have the spinach and
if you don't have the butter leaf
lettuce you can do a mixed green
you can look if it's all you got in
there is you just got lettuce then let's
try that but i want you guys to be able
to
do the recipe the way it's supposed to
be someday so that's
so i'm showing you so that's the
beautiful spinach i have in here the
baby spinach i got the butter leaf
lettuce in here too
i'm gonna mix it up and put a little bit
more put a little bit more butter leaf
i'm gonna put a little bit more spinach
in here so
it's really good to be connected to your
food like this too because you really
get connected with it it's not just
making a recipe it's
more than that
so so i'm going to mix up these greens a
little bit so the spinach and the butter
leaf i'm just going to use my hands
i'm going to try to read some questions
hi there it's moringa
and then i saw something about spirulina
moringa's not spirulina
and meringue is not as good as spirulina
um
and spirulina is not as good as the best
spirulina so don't get that confused too
um for any spirulina questions that's
the spirulina
that i use right there that's the
vimergy the is in victor i
m e r g y vimergy.com that's the spinach
i mean the spirulina talking about
spinach and spirulina that's the
spirulina that's the good one
moringa is really is really not
that it's kind of overrated it's not
that helpful
when it comes down to fixing things and
healing things you really need to know
what
helps you heal and there's so many
trendy
different things that like products that
have been out over the years but
you can put as many trendy products as
you want out there
and you know something can be a buzz hey
moringa
neem oil you know whatever you want to
throw out there
but it doesn't mean that it fixes
something
like what's wrong with you what's going
on what kind of illness do you have is
it eczema psoriasis
is it ra is it hashimoto's is it fibro
is it pots is it depression is it
anxiety
and so moringa can't remove toxic heavy
metals
from the brain to relieve your
depression and anxiety
but spirulina can the right kind of
spirulina can just like that
um so i'm just mixing up some greens i
got some beautiful butter leaf
i got some spinach leaves right here put
a few more in here and then i'm gonna
start chopping up some strawberries and
some bananas
so i'm to do good to see everybody
coming on
can you add rocket yeah you can
you can add rocket if you got if you got
rocket kicking around your kitchen
that's a cool question could totally do
that that's all right
so i got this all set here
leafy greens are not a vegetable just
always keep that in mind so it's not a
vegetable it's not like hey i'm having
my vegetables
nope it's not a vegetable it's a leafy
green it's separate
so you got the wild foods you got the
leafy greens
you got your fruits okay you got your
vegetables you got your sea vegetables
so but you know this
you know so it's in and then you got
your herbs of course um
so i'm just reading some questions here
i find it i find it have a lot of sugar
wondering
if it's not healthy so i'm not sure if
like when it comes down to bananas and
strawberries
that's not the the wrong kind of sugar
so
you know high fructose corn syrup that's
a bad sugar
table sugar that's a bad sugar and sugar
isn't the problem when it comes down to
sickness when it comes down to
you know having poor health or symptoms
and conditions it's the fats
so keep that in mind so it's always the
fat so in chocolate cake
it's not the sugar that's the real scary
part in chocolate cake
it's the fat it's the butter it's the
oil
it's the lard it's anything like that
that's inside a chocolate cake
and so it's the fats in the chocolate
cake
that cause the damage not the sugar so
then
everybody gets scared and they're like
i'm not gonna have a strawberry
i'm not gonna have a banana and we need
sugar to
survive without sugar we die so we can't
think we can't function we can't walk we
can't exercise we can't talk
and that's why you know they even care
about our
sugar you know that's why they even care
about our sugar blood
sugar is critical to stay alive it's
also why
how do you save a diabetic's life when
they're on the floor
you know somewhere in a store and
they're just they're seizuring out
and they're just literally laying on a
floor somewhere and they look like
they're drunk
and everybody's walking by them and it's
a diabetic well
you bring a little bit of orange juice
with it over to them
they drink a little orange juice and
they they're actually able to get off
the floor
and get home and hop into a car can't
tell you how many times i've heard the
story heard
from doctors i heard it from people who
are diabetics
it's like all of a sudden they're
flatline they're on the floor somewhere
in a grocery store or
they're out shopping and they're laying
on a sidewalk and everybody's just
walking by them
and they're just like hunched over and
no one knows what's going on
and all they needed was a sip of orange
juice sip of sugar to get them off the
ground and save their life so it's
it's really not like people think it's
really how it works
um what happens is we eat so much fat
that we trap the sugar
in our bloodstream and then the sugar
becomes a little bit of a problem then
but it's not the sugar in the end it's
the fat
that's in our bloodstream then we get
the insulin resistance
and then that insulin can't carry the
sugar into the cells of the body because
of
all the fat so you don't want to be
afraid of a strawberry when you take a
look at this strawberry right here and
i got them right here look at these so
see the strawberries right here you guys
that's a beautiful strawberry right here
so
that is a healing food an incredible
healing food everybody's worried about
how they look with aging they're worried
about
wrinkles they're worried about aging too
fast
and they're worried about their skin
they're worried about their nails
they're worried about all of that
and if you don't want to age you want
those kinds of foods right here so
look at that the strawberry but you know
what happens we're taught to be afraid
and we're taught to be scared and have
fear
and it's like fear about fruit fear
about bananas fear about strawberries
that's what we're taught and we're
taught that every day and it's sad
it's so sad anyway i got my leafy greens
here butter leaf lettuce
spinach leafy greens that's
the difference and you know what it kind
of like sounds a little silly when i say
it
somebody might be like oh he's he's just
you know he's saying leafy greens like
we don't know what leafy greens are wall
just so you know
no one talks about him no one talked
about them
okay they're like foreign to the health
scene
for years i can't tell you how many
health gurus that
contacted me for help wanted advice
wanted information to heal their people
or heal themselves
and the many you mentioned leafy greens
are like what like what
leafy greens i mean i'm talking about
top doctors in the world that are health
gurus that have books out they're like
leafy greens like what do you mean
and over the years spinach is now
now you'll see it more and more and more
and it's from the medical medium
information the spinach soup
this you know all about that um
so yeah and over the last five years now
but over the
last five years six years because the
medical medium books you'll hear you'll
hear about leafy greens more in spinach
and so forth but i got salad going on
here
um let's chop up some strawberries so i
got these beautiful strawberries
so i'm going to move this over for a
second
you can cut the back off the strawberry
you guys you can do that you see the
little
the caps you can keep them if you want
okay so i've been teaching about leafy
greens for over 30 years
and 30 years ago
forget it like what's a leafy green
even 20 years ago what's a leafy green
and
even still today even with all the
teaching the lectures i've done
how many um people in the health scene
reached out for help
reached out for answers from mystery
illnesses all these years
i've talked to thousands and thousands
of people
they still didn't know about leafy
greens
it's weird they would say do you mean a
salad
um aw are you talking about a salad
like yeah a salad of iceberg lettuce no
talking about leafy greens anyway
cutting the backs off of these
you don't have to if you don't want to
you can save those you can eat those
whatever you can do you can throw them
in yourself i like to take them off on
these
okay so i'm chopping uh
the little caps off the strawberries
right here
you guys can share a protocol someone
with chronic
lime okay so
in this book right here so you might
want to check
check it out on amazon okay this is the
revised and expanded so you got to make
sure it's the new edition revised and
expanded medical medium book
there's a lyme disease chapter and
i broke the truth out there about lyme
disease about the cause of lyme disease
and why people have neurological lyme
and how things like cats claw are
critical and other
other tools so and i talk about it in
here so
and i'll give you a little rundown of
lyme disease but you want to check out
the medical medium book one the new
edition
that's the all-time like information
about lyme disease
lyme disease is not bacterial so if that
turns you off or gets you
upset don't let it because
science and research have now because of
medical medium information in fact
a famous doctor just reached out to me
recently and said that
he's really happy that that's medical
science
took lyme disease out of the bacteria
category so
they don't believe it's bacteria anymore
because
of the millions of medical medium books
that told the truth that it's viral
so so millions of people took
the book the first book the first
edition right this is the second edition
they took the book into their doctor's
offices
and said he says it's viral and so
because of that it
changed lyme disease so all these years
later now they took they removed lyme
disease out of bacterial and now it's an
autoimmune category which means they
don't know the cause of it
but autoimmune the cause of autoimmune
is viral so just letting you know
so the first way to heal lyme disease is
to know
what the cause is what's causing my
symptoms what's causing my neurological
symptoms that someone
that a doctor says is lyme disease um
and so viruses such as epstein-barr
and here's the funny thing it's not
funny but interesting
is that doctors check they test for
epstein-barr now with lyme patients
because of medical medium books because
i said that hey lyme disease is caused
by epstein-barr and shingles okay and so
what they do
is they test for epstein-barr lyme you
know lyme patients they get tested for
that so they're always getting a lyme
test and an epstein-barr test now
they're getting both at the same time
because of medical medium books so i'm
cutting up these strawberries
right here putting some nice strawberry
pieces in the salad
you can cut them up as small as you want
to cut them up these are the sizes i'm
cutting up
cutting them up right here
so putting some nice strawberry pieces
on here
strawberry banana salad is what i'm
making you guys
when you eat a food like this when you
eat a recipe like this
be mindful for what it's doing for you
like keep that in your consciousness
okay
because when you respect the food
that's actually healing you a connection
is made
that's really important to know and hey
if you don't respect the food that's
healing you and you don't care and
you're just eating it or trying it out
it's still gonna help heal you
but so i want to talk about
why healing foods are so important for
us
one thing is fragrances okay so
fragrances that are made from chemical
companies that saturate us every day so
when you go into the store
you get hit you get assaulted by
fragrances
that's colognes that's perfumes and then
we're taught by chemical companies to
breathe it in to
like the smell air fresheners scented
candles
so here's the thing everybody's so
health-minded these days
everybody's you know like a health guru
now everybody's like a health hack or
everybody's like
into health and and you see that now
everybody knows a little bit something
about health right but at the same time
they seem to know a lot about health or
seem to know anything about health
they're lighting the candles so they're
doing all these things
to help themselves they're doing their
avocado toast they're doing their
oatmeal with some raisins they're taking
care of themselves right
they're doing their almond milk even
though that's not the best but whatever
they're doing these things and they're
like hey i'm eating healthier i'm
working out i'm exercising and then
they're burning scented candles
and they're they're they're going
against they're
countering all the good stuff they're
doing for themselves they're countering
it
so they might eat a good meal they might
stay away from processed foods and fried
greasy foods
but they're sucking in dangerous
chemicals like
scented candles air fresheners
fabric softeners conventional detergents
right and they're just breathing it all
in and they're doing it at their homes
and they're just they're sucking in all
that chemical oil
and that toxic oil those toxic chemicals
are more damaging and more
toxic than smoking so you know years ago
you guys everybody would be smoking
everywhere you'd smoke in public you'd
smoke in the hospital
okay you can be a patient in the
hospital
years ago in the 80s and you can smoke
cigarettes while you're in bed
you can smoke cigarettes while you're in
bed whether you're there for
like a you know something going on like
you know you had an anxiety attack and
now you're in the hospital or maybe you
had a fever
or something and you're in the hospital
you could just light up your cigarettes
right there
1985 1987
i used to visit people who would ask me
for help they would say can you visit
you visit my family member aw
can you go to the hospital and see a
family member that's
very ill because we want to see if you
have any answers the doctor wants to
talk to you and see if you have any
answers
so i would go to the hospital and you
just walk in or you walk by you walk
you walk down the hallway and in every
room
everybody's smoking in their beds and
that like 1987
1989 1990s just smoking in their beds in
the hospital right
you go into a restaurant everybody's
smoking in the restaurant sucking down
cigarettes everywhere
all that smoking is happening in the
restaurant some i'm chopping up some
strawberries right here
and so what happens is that
with all that smoking going on okay
um with all that smoking going on
everywhere in the past
they stopped it right it's banned you
can't smoke in a public place
you can't smoke in a hospital you can't
smoke
in church you could smoke in church
right after prayer
boom light up your cigarettes just be
smoking right inside
right inside the church but guess what
right you can't anymore
no smoking but guess what that smoke
was nothing compared to what you're
breathing in now
those cigarettes were a joke they were a
joke compared and they still are now
anybody's smoking now
it's a joke compared to air fresheners
that's the killer man that's the killer
no one's keeping tabs on
those cigarettes are a joke compared to
cologne
the cologne is the killer you slap your
man slaps on that cologne your man slaps
on all that cologne
he's killing you and you don't even know
it take that stuff
toss it out you know tell your man that
cologne's going
because the cologne is ladled in
chemical company toxins like
real serious ones aftershave cologne
hair products hair spray scented candles
fabric softeners air fresheners those
are the killers right now
that's the assault on women and women's
health and men's health
so man those cigarettes
they don't touch they don't touch the
destruction
and the damage that all those fragrances
are causing right now
they don't even touch it but here's the
sick part right
chemical companies want to make sure
that you're trained
that you're trained in thinking these
smells are good
you're trained to go hey i'm going to
light the scented chemical
candle and what does it smell like
christmas what does it smell like
you know what does it smell like a
christmas tree what does it smell like
you know in the whole bit
and we're being trained to actually
breathe all this stuff in we're being
trained
to get poisoned so you know it's kind of
funny i see a lot of people that think
they know a lot about health out there
okay and i've seen that for years right
you know i haven't been in this for two
years
or five years or seven years been in
this for over 35 years right
and i've shaped health of what it's
today like i've
shaped it all with the information from
mm going all the way back
and all so many of the tools are in
medical medium
medical medium tools are out there in
the world and people are using them
they're not
they're not citing it back you know some
people do
but the bottom line is
you know with this is that
there's information in these in this in
in these healing tools
to help us battle these things like
fragrances and other stuff but people
don't know about that stuff they just
don't even get it i mean there's so many
people that are into yoga yoga studios
that are like burning incense that have
chemicals in them and it's like hey a
friend of mine was at a yoga studio
and said this the smell was so strong
her eyes were burning it's because a lot
of the incense is not like
natural it's got chemicals in it the
fragrances are in there so you want
fragrance free wherever you go
you want to protect yourself when you
order new clothes
saturated with all kinds of chemicals
and
you got to think about children and you
got to think about babies
and if you got air fresheners in your
house pull them out of the wall
throw them out so that your babies
aren't breathing that in
just that's how you do it that's how you
protect your families
and get rid of the scented candles
because those are killers
those are killers and they're really
really rough on people
um so we're being yeah lorraine hey
lorraine's there
we're being trained to be poisoned we
really are and that's what's happening
and what's in these fragrances
are toxic heavy metals so that's another
thing too if you just guys just got on
there
i'm on a rant right here about
fragrances toxic heavy metals and
fragrances the poisons involved
how smoking is a joke compared to these
toxic chemicals that we're breathing in
every day
we're being trained to like the smell of
perfume we're being trained to breathe
in cologne it's
everywhere you walk into a grocery store
i mean it's pumping with all kinds of
cleaners
it's pumping with all kinds of cleaners
that they're spraying that they're
mopping floors with that are completely
toxic
it's it's pumping with clone aftershave
perfume everywhere
anyway i'm making the strawberry banana
salad it's a way to counter all this
stuff
so if you wonder why hey why should i
eat healthy
and another thing too is like
we should really like say something out
there you know we should talk about it
out there a little bit more we should
ask for the fragrance free the more you
ask the more you talk about it the more
they stop
and because you don't want all that
chemical soaking in your
your food right so i wash these
strawberries really good
because i noticed that when i got
these strawberries right that they had
like a cologne smell going on on the
packages
because of the store it had like a
chemical smell slash cologne smell
slash air freshener smell and i had to
wash these strawberries really good like
i had to wash them good
to actually get that off of them and
it's like it's just unfair
it's like what you know it's like you
may as well just bring the cigarettes
back man just bring them back
everybody's
smoke just why not who cares because
guess what we're doing
all the other stuff and it's killing us
so let's all just light up go into the
grocery stores light up everybody light
up and just
why not hey it's safer than all this
stuff i can tell you that it's actually
safer but no don't start smoking let's
get some bananas chopped up
anyway does that include organic
perfumes organic scented candles yes
because organic
doesn't mean anything because the
chemical fragrances get into those two
it's different if it's a candle that
just has an essential oil in it like
maybe it just
has essential oil and then beeswax
essential oil and then maybe a soy wax
say right and it's just a little bit of
that but
perfumes that even are organic are still
ladled in like chemical they're still in
there
that's the trick that's a whole nother
game too going on
um so i got some bananas so i'm just
going to cut them in these nice pieces
you don't want them too small but you
don't want them too big so i'm just
cutting them
right here this is a really nice banana
cigarettes are filled with chemicals
right yeah they are okay
scented candles
100 times worse i wouldn't even probably
worse than even 100 times
okay it's it's an oil base
scented candles have an oil base of a
soup
of dangerous chemicals synthetically
made in a chemical factory
that aren't tested no one knows what the
damage that it could be done
on people in their lungs their body how
it can promote cancer like
be literally a trigger for cancer
so here we're worried about cancer
everybody's worried about women are
worried about cancer
and they're being assaulted with all
these chemicals 24 7
breathing them in and their families and
their children and
this is no joke it's no joke man um
i'm cutting up these bananas and little
pieces here
that's what i'm doing i'm gonna stack
them and do it this way
put some nice little banana pieces here
carol how do you wash strawberries i put
them in a big bowl of water right
one one bigger than this you can use a
smaller one but i use a bowl like that
right
and i put a little bit of
no fragrance soap okay a little bit of a
natural
real natural clean clean soap um
you can use one you have that doesn't
have fragrances in it
okay just a little drop a couple of
drops you just give it a good rinse
i'm gonna put these banana pieces in
it's a lot better than what could be
you know on the food from the store
got my banana pieces in there i'm going
to put one more banana in here too
martha says cologne smell perfume
scented detergent
candles air fresheners send me gagging
and running out of the room
rightfully so totally rightfully so for
real
because um it's that bad
make sure all your products are
fragrance free
that's that's important right there
here's the other thing too
they have us chemical companies right
have a so saturated with dangerous
chemicals all the time
that we don't know what we're smelling
anymore we don't know
if you're in a home or apartment
or wherever you live right and wherever
you are
and you're there and you don't
have all those fragrances and you don't
smell all the smells and then you walk
into somebody's house
and you smell everything you smell their
detergents you smell their perfumes you
smell their cologne smell their scented
candles or air fresheners right
they won't even smell they don't even
know what they're smelling in there like
they have no idea it's that bad and
meanwhile
hey it's one more step closer to cancer
yeah one more step closer to chronic
illness one more step closer to chronic
fatigue syndrome
one step closer to depression one step
closer
to to anxiety those
chemical compounds those dangerous
synthetic chemical compounds in those
fragrances
will set your anxiety freaking
high send it high
is what it is what it can do
that's what it can do okay
um am i just
do i just
i don't make the party fun are you guys
all right just
mixing these up a little bit
got some some banana got some strawberry
in there look at that i'm gonna put a
little basil in here
that's what i think i'm gonna do get a
little basil
got some little basil right here a
couple of basil leaves
basil antibacterial antiviral
putting you know you want fragrance free
hair care products
it's another thing too to think about
i'm putting a few basil leaves on top
here
uh leaves right you can use lettuce in
here because that's what i have i have a
butter leaf lettuce in there so i have
spinach
butter leaf lettuce i got strawberries
chopped up
the strawberry banana salad i'm making
got the bananas i got the little bit of
basil here you guys
okay fresh basil is so great in anything
ebb says ebb and flow says absolutely
basil is lovely isn't it it's amazing
so i'm gonna make the strawberry banana
dressing it's an
option so if you guys want to know what
we're talking about here if you just got
on here
that's the recipe i'm making if you can
take a look
all right strawberry banana salad there
it is it's in this book right here
amazon.com check it out um it's there to
order
it's the new edition revised and
expanded i haven't even gone into
what's in this book it's so packed with
information 45 recipes i've put in there
uh it's an incredible book but we're
just answering questions talking about
stuff
so i'm going to make the dressing let's
do that that's next
i got the blender right here
okay what's incredible about this book
you guys
right just letting you know um if you
got anxiety you got depression you got
chronic fatigue you got fibromyalgia
got thyroid problems of any kind
hashimoto's thyroiditis lyme disease
r.a rheumatoid arthritis okay
symptoms of menopause adhd
autism if you're worried about candida
there's a candida chapter in here
um shingles whole thing about shingles
in here lupus it's another thing too
uh ptsd all that information is in here
but packed
information it's advanced it's the whole
thing about this book
is the first edition has already saved
millions of people's lives around the
world
this is the second edition i basically
put a whole book
inside this book it is beyond
a new edition so i put information about
the pandemic in here so
i'm making the recipe so i'm going to
make
that's this is just my this is just my
manuscript i handed in to the publisher
this is not what your book's going to
look like see how it's not in a binder
and everything
so this is just my copy this is my
manuscript right here slitting it up
so there's no confusion so let's make
okay so i'm going to put um about a
third of a cup of strawberries are going
to go in here
in this blender
so about a third of a cup it's a few
strawberries
is it going to print yeah bernadette
totally you can get on
amazon right now get the pre-order okay
you can
you know lock down a copy now on
amazon.com
barnes noble it's another one too
so i'm making okay it's about a third of
a cup
probably even a little bit more there um
i want to talk about chocolate a little
bit too in a minute because
i want to go into that a little bit i
want to talk about coffee too there's
one thing that people don't realize
that thousands and thousands and
thousands of workers over the years have
died
picking coffee so everybody can have
their cup and get jacked up on
on the coffee high and it's it's kept
kept on the down low
no one talks about it because the
caffeine industry is so powerful
that they don't let that secret out
right i talk about that in the medical
medium podcast at apple podcast
check out my my chocolate much tea
coffee episode on medical beam podcast
at apple podcast
and it's like it's it's really
disturbing how it works
when you're picking coffee all day long
and you're sweating
and you're you're rubbing on you're
rubbing on all of the leaves
and you got you're rubbing on all the
coffee and you're actually in the groves
and you're getting covered with that
toxin something happens and i talk all
about it medical medium podcast at apple
podcast and how many
people have died all through the years
and how serious that is um
and also we can have some coffee so we
can have you know
we can be jacked up in the morning so we
can hide all our symptoms and issues
that the medical industry doesn't want
anybody to really know we have
and you know and then
that's how it works so i'm gonna put
some banana in here
doing about a third of a cup chopped
banana
you don't have to do a lot this is just
the dressing
i just lost a piece right there
talk about chocolate in a minute too
it's interesting there's no
there's no such thing as fair trade when
it comes down to chocolate or
sustainable
it's really sad when you see that market
it like that because
the farmers who are farming chocolate
cacao
they're penniless they're in utter
poverty i mean i'm talking starvation
poverty they make about 100
100 a year so they sit there cutting
cacao
they kill themselves getting it to
market they get ripped off they get paid
nothing people in africa and
what happens is that um
i mean we're talking they're in poverty
and they get ripped off
so when when their cacao is bought for
them purchased from them
so it can go into into the market and
then become like chocolate cake
chocolate candies chocolate whatever
cacao
nibs what happens is that when when that
when that um chocolate finally moves
into the market nobody knows what
happened and where it came from and
everybody's ripped off so all the
farmers are ripped
off they given they're given pennies
they're starving they get
cheated and they're sitting there
sweating killing killing themselves
their families are trying to pick
a cow off trees so they can get one
penny
for like five pods of cacao one penny
for like 50 pods of
one nickel for 50 pods of cacao right
and so when you go in and you're buying
your chocolate bar you get your cacao
nibs and you're throwing on top your
smoothies you're throwing it on top of
your
your food and everything like that and
everybody's telling you to plant
medicine
it's good for you and meanwhile just
getting you high and jacking you up on
caffeine which
ages you fast and nobody realizes it
well you're being
told all that and you wouldn't believe
the wake of a disaster that's occurring
for the growers i mean it's so sad it's
devastating it's like armageddon it's
like literally the apocalypse it's so
bad
and they're intense and they're
literally dying some of them
intense they try to they get up they try
to they try to pick more cacao for you
and and they're getting pennies some of
them some families only make 50
for a whole year of harvesting and
killing themselves
getting cacao ready for the market and
when you think about that and then they
say oh it's sustainable this cacao is
sustainable this chocolate's sustainable
it's fair trade
it's like are you freaking kidding me
that's just sick it's actually demented
all right let's make it let's make it
dressing here
it's always something something to talk
about you guys
always something to talk about so
i got a little strainer here so i'm
gonna just drop some lemon juice in here
so you could do like one one teaspoon
two teaspoons
i'm gonna try for one teaspoon in here
to get it to spin
you do um and then i'm going to add a
little bit of water too
so a tablespoon of water one to three
tablespoons of water
let's put a little bit of that in there
i'm gonna try to blend this up
making the dressing for the salad so
here's the salad if you guys look
dr fan md
yeah are cocaine leaves sustainable
that's a good question
dressing
[Music]
all right so i got a little ramekin here
so
i like my dressing on the side you can
pour it on the salad if you like
but i like my dressing on the side as i
just spilled a little bit of it
so i wanted to show you guys so i angled
it your way see so that's the dressing
right here um
so i like the dressing
seat in the front okay that's cool
that's awesome right there
you can pour a little bit on the sap you
can pour it right over the salad it's
perfectly fine
what i do is i kind of like do that and
i dip it into the dressing
that's the way i do but everybody's got
their own their own you know little
thing that they do
so so you know i want to talk
you guys got a couple more minutes about
that about this i want to talk about a
little bit more about
the things going out there with
chocolate the things going on with
women's health
fragrances and stuff like that this is
the strawberry banana salad
just made it that's the butter leaf
lettuce right there okay
you see that um spinach okay
spinach trace mineral salts for the
brain
neurotransmitters so your
neurotransmitters they get dehydrated
and they dry up so here's what happens
everybody's doing their caffeine and you
could do your caffeine you could do your
chocolate i'm not
picking on anybody here i'm just telling
you what's happening so you know
but when you when you do when you're
when you're all cranked up
on the caffeine what it's doing is it's
burning out your neurotransmitters
so those neurotransmitters are priceless
those neurotransmitters are how you can
think in the end how you could keep your
brain alive long when you
when you're older so you don't get
alzheimer's you don't get dementia
and caffeine is a fast track to dementia
it's a fast track to alzheimer's because
what the caffeine does is it cranks up
your adrenals then your
adrenals are pumping pump and pump and
pump and pump in and that adrenaline
scorches all your neurotransmitters
inside your brain so your electrical
impulses they need those
neurotransmitters
your neurons need those
neurotransmitters your glial cells need
those
neurotransmitters and so what the
caffeine does is it stimulates your
adrenals your adrenals end up pumping in
all that epinephrine the epinephrine
just starts to eat away at your
neurotransmitters
and then you get that like you're in
your 50s you're in your 60s and just
like what
and you just start forgetting like
where's my car keys for the set for the
50th time
wait a minute i don't think i could get
my way home now i don't i think i'm lost
on in the car
like all that stuff starts happening and
oh no one ever said
20 years of coffee could cause this no
no one ever said
you know all those years of chocolate
caffeine coffee tea espresso
is gonna burn out my neurotransmitters
and then when you got the heavy metals
in there it's worse worse worse makes it
worse
and and no one ever tells women that the
reason why they're getting the hair
thinning is from the caffeine use
it's from the chocolate cacao it's from
it's from the coffee it's from the
espresso
it's from the tea because women's
adrenals
have a hormone in that in that in that
whole pocket of adrenaline in there how
there's a special hormone that keeps
hair on women's heads
it's different than men women's health
and men's health entirely two different
things
entirely two different things and no one
thinks about that
no one knows about that so it's like
okay hey let's make sure we do all the
caffeine we want to do but when your
hair's thinning and falling out and
you're getting all the
patches and everything else and your
hair is thinning and it's falling out in
your hands and it's on the shower floor
and no one's telling you it's from the
five years of caffeine the seven years
of caffeine
20 years of caffeine two years of
caffeine no one's telling it
and that's a whole other thing all on
its own so it's one of the biggest
contributors to women's hair thinning
and hair loss is caffeine
anyway why am i even talking about all
this because i want you to be able to
counter it because i'm not going to be
able to get you off your caffeine
i know that i'm probably not going to be
able to get you off of him and some
people i'll get him off of it
but doesn't mean i'll be able to get you
off with cacao does it mean i'll get you
off of chocolate i mean what do i have
to gain just eat it all you want right
like what do i have to gain if you're
jacked up on coffee every day and your
adrenals are pumping and flooding and
it's burning out your neurotransmitters
like why should i care
you could drink all the coffee you want
all the tea you want all the espresso
all the chocolate you want
but i do care that's that's the problem
i guess
i actually do care so i want you to be
able to counter it strawberry banana
salad
helps counter because i may not be able
to get you off your caffeine
but you can get the new addition
you can learn how to make the strawberry
banana salad
and donna cuff says what an eye opener
never heard this before
thank you thank you for being here
that's why you're on the medical medium
channel because it's always advanced
information
it's been like that for years and years
and years it's why doctors all around
the world contact me want information
for their patients it's why i'm well
known to be the guy
to have answers for bizarre symptoms and
that's how we do it
um so you know i put out the information
people take it don't cite it back you
know i put out the information about how
lemon water okay
16 to 32 ounces first thing in the
morning flushes your liver
and flushes toxins out of your body and
no one knew that they just thought lemon
water was good for you that was it no
one knew
it flushed out your liver in the morning
and
but no one wants to cite that back
that's 30 years of hard work but it
doesn't matter it's about you guys
getting your healing but you know what
does matter
when information's not cited back then
someone can't find their way
and figure out how to heal themselves
from lyme disease
no one can find their way to how to heal
themselves from m e
c f s lupus r a hashimoto's so i guess
it really
it does matter so you guys
strawberry banana salad right here so
what happens if people don't cite it
back then people don't know where to go
to heal
and it keeps others from healing and
that's on
those people man the people that won't
cite it back you want
you want people to stay sick it's not
fair
um heavy metal detox smoothie i just saw
that yeah
you guys if you're doing a heavy metal
detox smoothie don't just
use any old spirulina any old barley
grass i'll give you a couple of tips you
don't want to use
barley grass you're not going to get the
metals out so you want barley grass
juice powder that's the difference keep
that in mind okay
so that's the vimergy barley grass juice
powder i'm not sponsored
i don't own the company um but the
stuff's that good
it's what i take every day so i had my
heavy metal detox movie this morning i
used the vimergy barley grass
juice powder seed juice powder
and that's the best one vimergi visa and
victor i m e r g
y bimrg.com but that's
what here the reason why i'm saying this
is i saw the heavy metal detox smoothie
someone say something about it and what
people do is they use barley grass
guess what the metals don't come out
people don't get better
because the mistake was made the details
matter
they matter same thing with spirulina
like
not all spirulinas are equal that's the
one from vimergy that's the one that
works in the heavy metal detox smoothie
um details matter bottom line just
letting you guys know
so anyway when it comes down to taking
care of yourself
okay i basically want i was talking to
this doctor the other day he said
anthony i can't get everybody off
the coffee i can't get everybody to stop
eating chocolate
they think the chocolate's good for them
because they're told that it's good for
you right
he says i can't stop him so what do i do
i said counter it man
you got to counter it you can't stop
people
from hurting themselves because they've
been brainwashed and they've been
trained to hurt themselves so you can't
you can't easily stop it
right but maybe you can counter it
is what you can do so i told this doctor
look
get them on this rubber banana salad
because that's what i'm going to make
when i do the live get them on the foods
to counter it
get them on the strawberries get them on
all that good stuff
and so it's important um you guys
we covered some fragrance talk about how
dangerous it is how it's assault to
women's health
and how it declines women's health ages
them fast
so i know i know no one wants to age
quick men and women right
you don't want to age you don't want
your skin getting all wrinkly fast
you don't wanna you don't want the hair
to fall out
you don't want um you don't want all the
spots on the skin
right you don't want all the spots on
the skin okay you don't want that
you don't want your skin to get weak and
then hang
and get flabby right you don't want it
getting loose
all the skin to get really loose you
don't want that collagen
to get all eaten up right and then you
lose
all that a lot the elasticity falls
falls apart and everything okay
well i'm gonna give you some tips okay
the caffeine
will age you fast that's what will
happen
and anything you do good for yourself
you're just working against it to try to
counter it
okay keep that in mind the fragrances
will age you fast send the candles air
fresheners
clones perfumes all that stuff
will age you fast and you're trying
we've got to counter it if you're going
to still use that stuff
right and chocolate will age you fast
but if you want to still do it you got
my support 100
i'll still give you answers i'll still
give you protocols i'll still give you
the thousand protocols that are in the
medical medium book so you have answers
to heal
i'll still give you all that to make
sure you guys have the opportunity to
heal and move forward i still want to do
all that
um so yeah
anyway guys that's a little just a
little fun today i'm going to instagram
i'm going to head over there i'm going
to make the strawberry banana salad
again
on instagram so you guys coming over
and i'm gonna talk about some of this i
might talk about something else i might
answer a couple different questions
um i love you guys and
i stand with you on your journey to heal
um
and i believe in you okay and i'll see
you over
on ig yeah these strawberries are
organic i was just reading the comments
you guys
and these strawberries are organic
what's a good collagen to use
none what's a good collagen to use no
collagen
because collagen is a scam you can't eat
to create collagen that's you can't eat
a sheep's eyeball
to fix your eyeball if you got an eye
problem like you got like a retina
problem
detached retina if you've got glaucoma
if you got anything like that you can't
eat a human eyeball
to fix your eyeball if you got a liver
disease
you can't eat liver to fix your liver
see
you can't eat collagen to fix your
collagen that's the greatest scam going
on right now
it's just throwing money away if you
wanna you know you wanna get the
collagen better you do your celery juice
you learn how to eat these foods you get
the leafy greens
to build your collagen the leafy greens
i'm giving you guys the answers all the
time and you don't see me holding up a
collagen
i can make a medical medium collagen
probably sell a billion of them be like
here's a medical medium collagen but i
won't do that
because i'm not a snake because i just
want you to heal
and i want you guys to be just free of
pain and i don't want you guys ripped
off
um yeah just saw
somebody asked about menopause medical
medium new edition got a chapter on it
by the way let's check it out i'm going
to ig now
love you guys take care