hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 or 20 30 years to
wait to find out what's causing their
cystitis because that's strep related
what's causing their sinusitis that's
chronic where you have to get surgeries
all the time that chronic strep what's
causing your
utti that strep a cacus really elusive
really hard to discover or to diagnose
you know you can go to an ENT they're
not going to know what's going on they
might say it's bacteria they might say
we don't know it's
inflammation but strep is rampant we're
going to talk about it today and and we
don't have time to waste in the sense
where if you've suffered with this if
you dealt with it I know people have
dealt with sinus problems for years it
it's it can be tragic for a lot of
people without a doubt sinus congestion
sinus pain chronic sinus infection ear
infections otitis media that's you know
the ear infection in the middle ear
caused by strep okay
UTI gastric problems meaning intestinal
disorders sibo all this is Strep so if
you just logged on you better hang on
for the ride cuz today is a big day and
you want want to hear this show there's
no doubt about it because we're talking
about strepa cacus revealed strepa cacus
is an opportunistic bacteria that causes
far more health problems than medical
science and research currently know and
I'll talk about how strep is behind UTI
like I said before sore throats
digestive issues sibos sinus infections
and more so that's what we're talking
about today I'm excited about this
because so many people are lost with
this there they don't know what's
causing their societ is they don't know
that it was the strep throat they had
when they were 8 years old and then when
they're 35 years old and they got cystis
they don't know that that's what it is
it's still strep and strep has this
interesting pattern we're going to talk
about so we're going to talk about the
pattern of what it does and how it works
also what it's related to as well what
it's related to so that's a whole
another thing and uh we got lots to
cover and also have you locked down a
copy of life-changing Foods
um that is going to be so fun when you
guys open that book you're going to be
blown away and and unless I'm wrong but
I don't think I'm wrong about this we
painstakingly spirit and I painstakingly
put information in this book that even
supersedes the show I do here by far and
we really really knocked it out of the
park like we didn't hold back I didn't
care what it took I didn't care how many
nights I stayed up I didn't care how
many nights my brain was mush and
frazzled from taking data for hours and
hours and hours from Spirit to make sure
that we know all the diseases and
conditions that fruits and vegetables
herbs and spices and wild foods can help
us recover from if they're used the
right way including emotional levels
what it can do for Spiritual lessons we
can get from it it is definitely
interesting and so make sure you look
into that I'm excited about that I'm I'm
I'm giggly I'm because when you open
those when you open that book you're
going to be you're going to be shocked
and and that and I'm excited about it
because it's it was well worth the the
the pain of putting it together so I'm
so excited um anyway and a little bit
about me if this is your first show um
before we go on about strep and
everything and just if if this is your
first show started at age four um
diagnosed my grandmother of lung cancer
by hearing a voice perfectly clear that
said Grandma has lung cancer pronounced
it it took a couple of times to
pronounce it at the dinner table and uh
everybody's forks and knives dropped at
on the plates uh there was some Shock
going on some Shock value going on from
a four-year-old telling Grandma she had
lung cancer and then Weeks Later brought
her in and she did and that was the
start of what happened and it never
stopped and I've dedicated my entire
life of bringing truthful information
not
misinformation truthful information so
people can find their way out of the
darkness of misinformation because it's
one of the greatest things that holds us
back in healing all of our conditions
and it's also why millions of people
stay sick because the truth is not out
there in so many ways so I've dedicated
my life and and and decades and helping
tens of thousands of people with the
right information so that 30 years later
they're living a life right now
healthier than they ever did 30 years
ago and you know and this is this is
what what I've dedicated my life doing
and I've see it all the time you guys
people coming to me like sick for 3
years with with something that no one
can figure out sick for four years that
no one can figure out and then it gets
all the different labels and they still
stay sick and it's it's okay it's cute
and fuzzy to throw labels on people like
Lyme disease and everything else but if
they're not getting better or if they
keep on getting sick do you really know
what was wrong with them to begin with
and that's that's where we clear the air
here that's the whole point of the gift
I received that's the whole point of why
I'm here so you know how to get better
so you can get better from Lyme disease
you can get better from chronic fatigue
syndrome fibromyalgia there is hope for
Lupus there is hope for ALS there is
hope for Alzheimer's there is hope for
dementia there is hope for colitis there
is hope for Crohn's hashimotos
thyroiditis the list goes on Scleroderma
you know fibrosis just it keeps on going
it keeps on going and there is hope for
all of this including strange symptoms
like reena's disease syndrome to
everything under the sun
there is hope for all of it Addison's
Parkinson's Wilson's we can just keep on
putting as many doctor's names as we can
they're named after diseases as we want
and you know and there is hope with the
right information I've dedicated my life
to it and that's why you guys are here
that's why I'm here I'm honored I live
for helping you that's the whole point
so let's talk about strep let's do it
let's go into this so it starts out
interesting with strep it starts out
interesting when we're we're meaning
like it's it's a it's it's the whole
thing with strep starts out when we're
young most of the time and I'm going to
talk about what I mean by that see most
of the time it starts out when we're
little and we're young we usually pick
it up from a some place we either get it
from Mommy we can get it from Daddy okay
so let's not just blame moms uh blame
moms on for everything okay moms have
enough guilt on them they have they have
enough of that guilt where it's Mother's
guilt for you know for for nothing the
mothers have done wrong it's just the
guilt's naturally built in it's
naturally there when you have children
you just feel feel this and so it starts
out when we're younger and it can come
from Mom it can come from Dad it can
come from
anywhere and it can come from other
children it could come
from bathrooms strep is really tricky
and what it does is we get our strep
infections we get our strep throat When
We're Young And even if we don't get
diagnosed with strep throat we can have
strep in US causing sore throat that's
not diagnosed with strep throat we can
have strep inness that's causing chronic
ear infections all the time otitis media
um inner ear infection you station Tu
infections all of this is strap related
now there is some Epstein bars but they
connect to strep strep is the co-actor
of Epstein bar by the way and um but
there is some Epstein bars that cause
ear problems we talked about that tentis
we talk about that you know hearing loss
all this other things popping in the
ears fuzzing buzzing reading ringing
it's you know it's all Epstein bar
related but the otitis media the ear
infections kids get that's mostly shrap
and and what happens is streps a
bacteria and it's getting stronger and
stronger Each decade it's turning closer
to that super Super Bug level not quite
there yet but it's getting there strep
is not all the same strain either it's
not and you know this I've seen this
occur with a lot of relationships you
got young adults that are in one
relationship and we share our bacteria
in a relationship that's what we do so
when we lock down a relationship and we
have you know we're in a relationship
for 2 years we're starting our life and
then and then you know we're sharing our
bacteria
that's how it works and in that bacteria
is usually one or two varieties of strep
so someone can have one variety the
other partner can have one variety and
then we have two varieties and we're
kind of passing it back and forth and
living life and enjoying life and we
have the strep but when relationships
don't work out and we find other
partners because life is hard the road
is hard we can run into some different
varieties of strep I've seen people with
multiple varieties of streps some can
become
anti-biotic resistant all all of them
actually are becoming antibiotic
resistant and so this is the whole thing
with strep somebody can have strep in
their sinuses a variety of strep in
their sinuses and then they can pick up
a new variety of strep later on in their
life and have the worst UTI they ever
had in their life and that can be
another variety of strep and it could be
more
resistant acne is caused by strep and
the reason why acne suffers suffer
suffer for long term is because it's a
bacterial infection
and it's usually treated with
antibiotics to begin with and people
with acne usually had antibiotics a lot
when they were a child for different
things lung infections bronchitis you
know antibiotics instead of using
natural means to heal bronchitis natural
means we get thrown to the doctors
pediatricians just keep on giving the
kids antibiotics for every little thing
they have without teaching mommies how
to care for their kids naturally with
gold and seal and vitamin C and
Sovereign Silver and and zinc and you
know lomatium root and Elderberry and
Thyme and and you know so so moms aren't
taught how to take care of their kids in
this day and age so it doesn't really
exist yet we're not there yet so what it
is is you know you're a child you you
got a earache you get thrown into the
doctor's office you get given an
antibiotic and the strep gets stronger
it gets stronger even if it goes away in
that moment it comes back stronger with
another bad ear infection it could even
go into pneumonia monia it can even go
into you know chronic bronchitis it can
go into chronic
sinusitis and it can grow and grow and
grow it could get into the gut cause
sibo more antibiotics for sibo sibo
calms down goes away comes back raining
your day stronger I can't say how many
people where the doctors that the the
functional medicine doctors are like
here we do antibiotics for that sibo
yeah stupidest thing you could ever do
and I'm not saying the doctors are
stupid that's not at all they're
brilliant people don't get me wrong
brilliant it's just that no one's no
one's talking about the right
information really and that's what I was
saying at the beginning of the show
people don't get better because the
right information's AR out there look I
know I I I'm saying I'm sorry for having
to say that because I sound like
probably you know uh I don't know I
sound sarcastic I sound like I I'm I
know it all but the truth is the truth
and and and I only have to you know I
only I only deal with the straight talk
that's all I can deal with I can't deal
with crap in between or Crap around it
has to be real and it has to be real
like real information that's the truth
how it works it can only go that way cuz
Spirit won't have it any other way I
can't play around if I move to if I
think another thing like oh what if it's
no what if it's this and yeah do an
antibiotic for that spirit will
literally set me straight set my butt
straight and say that's not how it works
that's not what's going on this is what
it is and so that's how I have the
information so what happens is when you
do an antibiotic when you're young then
you're going to more likely end up with
sibo because the antibiotics are going
to be upgrading the strep constantly
upgrading it and the antibiotics have
Petroleum in it they have eggs in it I
mean I mean for all for Pete's
sake and you know and now now I'm going
to talk about the antibiotics for a
little bit because I'm not against the
antibiotics on on the whole I'm not the
antibiotic Discovery was absolutely
phenomenal and it's amazing and we need
them it's just that we burned them out
we misused them we we developed more
strains of bacteria like SEI and other
types of bacteria because of
antibiotics and because of the overuse
for the wrong reasons because the
medical world Medical Research Medical
Science did not set up a system to teach
mommies how to take care of their kids
yet it doesn't exist so we have to rely
on naturopaths of course and good
functional medicine doctors and good
acupuncturist and good you know uh
homeopaths and we have to rely on them
to teach mommies how to start doing
things for their kids that are much more
natural and that's the only way out
that's the only way out of the strep
world because those kids the CH our
children are going to turn into adults
and deal with chronic strap like us
adults are and it really stinks and it's
getting worse than it was 15 years ago
cuz the strep has gotten stronger
there's 100 different strains of strep
and like I said before we're picking up
multiple strains by the time I've seen
But now by the time women are 38 I mean
they got five or six different strains
they got the vaginal strains where
they're getting tons of discharge where
doctors don't know what it is it's the
yeast or who knows or what and constant
antibiotics they're getting citis
they're getting um sinus infections on
top of cystitis I mean 38 years old 39
years old women at are 42 it it's no
joke and the suffering that comes along
with it is no joke and the discomfort
and everything else around it and so you
know it's all fun in games it's all fun
in games and and but we got we got to
take it serious and so the deal is is
this is you know we start out young we
go to the ENT the ENT doesn't realize
we're dealing with strep treating us
with antibiotics non-stop instead of
going natural roots we end up taking and
you know we're a child we take
antibiotics for every ear infections for
every throat for every sore throat for
every cough and that's the
start and then another child could be
doing the same thing then the child's in
school and then fluids are passed by
accident through drinking out of a cup
you got another strep being passed to
another child it's a different strep
it's an upgraded one now the child's
battling two different Fridays of strep
the child's sck sick again nobody knows
why it's an endless situation
and I'm not trying to paint a dark
picture I'm trying to paint a picture of
Hope because we can do something about
it we can be aware of it we can do
something about it we can do the right
things we're going to talk about things
you can do for your children regarding
strep so we can start things out that
way and for adults when you have strep
and you have chronic strep for a long
time so and a lot of times now in the in
the youth the younger ones are children
they get the they get the sibo now
earlier they're getting diagnosed with
small intestinal over overgrowth of
bacteria and um bacterial overgrowth and
that's from antibiotics feeding
strep and sometimes moms or dads have an
you know upgraded version meaning they
have an upgraded a more angrier version
of strep in their system it gets in the
child so the child has to start out with
an upgraded strep to begin with you see
so this is this is like this is serious
stuff and but if I don't tell you how it
works if I don't give you the deal on
how it works if I don't give you the
truth if I don't give you the right
information how are you going to know
what are we going to do just you know go
on another decade and another decade of
just whatever and until the new trend
comes out oh it's candida again let's go
to back to that
Trend all right so um so let's go into
this a little bit let's start when
you're younger you know um building up
the immune system in your child is is
critical when it comes down to strep so
you want the you want the zinc the zincs
I talk about
you want to have the b112 that's immune
system all immune system support vitamin
C Elderberry syrup um very important and
and when your child's getting something
of any kind you want to do golden seal
so you visit your naturopath talk about
what you can do get support um because
it's important to to nip strep in the
butt so it doesn't get out of control so
you're relying on antibiotics all the
time so that's number one now Okay so
what's going on with different
conditions when we get older let's talk
about that a little bit um so let's talk
about sibo for a minute sibo is an
overgrowth of strep because that's the
dominant strain um sibo is not an
overgrowth of SEI but sibo is an
overgrowth of strap so that's the
dominant strain in when we talk about
sibo now doctors don't know that yet so
practitioners don't know what it is they
don't know what sibo is sibo is really
just you know you got bacteria
we don't know what it is you can do a
breath test you can do a blood test you
can try to do different ways of
diagnosing sibo it's difficult um you
know it's usually takes a little
intuition too uh good practitioner and
but knowing what strain matters and
knowing the history of the person so if
someone has sibo chances are they had a
whole bunch of other things going on or
they get they get headaches they get
sinus headaches so they get other
problems or they got a weak immune
system because strep is so dominant in
such a Troublemaker so um and then you
know strep can go all through the colon
and cause IBS um irritable valow
syndrome and it can um even even
instigate uh other intestinal conditions
that are that have other problems like
for instance colitis is shingles
shingles in in the colon um so but when
you have a high level of strep and
you're inflamed from strep too it makes
the colitis worse so strep is this
friend we don't want around because if
we have something else wrong with us
it's the biggest pain in the butt um
because it's hanging around so if you're
someone with a with a condition of any
kind the last thing you need is chronic
UTI now along with your chronic
condition now if you're a woman and
you're having you know um you know and
everything come happens when you're
having your period or having your your
cycle um when you're menstruating what
happens is that if you have strep in the
sinuses you're going to get your
problems more when you're having your
cycle if you have acne because you have
stre chronic strep causing acne you're
going to it's going to come on around
the cycle or around when the hormones
are shifting and the body's doing
something strange when you're ovulating
so you're having stress on the body
because of that and then they going to
get more acne somewhere around these
different time periods if you have
anything like uh cystitis it's going to
come more when you're um having your
cycle it's going to come on more
problematic
um you know could be anything UTI can
come on more when your Cycle's coming on
um let's see uh if you have
endometriosis and uh you have your cycle
it's going to be more problematic
especially if you have strep in your
system if you have pelvic inflammatory
disease which is basically anything in
any kind of inflammation in the
reproductive system whatsoever as a
woman that's all strep Mo 90% of pelvic
inflammatory problems are streps and so
that's going to happen when you're
having your cycle it's going to happen a
little bit more you're going to be a
little bit more flamed a little bit more
problematic so that's how it works
giving you the window into how strep
works and what it is it's really
critical now the reason why acne takes
so long to heal for people so many
people is because it's antibiotic fed
strep it's an upgraded variety of strep
and many of the people have bad acne and
um and there's nothing scary about any
of this this we're talking about we're
moving past it to clear it up and clean
things up and heal now I know I haven't
done an acne show per se I've done a UTI
show I talked about strep in the UTI
that whole thing if you want to look
back at that other show in the past but
acne doesn't go away right away it come
it es and flows because the strep Fights
Back constantly but building up the
immune system and cleaning up the diet
longer term gets rid of acne for good
I've seen people freed up from it who
have devastating cases for 10 15 years
in their life 20 years in their life and
I've seen it go away when we're diligent
and we're strong about it we're going to
talk about different foods and different
supplements too um that's going to help
all of this it's going to help acne it's
going to help the UTI it's going to help
the cystitis cystitis is scar tissue in
the bladder from strep so cystis is
actually scar tissue in the bladder
lining on the bladder lining it's like a
rash on the bladder lining but but if
kind of like scarred up tissue and
that's from strep being in the bladder
so long
and you know it's from um it's from old
UTI and sometimes you didn't have you
don't even have to have a UTI you could
just have it in the bladder and it's
sitting there you know and and and
causing trouble and it doesn't feel like
you have a real bad UTI once in a while
or whatever or you just feel like you
got little problems going on but that's
that's strep and that's what cystitis is
um once that rash in there gets U that
scar tissue gets kind of um inflamed and
the blood vessels get inflamed and
things are swelling up um then you know
it gets sensitive to any kind of food it
gets sensitive to how you how much uric
acid you have what's the acid profile
you have in your um urine um you name it
it just can get it es and flows in so
many ways but
stopping the strap is the key so I'm
covering all these different um
conditions you guys I'm covering these
different conditions so I can give you
ways of just getting out of all this
going to talk about diet foods and
supplements to get get out of it so what
are we trying to get out of we're trying
to get out of sibo we're trying to get
out of sinusitis sinus and chronic sinus
infections after sinus and surgeries you
name it all of that trying to get out of
um uh chronic otitis media um chronic
sore throats or strep throats um acne um
csstis I think I said it already UTI
we're trying to get out of all this this
is all strep fun fun fun fun with strep
that's all this is and and so uh and you
oh I forgot
sty um that's another one too good old
sty many of them are strep related not
all of them some of them are viral we
can get a we can get a virus in the eye
and cause a sty that does happen but
it's a different kind of sty not all sty
look the same not all sty are the same
and who's keeping tabs on all this by
the way where's medical research and
medical science you once again I think
about sometimes when someone approaches
me every now and then they get upset and
they say what do you know about Med
medical research and medical science you
and I'm like you tell me what do you
know does medical re science medical
science and research have tabs on all
the different varieties of sty and which
ones are bacterial and which ones are
viral no I mean what could go on and on
and on and on I mean seriously you guys
for real I me I could go on with that
one I mean you tell me what about the
mommy that can't take care of her kids
cuz she sick with strap and she's got
epsteen bar and no one can help her and
she's got the worst fibromyalgia ever
and all they could do is offer a
medication and tell her she's crazy you
tell me ask her where medical research
and medical science has left her and so
this is no joke here you know I take
people's Health serious so when someone
ever wants to challenge me a little bit
and say you know oh you don't you know
you don't have you don't have 10 years
in medical school what do you know and
you know it's it's you know what that's
basically disregarding when someone says
that they're disregarding someone's pain
and suffering they're disregarding what
someone's been through they're
disregarding how someone's been to 50
doctors looking for help and can't find
any help for their strep issues that
they're undiagnosed strep strep issues
so you know that's completely being
disrespectful for the people who have
suffered the people who have gone
through Howen back the people who lay in
bed dying of chronic illness and
so-called autoimmune meaning it's it's a
real Illness but they're diagnosed with
autoimmune and telling their telling
them their bodies are attacking the M
themselves so they die faster you name
it it's completely disrespectful when
someone says where's your 10 years of
medical school what do you know yet you
know what what do you know so and I say
this with passion and caring because
I've watched I get choked up emotionally
my heart gets a little funny and I get
choked up because I I've seen it all out
there I know what you guys have gone
through I know some of you have gone
through this I know that okay and my job
is to be on what you know watching your
back my job is be on your side okay so
I'm going to come across like this every
now and then so if new new uh listeners
logged in and they see I'm slightly
sarcastic or a little bit harsh on you
know what we've been through with the
medical systems and everything both both
alternative and conventional just hang
in there for the ride it's because you
know I I feel the pain of of everybody
who what they've gone through and I've
seen it forever since I've been here um
so here's the deal it's about building
up the immune system and battling strep
and cleaning it up it's about knowing
what we're going after you know if you
don't know what you're going after you
can't get better if we think acne is
just a hormonal pimple cystic acne is
just a hormonal pimple we're not getting
it better if we don't know what it
is if we think our sinus
infection you know is from uh pollen in
the air then we don't know we're not
going to be getting it
better you know if we think our cytis is
just because we're getting older then
how are we going to get better and if we
think you know all if we think our
vaginal discharge is just yeast how are
we going to get better so we get rid of
those yeast infections that are really
strep and not yeast how are we going to
get better if we don't know what's going
on how do you get better that's the
whole point and that's where we're
breaking the rules changing the rules
that's where it's going down okay I want
you guys to experience getting better so
when it comes down to all these things
we're talking about like sibo I don't
want your sibo coming back over and over
again I want to make sure we get rid of
that strep so your sibo goes away I want
your cystitis to go away I've helped
people I've had women women come to me
with cystitis so bad they didn't want to
live anymore I mean just didn't want to
live anymore that it was unbearable
unbearable to live you couldn't sleep
you couldn't eat you couldn't go
anywhere you couldn't do anything it was
that bad and we we've gotten it better
we've seen people through Spirit NS so
they could get past this and want to
live and get past this and heal so this
stuff could get serious okay so it's
about arming ourselves let's talk about
what we can do let's talk about the
different things we can do Okay so we've
covered we've covered a few things
there's different strains lots of
different strains so we're going to
cover you know lots of foods and
supplements even for the most powerful
strains of strep a coccus um you know we
talked about the sinus surgeries people
get from chronic strap but it doesn't
fix it and then people are Back in the
Saddle Again talked about the UTI talked
about acne strep throat and we talked
about how these these strep varieties
are antibiotic resistant um and we we
covered into that pretty good so let's
talk about what we can do food foods to
avoid what foods to avoid what
food do you know what foods can feed
strep cuz you guys are getting good you
know I noticed that I noticed that where
someone hopped on Facebook and they're
just like this is what you need to do
and I was like
whoa I was like you're right you're
right and I'm I'm hearing that a lot cuz
you guys are getting really good and
that was my dream actually is that all
of you become Health experts because you
guys become Health experts someday you
guys are going to be better than you're
going to be you're going to know more
than
me or I should say you're going to know
more than me but you're not going to
know more than spirit all right all
right so here's the deal I mean with you
guys knowing so much and learning so
much um it like I said before that is my
dream that's my dream come true so what
foods do you think we need to avoid with
strepa cacus the
bacteria eggs right we need to avoid
that I see people diagnosed with sibo
and they're told only to eat
eggs eggs bacon and then a few
vegetables and then maybe a a small
handful of like a
berry one Berry like a tiny little
handful of raspberries like once every 4
days and they have to be eating you know
four eggs a day some natural bacon and
um and then they can they can eat a few
vegetables and that's not how sibo works
that's not how it works that's not what
what goes on eggs feed sibo they feed
strepa cacus strepa cacus was raised on
egg by the way it was raised in
Labs by eggs you think strep just
appeared it's in our life now because
it's been
raised uh it escaped in the world it was
Bread on eggs just telling you right
now so you got sinus infections you got
cystitis that's the other thing if
you're a woman and you have cystitis or
a man with
cystitis and um you go to the doctor
you're told to eat
eggs that's that's you know so you feed
the bacteria and cause more citis even
if the egg you don't feel it when you
eat the egg like you don't feel it
irritate your scar tissue and your
bladder you're still you know you're it
it's still feeding the problem and you
know we're told you know we're told to
do this and I know this is off the topic
a little bit like
PCOS um women are told to eat lots of
eggs at PCOS worst thing we could ever
do eggs make the cysts they make the
tumors they literally are the tumor and
cyst grower of all time eggs feed breast
cancer cysts
calcifications nodules tumors on the on
the thyroid eggs feed all this uh do I
have anything against eggs no they taste
amazing and uh and and they're delicious
and you can make scrambled eggs taste
really good you can make an omelette and
make people happy and you can cook the
best eggs in the world and people love
it and I get it got nothing against them
but if you got something going on you're
worried about cysts and you're worried
about PCOS and you're worried about you
know cystitis and you're worried about
um you know cancer because it's in your
family or whatever it is then eggs is
gone so you want the eggs to be gone be
gone and um so the deal is is another
one is dairy products strep ferociously
feeds off of cheese milk butter ghee
ghee I know there's a big ghee movement
on there I'm not against the ghee
movement but if you got any of these
symptoms and you got strap of any kind
and you got what I'm talking
about then you don't want ghee in there
either you don't even want remotely the
hint of what would have been a dairy
product you just don't want it there
okay so that's important and I don't
care if it's a belief system if it's a
belief system somewhere I I don't have a
belief system I know I've told you guy
this the guys this before but I don't
have a belief system if I adopt a belief
system then I'm going to totally mess
you guys up instantly if I adopt one
belief system I'm going to mess you guys
up because you're going to be cheated
out of healing I just have to do what's
right that's all I just have to do
what's right so you can heal so you keep
the dairy products out milk cheese
butter ghee whatever it is you just keep
it out so that's important to know um
corn corn is such an instigator with
strep strep is a corn eater corn
feeder so um keep the corn out wheat
wheat gluten
Rye
Rye um that's another one so barley
wheat Rye not barley grass barley grass
juice is an
anti-
strep wheat grass juice is
antip wheat isn't barley isn't but the
juice of the grass is anti-strep because
it changed its structure to actually
have a phytochemical toward W off strap
very important to understand um so these
are some of the foods to avoid canola
oil is the ultimate ultimate ultimate
mistake for cystitis for strep for you
know anything going on bacterial vagino
bacterial vaginosis is strepa cacus by
the way um you know immune system
problems you name it intestinal
disorders Crohn's IBS anything you don't
want to go near canol the oil and I said
this on a previous show just recently
but there's just you know there's new
new people on the scene and new guys on
the scene that that are deemed
themselves experts and they got new
literature out that they've created and
written and it's out there and and they
think they're experts in you know
microorganisms and everything else and
they're promoting canola oil most
unbelievable thing I've ever
seen unbelievable so we have to have the
right information it's an example why
people don't get better you know and
that's why I need you guys to supersede
the experts that are out there because
technically that's what's Happening Here
you guys are learning the information
you guys are knowing the truth and
you're superseding the ex the experts
that aren't experts you're superseding
them it's amazing I'm proud of you I'm
so proud of you it's not even funny so
foods to eat bananas are fantastic for
sibo collects all the strep and pulls it
out of the system I don't care what
anybody says bananas do it they're
antibacterial they're antiviral berries
amazing for um for uh strep in any part
of the body spinach incredible for strep
incredible because what spinach does
spinach has so many beta carotenes in it
that are off the chart beta carotenes
okay that are off the chart these
keratins get to the skin and they have
phytochemicals that help stop acne lots
of spinach is critical for acne
sufferers where the strep is
lymphatically
there acne is caused by strep being in
the lymphatic system all the
time and all through the you name it the
cheeks the face the lymphatic system up
behind the ears around the neck all of
this you know the lymphatic system it's
a big deal you want um you want spinach
arugula another great one that's a great
one
Ginger Ginger is a strep fighter in the
gut strep Fighter for cystis UTI chronic
UTI Ginger builds up the immune system
helps battle
strep okay
oregano oil or oregano in your food
incredible I wouldn't take an antibiotic
for sibo I wouldn't take an antibiotic
for acne I would go on oregano oil
capsules I would go I would be eating
oregano the aromatic herbs aromatic
herbs oregano thyme rosemary
sage aromatic herbs are weapons weapons
of strep
destruction that's what they are weapons
destruction and so you you know or
exactly you want the oregano and even if
it's not organic that's what I'm trying
to say trying to get the words out even
if it's not organic time you can't find
organic time I'm totally fine it this is
what we need right here we need the
oregano we need the thyme we need the
Rosemary aromatic herbs the sage and
this is a Powerhouse towards knocking
down strep in the system now strep
doesn't go away right away it doesn't go
away right away you have to have
patience you have to have time and
patience because it's been there in most
of us for decades most of our lives and
it and it tends to creep up it tends to
get worse throughout our life causing
all kinds of problems causing headaches
causing fatigue causing a little bit of
fatigue causing um confusion causing um
fevers lowgrade fevers
causing all these different
things and it sits in a long term es and
flows with where immune system is and
where we are in our
lives and so it's going to take a little
time you got to incorporate these things
without a doubt in the um life-changing
Foods book I really laid it out in there
so if you gather all the foods in there
that help with the with the strep like
the aromatic herbs you can see what it
does for it so we got the Rosemary we
got the sage got the or you know oregano
we got the time garlic it's another one
someone told me the other day they said
you know I follow this other belief
system where Garlic's too hot of a food
or it's it causes too much trouble and
I'm like look you're you're cheating
yourself do you like garlic and they're
like yeah I like garlic I said you're
cheating yourself out of something that
literally can knock down your strepa
caucus
infections the person said well what
strep infections what are you talking
about I go didn't you get diagnosed with
sibo and they said yeah I did that was
your strep infection they're like oh I
was wondering what that
was same thing with the UTI same thing
with everything else people are like
what I was wondering what that was you
mean there you mean that there you know
what that is yeah so um garlic is a big
one winter squash amazing for strap
throughout the body sweet
potatoes kale kale is a STP killer so we
got the kale kale is great in any way
possible onions Ultimate Fighter of
strep in the bladder and in the
reproductive system with PID and you
know and in the intestinal tract and in
the colon causing
IBS and you know sty that are caused by
it you name it onions are amazing for
knocking down strep but you might say
hey Anthony I've eaten an onion and my
strep ain't better no no no no no no no
no you might have also had an egg a week
before you might and I'm not trying to
be mean you can still eat other things
in your life you can still have a piece
of fish you can still have if you love
turkey you can still have a little
turkey if you want some free range
chicken you probably could have some of
that if you're into that you could
probably have a little bit of grass-fed
beef if you're really into that but if
you have an egg your streps not going
away it's just
not you know so it's really important to
know um and if you're you know if you're
plant-based it's even more helpful for
strep when you're plant-based it
definitely is more helpful not saying
you know everybody has to go plant-based
but if you're dealing with bad strep
sinusitis and all these other things you
might want to consider a 28-day cleanse
to start you off like I talk about in
the first medical medium book you know
that you guys know about the medical
medium book and um you can do you know
modified 28-day cleanse you can bring in
other foods you can bring in more if you
want um but there's ways of at least
doing a little plant-based for a little
while life and get a jump on the strep
and then when you bring back animal
proteins or fish or whatever you want to
bring in you keep the eggs out and the
dairy products out and the other things
I'm talking
about but it takes more than an onion
once in a while you you got to have
onion in your food every day and you're
going to start knocking down strap but
you got have to have onion in your food
every day that's okay that's that's
possible chop up in a red onion put a
slice on your salad once a day it
matters you know if you can get it every
other day it matters turmeric is a great
anti-er that's a great one anti-strep
totally knocks down that strep so
turmeric's a good one there's turmeric
juices out there I honestly just juice
your own turmeric you know I I don't
know they're just so expensive and
everything you go into the health food
store and you can get a torous you know
turmeric drink for you know
$19 I just I would just buy some
turmeric and run just a little bit
through your juicer if you want with
with cucumber with celery and just run a
little bit of turmeric and you'll do
more for the strep and you'll save a lot
of
money um so that's a way of doing it
celery juice
instantaneously starts knocking down
strep in the body I've had people tell
me my acne is gone because of celery
juice fat people tell me my cystitis is
gone because of celery juice fat people
tell me my sio's gone my IBS is gone my
you know my bacterial vaginosis is gone
you know whatever it is and my sty are
are gone my sinus problems are gone from
celery juice now some of you you might
have a strep that's in there might be in
there for a long time could be an
upgraded version could be more of a
bacterial you know resistant uh version
and so might take longer to do and you
might have to do a few more things with
it all and take out some of the foods
we're talking about but we can do this
and if you're not ready to do it now if
you're not ready to do anything for it
now I'm on board
100% because I still want you learning
because you might tell somebody else to
do it I have people that won't do
anything and I stand behind them because
that's where they are in the moment of
their life well I I stand behind them
with total respect because they're just
they're not there in that moment to to
to want to do a lot for their health and
I I stand with them meaning I'm what are
you kidding I'm I'm with them I'll be
like okay I totally agree I'm with you
you don't want to do it now I'm on board
you got my support I'm going to support
you to not do it
okay I know it sounds funny but I'm
serious because I also know you're
learning that person's learning that
person's listening I got people to
listen to the show you guys there's
people out there like some of you are
listening to show and you really don't
do some of the things I want you to do
but that doesn't matter to me because
you're learning and you're becoming a
health expert and then you turn around
and don't even realize it and you tell
somebody in the health food store hey do
that that can help with
that and and it's powerful man it's
powerful so so like I said I'm we're all
we're in this together I don't care if
you're you know if you're eating you
know nachos and cupcakes and you know
and whatever and egg egg burritos right
now I'm just I stand behind you 100%
we're going to work on this together all
right um cayenne pepper hot peppers
they're great for any of it just don't
overdo them you know if you're sensitive
try not to overdo it you know I've done
that before because I like hot peppers I
like cayenne pepper so I've gone to town
with it and I've been like oh man I
pushed it to the Limit here and so you
got you know be careful you don't do
that there's reasons why raw honey raw
honey I said this in a show before this
came out of my life-changing Foods book
and it's an example of why I am so
excited when you guys get the
life-changing Foods book I I'm I'm just
you know get a copy get a pre-copy a
pre-order in because I'm hoping they
stay in stock and and here's the deal
cuz the last book was out of stock for
virtually practically three and a half
months in total so you yeah this this
book's going to wow you raw honey has
over 200,000 phytochemicals because the
bees are collecting them from different
flowers that have already phytochemicals
in every different flower it's no one
knows this secret or this truth truth
except for me and spirit life-changing
Foods that's in there and raw honey has
phytochemicals that destroy strep that
that prevent strep that stop strep that
stops
staff staff isn't staff by the way isn't
the scary bug it's strep meaning meaning
the bug that causes the most problems
are strep they do the most of these
illnesses I'm talking about staff
doesn't really do that staff is
everywhere it's in us it's around us
it's on our skin but it's it's different
than SHP but honey stops staff it stops
seiff it stops ecoli it stops all the
different strep bacterias it gets rid of
cystitis in people over time it stops
sinus infections over time it knocks
down strep in every way strep throat you
name
it I mean
seriously I'm serious so that's the
power of raw honey so don't be afraid of
it but guess what you might hear
somebody else's podcast or some new
fangled book that says it's got sugar in
it so stay away from it and you get
cheated you get cheated it's like going
to the grocery store and you you know
give somebody a 20 and you just bought a
bag of chips and you gave them 20 and
they give you back like a five like it
never it it's by accident it's by
accident and that's what I'm trying to
tell you is people people out there that
have misinformation saying Honey's bad
for you don't you know don't use it it's
got sugar it'll feed this it'll feed
that that's just by accident too cuz
they just have misinformation it's like
in the grocery store you know the clerk
is not trying to cheat you out of $15
the clerk has made a mistake and but it
doesn't feel good it doesn't feel good
on our end so it doesn't feel good on
our end when we're cheated out of honey
when honey can actually heal us so you
just need to know that honey can help
help you sleep it can help stop insomnia
I got a whole list of what honey does in
life-changing foods not to mention
spiritually emotionally you name it
spiritual lesson it provides spiritual
lessons that change lives so that's a
great one
supplements vitamin C secret weapon
without a doubt for strep infections of
all kinds take a lot of it talk to your
practitioner take more ask for help in
um in in my Facebook groups everybody's
learning all this stuff zinc one of the
reasons why strep is rampant and strep
has gone to the degree it has is because
everybody's zinc deficient everybody's
zinc deficient so zinc is critical you
get zinc in your system your strep will
will minimize and disappear over time
lemon balm cat's claw cat's Claw is
incredibly you know uh it's an
incredible weapon it really is
incredibly helpful to knocking down
strep on all levels intestinal track
sibo you know
UTI all of it all of it it's that
powerful cats call lemon bomb monol
Lauren monen from coconut you can even
do coconut coconut meat coconut products
coconut water very helpful for strap of
all
kinds so these are the things to focus
on you know just and look a little bit
goes a long way you get a little bit of
cats claw in you every day you get your
zinc levels up to par every day you get
your vitamin C in you every day but wait
a minute you're doing oregano time
rosemary sage somehow meaning some
oregano capsules little time tea you got
some Sage chopped up in your food and
you're moving forward you see that you
got banana smoothie with wild
blueberries in the morning that's
amazing and it goes on and it goes on
but it builds over time and you can be
freed you can be freed and you can
protect your
children and protect their children you
get the zinc up to par in your children
you get a little bit of Elderberry syrup
in them you get some vitamin C in them
and we can minimize the antibiotics
but the antibiotics are this catch22
it's like you get a bad UTI that's so
out of control because you've eaten all
these different wrong things and your
strep is out of control causing the
worst UTI ever and your immune system's
dropped because you don't have zinc and
then you have to take an antibiotic and
it suppresses it and it pushes the strep
down but then the strep comes back and
two months later with another raging UTI
we have to build all this up so we don't
have to rely on the antibiotics
eventually so we're coming to the end of
the show I got to tell you guys I love
you you need to know that I really do my
heart is with you I truly love you I
truly care about all of you I really
want you to know that I really do
actually
care and spirit cares and we want you
better take one day at a time I stand
behind you you didn't create your
illness you didn't that's not how it
works okay I I believe in positivity I
believe in tracting good things in our
life I believe in staying on that
Forefront but don't think that you
created your illness cuz you had bad
karma and that created your illness or
you're a bad person or you deserve it or
you're just terrible person or you know
you're faulty and your body's faulty or
your body's attacking itself just don't
believe that cuz that part's off that
part's wrong so I stand behind you I
believe in you and I love you and this
gift here wasn't given to me for me it
was given to me for you okay what I get
out of it is seeing you healed
and that's what I get out of it is
seeing you get better and seeing you
benefit your lives and seeing you help
others and help others we're all working
with this together in our lives right
now we're all doing it together I'm on
board just remember that take One Day at
a Time start out with that wild
blueberry smoothie take one day at a
time get some of these things in you
learn and grow you guys are the health
Experts of the day
that are moving forward just so you know
in life you guys are the health experts
that are moving
forward remember that don't forget it
okay I stand behind you
100% I back you up talk to the angels
too bring the angels in when you can
okay make sure you talk to the angels
out loud make sure you're saying to the
angels can you help me so I can do
better with my foods can you help me cuz
I need some help here check out the in
my book one and by the way in
lifechanging Foods I have an angel
chapter in there angels that no one
knows about angels that have never been
in any book and they are so helpful they
are life-changing they're called the
life-changing Angels so get yourself a
copy but anyway I love you take care
many
blessings and uh know that I care
bye-bye