a lot of people are upset by stretch
marks they feel that they feel upset
they feel like betrayed they work so
hard to lose their weight they work
really hard and then they have the
stretch marks and they're like wow I did
all this work I got rid of some excess
unwanted pounds and now I'm dealing with
stretch marks reason for those stretch
marks obviously is because you're
expanding right when you gain weight we
expand so then we get more more tissue
growth if someone gains a few pounds or
10 lb 15 or 20 lb and they lose the
weight some people their stretch marks
are a lot worse than some other people
the reason for that is the very base The
Landmark I'm talking about that we want
to protect and we want to support that
very landmark and base it's deficient
and it's saturated and soaked up with
toxins and free radicals that have been
there for years and it's deficient of
things that it needs so that sponge got
oversaturated with too much poisons
fight ORF flight too many toxins right
here at the base right here at the
bottom too much adrenaline and it got
damaged and when that base that bottom
of that Derma gets damaged we don't it
doesn't bounce back easy a staticity is
gone collagen weakens we lose Vitality
in the bottom of our Derma that's where
it starts to really disappear and if
you're dealing with somebody with a
stagnant sluggish liver which is a big
part of it all cuz that's saturated with
toxins and poisons it doesn't help in
fact that's a big deal on its own some
people might have a really toxic liver
because they're so toxic that the Derma
got filled up with a lot more toxins and
saturated with a lot more adrenaline and
then when they lost the weight thees the
elasticity is actually gone they don't
have that play that room to play anymore
it doesn't Revitalize easy it doesn't
bounce back quick at all and then we
have the stretch mark when it comes down
to skin repair and has to start from
deep down into the Derma it has to be
down deep we got to go low you want to
work on skin and keep skin good you
don't want stretch marks taking over
when you gain weight and then you lose
the weight and you lost all the L right
elasticity of the skin and you got the
skin is is way too
played and it's not bouncing back and
everybody's trying to get the tummy tuck
and they're trying to get all the
different surgeries and Tucks their skin
won't work with them or maybe you just
gained a little bit of weight and then
you got the stretch marks from a little
bit of
weight the way we have to address all of
this is always remember no matter what
that when we're addressing skin it has
to be from the bottom up it has to be
from the ground up so from the ground up
it can't be
surface it can't even be follicle
level it has to be right at the base
which is what I call the foundation of
your skin deep within the Derma and
right under the Derma right under the
skin it's all about immune power it's
all about immune system our immune
system patrols that area our immune
system needs
antioxidants in that area antioxidants
are one of the critical
Builders right there by the way you guys
know I work with vimergy this is the
vimergy micro immune power with the
organic bamboo silica this is the
vimergy MSM with the bamboo silica we're
going to be joining these two we're
going to be putting these two together
and vimergy is going to give anyone
who's actually getting this a free lemon
balm and 5% off of the MSM on top of it
so what I love about the Skin Potion
what I'm showing you is immune system
and then building blocks for
skin