sorry just having breakfast just having
a big bowl of brown sugar CU that's what
everybody does right they start their
day with a massive bowl of sugar because
that's all everybody does right they eat
sugar and hey everybody out there is
that what you did too you did that this
morning this is brown sugar I like white
sugar I like brown sugar I have it every
morning a big bowl of it just like this
I know some people have cereal and some
people have bacon and eggs I have a big
big bowl of brown sugar all this sugar
right here 2 G 3 G 10 G 20 g of sugar
that's what 25 g of sugar no that's 30
gram of sugar how many grams are in that
spoon right there so maybe I eat more
than 30 gram of sugar I think I'm eating
a pound of sugar is this a pound that's
what I have every morning for breakfast
just like everybody else almost
everybody else we eat straight straight
sugar right by the way you guys before
we go into sugar fear it's very
important topic for a lot of reasons cuz
everybody is brain screwed over sugar
brainwashed they're demented over sugar
you see it out there it's like what is
going on another thing too white lung
syndrome mystery pneumonia heading to
town heading to a theater near you we
have the mystery pneumonia heading to a
theater near you heading to a town a
village near you around the globe
mystery white lung
pneumonia courtesy of wherever
crazyville exactly you guys so the
bottom line is do you have your tools
are you ready I'm going to talk about
like pneumonia a little bit you know the
fluid in the lungs how that works what's
going on with that I'm going to go into
that a little bit and talk about also
what you can do to protect yourselves so
when you catch white lung you have a
shot a shot to surpass it with ease or
more ease than say somebody else so you
don't get all that fluid in the lung and
everything else very important topics
today sugar fear and the white lung
syndrome mystery pneumonia that's
spreading rampantly we're going to go
into details about that too a little bit
about like what is it they're calling it
just like micoplasma what what is it
bacteria huh what they're saying too you
guys got to hang in there for this
episode seriously we're live right now
by the way oh by the way guess what I'm
making I'm making mini
frittatas
woohoo mini frittatas stick around for
that it's easy easy to make and when I
say easy I say easy I the oven on set
for 350 we're going to be jamming on
these things you guys do you have your
protocols book if you don't have this
book get it get it if you don't have the
$20 or whatever it is for amazon.com us
go to the library get it for free why
critical reasons here's one right now
tell a friend or whatever tell somebody
you know critical reasons and I'm going
to one right here okay so because of
Cold and Flu see the cold and flu
section right here children's dosages so
forth and adult dosages and so forth
look right here in this book protocols
book get this book have it bring it to
your doctor whatever you want to do have
it ready look at the protocols for
mystery flu flu cold whatever what have
you C what have you it's in here check
it out make sure you have the protocols
book you won't be disappointed critical
critical so and I didn't put this book
together for no reason very important
and it's
55% off the brains saer book is
55% off that one right there too by the
way get these books get them free at the
library if you need to very important
but either way have them so check them
out get them for Christmas get them for
president pres presentence get them for
President's Day that's actually really
good that's a good one right there get
the books for President's Day hey it's
President's Day get the medical medium
books so listen protocols this is
protocols it's 50% off amazon.com us
right now if you guys just came on here
stick around if you're getting kicked
off kicked off right now of IG because
that's what happened they they start
kicking everybody off it's just
everybody just starts getting kicked off
go to telegram go to rumble go to
YouTube right now if you can even find
it if you're lucky medical medium
YouTube go to Medical medium.com see
this stream live right now now at
medicalmedium.com tell somebody else if
they get kicked off they're like where
did he go what happened just whatever
try to get somebody there but either way
you want to catch this white lung
syndrome talk you want to catch this
mystery pneumonia talk and you want to
catch the sugar fear talk please and
right there
dosages
protocols critical information in the
protocols book we're going to talk talk
about that fluid that gets in the lungs
we're going to talk about that pus that
everybody has anyway in their liver
people walk around with this puss in
their liver every day in lymphatic
system because their lymphatic system is
overflowing with pus and yellow crap
coming from their burdened livers and
then when the mysterious pneumonia
rushes through which we're going to talk
about a little bit more about what that
is when that pneumonia is rushing
through and people are already filled
with pus because they're not doing the
28 day cleanse they're not doing the
mono cleanse they're not doing the heavy
metal detox they're not doing the hmds
you know cleanses they're not doing any
of the good stuff they're not doing the
morning cleanses they're not taking care
of their liver and then when that white
lung starts to pour into
town yeah all that pusit in the liver
that's been built up over time just
really explodes into the lymphatic and
everywhere else the lungs fill up with
fluid you get the pneumonia you get the
cough that's from also being burdened
everybody's so burdened with all kinds
of things but either way Protocols are
critical when you're dealing with that
kind of stuff coming to town Santa Claus
is Coming to
Town yeah making that list he's checking
it twice going to find out if you've
been naughty or nice uh-huh the white
long stuff is Coming to Town Wendy says
I'm currently on day 13 of the 30 days
brain shot therapy cleanse that is
really awesome love it brain shot
therapies as well I'd like juggle these
in the moment these are actually really
heavy books by the way be careful don't
drop them on your foot these are like
really thick fill with information all
right let's get down to it let's stop
fooling around we got to take stuff
serious have you downloaded the cold and
flu tool kit have you done that you guys
can tell I'm excited today I'm excited I
am it's been a little while haven't been
live in a little while and I want to
make sure I can offer you guys
everything I can and I'm I'm excited
about it and we're going to make some
food and I'm freaking hungry so I'm
excited onig right there what this book
helped me quit alcohol and weed life
changing I'm not allowed to say the
word not allow to say the
word not allow to say it because Tik Tok
kicked me off once again just from
saying mea
somebody it's actually insane um
Aquarius says the first time I got C I
didn't have this critical info I was
sick for a month the second time I had
and followed these protocols I was sick
for 2 days I hear that all the time
friends and family and everything with
these protocols get your cold and flu
toolkit download that medical.com look
at the link is in the description and
make sure you have protocols for the
those protocol infos does your books
talk about radiation damage it's the
only books that mentioned radiation the
very first darn book did a radiation
T hello hello hello the hmds is
incredible for
radiation the heavy metal detox smoothie
is freaking
amazing every time I go through an air
airport man I'm doing the
hmds I'm doing the heavy metal detox
movie because I need to suck up that
radiation because that's how much
radiation is in the airport when you go
through it so yes that's all I've talked
about is radiation these are the First
Health books talking about all the
different aspects of radiation it's this
book series right here and so yeah and
iidea the heavy metal detox smoothie
want to go through the airport you
better believe it after the airport boom
you better believe it I want to suck up
whatever radiation just went into me
that foul R radiation that just goes
into everybody all right
so moving right
along we got a lot to talk about but I
just want to make sure truly that you
guys are protected and understand that
there is ways to protect us it's right
here in the cold flu and see protocols
right there cold flu and C
protocols right there hair supplements
dosages all of it this is powerful
people all over the world use this right
here do you have this
book
seriously all right let's get into it
link is in the
description in the bio the cold influ
tool
kit all right you guys I just want to
help that's what I wanted to do you mind
you guys mind all right I still have a
heck of a big breakfast I want to finish
just bear with me a second
here sugar straight sugar just a whole
bowl of brown sugar right there and um I
find it refreshing in the morning I do
because everybody does that right you
guys do it you just eat a big big ass
bowl of sugar in the morning no you
don't that's right no one does that's
right no one does that's right okay no
one eats a freaking bowl of sugar in the
morning but everybody acts like they are
everybody talks like they are no one
sits there eating a big stupid bowl of
sugar every day they don't but that's
how ridiculous the health movement has
been that's how ridiculous ulous all the
health whoever have been because no
one's eating straight sugar you know why
you know what they're doing I'll tell
you why this is critical critical to
know they're eating sugar
with
fat they're eating sugar with fat you
see that right there what's on top of
those pancakes right there you see that
you see it's on top right they're eating
sugar
with fat combined combined that's where
the problem is I've been watching the
health movement
literally re-engineer itself trying to
figure it out for decades and they don't
get it oh I quit sugar really what did
you quit were you eating sugar all day
long no I never eat sugar out of a bowl
all day long then what are you talking
about you quit sugar no you mean you
dialed it down on the fat that's what
you dialed down on you dialed down the
fat and the sugar combined you weren't
eating sugar you dial down the fat
because in those pancakes is a whole ton
of fat and milk egg fat butter fat
whatever butter on top of those pancakes
that's the whole point what you dial
down was the fat that's what you dialed
down do you guys get
it hey I quit sugar I quit eating sugar
I cut back on sugar hear it all the time
yeah I'm cutting back on sugar I'm
working out now I'm in the gym you know
I'm kickbox in right I'm doing this I'm
doing that I you know I'm I back down
the sugar no you back down the fat yeah
with some
sugar but that's what you back down do
you know you can talk to the smartest
what you think is the smartest dudes
trainers the smartest like exercise
dudes the smartest Health gurus the
smartest podcast doctors you want to
talk to and them guys don't even get it
none of them get it and they're all
doing the same old broken record yeah
you cutting back on the sugar you
cutting back on the carbs or you cutting
back on the sweets processed foods right
all the sweets that's what you're
cutting back on that's the bad stuff you
go to a dentist cut back on your sugar
cut back on your sugar did you cut back
on your
sugar you cut back on the fat and that's
why people
improve they cut back on the fat that's
why they okay is that is that a bowl of
sugar I want to know is that a bowl of
sugar everybody thinks it's a bowl of
sugar right there that's
fat ice cream
fat so important to know you guys this
is critical to know right here right you
cutting down on the sugar oh I'm cutting
down on the sugar no dude you're cutting
down on the piles of fater eating oh I'm
cutting down on the sugar right here no
dude you're cutting down on the fats
you're
eating right oh yeah I'm cutting down
cutting down on the sugar right here
cutting down on the sugar you're cutting
down on the fat load it load it load it
with fat that is what you are cutting it
down on that's why you're losing a
couple of pounds that's why you're
starting to get a little healthier
that's why you're following this trainer
he's got you cutting down on the sugar
dude you're cutting down on the fat
that's the reason why you're turning
your life around a little bit that's how
it
works simple as that hold on I got a
delivery delivery right here around the
corner don't worry here right thank you
yeah no no the tip the tip is right
there yep thank you oh God I can't wait
to eat this I'm actually hungry for this
right here today because you know what
you know the only thing is though is I
better back down on this pizza you know
why I need to back down on the sugar
that's why I need it back down in the
sugar
no it's not
sugar it's the fat in that pizza it's
that pepperoni fat it's that cheese fat
it's the oil fat that's been dumped on
your pizza that is what the problem is
that makes sugar evil that's what turns
sugar into evil and people don't know it
but that's it right there it's all the
fat can't eat that pizza lots of carbs
man I got to back down on my sugar I'm
backing down on the pizza dude you're
backing down on the
fat that's the point because no one's
just eating sugar no one is eating just
sugar it's not happening on any level it
does not happen if you're eating bowls
and bowls of sugar in the morning then
you're the only person on this planet
doing
it only person on this planet that's
it if you're eating a big old bowl of
sugar you're the only one on this entire
planet only one and even if some dude is
in a sugar cane field and he hacks a big
stock of the fresh sugar cane and he
presses it through a press and it juices
the sugar cane into a big old
Bowl guess what that's part sugar big
part of all water Trace minerals
nutrients phytochemical compounds the
sugar is this much everything else is
there the sugar is this much everything
else is there in there you see no one
eats straight sugar like that in the
morning it doesn't exist but you sure as
hell can think they do if I did not know
anything if I came off of a
spacecraft if I was abducted to 20 years
ago by some alien race and I and they
had me up there and they were
experimenting on me and doing whatever
and they decided to let me go 20 years
later and drop my butt off and I was
dropped off I didn't know nothing or 40
years later didn't know nothing or I 50
years whatever if they abducted me when
I was 2 years old and dropped me off now
I would think everybody was eating tons
and tons of bowls and bowls of sugar I'd
be on the internet like whoa this person
quit carbs whoa this person quit sugar
whoa this person's off their sugar I'd
be like whoa what was everybody doing
eating piles and piles of sugar and
that's how ridiculous it is Brad says
no carbs turn fat into
[Music]
[Laughter]
evil fat turns carbs into
evil yeah that's how it goes all right
so what happens when you put fat and
sugar together
together when you put fat and sugar
together you inhibit yourself from
getting something so important which is
the nutrients nutrients I'm taking this
supplement I'm taking this powder I'm at
my doctor's office he gave me this
powder I'm taking this supplement I'm
eating this oh I got a superfood here
and guess what without sugar
useless useless the sugar takes
nutrients into your cells mm info right
there have to say
it I'm been screaming it published it
you name it nutrients don't enter the
cells unless you have sugar to take them
in so the all those nutrients that we
have vitamin B's Vit D this that you
need nutrients to take it in all kinds
of different anthocyanins antioxidants
you need nut you need sugar to take the
nutrients in you need that sugar to
drive it in you want those nutrients in
you want to get those nutrients to get
into every cell you want them into your
nerve cells you want them into your
brain you want them into your liver you
want them into your pancreas you want
them into every aspect of your body but
those phytochemical compounds those
healing nutrients those polyols those
anthocyanins all of it can't enter into
a cell unless sugar takes it in so but
everybody's and
sugar and in the end all they do is
because they don't know and haven't been
taught they end up just binging on
garbage that has fat and sugar because
they end up starving themselves from
carbs but their brain needs the sugar so
they hold off the carbs and what happens
is they get hungry and then next thing
you know what they're eating guess
what they're eating a chocolate bar
that's what they're eating a nice
chocolate bar bar this looks like a good
chocolate bar this is a really good
chocolate bar right here that's a good
one then they become like slaves to
Chocolate slaves
to to caffeine slaves
to that's what they become slaves to
it's terrible and then they're high
because they have to go to Chocolate
every minute because they're hold
withholding all these carbs they're
withholding all these sugars but
ooh what's chocolate
what's a chocolate bar sugar sugar and
fat combined once again sugar and fat
combined and every time we have sugar
and fat combined what you get is insulin
resistance everybody's walking around
with insulin resistance every single day
they're walking around with insulin
resistance that's what they're
doing yeah you got it and their A1C gets
driven up over time their A1C gets
driven up they don't know what to eat
they don't know what to do then they
hold off away from carbs they stay away
from fruit they stay away from
everything they're scared to eat
anything and then then they end up
binging cheat days cheat days to make up
for the loss of carbs cheat days to make
up for the loss of
sugar and then those sheat days end up
being fat and sugar combined back to the
evil back to sugar and fat
combined and you see it out there all
the time it's unbelievable so called
glucose experts now influencers seem to
know a lot about glucose influencers
seem to know a lot about type 2
diabetes but they don't they'll sit
there and be like what you need to have
your nuts with um your Apple you need to
have a you need to have this with this
and it's like dude you're just making
insulin resistance for the person I go
we got a food plan you can buy buy our
$300 food plan and you'll learn when to
eat something and when not to eat
something when you look at that I look
at that stuff I look at that stuff now
and I'm like oh dude you just made an
insulin resistance bomb for that person
that person in two years is going to
have hypoglycemia hyperglycemia they're
going to be all over the map and they
just paid for your your useless $300
program and they're not going to know if
they're coming or going in a year or six
months they're just going to be all over
the food map like what is going on it's
crazy out there what's
happening what I recommend from s so is
you don't have fat in the morning if you
can help it if you're going to eat fat
during the day some sometime so be it I
can't control you I can't stop you you
got your own free will I can't just
whoop show up at your door and be like
whoa what did you just eat I can't but I
get it life is hard we eat all kinds of
different stuff the point is is that
people are just stuck on in a place
where they're boo chasing their tail
tail and they got the insulin resistance
bodybuilders have to bulk and cut did
you know that they bulk and cut and did
you know something else
okay I you see all over the place Tik
Tok wherever Instagram and everything
see all these Health influencer experts
they're 20 they're
24 they're 23 they're 28 you see these
bodybuilder dudes are like 31 28 29
they're young when you're young you
could sit there and a lot of people when
they're young you could eat a pizza a
night go to the beach for 3 hours bake
in 98°
heat drink drink a whole ton of vodka
and tequila at night sleep it off Boom
the next day you're in the gym you can
get a burger and fries in the middle of
the afternoon you're young you're young
you know they're giving tips everywhere
this is how my skin looks good dud
you're 24 years old this is how my skin
looks good this is working here oh see
how luscious my hair is over here did
you're
22 oh try my hair care products try my
skin products she
try I'm a model and here's what I
recommend I'm a model and I'm over here
in France and here's what I recommend my
skin care line you're 26 years old
you're 26 years old and you're pampered
pampered to death so you know the thing
is is it's like I noticed that that's
like the younger the influencer it's
like it's like next you know like it's
unbelievable able right but meanwhile
it's like s has written in the books
before everybody's a chump that follows
a chump that follows a chump that
follows a chump and they all go down in
the pit of death together in the
end and in the end it doesn't even
matter cuz who the hell cares because
we're all going to
die what you're going to live to be 180
I saw a podcast doctor saying I'm going
to live to be 160 165 years old and the
guys like doing some resistance training
as a podcast doctor I'm going to live to
be 165 with my programs I can sell you
you guys in on it you in on it yeah okay
because chump follows chump follows
chump follows chump and they all land in
the pit of death together in the end no
matter
what whatever all
right that's what you do when you have
celery Force before you go
live I try not to have celery Force
before I go
live uh but sometimes I do it all right
okay we got a lot to do I got to make
food I got to cook you name it but let's
talk about white lung a little bit we
talked about insulin resistance we
talked about nutrients getting into
cells you need the sugar to get it into
cells brain cells need sugar
they do brain cells need sugar your
brain right it's upside
down your brain needs sugar critical to
keep it alive it dies without
sugar it needs it glucose without
glucose going to the brain cells they
die quickly neurons nerve cells
neurotransmitter chemicals won't work
yes you need trace minerals that's why I
love the celery juice boom yes you need
need oxygen that's why we breathe and we
get oxygen but if you don't have the
sugar that oxygen those trace minerals
aren't going to get you far it has to be
sugar which is glucose combined with
those trace minerals boom medical medium
information in the books the trace
minerals the electrolytes with the
sugar it's that combination that brings
our brain to life and then if you want
to get metals and junk and garbage out
of the brain that's inhibiting creating
OCD and bipolar and depression anxiety
and all these problems you want to get
those medals out then you need the tools
right you need the tools just a reminder
really quick you guys this is on sale
50% off amazon.com us if you think I'm
trying to sell you a book cuz I'm trying
to sell you I'm measly book go to the
library get it out for free I am fine
with that everybody go to the library
please I beg of you I ask you go get
them for
free many years I've dropped a lot of
books off to library I've purchased them
myself I've delivered my them to myself
to
libraries and so get them for free but
either way this book is critical we're
going to talk about white lug in a
minute we're just still cutting through
a little
bit all
right so what kind of sugar do we need
I'm screaming
sugar I'm yelling sugar but what the
heck am I talking about oranges mangoes
Cherries Berries plums apples pears
bananas melons anything else I can think
about at top of my head fruit right
different berries grapes are fine too
right all these different fruits are
great and then winter squashes potatoes
sweet
potatoes boom red sweet potatoes red
potatoes purple potatoes maple syrup
yeah honey coconut water too just a
little bit of sugar in there as well
combined with electrolytes and all that
Dr fwn good to see you breast Dr fwn
breast milk is mostly sugar that's why
it's so sweet and is the best food for
de developing human brains breast milk
isn't made out of corn
oil corn oil and soy oil breast milk
isn't made out of GMO so soy and corn
like the formula the baby formula I'm
not harping on the baby formula if
that's all you got if you're a mommy you
can't breastfeed and you're in a
situation where you don't know how to
make your own breast milk no one taught
you how to make like right the medical
me and breast milk which is an
incredible option for women that can't
breastfeed if you haven't learned and
you don't know about
it and you see you got to use a can of
baby formula and that formula is nothing
but GMO corn GMO soy I understand but
our breast milk isn't made out of that
it's not made out of whey protein powder
mixed with corn oil corn syrup corn
sugar and soy oil that's not our breast
milk our breast milk is made out of
glucose from anywhere it can possibly
your body can possibly get it from and
then a small amount of protein and small
a hyper small amount of fat a hyper
small amount of
fat breast milk isn't all this fat
breast milk isn't butter in all this oil
and all this grease breast milk isn't
that it
is primarily sugar and water and
minerals women who don't get enough
glucose they'll have trouble making
breast milk for their
babies I've helped people one one-onone
for so many years you guys so many
different people over the
years and their breast milk would
dwindle down no matter what they they'd
be eating cheeseburgers they'd be eating
whatever eggs and their breast milk
would actually lessen and become weak
with with a lot of women not all women
but a lot of women won't have that
glucose storage
inside and so they're eating all these
things and they're they're getting
enough carbs but something's wrong and
then you have to switch gears you got to
remove the fats you got to get the fats
down and then the breast milk gets all
juicy and it starts to fill when there's
enough carbohydrate and a little less
fat it's critical for bringing breast
milk back I didn't know I'd be talking
about breast milk today thank you Dr
Fawn for um putting that out there a
good place to start is medical medium
morning
cleanse medical medium morning cleanse
is a great place to start you can just
start here cleanse the heel if you want
want the medical me morning cleanse
helps to clean up the liver helps to
cleanse the liver helps to move it
forward it's one thing on its own all
right so let's move into white
lung
so
look I'm just saying right that if I
caught the mystery
pneumonia that if I caught it
I'll tell you what would not be in my
diet I would not be eating
eggs I would not be eating cheese I
would not be eating milk I would not be
eating those there's no way I would be
eating those when there is something
going around that's going around like it
is right I would not be cracking the
eggs
open I would make eggs for a family
member for a friend if they came over I
would go and get some
eggs if I had a guest that liked
scrambled eggs and I would literally the
medical medium okay has many times many
times a guest coming over a family
friend coming over medical medium has
many times went out got the
eggs got the eggs out cracked open the
eggs medical medium didn't make them do
celery juice and make them do the heavy
metal detox smoothie and make them do
the spinach soup and the healing broth
no I got some eggs I cracked them open
cooked them right in my pan right in the
kitchen and fed everybody the best
scrambled eggs you ever ever could
eat the best stuff you could ever eat
the best scrambled eggs you could ever
eat it doesn't change the fact that the
eggs are how the white lung pneumonia is
even here is even here
so the white lung
pneumonia pathogen they're not calling
it viral but it's viral it's
viral they'll call it micoplasma
bacteria but it's
viral the white lung pneumonia that's
here now was
raised in
those was raised in those and labs and
then somehow got
out that's why whether egg people and
trainers and all the anti and all the
dieticians on Tik Tok and anybody else
who's talking to anybody else that's a
hater of medical medium sitting there
screaming about eggs and how I'm wrong
and those morons don't realize that
that's how these bugs got even here
because what classified medical research
and science did was they just opened up
the top of the egg and they put the
pathogens in and procreated them and
that's how they make them that's why C
is
here that's why pneumonia that's why the
flu that's why whatever colds are still
around that you think are still around
that's why anything and everything is
still here that's why your herpes
simplex
one is even here to begin
with that's why your epscene bar is even
here to begin with it was raised in labs
in eggs so what I'm trying to tell you
is first thing I would do I would get
the info know what I'm doing I would get
the protocols take it to your doctor if
you'd like okay stopped eating eggs for
3 Days drinking celery juice and feel so
much better crazy to think I've been
eating eggs every day I got mono in high
school and searching for
advice um grateful for medical
medium yeah an
Anique and K
so when white lung is going on out
there I would not eat an egg I don't eat
eggs
anyway but I would not eat an egg cuz I
don't want this in my body feeding that
bug that's going around cuz I don't want
fluid in my lungs and I don't want pus
in my lungs and I don't want my
lymphatic system taken over by fluid and
pus and I don't want my liver beaten
down and so I'm not going to eat an egg
I'm
not another thing I'm not going to eat
because of white lung going
around see if I can find some right
here another thing I would not
eat since white L's going
around
cheese would not eat
cheese you can eat what you want you got
your own free will you got your own
doctors you got your own whatever
healthc care providers telling you what
to do you listen to them right
but I'm saying what I wouldn't do I
would stay away from cheese with these
bugs going around because then bugs they
love to eat this and if this is in all
tied up in your lymphatic system the
mucus and the crud from this is all
sitting your L lymphatic system your
lymph it's all sitting in your liver
what's going to happen is it's going to
make it so when white lung comes around
that virus that comes around is going to
spew out so much mucus is going to
produce so much mucus and and it's not
going to have a place to go and that's
why people's lungs fill up it's why
kids' lungs are filling up and they're
in the hospitals right now their lungs
are filling up with fluid because
they're on so many of these things of
course their immune system is also low
for a host of different reasons they
don't know about the protocols you know
you got all these people I see it every
day I hear about I had a doctor friend
tell me there's so many kids in the
hospital with this white lung and the
families don't know about protocols and
what kids need and stuff they they don't
bring these to their
doctor and the kids are on cheese the
kids are on
eggs the adults are on cheese adults are
on eggs and then it rips through the
family and it knocks people down and
knocks nurses down and knocks everybody
down you
know and then it's the craziest thing we
go through life we go through life I
going do it all over again if you
believe that this isn't our only
lifetime do you believe that this isn't
our only lifetime tell me like it's okay
if you believe this we got one shot and
one shot only we never come back our
soul is not even there we don't have a
soul our soul doesn't come back into
this lifetime our soul doesn't come back
into another body there's no way aw it
doesn't happen we die and that's it well
okay okay you die you're gone that's it
then but if you believe we come back
here
and we come back here again and we may
come back here again if you believe that
this isn't our only shot here this isn't
our only moment our soul gets to walk
into a physical form
here then you may not want to do what so
many people do over and over again they
come back here they're a baby they're
born get older die come back again
they're
born
and they get older and they die come
back eat good macaroni
cheese boom get older
and die come
back Linda Prescot Prescott said what
I'm saying is I'd like to break the
cycle there's a cycle wouldn't you like
to break the cycle wouldn't you like to
break the cycle wouldn't you like to
break the cycle once once and not get
suckered not get
suckered Linda Prescott says this old
nurse likes your food ways amazing
honored you're
here some nurses they like medical
medium stuff some nurses say blood draw
they don't take more than one
vial from what I've seen in 20 years of
practice dude they take 30 vials from
people who are chronically sick they
take 40 vials they take 45 vials from
people are sick so some nurses they just
like totally out some nurses are Keen
they're like right on it they get it
they get the medical medum information
they get the whole thing with the blood
draw how they take too much blood they
get the whole thing with the foods and
all that and you get some nurses they're
like you better get your protein you
better get your protein I mean all
nurses are great cuz we need help out
there but you better get your protein
and no such thing as drawing more than
three blood vials of blood I've never
seen that what it's all they do suck
people
dry all right let me show you a couple
things okay first of
all here we go all
right we still got to talk about white
lung and pneumonia cold and flu tool kit
what's in here I'm going to open this up
all right you got
supplementation
um ideas okay you got all that in here
but you also have the time tea
water when this time of year comes
around we're heading into the holidays
we're heading into Christmas everybody
is super spreading right everybody's
sick everybody's coughing their lungs
out people are fevered up time t water
you want to dial this up here do you
have the cold and flu toolkit just link
is in the B link is in the
description right Elderberry syrup how
to make your own Elderberry syrup great
tool all in its own right there love it
healing
broth medical medium healing broth woo
you start getting
sick and you're about to like come down
with it you're about to come down with
the white lung I don't talk about white
lung in a minute what it even means and
all that but you're coming down with the
cold you're coming down with the
flu and you don't want something heavy
you don't want a steak dinner in you you
don't want a stack of pancakes like this
either you don't want a chicken you
don't want that you don't want a pizza
big greasy oily pizza because it's hard
on the immune system your immune
system's not going to be able to defend
you and clean up that virus in those
bugs okay so and I'll show you some
recipes too that are options but the
healing broth if I came down with a
virus that's going around right now
giving people pneumonia I would be doing
the healing broth I'd have my celery
juice I'd be doing cooking of water I'd
be doing the healing broth I'd be doing
lemon water
actually so these are the things I'd be
doing Ginger and tea water is what I
would be doing right there check out
this cold INF flu I would have the brain
saver books
uh-huh I would have the protocols
book Big Time both books okay these are
just some of the things it's called
inclu toolkit let's move on to some
options I'm want to show you some
different incredible things in the
protocols book right here look at the
foods in here in the
recipes
okay going to put this down for a second
and we're about to make food right now
but I'm just this is um this is just
such an Inc oh my God this is such an
incredible book the recipes are
insane and they are so easy on the
system easy on the immune system
supportive to the immune system these
are the things we need when we're
dealing with like the white lung
neumonia that's going around we need
foods and options that are really
helpful I mean I can go in here all day
look at this this is what I'm making
right here take a look you guys split
screening that baby
look that's what we're making today it's
with chickpea flour now I want to tell
you something I know I make some
pretty pretty intense recipes sometimes
overall and you might be somebody that's
already on the medical medium monoc
cleanse or you're somebody that's
already on the you're on the morning
cleanse then you do your hmds you do all
this other stuff you do the 28 day
cleanse
and this might not be what you want
right now but for the people who
actually want something like this is an
option we got
them all right cheese stay away when the
bugs are out to play okay eggs stay away
when the bugs are out to play okay
important to know if you can if it's the
only food you have and you're going to
starve eat the eggs then if it's the
only food you have you have some
chickens in the backyard you can't get
to a store you're going to starve to
death eat the eggs if you got nothing
else but an old piece of cheese in the
refrigerator and you got nothing to eat
that day and it's the only thing that's
going to keep you like stable meaning
something in your body so you have some
kind of substance something like that
you can actually function with then eat
the cheese but I'm saying if you have
options stay away when you're up against
the pathogens that are out there right
now that are sweeping through like the
white lung
very important so I want to go into the
Colden
flu right here just for a little
bit you'll see
dosages and I'll show you on a closeup
too we'll see if the close-up camera can
get up
here and check this out what's
incredible about this all right let me
see if I can get in there yep there you
are right voila focus focus
okay it says supplements for cold flu
and C right for
children and then there's adults as well
so it goes into that but it shows you
dosages and you can just do maybe three
of these things ask your doctor what's
right for you but you can do three of
these
things five of these things you don't
have to do everything if you don't want
to but you'll see at the top of the list
it'll say fresh celery juice that's not
a supplement but if you can do it how
incredible that is that like it says C
fresh celery juice right there for Cold
and Flu fresh celery juice right there
for cold and flu that's incredible the
next one is zinc next one's vitamin C
next one's lemon balm golden seal check
this out time
tea so time tea if that's all you can do
then that's what you can do but at least
you have
options it's really an incredible
resource to help protect people I don't
even know what else to say Maria says
what is the title of this book an
author well you know the author see he's
a nice guy the author to this book yeah
he's he's a nice guy he's helped a lot
of people and I really like them I'm
just letting you know the title of the
book is brainsaver protocols cleanses
and recipes for neurological autoimmune
and mental health it's by this guy named
Anthony William who's a pretty cool dude
you know he's helped a lot of people
he's changed a lot in the health scene
been around for many many years I like
that guy so if you get a chance check it
out all
right moving right
along that was exhibit a we went through
exhibit B what about Exhibit
C Barbara can you help when I drink
celery juice I get bad stomach cramps
when
and loose stools is this normal in the
medical medium
books okay I talk about you can start
very very little very little if you have
a lot of things pathogens bacteria yeast
unproductive fungus mold a lot of people
have all kinds of stuff right inside
here okay and in their
liver celery juice kills off
unproductive yeast and mold celery juice
strips down bad bacteria strep
sea hpylori
bacteria like eoli that actually develop
people develop
ulcers diverticulosis
diverticulitis they have all these
different little bit of bacteria like
strep eoli sedith staff all sits in
there in the little pockets inside their
intes track you put the celery juice
down if you're making it fresh that's
best maybe you're buying some store
bought one that's HPP and that one might
be giving you cramps I don't know a lot
of people do that well they'll tell me
they're drinking celery juice and
they're getting the store bought one
it's got all this junk in there it's got
different things mixed in it it's it's
HPP high pressure pasteurization which
is actually not it means it's not raw it
means it's
cooked with an an experimental way of
cooking it which is actually scary if
you're going to cook something i' rather
have you put it to heat and cook it but
whatever it is if you're doing if you're
getting a little cramped up from celery
juice are you straining it do you know
the guidelines do you know the
information are you straining the celery
juice you got to strain it that bring
dials that down right there that's one
of the reasons why you have to strain it
it's critical right and then the other
thing is you do a little bit at a time
if you could only do 2 O of celery juice
run a few sticks through and do 2 oz you
start with that and see how it rolls a
lot of people have to acclimate they got
to
acclimate all right making a
Kye and we're going to talk about white
long where we're doing it we're not
making a kiche where did I get that
idea we're making a
fata key
we making the kich or the fata let's
make it let's go let's figure this
out we need to figure it out right here
okay all
right so four here's what it is it's two
cups the recipe calls for two cups of
chickpea flour guys hang in there I'm
not done with white lung I want to talk
about mucus I'm going to do that when
the um frittatas are cooking in the oven
and then we're going to go into exhibit
D or Exhibit C and that exhibit is the
lungs right
here the lungs immune system the white
lung that's going around the mystery
pneumonia the pus and the mucus please
hang in there but I got to make some
food I have to I'm hungry if you can
have some patience that would be amazing
that would be amazing all right I'm
doing four cups of chickpea flour so it
calls for chickpea flour okay and
yeah I'm going to put it in here so that
is oh nice cameras are working good
today um there's the chickpea flour
right there see four cups cuz I'm making
a big batch not a small batch so we got
that in there so let's start putting
some stuff in here let's cut in onion to
begin with actually let's get some
baking powder in here two teaspoons of
baking powder for four cups two cups one
teaspoon so bear with me I'm going to
put two teaspoons of baking powder in
here fantastic I'm going to put
different spices some garlic powder two
teaspoons of garlic powder let me drop
that in here well this is going to be
really
good if you want to use fresh you can
use fresh that's okay paprika two
teaspoons you can use fresh though if
you really want to
um comes out good either way I swear it
does here's the onion powder two
teaspoons woo some
oregano let's get this top open here
little bit of oregano here two teaspoons
right okay hot pepper flakes or Cayenne
do you guys see this this came out of my
garden right here though I don't know if
you guys have seen this right here but
let me just take some of these out look
at
this these
are out of my garden I grow a lot of
cayenne peppers I love cayenne peppers
all I need is one for this cuz these are
hot so what I'm going to do is chop this
and this is going to go right in I'm
going to move this over this is going to
go right in um the bowl we're going to
mix this look you can do hot pepper
flakes check that out look at that right
there you guys sorry about the noise
sometimes I hit the knife really hard on
it there I'm going to stir this
in okay got the wooden spoon let's stir
this in look at
that I want to get this all nice in
there and
then o no
no bigger mess for
later
okay that's mixed up let's get the
carrot in there I'm going to start with
some carrot so what I'm going to do is
I'm just going to peel this carrot you
can you don't have to peel a carrot I'm
going to peel it because I want a
certain look too when you open up that
cooked beautiful cooked muffin right so
I want
to peel that carrot now what I'm going
to do is I'm going to use the peeler to
make the carrot like like nice and like
thin pieces because I'm GNA chop those
up I don't want hunks of Raw carrot in
this
fata so what I'm doing
is I'm peeling the carrot back and I'm
making this these strips and I'm going
to cut those strips you see you guys
right careful when you use one of these
I mean you can catch your finger
and that would not be good and I'm kind
of like I'm kind of like I get a little
intense right here so could easily
happen all right that should be good
right there you can do a whole carrot if
you want but you'll have a carrot cake
so you got to look out you don't want a
carrot cake in this situation I think
that's like a lot I think that's plenty
okay so I'm going to do a little bit of
chopping if you don't
mind and you don't want the strands to
be really long inside your muffins right
there cuz I'm making
muffins
okay we want to chop these up pretty
good if you guys are still on your
hanging out I just want to tell you a
couple of things if you like what I'm
talking about with the white lung and
the sugar and everything else um give me
a thumbs up that would be cool subscribe
if you haven't go to my telegram cuz you
guys that's where I'm going to be a
that's where I'm going to be a lot in
the future I'm just letting you know so
make sure sure you're there at my
telegram sign up because I'm going to be
there a lot check it out link is the
description you can go to Medical me.com
too all right look right there so what I
did is I finally minced some carrot and
then going to drop that carrot right
into the
mix like I said before you don't want so
much carrot that you made yourself a
carrot cake nothing wrong wrong with a
carrot
cake I mean a healthy carrot cake right
I want people they're eating a carrot
cake filled with all this junk on it in
it and they're like I'm eating a carrot
cake is that healthy I'm like uh all
right zucchini right here let's go so
I'm just going to cut off the ends of
that
zucchini now the same thing with
zucchini okay I'm just going to cut off
a couple little
pieces
all right just a couple little strange
pieces you go to the store you buy
zucchini you'll see that right there
I'll show you in a
closeup that's somebody's fingernail
that went through there and it ain't
mine
so if I want to scare the crap out of
myself I'll ask Spirit of
compassion whose fingernail was that
what was under that fingernail what
could potentially be in that zucchini
but I try not to ask Spirit of
compassion those questions I just know
that anything could be under somebody's
fingernail
from the's the strap to everything under
the sun I've talked about this for years
okay so let's chop this up here so not
only do I wash stuff and I'm going to do
like a whole show on washing produce for
sure so I'm going to slice this in kind
of like these kinds of slice pieces
right here now you don't want these
really big and hunky either in the
mix okay so what I'm going to do is cut
these
small see
guys so anyway I wanted to talk about
this pneumonia that's that's rushing
through the us right
now I would say right around Christmas
time it's going to be in the major
cities a lot of people are going to be
in the emergency room a lot of people
take taking a lot of antibiotics and
hopes to curve it I'm not trying to
freak you out or anything it's just that
if I don't say anything about it like
when the next flu comes through or the
next mysterious pneumonia comes through
if I don't remind people to be a little
more cautious like use a handy wipe at
on the shopping carts on the carriage
handle cuz all the Simplex on there and
all the strap and all the the flu on
there and the white lung flu will be on
there
so what I'm saying is there's different
precautions you can take and then of
course protocols right you want your
time tea every day you want that cold
and flu
protocol okay guys getting this in
here might be like pretty much all I
need and once this is in the oven we'll
talk about the white flu all
right okay next on the list
onion the only thing with the onion is
I'm just not in the mood to like be all
teared up from the onion and I'm not in
the mood for that right now you know the
watery
eyes cuz this onion I noticed has been
kind of sharp I've been using this onion
lately this yellow onion it's been
pretty darn
sharp
okay an
anti-pathogenic power the onion has
that's the kind of stuff you
want okay you want that
anti-pathogenic
Powerhouse which is herbs like onions
and garlic you want that you don't want
you know cheese cheese is just going to
gum up the works and feed a pathogen
feed a virus that's going around making
it worse then like cheese cheese is
going to just tie up your lymphatic
system I love it I love it when haters a
medical medium like say like certain
dietitians or something they're like
he's starving people from cheese people
need their protein they need their
cheese I'm going to have Samantha
eventually come um over and make an
appearance and talk about cheese and
protein and things like that but
Sammy hasn't been feeling good lately
she's been under the weather herself she
caught a little something and Sam's been
sick herself so yep she's been coughing
she's got a UTI Sammy has a bad
UTI um She's coughing a lot so Samy's
doing that okay I'm put a little bit
more onion in here can't help it and
then we're going to do some fresh
squeezed lemon boom might even do some
other stuff too we're going to do some
red bell
pepper
so
so I noticed
that Spirit of compassion was telling me
that even though we just dealt with the
whole issue we did with four years ago
with the bugs going around and stuff
Spirit of compassion has told me that
we're due for a really bad one not not
the one that's coming right now that's
already landed in the
US that one right
now where is my hand
tow
that one's really annoying for sure but
s so tells me that eventually there's
going to be a really bad Bruiser of a
brute that's going to be coming to
town and so we want strong immune
systems we want to be armed and ready we
want to know what foods to eat we want
to know how to take care of
ourselves duh Mystic
MSM I'm so sick of YouTube censoring and
shadowing and banning I came on to
YouTube at least half an hour ago and
this live stream did not come up for me
in my feed I was um I was censored on
YouTu even though I have a few people on
YouTube right now right like you know
you're on there in that moment mystical
but I've been censored on YouTube um
four years ago three and a half years
ago they censored me on YouTube so they
only let a few people see if I'm on or
you have to look for it and and very few
people can find my
YouTube I'm I'm really shadowed Bad on
YouTube it's just it's actually
incredible Louie and I'm totally
censored on on um X totally censored so
the whole free speech thing on X
whatever that whole thing was it wasn't
for medical medium Louise says Sammy is
so good bring on the Sammy I laughed and
laughed last time she visited thank you
Louise I'm so glad you're not upset from
Sammy coming on because I got so much
crap when Sammy came on here people were
so angry they were like so mad but a lot
of people weren't a lot of people were
happy sammy came on all right all right
let's see I'm going to pick this one
right here are you guys okay with that
once we get this in the oven I'm going
to be talking about the pneumonia what
happens come on I want to get
there right taking out I want to show
you this ready check this out this is
how I do the pepper ready here's how I
do it I put the knife right here ready
see that watch this see you got this
already set see this right here throw
that away take your hand in here just
like this you see that boom you see this
you see that you see this you see that
you see this
look done that's how I like doing my
Peppers just like
that all right all right
nice nice all right I think I'm going to
do a whole pepper in this this batch if
you guys don't mind yes Sammy wants to
come on but she's got a UTI she's got a
cold sore so she's got um a fever
blister and she has um
she has some
bloating she has a really bad set of
acne that came out so she's got a whole
acne breakout Sammy has that plus
UTI Sammy also has the fever blister
that came out and she's sick with a cold
she says it's a cold
um so that Sammy when she's better she's
going to come out and she's going to
talk about everything from protein to
maybe other stuff too actually she's
going to really go into it if you guys
don't mind all right hang it in there
still have to talk about pneumonia
because even though I K around here and
there about some stuff um it really is
important that you know what's up how
the lungs work with this all right check
that
out that is going to be it's going to be
incredible right here let's mix this up
and get this in let's add some water to
it
boom
nice okay waterwise oh I need lemon
juice what am I doing what is wrong with
me these are mini
frittatas we need lemon juice now now we
need lemon juice
quick not later we need it now
okay get some lemon juice in there you
guys you guys I got like nervous when
I'm making the food for you guys because
I feel like I feel like I can't mess up
I have to do it
right you know if you guys aren't here
you know I'm like more more like you
know it's all right if I like if I throw
something in the air and I miss
it all right getting some lemon juice in
here these are going to taste so good
it's going to be insane it's
insane
okay so we did the oregano we're doing
the okay we're doing the 1 and
3/4 we're doing three and 1/2 cups of
water that's what we're
doing but I'm going to be careful with
the water because you don't want it too
liquidy so you got to kind of gauge it
all right here we go there's a
lemon
W all
right water
water it's the
water it's this one cup of water right
there let's do another
cup am I going crazy is that too much
did I mess
up did
I don't tell me this thing is going to
be too too
liquidy
no
no no come
on don't do this to me not live in front
of everybody don't embarrass
me no
way if you guys really love salt or
something and you know just don't overdo
it but if you want to pinch of salt or
something like that you can put that in
here
can't wait to talk about
pneumonia can't wait all right so let's
get this in the muffin tins let's just
make sure it's mixed up enough you don't
want like hunks of
flour you don't want all the hunks of
glutenous wheat flour that I put in here
you don't want that gluten all that
protein that glutenous flour in here the
gluten just kidding this was chickpea
flour it was glutenfree come on have a
sense of humor it's okay this is going
to be I love when people try to school
me and they're like he does restrictive
stuff he makes you eat spinach soup he
does he's restrictive but by the way
check out the way I eat I eat oh a
little portion of my special beef I eat
oh one hard-boiled egg slice just like
this in here in the corner I have three
carrot sticks right here that my kids
also eat and I have a little piece of
cheese here it's like dude you're
restrictive too unless you go to
McDonald's and you're ordering the Big
Mac shut up shut up shut the up I mean I
love it when the haters whether
dietitians or health haters Health
influencers they hate medical medium
they'll be like he's too restrictive
he's keeping eggs out right he's keeping
corn syrup out he's keeping pork out and
then they go but check out how I'm
eating and they have a tray and the tray
has like one hard oil boiled egg all cut
like that dude if you're going to eat
eggs eat a freaking omelette and have
six half a dozen eggs with cheese
they're like I have this little piece of
hardened cheese from France I got this
little bit of beef that's $1,000 a pound
right here and then I have this and I
have that and it has to be pasturized
ized I mean pasture raised and it has to
be this and in the end you look at it
dude you're restrictive too don't tell
anybody that medical mean is restrictive
when your stuff is restrictive unless
you're eating anything you want and go
into a restaurant and you just ordered a
bacon double cheeseburger and a whole
crap load of onion rings and the
slimiest milkshake you've ever drank
unless you're going out and eating that
every day you're restrictive too you're
restrictive too so when you see that out
there you guys if you see people doing
that you see like dietitians or health
influencers or or just straight medical
medium haters that have a platform if
you see them saying how restrictive
medical medium is and how they're
starving people the the diet is and
orthorexia if you see that but then you
see what they're doing how they're
eating they're eating like insanity it's
so restrictive it's like where's what
they're doing they're like they got a
little bit of the special grass-fed beef
right here a little if you're so damn
worried about restrictive why aren't you
eating any beef why aren't you going and
having a beef taco at some Diner
somewhere because you won't because
you're restrictive you're really
restrictive has to be a certain little
they got a little hardboiled egg cut
here they got a little bit of almonds
right here some almonds they have a
little bit of cashews right here and
they have a radish right here I go are
you freaking kidding
me Linda wolf I was a registered
dietitian for 33 years so it kills me to
listen to
Sammy We're so misinformed in our
profession there is a lot of humor to
Sammy it's just embarrassing for me to
watch sami's 24 years old and Sammy is
going to come on so we'll see all
right getting lost
ready here's what we're doing we got to
put these little paper things in
here check this out
okay I got these little paper cupy
things right
here boom one let's get these in let's
get this done cuz I want to talk about
pneumonia I'm worried for people if
they're not at least partially prepared
because who wants to be sick in bed who
wants to be at the hospital with a bad
case of bronchitis and then told they
have Walking Pneumonia
for the next month and pneumonia can
like really Tire people out it can just
linger and linger so many people who get
it they're just like they're just like
in like this place where they've lost
their energy they can't get oxygen in
their lungs they have too much mucus
drowning out their
lungs and it's really sad when there's
things we can do we can protect
ourselves there's information out there
you're getting kicked off of a at all
just go to medical.com I'm streaming
live right there right now you can also
go to rumble streaming live right there
YouTube's a little tricky because they
have me uh shadowed on YouTube for three
and a half years now you might be able
to get in you might
not if you are on YouTube give me a
thumbs up if you don't like this video
give me a thumbs
up if you like this video give me a
thumbs up if you don't like this video
give me the middle
finger all
right I'm filling these up right now now
what I'm doing is I'm trying not to make
a
mess uh in aw's kitchen
know there's kind of a like there's
always a mess being
made and I'm just going to first of all
I'm going to top these off but I'm just
going to get enough in here like this I
just want to make sure there's enough
going on
here all right you guys hang in
there there we
go why am
I this is working out really good I just
got to clean that one little spot there
there we
go all right actually looking pretty
good A couple little spots there okay no
more let try
this try a
spoon all
right
smart
okay you guys see these last three at
all the problem is you catch a flu it
knocks you down lowers the immune system
you recover you catch another flu knocks
you down lowers your immune system you
recover but you kind of get you don't
get this reprieve right you're getting
knocked down all the time then the white
lung mysterious pneumonia virus comes in
knocks us down
right and then we
recover but our immune systems are
beaten down over time it's really
difficult for so many people
and we have to like look out for
ourselves in any way we can there you
go all right this is going in the oven
and then we're going to get down to
business we're going to get down to this
free this free
talk you don't have to pay you don't
have to subscribe and pay some fees I'm
just adding a little bit more to this
one if we can again there we go there we
go
okay and what I'm going to do is I'm
going to move this in here a little bit
that move that one in all right going
in I want to show you what it looks like
right there though there you go and I
want to show you up close right you guys
can you see that and can you see that
right here it's going in the oven these
are incredible one's a little
shallow
that can happen all right so it's
350° it's
in
yep let's get this cleaned up and we're
going to do Exhibit C or is it exhibit D
should I
say is it exhibit
e or exhibit f
let's see what we
got I IG I don't find medical medium
restrictive thank you there is some
serious haters out there that do
meanwhile if you look at what they're
eating they kill me
now mm
restrictive restricted question mark I
have never eating as much as I do now
exactly how many times have you guys
seen this if you're seasoned and you've
been around how many times are you told
don't eat this don't eat that let's do
an all cat let's check out your food
allergy testing don't eat this don't eat
this let's check your IGG don't eat that
that that that that that that try the F
map try this try eat right for this try
to do that and it's like oh restrictive
here restrictive here restrictive here
it's just constantly like that all the
time carnivore restrictive boom you name
it even carnivore guys that were
preaching carnivore they hit the wall
their brain didn't work and they had to
start bringing in fruit and honey and
lemon because they were literally dying
on straight carnivore they were so
restricted and it's like now they're
like you know all of a sudden like
functioning again because they're
getting some type of sugar in them I
just had the pneumonia and almost died
we need to stop World Travel for
real for
real all
right
dummy
here pH crispy perspective oh my God
been through that and done that so
you've actually been through that you're
seasoned you know what's up you do right
now you guys are so much hate and attack
on medical medium it's
unbelievable out there and they're just
so jealous and they're all trying to
sell all their programs and they're
trying to sell all their build their
Empires and they're trying to do you
name it and they're so pissed at Medical
medium they're tired of hearing people
say medical medium fixed me medical
medium healed me medical medium
literally changed my life and I got
better I was bedridden they don't want
to hear that they don't want to hear it
people are
asking and people ask about these bad
bugs you know it's important to answer
and talk about it a little bit so first
of all first thing to know what is it
what is this
bug well
the
CBC see how I changed the
acrom the
CBC right says oh don't worry it's not a
virus don't worry it is it's viral it's
a virus yes it
is okay it's
another viral issue at hand
but no one wants to talk about it
because they think everybody's just
burned out from the last virus so
they're trying to say oh maybe it's it's
myoplasmic
maybe it's bacteria and that's what
they're going by but it's viral very
important to know okay so here's how it
works when you catch a
bacteria okay our body does not do the
same thing it does
with viruses so what people are getting
is lung infections so
rapid critical lung
infections those are only caused by cyto
storms
cyto
bacteria does not
create a
full-blown cyto storm
it's one thing if I'm sitting here and
I'm just going to talk to you guys about
this and say wait long wait long wait
long pneumonia ponia build your immune
system it's another if I can at Le it's
one thing to do that it's another so you
guys know what's going on so you guys
hear it here you hear it here first you
know you learn about it you know the BS
that's happening out there
okay
viruses
Airborne like the flu and like C create
cyto storms whether it's a small cyto
storm or a large cyto storm the only way
to get pneumatic fluid in the lungs to
this degree is you have to be doing some
type of cyto storm and the only way to
do that cyto storm to this degree is it
has to be a virus it can't be bacteria
but see that's how you know how foul the
game is played and how the game
is played out there so just be like oh
it's m
micoplasma it's it's you know it's
bacteria no no that that can already be
in you and when your immune system gets
knocked down by a cyto storm from a
virus getting into the lungs then
yeah other bacteria can Thrive and in
some people can Thrive so much that you
end up getting even more fluid in more
problems and more issues another person
they may not have that type of bacteria
that's really in their system that can
Elevate like they don't have enough
strap and they don't have enough other
varieties of bacteria so they don't get
that elevation of bacteria but they
still get the cyto storm and the fluid
in the lungs and the
mucus you guys I didn't listen I want
you know I didn't say stop World Travel
that was I was reading a comment of
someone who said they almost died from
the pneumonia and they said they would
stop World Travel so that wasn't me
saying it what I say is make sure you
have information wherever you're
traveling make sure you have protocols
and understand what's going on so you
can protect yourself and make sure you
have that while you're traveling and
that's what I
say so the first lesson here in this
exhibit is to know that when you see
somebody going through white lung
they're going through cyto storm now
here's the next part that's really
critical to know this tells you if it's
virus get
ready if it's titled white lung why
they're titling it white lung because
they're seeing scar tissue in the
lung they're seeing scar tissue in the
lung that's
why why is there scar tissue in the lung
because of a cyto storm only a cyto
storm can create White Scar Tissue seen
on the scans in the
lung because of a
virus that's Advanced information right
there extremely Advanced information
about what's going on out there and how
it
works this one thing to be like oh you
know what is it out there what's going
on
oh it's another to actually know how it
works virus enters in through your nose
the virus enters in through your mouth
you eat the virus if you're eating out
you know somewhere out and and somebody
coughed on the plate you're eating the
virus you're breathing it in if
somebody's sneezing if somebody's
breathing you're breathing it in you get
it in and when that virus gets in you
goes down into the
lung it gets in the lung and then
there's a war
a war that
ensues so next
piece next piece been critical
information here it
is right there your white blood cells
your white blood cells
and the virus that's going around right
now they go into battle they fight and
as they're fighting and totally just
pissing each other off and they're after
each other and and the virus is trying
to kill the immune cell
that's what the virus is doing he trying
to destroy and kill your immune cells
and your immune cell is trying to stay
alive and it's sit you're trying to kill
the virus it's trying to eat the virus
and this war that's
happening is the cyto
storm and if the immune system is
weakened and beat down then the virus
can bypass it and get into lung tissue
and start to eat up some of the lung
tissue cells which creates a scar scar
like
tissue and that's what the cyto storm in
white lung is and that's what's going
out going around right now so all these
kids and adults are getting these Scar
Tissue markers in their lungs where they
don't really know what it is well that's
what it is it's scar
tissue and that's what's going on there
okay
so a tremendous amount of
lymphocytes
and white blood cells and killer cells
die from this cyto storm so you're in
crisis with the cyto storm because your
immune system is exploding just like
this white blood cell just did so it
fell apart it just boom exploded and
that's what happens so when people are
dealing with this they're actually
losing white blood cells left and right
thousands of them and then your bone
marrows going into overdrive producing
more white blood cells and more immune
killer more immune cells and those are
coming back up to the lungs and the war
still goes on so finally after things
dumb down a little bit you get a mucus
an overload of mucus from this process
it starts out where the mucus doesn't
start the mucus starts out a little
later so this whole white lung
mysterious pneumonia syndrome is mucus
that starts a little after a little
later on after already The War Began
with the cyto storm and as the War Began
it started to the war started to die
down and finish and what was left is now
the mucus from the byproduct of all of
the viruses that have been killed and
destroyed by your immune system and that
byproduct helps to produce a tremendous
amount of mucus and pus and yellow mucus
and clear mucus and all that mucus
builds up in the lower sections of the
lung because when it comes down to a bad
virus those are the viruses the bad flu
viruses the bad sea viruses the bad
white lung
viruses those are the viruses that
actually trigger off lower lung issues
they go deeper they just don't sit up
here where you have postnasal drip and
you get like cold in the head or a mild
flu in the head and then the drip goes
down into your lung no that's not what's
Happening
Here someone can get a flu the flu goes
into their sinuses gets into their head
it produces a tremendous amount of mucus
the mucus and the sinuses drains down as
you're sleeping into the night you're
sleeping and it's draining down into
your lungs but it's draining down into
the upper lungs
upper area of your respiratory and then
that's the cough and the crack and the
cough and the carak and that's what that
is you're trying to expel you need the
expectorant you need it to come out but
the difference is when it's like the
white lung the mysterious pneumonia bugs
those viruses they go deeper into the
lung they go into the lower
lungs where they're sitting in there
trying to do
damage and that's the difference and now
that's where you can't breathe good and
you feel like you're drowning in mucus
and pus and you're drowning in it and
that's what it feels like you see you
guys and when you're in that position
you're kind of stuck where whoa do I go
to the doctor do I go to the hospital I
can't breathe good and they're now
they're throwing everything at you
they're throwing you know the seatbacks
at you they're throwing the antibiotics
they throwing you the the steroids the
5-day steroids they throwing everything
they can at you to dumb went down but
that's what's happening so right now on
the rise is a
virus tagged out there as white lung
syndrome something like
that and mysterious pneumonia and what
it is is another pneumatic virus going
in here creating a cyto storm by
battling your white blood cells going
deeper into the lungs the lower part of
the
lungs and how much mucus is produced
also depends on what you're doing for
Foods if you're coming down with that
baby you don't want to be eating this
when you're coming down with that
pneumonia when you're coming down with
any kind of bug flu virus you don't want
to be eating all that cheese and all
that fat you don't want to eat
that and there's there's sea viruses
going around right now there's flu
viruses going around right now and then
there's boom this virus going around
right now they're going to name it
anything they want to name it but right
now they're keeping it everybody from
knowing it's a virus but you never know
maybe in a month they'll be like that
was a virus that wasn't micoplasma that
wasn't this we'll see what
happens but you don't want to be eating
this or too much of
that when this stuff is going around you
don't want to be eating too much cheese
you don't want to be eating any cheese
when this stuff is going
around you don't want to be eating eggs
especially eggs when this stuff is going
around
okay right you don't want to be eating
those
too because these feed the virus that's
going around so what's happening here
okay
is these babies are
feeding that virus that's getting into
people's lungs it loves to eat this and
when it eats this it get gets
stronger more mucus is
produced a virus going around flu virus
C virus any kind of virus going
around produces mucus all on its own
because it's it's it's leaving all this
byproduct talked about that for years
the byproduct from pathogens all that
byproduct that
byproduct saturates the system the
lymphatic system the liver the lungs and
all that byproduct helps to build up all
that mucus all that
pneumonia yellow
pus same with cheese you don't want to
be doing cheese when these bugs are
around you do the cheese it's the same
thing you got to look out it's these
things that
matter if it was me and I was coming
down with something or I knew somebody
there had something I'd be cautious
making sure there's no cheese there's no
milk there's no dairy products there's
no eggs I would keep corn out
make sure there's no corn corn syrup I
would keep the fats low make sure
there's no pork if you're a meat eater
right eat lighter if you're a meat eater
and I would make sure I would have that
protocols book right
there I would make sure that's there
because that's the greatest companion in
times like this you can actually know
what you can do for yourself how you can
arm yourself what you can look out for
yourself with it's for all important and
this is free this is free at the library
this is free now and I'm not charging
for this you guys excuse me did I put
$33.99 on this thing on the internet is
this thing
$40 no and it cost me a lot of money to
create and make this right here is free
check it out get the time tea going get
the healing broth
going go to Medical mem.com you can get
the book there you can get this there
you can go to amazon.com yes I'm just
showing let me check the fadas let's
go
nice looking good what you want to do is
you want to stick a a toothpick in the
into the muffins into the frittatas I
don't have a toothpick so what I'm going
to do is stick a chopstick in
there yes I
am
yes I
am right there so I'm going to put this
in there in a minute so just hang in
there I can't wait you
know all right so let's get into this
exhibit e coming up
next want to talk about sugar a little
bit and sugar
fear got a comment to
read so
um how do we heal the scar
tissue all
right so our lungs like to regenerate
they like to heal over time what I've
noticed all these years is that the only
way to heal scar tissue in lungs is
antioxidants high amounts of
antioxidants namely vitamin C is one of
the best ones right there vitamin C is
one of the big ones for healing Scar
Tissue associated with viruses that are
airborne they get into the lungs damag
tissue damag
cells vitamin C is a big one I'm just
giving you one tool there's plenty of
tools in the brain saver protocols but
I'm giving you one powerful tool all in
its own Michelle says B12 that's that's
important too B12 is important for for
every single cell in the body but if you
can't do any of that make sure you're
staying away from a lot of the foods
that gum up the works and I'm just using
that basic term gums up the works okay
like foods that dog the liver foods that
slow down the liver foods that actually
create a problem with the liver where so
much mucus is being produced in the
liver that the lymphatic system is is
getting the the like the load the excess
mucus and lymphatic drainage isn't going
to cut it if you keep on dumping all of
this stuff these mucus forming Foods
mucus forming Foods because pathogens
are feeding on these
foods and that's a big reason why
they're mucus forming because pathogens
feed on these Foods it's a big part of
it and then the byproduct from the
pathogens and man when this white lung
comes through and it's it's hitting the
cities now and everybody is coughing
their chest is tight they're all walking
around with walking pneumonia and then
they go and they eat a slice of pizza
they go and they eat two scrambled eggs
they go and they have right some cheese
on a
burger if you want to be an animal
animal protein
person keep the dairy products
out keep even the pork out way too high
in
fat
right keep the eggs out keep the milks
out keep the goat cheese out keep the
kefir out all those things gone keep the
way out keep just anything related keep
the colostrum
out yuck colostrum does nothing for our
immune system by the way it's probably
one of the biggest
scams in on the market for 20 years now
is colostrum how many people tried that
and they didn't get out of bed how many
people tried colostrum and they couldn't
get out of bed and
recover that's this doesn't work but you
don't want to be doing
classroom when that's happening right
there so I see all kinds of comments
right there right
now
um hold on you
guys check in check
in so technically like a half an hour
really does it
but I'm going to put this Chopstick in
here little bit more we got a little bit
more time to go it's a little too moist
in the
center if you guys see right
there all
right so
oh so right here on the stick I'll show
you I got to remember we also have a
cooking show here and it is important to
know I I forget we have a cooking show
going on at the same time see right
there it's just a little too moist on
the
center toothpick is all you need but all
I have is a chopstick forgive me I might
order some
toothpicks
okay all
right Andrea I'm currently living in
Mattress City
never really recovered from
c19 I tried keto carnivore and it made
me worse bought two of your books hoping
to heal thank
you I don't know what books you have do
you have medical medium New
Edition there's a protocol in here
that's really good too um
now what I like about this book right
here what I like about all the books
really goes heavy into Epstein
bar a lot of people are in mattress
Island because of Long
Haul okay medical medium information
before covid put out how
flu Ematic viruses knock down our immune
system so much that Epstein bar Rises up
up when Epstein bar Rises
up okay it rises up in our system and it
beats us down and we end up in
bed so so many people because of the
bugs going around like C end up on
mattress Island for a very long time
because of epine
bar and epine bar Rises up in their
system and it keeps them neurologically
sick and they're stuck in bed and stuck
in bed anybody going through that get
the medical medium New Edition not the
not the first book this is the new
edition it's much more packed I added a
whole another book and a half to this so
so just so you know um so you can learn
about epine bar or you can just go with
the brains saer books it's packed with
the information for all the neurological
symptoms so if you're somebody in on
mattress Island take this to your doctor
or anything just take a look at these
books learn the information all the
neurological symptoms in here and then
look for a protocol customize it to
yourself take it one day at a time even
if it's just baby steps and one thing
one thing out of the
protocols have hope have
[Music]
faith there is no question no
doubt there is not a single bit of Faith
lost
there
is tremendous hope that you can
heal thousands upon thousands and I mean
thousands and thousands and hundreds of
thousands and it's in the millions now
around this planet have healed cuz the
medical meme information they've gotten
off a mattress Island you can do it too
you can do it you can heal you can get
off a mattress Island be easy on
yourself pat yourself on the back you're
not a bad person and whatever you do if
you're stuck on mattress Island because
of sea
originally or you're stuck on mess on
cuz you don't know what wear do not hate
yourself do not be hard on yourself and
don't think you have a faulty body don't
think that you can't heal cuz you can
heal you can and you'll get out you'll
rise out of the ashes and you'll look
back don't let the haters or anything
like that throw you the track record is
in these books in this information and
millions have healed around the globe
and that's why the hate is so heavy on
medic IAL medium it's why the hate is so
big and so heavy because it's the light
and it's changed lives it's completely
changed the health
movement and it's brought people from
literally their deathbed it's brought
people from just couch Island it's
brought people from fatigue Island from
mattress island people who are really
also really sick it brought them back
they rose out of the ashes they got
better their neurological sensitivities
their symptoms got better and got better
and got better and they healed multiple
sclerosis ALS and they healed the track
record is in these books I haven't seen
that anywhere else in health the health
movement whatsoever you know what they
do you know what I notice all these
Health influencers all these health
program people and everything they take
one person that started getting better
because they cleaned up their diet and
they Harald it it's like the greatest
testimonial in the world yeah try
thousands and hundreds of thousands of
people that were bedridden and tried
everything and seeing them heal and get
out of wheelchairs and get out of
mattress Island that's what I call real
real track record and
healing if I had pneumonia I would be
sticking to eating fruits and leafy
greens if I needed to the healing broth
cucumber juices the celery juice the
medical medium soup recipes the medical
medium shock therapies ask your doctor
if that's right for you I would keep the
fats out I would bring in the medical
meat and raw garlic therapy but I would
be doing different things if you get the
white lung the pneumonia I'm gonna get
those muffins out they're
[Music]
ready all right got to move the the
dummy over
here got some nice red bell pepper there
let's get these
going Michelle says I still get shamed
by people yep no I understand I do I do
I understand okay my heart pours out to
you okay Jennifer says medical mem saved
my life in
2016 that is
everything all
right okay you
guys let's do
it I'm going to take these
out
yep get them out of
here I'm going to try not to drop
them note to self do not use a hand
towel to get very hot items out of the
oven because there's always going to be
this weird spot or something's up cuz
it's not an oven mitt and you can get
like some really serious heat on your
hand but I'm
okay I did not burn myself but I can can
tell you this was some hot going
down all
right okay problem with the flu viruses
is they knock our immune systems down
they bring them down to the ground right
their body has to go into overdrive and
overload and then other pathogens that
are sitting inside of her body like the
hhv 6s and the Simplex ones and C cyto
viruses and everything else in the
Epstein bar all start to rise up and
they rise up and then he keep us sick
with neurological symptoms it's all the
herpetic family viruses they rise up and
that's the problem with these flu
viruses the sea virus the white lung
virus it all happens because you know
that and I've talked about this for
years I published this years ago I've
talked about it I've done lives about it
I did a live about it in 2019 how these
bugs knock our immune system down
creating that long haul creating that
boom where now we're stuck we're sick
creating that problem where we're now in
bed after getting all these bugs that's
why every time something's going down I
come out here and I say to you guys look
get the protocols make sure you have the
protocols make sure you have the books
seriously like that protocols book that
thing is priceless make sure you have it
and that's why I say this stuff make
sure you get this that's why I say this
stuff okay sorry about IG they won't
give me the the the flip option you know
the mirror option so they won't do that
so you always see everything
backwards
all right we got the muffins let's get
them
out whoa did you guys see
this you get a closeup on
this look at
that I am going to do this take a look
you
guys am I going to eat all of
these
someone asked a question am I going to
eat them all
yeah yeah I'm going to eat them
all uh-huh no oil no
fat there's no oil in
here there's no grease in here there's
no pork in here there's no lard in here
there's no vegetable oil in here like
seriously I'm I'm
serious no overt fats there's no you you
guys there's fat in never anything but
there's no overt fat in here it's a hot
tray look out it's a hot
tray
nice welcome to my
kitchen I have made fatatas for
you this would be great with a pear or a
glass of
champagne that's a hot pan move that
over take a look you
guys I'm going to show you guys on
YouTube i g Rumble I'm going to show you
guys how about that can I use that as a
thumbnail hope so you see that would be
amazing there a
thumbnail all
right I'm letting them cool down a bit
they got to kind of like
settle they're blazing
hot I'm going to eat one
can't I wait I can't
wait let me get a
plate I cannot wait any
longer
hungry
hungry which one do I want do you guys
ever do that like you don't know which
one you want to pick you don't know
which one you want like do you ever run
into that where it's like which one do I
want right here like which
one
H I'll take this one right here why not
and what I did was I put it in these
little cupcake this little cupcake
holder right there take a look right
that's what I did okay now you can peel
this back like this the cupcake part you
got to let them settle I noticed if you
do that in a cupcake that kind of sticks
to the wrapper you ever have that stick
to the wrapper a little with the cupcake
let me cut this in
half
okay have it a little fun
today yeah that's incredible it's like a
bread I Can't Describe I'm showing you
guys here and then I'm showing you wait
where am I going wait oh where on back
and
forth look at that
that's a cupcake that's a Pata am I
allowed to have some right now peel away
some of the paper there nice oh that
looks good get the muffin wrapper away
there you
go come
on shut
up come on shut
up oh man that that freaking
sick
that's a that's bronen bronen Bronco
man that's
a that's really
good
freaking I was diagnosed with MS and
healed one of my brain lesions you
healed with medical medium information
and focusing on sugar from fruits while
reducing my
fats usually they push High healthy fats
for Ms and brain health okay I want to
talk about that for a
second you
guys one of the most devastating things
I've seen with multiple sclerosis is
they push high
fat
awful lowers the immune system doesn't
help somebody
heal and then they push the worse fats
I'm not like
anti-fat
I mean avocado if you want to eat
avocado have some
avocado have a really high quality like
sesame seed or
something if you want to do a little nut
butter do a Little Nut Butter but I'm
not against fats that's not it it's just
that when you're really sick the fats
they load up on you especially with
multiple sclerosis or anything or any
kind of condition are the worst fats and
they and they load up too much of
them so good over there in IG wild
blueberry dreams a new study
from Ms news
today just came out showing a lowfat
mostly plant-based diet significantly
reduced fatigue in Ms patients sounds
familiar
uh-huh 10 years ago they're 10 years too
late published it first
uhhuh and also published that the cause
of multiple sclerosis is EP
virus combination of metals
too and they poached and stole that too
they have no
Integrity well that's the world we're in
you guys have figured that out now right
you figured out how it goes people don't
give a
crap they just want to climb and get
their accolades and get their
achievements they don't care who they
step on they don't give a about The
Chronic
Leo and they don't care they just want
to build their Empires as fast as
possible to step on anybody to do it you
better believe it there's nothing wrong
with being an entrepreneur or anything
like that out there that people
do there nothing wrong with
that let me tell you
this they don't care about the
chronically ill out there I can tell you
that and they poach and steal published
information that was already published
in New York Times bestselling
books I tell you if you ever get
invited out to a fancy restaurant with
some fancy people make sure you chew
with your mouth
open and make sure you talk while you're
chewing and if you really want the best
trick if you ever get invited over to
like a person's Mansion a bunch of rich
people bunch of stuck up rich people
what you do
is you put some food in your
hand right two hands and you eat with
two hands you go like
this excuse me
Mrs I'm sorry dutches of uh what did you
say um dutches of
DeBerry what these are really quite good
these
Tarts yeah um princess of
notam what did you
say
or if it's not overseas or something and
it's in the
US and you're fine dining with here with
some rich people that are stuck up
snobs in us do this I can't hear you
what what' you say lower that class
music down oh my God
kiss did any of you guys cat catch the
KISS concert last
night Jean Simmons Paul Stanley did you
guys catch that Jean Simmons Paul
Stanley last night their last show ever
their last show Madison Square Garden
kiss did you guys catch
that that was insane God bless
them
God bless them Pearl ZZ ZZ yes I'm
hearing your information being repeated
by influencers on some health
professionals a lot too now and they are
claiming the info as their own I'm going
to tell you right
now it's dozens and dozens and hundreds
of influencers now that take published
medical medium information they claiming
is their own to sell their products and
stuff and they don't cite anything
studies or anything to it that actually
even connect to it they are cheating
people from healing they won't say where
it originally comes from people are left
with tidbits information which makes
them interested to follow them but yet
in the end they won't be able to get
anybody better and it's all a freaking
scam and they're doing it and building
their businesses on the back of medical
medium information on the back of the
medical medium books they're doing it
literally on the back and they're doing
on the back of the chronic Leo and it's
disgusting absolutely
disgusting
anyway
these are so
good it's actually sick oh here's what's
really
sick meanwhile some of those same
influencers use the medical medium
information and then talk about
medical medium out there on social while
they're stealing the information oh my
God it's
like do you guys believe there's a
hell I'm not trying to go there or
anything like that but do you believe
there's a hell or if you don't believe
there's a hell do you believe there's
some type of Reckoning do you believe
there's some type of like
soul soul realization right before we
leave this planet do you
believe that we got to like fess up to
our and what we've done and the
stupid crap and the Darkness we kind of
went along with do you think we have to
kind of like talk that stuff out before
we leave planet
Earth do you think so maybe you don't
believe in hell but do you think there's
some kind of Reckoning we have
to find peace
with some type of situation when we're
leaving this planet our soul has to say
you dumbass the you did and led
people down the wrong way by cheating
this and cheating that and poaching this
and stealing this and you didn't give
one rat's ass about The Chronic e and
you took that guy's information and
right when you're about to die years
years down the road you have to come to
terms with that and then the Angels come
and say you
[Music]
dumbass you think you're going to the
highest heaven cuz you're so pure and
mighty when you cheated millions of the
chronically ill out there from getting
the answers they need it doesn't work
like
that or what works like that all
right
cool feel good it does work like
that all right
guys on that frightful
note meanwhile if they just told people
where the information came
from and weren't so just like trying to
build their Empires every second or
cheat cheat and this and do that and
they just had some integrity and they
said
look you're on mattress Island because I
read in the medical meeting book and
heard from one of his podcast that you
got the epen bar and that guy was known
as the epen bar guy he's the one that
published m is even caused by epine bark
go check out his stuff and heal man and
after you heal maybe check out my stuff
after but no they won't do
that
because they're sick
bastards
mhm that's right Jenny
mac oh you want to hear a
story you guys want to hear a
story
okay I know somebody
personally
right that was bedridden back in
2011 okay
2011 and they couldn't find
answers so they went to a
chiropractor a chiropractor that knew a
little bit about alternative medicine in
2011 that chiropractor mentioned to
them could be upstein
bar but the chiropractor never mentioned
where the chiropractor got that
information that chiropractor never
said that they were a client of medical
mediums in
2011 and that to get you out of bed off
of mattress Island you need to get a
hold of that
guy
and start learning how to do
it and then that person stayed bedridden
because that chiropractor wouldn't tell
them that they found out about epine bar
from being a client to Medical
medium yeah so that chiropractor though
didn't want to lose Pride
or ego or whatever the heck it was
however you want to say it and didn't
want to say to the person who was
bedridden look I talked to a guy he
knows all about what's going on with
your nervous system and he knows all
about what's going on with epen bar you
need to at least try to contact him and
if not contact him maybe I will because
I'm a client of his and I'll contact him
and tell him about your situation and
maybe get some tips or something so I
can work through you through him but no
he didn't do that because this
chiropractor did not want to fess up
that he didn't know anything about what
he was saying but he knew just enough to
make it look like he knew something so
the person who was sick in bed dying had
no way to heal but guess what years
later that person found me years later
and told me personally what happened and
told me the chiropractor's name which
was a client of mine and it was so sad
because the woman went through years of
suffering I'm talking years of suffering
she asked him several times what more
could she do and he withheld the
information about me and epin bar and
all that I knew and even working through
me to help her and that is how it works
and that's just one example of the
thousands that's happening right now
with medical medum information because
yeah because it's dark and dirty and the
health movement's dirty and nasty and
stinky and slimy and you see it every
day from the people running the ads to
the medical me Community you see it
every day with them stealing the heavy
metal detox information and the heavy
metal information they would have never
known you see it every day it's a gnarly
gnarly gross disgusting world out there
and people don't give a about The
Chronic leil but they give a about
the bottom line the money they make and
they want to reel in The Chronic leil so
they could sell them all their and
programs and garbage and
everything
anyway all
right and Harry says that was very evil
it was very
evil it's sad and it's unfair and what
happened was this person believes that
God LED them to the first
book because that chiropractor didn't
and that person suffered on mattress
Island for another four
years and they believe that the angels
and God LED them to the first book and
by chance somehow
someway the door opened
up and they were able to tell me at a
live event at a live event when I was
walking through that that event at a
live medical medium
concert in
2015 they were able to tell me in the
spring of
2015 when I was live in
Colorado in
Denver they were able to tell me and
stop me and say Mr William and I said
what what cuz I'll talk to anybody I
said what and they said Mr William I
have to tell you a story and I said okay
tell me that story and I sat down I was
supposed to go live in 10 minutes and
there was 3,000 people in the audience
just to see me in
2015 place was packed tickets were sold
out and I sat down I pulled a chair to
the corner and I sat down with that
person before going live and I saw
people freaking out I saw the producer
users freaking out I saw everybody
freaking out saying what the hell are
you doing talking to that person and I
said just calm down I said wait calm
down I want to hear this story and I sat
down and I heard that whole story right
there right there about what happened
and that's how screwed up our world is
meanwhile that chiropractor had an
opportunity to do the right thing that
person was led to that chiropractor to
be led back to Medical
medium and the chiropractor made the
wrong choice and that choice is is on
their soul just like I see
chiropractors constantly like
advertising to the medical medium
Community using medical medium
information but leading them to a whole
bunch of
BS but they're using mm info it's on
their
soul anyway all right you
guys lot of good stuff Happening by the
way santar good to see you God bless you
too lot of good stuff happening coming
com up just letting you know all
right God
bless and if you don't believe in God
Universe bless if you don't believe in
the universe Creator bless if you don't
believe in the Creator then light blast
if you don't believe in the light
blast being blessed by light being
blessed by the universe being blessed by
the Angels if you don't believe in
angels if you don't believe in
anything that's okay
too if you believe it's just a rock
we're on and we're floating in space and
the Earth is flat and not
round I still got respect for
you take
care figures they pause me well it looks
like it's low
battery that's
why all
right
bye
guys